<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-19T09:18:08-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>f25efff1-19ad-4ca1-8bb2-ebf05ebc7f93</id><title>7/31 - Juried Exhibition &amp;quot;SHOW YOUR WORLD&amp;quot;</title><updated>2019-07-19T09:18:08.627151+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;RE:ARTISTE International Art Organization&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $39.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.reartiste.com/show-your-world-2019-juried-exhibition"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All entries are accepted. Twenty Winners will display original work at the “Show Your World” exhibition in New York City in November 2019 at Gallery MC. The digital installation is part of our art show: artwork of all participants is projected at the gallery during the entire show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is more than just a plain exhibition. To promote our artists we host various art &amp; social events to attract a broader audience and your potential buyers. For artists, we organize networking meetups, workshops, consultations. This festival-like art show attracts thousands of visitors - YOUR ART WILL BE SEEN. Show your art and make new connections. Meet new art enthusiasts and sell your art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our Fifth Annual Art Competition and Juried Exhibition “SHOW YOUR WORLD” is open to artists of various media around the globe. Artists of all career levels are welcome. Painters, photographers, mixed media artists from more than 40 countries took part in the previous four editions of “Show Your World”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Be exhibited in New York City - New York is considered a center of contemporary art life. The world famous art neighborhoods - Chelsea and Soho, Lower East Side and Bushwick, Dumbo and Williamsburg - are located in New York City. The city hosts more than 1500 galleries and hundreds of art shows each year. New York is the place where you can view internationally renowned artworks along with witnessing how modern art emerges. Get the chance to show your world and art to thousands of visitors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;"The artist's job is to be a witness to his time in history." - Robert Rauschenberg&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art is a non-verbal language understood by people speaking different mother tongues. It conveys both historical and social facts, lifestyle, inspiration, and feelings. We’ve been creating a dialogue among artists from various cities and countries.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EVALUATION: The Jury Panel represented by gallery board members, curators, exhibiting artists, art business professionals is evaluating our 5th International Juried Exhibition “Show Your World”. Find out more about the Jurors here.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;INSPIRATION: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Being traditional or rebellious, figurative or conceptual artist, SHOW YOUR WORLD, views, ideas:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Show YOUR World – happy or sad, active or laid back, open or intimate&lt;br/&gt;Show what only artists can depict – feelings, emotions, or relationships&lt;br/&gt;Show wildlife, nature, or urban landscapes&lt;br/&gt;Show what’s close to your heart or what destroys your comfort&lt;br/&gt;Show your inspiration – whether it’s a person, a place, a book, or another work of art&lt;br/&gt;Show your childhood or your future&lt;br/&gt;Show the world you love, hate, or dream about&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS: Entries must be in JPEG format, no larger than 1400 x 1800 pixels, and under 2MB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following disciplines are accepted:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Painting&lt;br/&gt;Drawing/Illustration&lt;br/&gt;Photography&lt;br/&gt;Mixed Media and 3-D Art including Ceramics and Textile&lt;br/&gt;Digital Art&lt;br/&gt;Installation&lt;br/&gt;Performance&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE include your show statement – it will help the jurors and curators understand your work better.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: JULY 31, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION: As soon as your entry is submitted you receive a popup web page confirming your submission. The finalists will be announced on the RE:ARTISTE website by October 1, 2019 and will be personally notified via email. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;COPYRIGHT: The submitting artists own the copyright to their competition entries as their author(s). By submitting an entry to the art competition the artist gives RE:ARTISTE permission for the entry to be used on the RE:ARTISTE website and its social media channels. The artist gives RE:ARTISTE the right to use his/her name and city of residence for the sole purpose of identifying the artist as the author of the entry. The entry fee is not refundable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Entries must be in JPEG format, no larger than 1400 x 1800 pixels, and under 2MB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following disciplines are accepted:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Painting&lt;br/&gt;- Drawing/Illustration&lt;br/&gt;- Photography&lt;br/&gt;- Mixed Media and 3-D Art including Ceramics and Textile&lt;br/&gt;- Digital Art&lt;br/&gt;- Installation&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE include your show statement – it will help the jurors and curators understand your work better.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info please email at info@reartiste.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f25efff1-19ad-4ca1-8bb2-ebf05ebc7f93" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>862cdae5-0143-48a0-b13b-3e0d776efdb7</id><title>9/2 - Fresh Blood</title><updated>2019-07-19T09:18:08.627110+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;PROTO GOMEZ&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/02/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://protogallery.submittable.com/submit/137177/fresh-blood"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FRESH BLOOD is an international open call exhibition opportunity hosted by PROTO GOMEZ, a storefront contemporary art gallery, located in the Two-Bridges neighborhood of Manhattan, New York City.&lt;br/&gt;http://proto-gomez.gallery&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FRESH BLOOD as an art show, seeks to showcase exciting and innovative contemporary art, produced in a variety of media. While there are no restrictions and applications are open to all, selection preference will be given to artists who have not previously shown with PROTO GOMEZ, PROTO Gallery, The Dorado Project, and their affiliates. FRESH BLOOD will be curated by Nick De Pirro and Enrico Gomez, co-founders and owners of PROTO GOMEZ. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In addition to the art show FRESH BLOOD, this open call has been created to provide an organized means for emerging and mid-career artists to bring their work to the attention of the gallery as well as independent curators and arts organizers we collaborate with. Submitted work will also be considered for one or more of the following:&lt;br/&gt;• Solo exhibitions at PROTO GOMEZ Gallery&lt;br/&gt;• Online Group Exhibitions Presented on our PROTO GOMEZ Artsy Profile&lt;br/&gt;• Solo and Group Exhibitions in our affiliated 2500 s.f. gallery, PROTO Gallery, located in the historic former R. Neumann and Co. leather goods factory in Hoboken, NJ.&lt;br/&gt;• Future Art Fairs&lt;br/&gt;• Inclusion in our Gallery Inventory and Artsy Listing&lt;br/&gt;• Exposure to Independent Curators in partnership with PROTO GOMEZ for In-house Projects as well as Affiliated Galleries and Art Spaces&lt;br/&gt;A submission to this open call does not guarantee inclusion in the FRESH BLOOD exhibition or affiliated opportunities, however all entires are seen and considered by Nick De Pirro, Enrico Gomez, and selected independent curators.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thank you for your interest in our FRESH BLOOD 2019 open call.&lt;br/&gt;https://protogallery.submittable.com/submit/137177/fresh-blood&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applicants must apply via our Submittable link below:&lt;br/&gt;https://protogallery.submittable.com/submit/137177/fresh-blood&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FRESH BLOOD DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Application Announcement: APRIL 10, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: SEP 2, 2019, 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;Acceptance Notifications: First Week of OCT 2019&lt;br/&gt;Accepted Artworks Received By: SAT NOV 16, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: DEC 4 - DEC 22 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: WED DEC 4 2019 from 6-8PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: &lt;br/&gt;All artists over the age of 18 years old are eligible. While open to all, selection preference will be given to artists who have not previously shown with PROTO GOMEZ, PROTO Gallery, The Dorado Project, and their affiliates.&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $30.00 US for up to five (5) images. All entries must be registered/received by Sep 2, 2019 11:59 PM ET All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 48” X 48” X 12” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Date, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;4. Accepted work may be refused if it does not conform to the entered image. NO SUBSTITUTIONS of accepted works will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt;5. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss. (A Condition Report will be issued to each artist upon receipt of their artwork to the gallery). Shipped work must arrive at the gallery (or alternate, mutually agreed upon location) by SATURDAY, NOV 16, 2019 in a reusable container. A computer-generated return label for return of work MUST be enclosed. Pre-paid shipping arrangements must be made through UPS or FedEx websites. No U.S. Postal Service or COD returns. No Cash, Check, Stamps, or Credit Card Information Will Be Accepted For Return of Work. NO EXCEPTIONS.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;PROTO GOMEZ, and their respective representatives and affiliates, is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but PROTO GOMEZ, and their respective representatives and affiliates,  assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist may, if they wish, provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for retail sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, prior to the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;PROTO GOMEZ will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the final retail price. Any Discounts (of up to 10%) are agreed upon in this agreement, and artist and gallery agrees to split discount equally. (Discounts greater than 10% require prior approval of the artist). An additional Consignment Form will be e-mailed to accepted artists and need to be filled out, signed, scanned by the accepted artists and e-mailed back to gallery prior to the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the FRESH BLOOD Exhibition, the artist agrees to all of the above terms and conditions set forth in these exhibition guidelines. Your fee payment will serve as your acceptance of the terms and conditions stated in this prospectus.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLY via Submittable:&lt;br/&gt;https://protogallery.submittable.com/submit/137177/fresh-blood&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/862cdae5-0143-48a0-b13b-3e0d776efdb7" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cf8e0aa7-3280-4f7a-bcc0-cfcb71031297</id><title>9/10 - Monochrome</title><updated>2019-07-19T09:18:08.627045+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monochrome &lt;br/&gt;November 1– November 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Monochromic works are works of art in black and white or in varying tones of a single color. By reducing their color palettes artists can to push the viewer to think about the work in a new way, understand a new concept or subject. Site:Brooklyn is looking for monochrome works across all mediums and utilizing all processes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Donna Harkavy is a New York-based independent curator. She began her curatorial career at the Walker Art Center in Minneapolis and later worked as Exhibitions Coordinator at ICI in New York. From 1990-1995 Ms. Harkavy was Curator of Contemporary Art at the Worcester Art Museum in Massachusetts, where she founded the contemporary art program. She is currently on the Board of Trustees of the Munson-Williams-Proctor Arts Institute, Foster Pride, Dorsky Gallery Curatorial Projects and the Raoul Hague Foundation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: July 17, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: September 10, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: September 19, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: November 1– November 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, November 1, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in drawing, painting, printmaking, sculpture, collage. Photography, video. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $35.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by September 10, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:  &lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2xQb7mv&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 60” X 60” X 24” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;4. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Monochrome” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:  &lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2xQb7mv&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cf8e0aa7-3280-4f7a-bcc0-cfcb71031297" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>