<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-23T02:18:14-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>0055809f-563a-480a-adb9-641e888cdfa3</id><title>10/10 - New Orleans Exhibitions, Residencies, and Publishing, with $$, Travel, and More!</title><updated>2019-07-23T02:18:14.000514+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Antenna&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Orleans, LA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://antenna.submittable.com/submit"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EXHIBITIONS DEADLINE: 10/10&lt;br/&gt;FEE: $35&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Individual Visual Artists or Collaboratives working in any media are encouraged to apply to the Antenna:: Exhibition Open Call. Selected artists receive: a solo show for the 2020 calendar year, include funding for travel, $1,000 honorarium (to be split with collaborations), accommodations in Antenna’s residency space, and the publishing of an exhibition catalog, artist book, or other similar ephemera to be determined in collaboration with the artists and Antenna’s Paper Machine. Exhibition opportunities are also available for Louisiana Residents and for projects exploring the intersections of visual and literary arts. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RESIDENCIES &lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: 10/25&lt;br/&gt;FEE: $35&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Antenna offers two residency opportunities for Artists and Writers to produce new work in New Orleans. The Antenna::Spillways Residency aims to develop creative feats within the greater New Orleans region, supporting ambitious works that question, transform, or expand the vibrant visual and literary culture of the area. Residents are selected based on past work, provided resources for an initial visit, and from their visit experience encouraged to develop a proposal for a project. A limited group of projects are then selected for development, which are supported in an open ended process and given the time and resources needed for them to thrive. The Paper Machine Publishing Residency provides funding, space, and time for artists and writers to produce a print based project during a month in New Orleans at Antenna’s center for creator publishing, Paper Machine. Residents explore the possibilities of prints, publications, or multiples, and have the time to develop a focused project on a variety of cutting edge and traditional print equipment with the assistance of Paper Machine staff. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BOOKS: &lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: 10/17&lt;br/&gt;FEE: $20&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Antenna publishes new Comic Books, Chapbooks, or Guidebooks, all through open call processes. Check out current works produced by Antenna here: &lt;a href="https://antenna.works/book-order" target="_blank"&gt;https://antenna.works&lt;/a&gt; Selected projects receive funding, project development support, and books!  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To see the work of Antenna created from open call opportunities such as these visit: &lt;a href="https://www.antenna.works/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.antenna.works&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All application information and guidelines can be found at: &lt;a href="https://antenna.submittable.com/submit" target="_blank"&gt;https://antenna.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0055809f-563a-480a-adb9-641e888cdfa3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0382ff04-8cc9-4b9b-8994-43f42e0dbc0a</id><title>8/6 - OPEN CALL FOR ARTISTS NEAR AND FAR: OUR 2019 MAIL ART BIENNIAL</title><updated>2019-07-23T02:18:14.000454+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ground Floor Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://groundfloorbk.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to officially announce the return of our summer show, “Priority Mail: Our 2019 Mail Art Biennial,” our sweeping survey of small, original artworks mailed to us by contemporary artists from across the globe, “Priority Mail” is a grand and inclusive gesture for our intimate gallery space in Park Slope, Brooklyn: ALL submissions mailed to the gallery will be accepted and shown in the exhibition! Submissions from down to the block to across the country and the globe are encouraged. NO FEE. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you’ve followed the gallery and have wanted to show with us – now is your chance! We look forward to showing artists from near and far while supporting a cause that is near and dear to us as well! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In the spirit of inclusion and accessibility, all artworks will be priced at $125. The gallery and artist will receive 50% commission and 10% of gallery profits will be donated to the Committee to Protect Journalists in their tireless efforts to defend freedom of the press worldwide. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Thursday, August 8th, 6-9pm &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE NOTE: Due to the scope of the exhibition, we cannot return unsold work. You can arrange to have it picked up or it will be donated to a local charity or school in our network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists, please carefully review the guidelines below.  Work that does not adhere to the guidelines will not be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUIDELINES: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Mail your artwork to the gallery by August 6th, 2019. If it arrives later due to late notice or postal issues, we will still hang it when it arrives!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- NO phone calls.  Please direct message us on Twitter, Instagram or Facebook with any and all questions to @groundfloorbk and we’ll respond promptly.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- All work must be sized 5” x 7” (up to 6” x 9” if framed). The work does not have to be framed but, in our experience, framed and mounted work sells best. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Work in all media will be accepted (photography and prints MUST be limited-edition works). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Only ONE submission will be accepted per artist&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- You MUST have your name, email, phone number, artwork title, materials, year and location (e.g. Brooklyn, Madrid, London, Sydney, etc.)  included on the back of your artwork.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Email up to 4 hi res photos (under 5 MB each) of your complete artwork with caption (name, title, materials, year and 2 sentences about the work) to info@groundfloorbk.com with the subject: Priority Mail.  Please name each jpeg with your name, for example: RayJohnson1.jpeg, RayJohnson2.jpeg. We will use these images for documentation and promotion.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DO NOT drop off submissions.  That defeats the whole purpose. All work should be mailed to:&lt;br/&gt;   &lt;br/&gt; Ground Floor Gallery&lt;br/&gt; 343 5th Street&lt;br/&gt; Brooklyn, New York 11215&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0382ff04-8cc9-4b9b-8994-43f42e0dbc0a" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>