<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-15T13:15:56-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>befd9e06-8801-4c97-ae86-e7e7cf55cc0b</id><title>5/18 - Open Call for Project Proposals</title><updated>2019-04-15T13:15:56.750485+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Art in Odd Places&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/18/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.artinoddplaces.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art in Odd Places (AiOP) invites proposals for its fifteenth annual public art and performance festival taking place along 14th Street in Manhattan, NY – from Avenue C to the Hudson River this fall.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art in Odd Places 2019: INVISIBLE scheduled for October 17-20 curated by LuLu LoLo seeks imaginative proposals by artists who are sixty years old and older – either working solo or collectively. We also welcome various forms of intergenerational collaborations: parent/child; mentor/ protégé; partners; lovers; and others. Proposals should be artistic projects or performances that actively engage the public on 14th Street NYC. Selected artists will address the focus of INVISIBLE in an imaginative way. For example: people with no voice: older adults, the homeless, immigrants, children, animals; Concealed emotions: kindness, hatred, grief; Hidden conditions: hunger, pain, illness.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The open call for AiOP 2019: INVISIBLE is an actual telephone call. Interested artists and collectives will have three minutes to leave a message on Saturday, May 18 any time from 12am to 11:59pm or speak to a live operator from 1 to 3pm. It is our hope that this format will easily facilitate applications from older artists who do not have access to a computer. In line with the focus of INVISIBLE the artwork proposed will not be seen, only heard in the description in the telephone call application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists have the opportunity to propose one idea from two different options: 1) An individual performance or visual artwork  in an odd place on 14th Street during the festival. AiOP welcomes a mosaic of art  disciplines: OR 2) Participation in Promenade of Visual Flâneurs: paintings, sculpture, costumes by an older artist. Art will parade en mass the 2.2-mile length of 14th Street on Saturday, October 19 and Sunday, October 20 by the older artist or their proxy. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.artinoddplaces.org/call-for-proposals/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.artinoddplaces.org&lt;/a&gt; for PDFs of the Open Call and the FAQs. Questions call + 1 347-313-8653 or email aiopnyc@gmail.com before May 18.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, May 18, 12midnight to 11:59pm, Applicants should call: + 1 347-313-8653  (Live operator from 1 to 3pm) 3 minutes max. Callers will give  their name, age, phone number, preference for inclusion in festival or promenade, project title, and project proposal. Selected artists will be notified by phone.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/befd9e06-8801-4c97-ae86-e7e7cf55cc0b" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>