<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-09T19:17:56-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>49be5d45-4f2b-4334-af9e-c6741805d699</id><title>8/8 - NOVADO GALLERY Announces First Annual International Juried Art Exhibition:  &amp;quot;Artfirst&amp;quot;</title><updated>2019-07-09T19:17:56.327599+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Novado Gallery, LLC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Jersey City, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/08/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.novadogallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call for Art: "Artfirst" focus is on the quality, maturity of vision, and freshness of the artwork, regardless of the artist's religion, gender, sexual orientation, politics, education, exhibition history, economic status, or country.  Exhibition runs September 13 - November 2, 2019.  Submission deadline is August 8, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOVADO GALLERY is Hudson County's largest contemporary retail art gallery located across from Manhattan.  Artists across the globe are invited to submit up to 3 works for possible inclusion in the juried show: "Artfirst".  &lt;br/&gt;Two artists will be selected for an exhibition in 2020. &lt;br/&gt;Jurors:  Anne Novado and Eleazar Sanchez&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Full prospectus with Payapal payment information available at: www.novadogallery.com&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility for "Artfirst" at NOVADO GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;*All artists 21 years or older may submit works for this show.   Artists must have an active email account.&lt;br/&gt;*Only original works of art not shown previously at the Novado Gallery and created within the last three years are eligible.  Email up to 3 total submissions via jpg or PDF, and up to 3 detail shots per work.&lt;br/&gt;* Email high res jpgs (1.5MB to 5MB) or PDF files to novadogallery@gmail.com.   Label attached files:&lt;br/&gt;Last Name_First Name_(Entry #)_Title_.(jpg or PDF)&lt;br/&gt;*Works in the following categories may be submitted: painting, drawing, mixed, collage, sculpture, photography, fibers and print making.  &lt;br/&gt;*All accepted works to be hung must be ready to install with included D-Rings, picture wire, cleat, or Wallbuddies, or to be hung from canvas stretcher bars  or cradled wood back supports (no screw eyes).  If works are subject to damage, they must be framed under Plexiglas or glass with acid-free materials (no cardboard backing).  No glass clip mounting will be accepted. Three-dimensional work must sit solidly on a flat surface or be properly mounted for hanging. If works are not adequately prepared for display, are dusty or dirty, or have insects in the framing,  they will be withdrawn from the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;*Accepted shipped works must include return shipping, return address label, and artists are responsible for insuring works in transit both ways.  Use of styrofoam peanuts in packing is strictly prohibited in shipped and delivered works and will not be accepted.  See shipping address on prospectus on NOVADO GALLERY'S website.&lt;br/&gt;*Size restrictions for 2D work up to 48" in height and 40" width including frame.  Sculpture up to 48"h x 36"w &amp; depth. Weight restriction on all art up to 35 lbs.&lt;br/&gt;*Selected artists will need to supply an artist statement and their CV. &lt;br/&gt;*Accepted works must be for sale.  Novado Gallery commission rate is 50% of full retail.  Payment is Net 30 from close of exhibition for commissions on sold work.&lt;br/&gt;*Novado Gallery allows clients the option on art purchases through the global financier, Artmoney.  Novado Gallery bears half of cost the 10% financing fee with the other half off of the artists commission on works sold using Artmoney.&lt;br/&gt;*Price of works must be consistent with the artist's other venues.   We will convert price to USD if you are unsure of the current exchange rate. &lt;br/&gt;*Submissions must include application fee of $35 in order to be reviewed.  Payment also accepted by emailing credit card number, expiration date, security code, name on the account and billing address.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/49be5d45-4f2b-4334-af9e-c6741805d699" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>73c19d79-65a5-471a-9887-f4ed668110a9</id><title>10/31 - Open Call for Women Contemporary Artists</title><updated>2019-07-09T19:17:56.327531+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Pen + Brush&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.penandbrush.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NO FEE&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Open Call: Women Contemporary Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Long-established non-profit contemporary art gallery, Pen + Brush, seeks women artists for various exhibition opportunities.  These opportunities include, but are in no way limited to: solo exhibition at ground floor space on 22nd street, group exhibition in our ground floor gallery as well as off-site, inclusion in exhibition catalogues written by art historians and curators, and exposure to curators, museums, as well as our network of art professionals and collectors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This opportunity is *OPEN TO EMERGING, MID-CAREER, AND ESTABLISHED WOMEN ARTISTS* who feel their voices should be represented in the contemporary canon of art. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Represented and non-represented artists are encouraged to submit works. The gallery will work in tandem with represented artists and their respective galleries. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Pen + Brush is a 125-year-old publicly supported not-for-profit fighting for gender equity in the arts. It works to elevate and sustain the careers of important contemporary women artists who are contributing to the current art landscape and offering new voices and perspectives through their work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;P+B provides a platform to showcase the work of female artists and writers to a broader audience with the ultimate goal of effecting real change within the marketplace. We encourage and mentor emerging professionals and aim to expose the stereotypes and misconceptions that perpetuate gender-based exclusion, lack of recognition and the devaluation of skill that is still experienced by women in the arts. All art work is for sale, 75% of all sales go directly to the artist and 25% comes back in to feed the organization’s work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;- ALL work submitted must be contemporary.&lt;br/&gt;- Submitted work must be complete.&lt;br/&gt;- To be considered work must meet standards of quality.&lt;br/&gt;- Every work in a submission must be for sale.&lt;br/&gt;- Artists must meet professional standards of composition and presentation of their work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applications:&lt;br/&gt;All submissions must be made online via our website. &lt;br/&gt;- Please visit www.penandbrush.org/explore/visual  to submit your work online. &lt;br/&gt;- Upload 6 to 12 high resolution images of at least 300 dpi or 1,000 x 1,000 pixels.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/73c19d79-65a5-471a-9887-f4ed668110a9" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>