<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-27T11:15:29-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>c6e6c148-b253-4a64-8265-8cbde9b6ebcf</id><title>4/10 - transit |ˈtranzit|noun 1 the carrying of people, goods, or materials from one place to another.</title><updated>2019-03-27T11:15:29.972275+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Krasdale Galleries&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hunts Point and White Plains, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/10/19 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://none"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking 2-dimentional artwork from artists that live and work in the NYC metro area, Westchester and the Hudson Valley that reflect an interest in the movement of people, goods, and materials from one place to another throughout the world. The only restriction is that it cannot be outwardly political in nature. These exhibitions are partially used to bring new awareness to the employees on how artists use various styles, media, concepts to depict a similar subject matter.&lt;br/&gt;Krasdale Galleries are housed in the offices, foyers, and hallways of Krasdale Foods executive offices in White Plains and at the Distribution Center on Hunts Point, the Bronx. Started by Sigmund Balka in 1984 that featured six to four rotating exhibitions per year. This exhibition will be up for six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a full prospectus please send your inquiry to krasdalegalleries@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;In the subject box please write prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c6e6c148-b253-4a64-8265-8cbde9b6ebcf" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>