<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-12T17:15:52-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>6985bd3e-0fdd-43fa-889b-375f2f112714</id><title>5/1 - Become a West Elm LOCAL Artist</title><updated>2019-04-12T17:15:52.699140+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;West Elm&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://Www.westelm.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The West Elm Chelsea store is looking for New York-based artists to become a part of our Local program. As a featured maker your work will be displayed and sold in the heart of Chelsea, with a retailer committed to connecting our customer to independent artists and creators.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are currently curating a LOCAL wall art gallery, and looking for two-dimensional prints, paintings, drawings, or photography with a strong individual aesthetic and a commercial appeal. Ideal makers should be able to fulfill new orders from the store as work sells off the wall. Pricing for framed works should be under $750.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What is the West Elm LOCAL program?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At West Elm we believe in supporting great design and the power of making - from around the world to around the corner.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The West Elm LOCAL program began in 2013. The program launched as a new chapter in our commitment to quality craftsmanship and the communities where we work. West Elm LOCAL is all about supporting domestic manufacturing and stimulating local economies by tapping into the maker movement - supporting makers, artists and designers right in our own backyards.&lt;br/&gt;By creating a locally designed, locally made, locally sourced assortment in each of our stores, we’re establishing West Elm as an active community hub that offers a unique shopping experience. West Elm LOCAL anchors our customers by giving them a sense of their neighborhood and celebrating the place they call home.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Learn more about the program and find other LOCAL makers at &lt;a href="https://www.westelm.com/shop/local/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.westelm.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are looking forward to hearing from you New York!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit cover letter expressing your interest in this opportunity as well as a link to a current online portfolio or retail shop, including price ranges for your work. No jpegs or attachments please.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6985bd3e-0fdd-43fa-889b-375f2f112714" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8b40793e-b116-4336-b6c2-c1cb4b44a522</id><title>5/24 - Upstream Gallery PaperWorks 2019-Theme &amp;amp; Variation</title><updated>2019-04-12T17:15:52.699050+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Upstream Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hastings on Hudson, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/24/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.upstreamgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL FOR ARTISTS&lt;br/&gt;Upstream Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Hastings on Hudson, NY&lt;br/&gt;PaperWorks 2019- Theme &amp; Variation&lt;br/&gt;Deadline May 24, 2019. Multiple price options&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As artists, most of us find our voices through examining similar ideas over time.  Ultimately, these become our “thematic materials”.  Upstream Gallery invites artists working on paper or making paper based constructions to submit work from their own practice that speak to the idea of theme and variation for our 7th Annual Juried PaperWorks exhibition.  The exhibition will be at Upstream Gallery, Hastings on Hudson, NY from June 27th to July 28th, 2019. Reception: Sunday, June 30th 2-5 pm. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Work: Artists are invited to submit 2-D or 3-D work that is primarily paper based.  Successful entries will demonstrate thematic relationships among two or more pieces.  Photography is not eligible for this exhibition; we hold a separate show for photographic work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Specifications: Maximum framed size may not exceed 20 x 24 inches. Accepted pieces must be able to be hung and properly wired or mounted for hanging. The gallery reserves the right to reject poorly presented pieces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jurors: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Antonio Alvarez:  Cuban born Alvarez is a both a remarkable abstract painter and a world-renowned art conservator specializing in the restoration of works on paper. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Nancy Egol Nikkal:  Nikkal is a graduate of Hunter College in Art with postgraduate work in printmaking.  She is a painter who works on canvas and in collage, where she uses papers she paints herself as the foundation for her elegant and witty work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Rachel Weatherford Whitlow:  Whitlow is a graduate of Cooper Union in fine art who also studied painting, lithography and print making at Academie Minerva in Groningen, Netherlands.  She is a master printer of both Tamarind and Paris methods of lithography.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee: Minimum entry of 3 pieces $45; each additional entry $5 up to a maximum of 6 pieces ($60) The jurors may select two, several, all, or none of your submissions.  All pieces must be for sale. The gallery will retain a 30% commission on all sales. To enter please go to:&lt;br/&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT DATES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Entries, Friday, May 24th 2019.  All entries must be made via Submittable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, June 21st by 5 pm deadline for delivered work if shipping&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Monday, June 24th 10 a.m. to 2 pm: Delivery of artwork to gallery if local;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thursday, June 27th: Opening of exhibition &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sunday, June 30th, Opening reception – 2 to 5 pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sunday, July 28th, Last day of exhibition&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Monday, July 29th, Local Artists pick up work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please go to upstreamgallery.com &amp; click on juried shows, or go to&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href="https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit" target="_blank"&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8b40793e-b116-4336-b6c2-c1cb4b44a522" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>