<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-12T13:17:19-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>7b423b92-f29b-413f-8b6f-b6e6c5497be3</id><title>Build Your LA Collector List | Apply to Superfine! Art Fair in LA</title><updated>2019-06-12T13:17:19.486680+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Superfine! Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 Los Angeles, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists: there's a better way.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Level up your career. Learn how to build sales and a collector list from our marketing experts. Curate to sell with our friendly guidelines, and meet your next collector in our hip DTLA location just blocks from the LA Art Show, the country's highest-attended art fair. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: The Reef, 1933 S. Broadway, Los Angeles, CA 90007&lt;br/&gt;Fair dates: February 6 - 9, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: January 6, 2020. Booths are selling quickly, so we recommend applying early! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A whole year of exhibitions in one weekend.&lt;br/&gt;- 6-10,000 motivated, art-hungry visitors during the four days of the fair.&lt;br/&gt;- 25% of our visitors make a significant ($100-$2,500+) art purchase.&lt;br/&gt;- More than 50% of our exhibiting artists receive major media coverage.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Make art. Sell art. We do the rest.&lt;br/&gt;- Meet your next collectors in a friendly, welcoming space: the ideal environment to discover, collect, and sell art.&lt;br/&gt;- Innovative cost-saving and cost-spreading financing options that work with every artist's budget to make exhibiting and selling a reality.&lt;br/&gt;- Serious opportunities for features in Superfine!'s earned (press + PR), owned (website, blog, and social), and paid (advertising) media.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: Superfine! takes no commission on any artwork sold either in person at the fair or via our online E-Fair.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You’re the art-making expert. We’re the art-marketing experts.&lt;br/&gt;- The smartest and most sophisticated marketing engine in the industry: we get the eyes you want in front of your work. Our audience is 26-45, affluent ($120k+/year), and buying art now.&lt;br/&gt;- We're top drawer: a professional, courteous, and knowledgeable team of experts guiding you every step of the way. Exhibit and sell your work, and gain champions of your career.&lt;br/&gt;- Lead-up webinars and curatorial guidelines geared towards success. Take what you learn with you and make it work for you year-round.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Get to Know Us&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Founded by art collectors Alex Mitow and James Miille, Superfine! started out in 2015 as an alternative to boring, stuffy art shows and complicated art world politics. From the start, we caught flack from the art establishment when we broke down barriers and opened the gates to everyone from serious long-time art collectors to people who just love art and never thought they’d collect. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As it turned out, nobody cared about the art world and their politics. Our open and transparent approach worked: imaginations have been sparked and countless new collections have been jump-started at Superfine! fairs as we continue to spread our message of a more inclusive art market across the country. Since 2015, we’ve had one goal: produce badass, expertly curated art shows where über-talented, diverse global artists meet their new fans in iconic locations across the US and beyond.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FAQ:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1) Can I share a booth with a friend?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our 8' and 12' artist booths are intended for solo artists only, but our 16' and 20' booths can be shared by up to 3 artists. However, one person must be appointed as the booth representative for communication and payment purposes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2) I'm a gallery, can I apply?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! is an artist-driven fair but we welcome progressive, forward-thinking galleries, collectives, and artist-run programs to apply. Each fair has a dedicated number (between 5 and 20) of larger booths ideal for galleries. Contact our sales team at exhibit@superfine.world for more information about coming on board as a gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3) Can I get a discount?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We do offer a 5% per-fair discount for booths paid in full upfront, within three business days of a signed application. If it's immediate cash flow that's a concern, we offer options to spread booth costs over as much as a year - just ask us!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4) Why did you choose DTLA?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our beautiful, plug-and-play DTLA venue at The Reef is not only a three minute sprinter shuttle away from the LA Art Show but is surprisingly affordable. Founded by art fair veterans, The Reef cuts our production cost which allows us to dedicate considerably more resources (more than double the budget of other fairs) to marketing the fair and our artists. Our core demographic (affluent, 26-45, creative early adopters) is also very prevalent in the DTLA and adjacent neighborhoods (Echo Park, Silver Lake, Highland Park) and our targeted marketing brings them to the fair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more and apply: &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/before-you-apply" target="_blank"&gt;https://superfine.world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: January 6, 2020. Applications are rolling, so we recommend applying early! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: Superfine! takes no commission on any artwork sold either in person at the fair or via our online E-Fair.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7b423b92-f29b-413f-8b6f-b6e6c5497be3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d1c6244c-15aa-41ee-a6fd-4ef4af9f69f7</id><title>Artist Collectives: Make Your Mark on the Art Market This Fall at Superfine! Art Fair in DC</title><updated>2019-06-12T13:17:19.486559+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Superfine! Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 Washington, DC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/before-you-apply"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the second year in a row, we're inviting top artist collectives, solo artists, curators, and galleries to join us for the foremost artist-driven art fair in the country at bustling Union Market in Washington DC (more than 25,000 visitors per weekend). We're all but sold out of solo artist booths, but we do have a handful of larger booths available which are ideal for an artist collective.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: Union Market, 1309 5th St. NE, Washington, DC 20002 &lt;br/&gt;Fair dates: October 30 - November 3, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Application deadline: September 4, 2019. We are more than 80% full and DC's fair is in very high demand, so apply soon to confirm your placement. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Here's what you can expect from Superfine! DC:&lt;br/&gt;- 8-12,000 unique visitors during the five days of the fair.&lt;br/&gt;- 25% of our visitors make a significant ($100-$2,500+) art purchase.&lt;br/&gt;- An easy, efficient exhibition guided by our expert curators.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Benefits of Showing as a Collective&lt;br/&gt;- Larger booth = greater impact + higher visibility.&lt;br/&gt;- Split booth fees and share expenses among multiple artists.&lt;br/&gt;- Build your platform to exhibit in future fairs around the world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: A single collective member must be appointed for all financial and curatorial communications with the Superfine! team.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! Art Fair: A Year of Exhibitions in One Week&lt;br/&gt;- Connect with collectors in a friendly, welcoming space designed as the ideal environment to discover, buy, and sell art.&lt;br/&gt;- Innovative cost-saving and cost-spreading financing options that work with every artist's budget to make exhibiting and selling a reality.&lt;br/&gt;- Opportunities for features in Superfine!'s earned (press + PR), owned (website, blog, and social), and paid (advertising) media.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: Superfine! takes no commission on any artwork sold, either in person at the fair or via our online E-Fair.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Make art. Sell art. We do the rest.&lt;br/&gt;- The smartest and most sophisticated marketing engine in the industry.&lt;br/&gt;- A professional, courteous, and knowledgeable team of experts guiding you every step of the way.&lt;br/&gt;- Lead-up webinars and curatorial guidelines geared towards success.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Pricing &amp; Booth Availability (as of 6/11/19)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;16' - $4,000  (6 left)&lt;br/&gt;26'  - $6,500 (3 left)&lt;br/&gt;28' - $7,000 (2 left) &lt;br/&gt;30' - $7,500 (1 left)&lt;br/&gt;32' - $8,000 (1 left)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more: &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/before-you-apply" target="_blank"&gt;https://superfine.world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply: &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/exhibit-dc" target="_blank"&gt;https://superfine.world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: September 4, 2019. Booths are almost sold out, so apply ASAP to secure your place.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d1c6244c-15aa-41ee-a6fd-4ef4af9f69f7" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7b4931b9-75f5-4764-ac31-4b40cd16c698</id><title>7/9 - Red Hook Summer POP UP show</title><updated>2019-06-12T13:17:19.486503+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Brooklyn Waterfront Artist Coalition&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://bwac.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come join us for 3 summer weekends July 20-Aug 4th to exhibit your artwork in Red Hook, Brooklyn at Brooklyn Waterfront Artist Coalition. We are a 200 member artist coalition located in the civil war era Beard Street warehouses located right on the pier facing the Statue of Liberty. Our galleries are 25,000 sq feet allowing artists the rare luxury to think big! Please submit 3-5 images to Adegener7@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send 3-5 images&lt;br/&gt;Larger installations will be considered as well&lt;br/&gt;Please send proposal&lt;br/&gt;An additional $25 installation fee will be required upon acceptance&lt;br/&gt;$50 total to exhibit once accepted which can be applied to becoming a member of BWAC!&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7b4931b9-75f5-4764-ac31-4b40cd16c698" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>