<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml</id><title>open-calls-7</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>43b3dd19-4fa4-4e8f-aba8-89405d5a2c1b</id><title>12/3 - Request for Proposals - Rosalie Garder Jones Monument</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.904362+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Parks Recreation &amp;amp; Historic Preservation&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cold Spring Harbor State Park, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/03/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.nyscr.ny.gov/iframes/openAdDetail.cfm?id=77B04B69-54CD-48B7-A966-053D540DDB16"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPRHP is interested in commissioning a figurative or abstract work of art, not necessarily a sculptural portrait, of Rosalie Gardiner Jones that captures her unrelenting dedication to women’s rights. Bidders are encouraged to develop their own understanding of the context of her life and her achievements. The key objectives are to create a lasting tribute to Rosalie Gardiner Jones that is integrated with the Cold Spring Harbor State Park site and utilizes materials that are durable and require minimal maintenance and care.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you choose to visit the site, OPRHP will be holding an optional site visit on 10/8/2019, please reference the RFP for further details.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To obtain a copy of the Request for Proposal package, please contact contracts@parks.ny.gov&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Due Date: 12/03/2019 3:00 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contract Term: 2-year contract upon OSC approval&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: Cold Spring Harbor State Park&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Direct Requests for RFP details and any questions can be submitted to contracts@parks.ny.gov. The deadline for proposal is December 3.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/43b3dd19-4fa4-4e8f-aba8-89405d5a2c1b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>09dea911-e0d1-46f4-be5f-e802462427d0</id><title>Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transportation Authority (Metro) launches Call to Artists</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.904289+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transportation Authority&lt;br/&gt;📍 Los Angeles, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.metro.net/artistpool"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL TO ARTISTS – 2020 Artist Pool&lt;br/&gt;(Request for Qualifications)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Metro Art invites visual artists to respond to our 2020 Call to Artists. Metro Art commissions artists to create artworks that improve the transit customer experience and contribute to the artistic vibrancy of the communities we serve. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: Online submittal must be completed via SlideRoom by 11:59 p.m. (PST) on December 9, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Interested artists are encouraged to learn more about the 2020 Artist Pool through our website. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist Opportunities&lt;br/&gt;•	The Artist Pool will be one of the primary methods for inviting artists to apply for future Metro art opportunities.&lt;br/&gt;•	Opportunities include artwork integration within the built environment and short-term exhibitions in media such as lightboxes, posters and construction phase banners.&lt;br/&gt;•	Inclusion in the Artist Pool does not guarantee a commission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility&lt;br/&gt;•	Professional artists working in two- and three-dimensional media at all career stages that are interested in creating art for the public realm.  Prior public art experience is not a requirement.&lt;br/&gt;•	Artists who are legally authorized to work in the United States (per U.S. Department of Labor).&lt;br/&gt;•	Metro employees and contractors are not eligible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Metro Art&lt;br/&gt;For more information about the Metro Art program, projects in the works, tours, events, publications and artist opportunities:&lt;br/&gt;•	metro.net/art&lt;br/&gt;•	Instagram.com/metro.art.la&lt;br/&gt;•	facebook.com/metroartla&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Information and support materials must be submitted through Slideroom.com at &lt;a href="https://metroart.slideroom.com/#/login" target="_blank"&gt;https://metroart.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The submittal package must include up to 10 digital files of their artwork, a professional resume and an artist statement.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applicants can receive technical support for submissions by emailing support@slideroom.com or by accessing the online help desk: &lt;a href="https://support.slideroom.com/" target="_blank"&gt;https://support.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Allow adequate time to familiarize yourself with the SlideRoom submittal process and to receive any needed technical support.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Information submitted by mail, email, fax, hand-delivery or after the deadline will not be considered.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Incomplete submittals will not be evaluated.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists who do not meet the eligibility requirements will not be evaluated.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/09dea911-e0d1-46f4-be5f-e802462427d0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>128dbbac-d566-4222-bd1a-c0e9ba9bc521</id><title>12/21 - Open Call for Contemporary Ceramics Exhibition curated by Matt Nolen</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.904261+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Long Island City Artists @ The 12,000 sq ft Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Islanc City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_claytopian_ny"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Deadline: Saturday, December 21st, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition on View: February 20th, 2020 to March 15th, 2020&lt;br/&gt;“Claytopian New York” curated by Matt Nolen invites sculptors to apply who use the universal language of ceramics to express the idealized universe of their artistic vision and diversity. Visions that include references to the spectrum of history, traditions, world culture, gender, social and political issues and notions of beauty- life in the Metropolis.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Invited Artists include: Ron Baron, Sin-ying Ho, Julia Kunin, Sana Musasama, Steven Montgomery, Melissa Stern, Derek Weisberg, Adams Puryear, Eun-Ha Paek, Elise Siegel, among others.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: The Plaxall Gallery, 5-25 46th Avenue, Long Island City, NY&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Saturday, February 22nd, 7-10:00 PM&lt;br/&gt;Curators Talk: Saturday, February 22nd, 6-7:00 PM &lt;br/&gt;Medium: Ceramics&lt;br/&gt;Curated by: Matt Nolan&lt;br/&gt;Application Fee: $25.00 LiC-A members, $40.00 non-members&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: Saturday, December 21st, 2019&lt;br/&gt;www.licartists.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the curator:&lt;br/&gt;Matt Nolen is a studio artist living and working in New York City and Narrowsburg, NY.  Nolen’s work has been written about and reviewed in the New York Times, American Ceramics, Ceramics Art and Perception, Masters of Craft, Confrontational Clay, Postmodern Ceramics, Painted Clay and more...He has recently served as President of the Board of Trustees for Watershed Center for the Ceramic Arts in Newcastle, Maine, is currently serving as Trustee of the Robert M. MacNamara Foundation and is Adjunct Professor of Art at New York University, Hunter College, and Ceramics Area Coordinator at Pratt Institute.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.nolenstudios.com/about&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please go to the online submission form to enter:&lt;br/&gt;https://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_claytopian_ny&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/128dbbac-d566-4222-bd1a-c0e9ba9bc521" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e9228982-504b-4658-8750-3580d4d8a957</id><title>1/13 - Earth Works:  Art in Ecological Context National Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.904232+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Barrett Art Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Poughkeepsie, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/13/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.barrettartcenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juror: Karl Kusserow, John Wilmerding Curator of American Art, Princeton University Art Museum&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: January 13, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: March 28 – May 2, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$500 Juror’s Prize, $250 Second Prize, $125 Honorable Mention&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Barrett Art Center invites artists to submit work that explores mankind’s impact on the environment and our relationship with the earth.  Artists are likewise invited to submit works that stimulate conversation about our evolving ideas about the landscape, the landscape tradition, and climate change in contemporary culture. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Drawing, painting (all mediums), pastel, printmaking, photography, sculpture, fiber, mixed-media, new media, and installation works are eligible. We invite proposals of both contemporary and traditional pieces that create a visually-compelling complement, or counterpoint, to Barrett Art Center’s 1840s Greek Revival townhouse interior. &lt;br/&gt;About the Juror:&lt;br/&gt;Karl Kusserow is John Wilmerding Curator of American Art at the Princeton University Art Museum. He recently co-organized Nature’s Nation: American Art and Environment (2018), a traveling exhibition reexamining 18th-21st-century American art in relation to issues of ecology and environmental history. Its catalogue received a 2019 Award for Excellence from the Association of Art Museum Curators and was named the Art Exhibitions category winner by the Association of American Publishers in its 2019 PROSE Awards. Kusserow is currently preparing a related volume, Picture Ecology: Art and Ecocriticism in Planetary Perspective, for publication, in addition to Object Lessons: American Art from Princeton, accompanying a forthcoming traveling exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;His exhibition, Nature’s Nation: American Art and Environment was featured at the Princeton University Museum of Art; the Peabody Essex Museum in Salem, MA; and the Crystal Bridges Museum of American Art, in Bentonville, Ark.  See, “Can Art Help Save the Planet?”, New York Times, March 12, 2019:  &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/12/arts/art-climate-change.html" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.nytimes.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists can submit artwork through Call for Entry: &lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=7209" target="_blank"&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e9228982-504b-4658-8750-3580d4d8a957" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6aa3c50d-4730-4473-996d-ef2d778aa02e</id><title>1/8 - She: an expression of womanhood</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.904205+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Annmarie Sculpture Garden &amp;amp; Arts Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Solomons, MD, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/08/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She: an Expression of Womanhood focuses on the theme of women in art, as creators, innovators, consumers, and subject matter. In an era of multiplying female voices, world-wide political movements, and fluid gender roles and identities, this exhibit invites artists to dive into the vast and often contentious conversation about the meaning of she. Works that delve into human rights and agency, gender roles and relationships, and cultural events like the #metoo movement, are also welcome. The goal is to create a rich exploration of womanhood that celebrates and embraces different voices, experiences, and interpretations. All media welcome; small to large scale works; indoor and outdoor works; cash awards will be presented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PROSPECTUS/APPLICATION: &lt;a href="https://annmariegarden.wufoo.com/forms/she-an-expression-of-womanhood/" target="_blank"&gt;https://annmariegarden.wufoo.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CALL FOR ENTRIES - a national juried exhibition. All media welcome; small to large-scale works; indoor and outdoor works accepted; cash awards.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;She: an Expression of Womanhood&lt;br/&gt;February 14 - September 27, 2020, Kay Daugherty Gallery&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNMARIE SCULPTURE GARDEN &amp; ARTS CENTER&lt;br/&gt;In Association with the Smithsonian Institution&lt;br/&gt;Solomons, Maryland, 20688 USA&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE to apply: January 8, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CONTACT: art@annmariegarden.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6aa3c50d-4730-4473-996d-ef2d778aa02e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>10639141-4e71-466a-b5de-7bce50f1e3ca</id><title>12/11 - Viewpoint: Landscape and Architectrue</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.904179+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on landscape and architecture at Black Box Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/10639141-4e71-466a-b5de-7bce50f1e3ca" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>05390190-baeb-44ff-b523-5da25aeeeec3</id><title>12/13 - Publication Opportunity for All Artist</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.904153+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Plus Magazine, LLC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/13/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.plusmagazines.net"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Publication Opportunity for All Artist&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are seeking passionate artists/creatives to join us for our issue 2 of Plus Magazine!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Plus Magazine seeks to offer encouragement, to provide opportunities for growth and to highlight gifts the world may have overlooked. Here, art is more than a canvas or clay. Here, we honor ingenuity and drive. We showcase rising talent in all disciplines and fields and aspire to find their common threads. Here, we feature experienced voices to inspire those who are working to find their way; who are trying to make an impact in this complex world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details:&lt;br/&gt;Artists working in all media are encouraged to apply for this open call. We are looking for artists who are willing to create new works starting from January through March 31. Selected artists will be awarded an opportunity to showcase their new works in our second issue of Plus Magazine, which will be expanded not only in the U.S. market but also in Europe and Asia. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are always excited to see new works and rising artists who are passionate about the creative field and we want to learn more about your stories and works through Plus Magazine!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE SUBMIT&lt;br/&gt;Submission materials:&lt;br/&gt;• Up to 8 images of work/link to the portfolio&lt;br/&gt;• CV &lt;br/&gt;• Short statement &amp; bio&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;Submission- December 13, 2019 (midnight, GMT) &lt;br/&gt;Notification -December 16, 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please contact us with questions at  info@plus-mag.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/05390190-baeb-44ff-b523-5da25aeeeec3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9f2b0cb7-7e5d-46bc-939e-7e78ecb1afbe</id><title>12/1 - ECOCA&amp;#39;S Open Call 2020</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.904123+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ely Center of Contemporary Art&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Haven, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://elycenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ely Center of Contemporary Art is pleased to announce Open Call 2020. &lt;br/&gt;Submissions will be considered for:&lt;br/&gt;	•	Exhibition guest curated by Two Coats of Paint's, Sharon Butler, Jan. 12–Feb. 16, 2020 &lt;br/&gt;	•	Solo exhibitions curated by ECOCA&lt;br/&gt;	•	Grace’s Trust, an on-line exhibition platform&lt;br/&gt;	•	Thematic exhibitions&lt;br/&gt;	•	Project space for video, installation, and experimental works&lt;br/&gt;	•	Perspectives Gallery @ Whitney Center, Hamden, curated by Debbie Hesse&lt;br/&gt;	•	Other off-site programs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://elycenter.org/open-call-2020" target="_blank"&gt;https://elycenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9f2b0cb7-7e5d-46bc-939e-7e78ecb1afbe" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>512326af-3b1b-4563-97e6-5c887d01f665</id><title>Events+Workshops // a platform for launching open-ended and experimental events+workshops</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.904045+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Painted Cloud&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.thepaintedcloud.com/open-call"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Events+Workshops are ideas that are not fully realized and do not have a planned outcome. Presenters, who are experienced and experts in their fields, explore a material or a facet of a topic that they themselves have not yet fully explored. As a presenter, think of yourself as an experienced captain steering a boat in uncharted waters.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are not limited to visual arts. Past events+workshops consisted of performance, screenings, readings, and more. We are open to your ideas.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are promoted to the public as pay-as-you-wish (suggested $10-$20). All money collected for events+workshops is split 50/50 between the presenter and The Painted Cloud after material costs(up to $35) are reimbursed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are 2-4 hours long in duration and occur one Saturday per month.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are one-offs.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are open to the public.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are developed for adult participants, but teens can be included depending on the proposal.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are promoted through our email newsletter and social media. The presenter's 'fee' requires presenters to promote through their newsletters and social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call link here. Read the information on the link and submit your proposal at the bottom of the page.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/512326af-3b1b-4563-97e6-5c887d01f665" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c74598ce-a7f6-4888-a030-4b9794daa124</id><title>11/25 - Dear Diary - open call for art</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.904014+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC ARTS OPEN&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open invites artists who document, report and journal to participate in Dear Diary.    Diaries are fascinating objects that usually contain secrets, private thoughts and we invite artists of all disciplines and mediums to participate in our show which will be on show at LIC Arts Open's Gallery ONE at The Factory LIC, 30-30 47th Ave, LIC, 11101.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We accept all disciplines including painting, sculpture, photography, video, installation and multi-media however video equipment is not provided and if your project requires technology please state so on the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are encouraging as many artists as possible to show in our 2000 sq foot gallery in one of LIC's signature buildings, The Factory.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline Nov 25th, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Notification Nov 27th, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Drop off Artwork Nov 30 &amp; Dec 1 (Times TBC)&lt;br/&gt;Reception December 5th 5pm - 8pm&lt;br/&gt;Show Closes on Jan 3rd&lt;br/&gt;Pick up Jan 4th &amp; 5th (Times TBC)&lt;br/&gt;*Please note there is an application fee that offsets the installation costs and helps to pay for the refreshments. If you have previously participated please select option 2 otherwise if new to LIC Arts Open please select option 1.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork should be dropped off on November 30th &amp; Dec 1st between the hours of 2 -5 pm only. We cannot accept work at other times.&lt;br/&gt;Work must be ready to hang and we do not allow shipping; all work must be hand-delivered on the designated times and dates.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Gallery commission is 25% please price accordingly&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Information&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Standard Artwork Drop off&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork must be ready to hang with appropriate fixings etc. Please know that some walls are the cinderblock/cement and others are drywall. If you are bringing a sculptural or video work, please provide the necessary technology. If you can provide pedestals that are helpful but not required.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have proposed performance or other live work (an installation, etc.) we will contact you directly with further information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Please take/remove your wrappings at drop off unless you are fine with it being disposed of; we do not have storage for wrappings, boxes, bubble wrap, etc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Storage:  We have no storage for wrappings or art.  Please only bring the pieces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are really interested in showing the work of artists from outside of LIC, Queens &amp; NYC but all work must be hand-delivered in person (i.e. either yourself or someone dropping off in your place). Nevertheless, if you live in another city but can drop off and pick up the work at the specified dates and times then please feel free to apply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please use this form to apply, please cut and paste into your browser&lt;br/&gt;https://form.jotform.com/trimistopheles/dear-diary-open-call&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c74598ce-a7f6-4888-a030-4b9794daa124" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f0e235d6-7f02-4cc3-bfb8-29815833a07b</id><title>11/25 - &amp;#39;The 2020 Socrates Annual&amp;#39; Fellowship</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903978+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Socrates Sculpture Park&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="bit.ly/2Cpgprv"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;‘Call and Response: Making Monuments Now’&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In light of recent debates about monuments and some recent removals, Socrates asks artists to propose prototypes for new monuments for New York City for presentation beginning in the fall of 2020. Artists are invited to consider and respond to the following considerations and questions:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As symbols of Confederate and Colonial power are currently being destroyed, dismantled, reconfigured, or exiled from public view, what new representations should fill their void? What monuments should be created to reflect today’s values and our desire to project those into the future? Who or what should be given the space, representation, and honor in these new monumental artworks? More specifically, as the reconfiguration of monuments in public space reflects the process of history writing, what histories of New York should be remembered or recovered?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What kind of monument might shape public consciousness in the creation of civic agents empowered with social and political self-determination? What kind of monument might best to serve and preserve the reclamation of New York’s underrecognized or repressed histories? How might monument-makers resist the obdurate, authoritarian chauvinist impulses that commonly accompany traditional representational strategies of monuments?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This open call will be the major component of Socrates Sculpture Park’s year-long engagement with recent discourse on the current state and future of monuments in the United States. It is a thematic adaption of ‘The Socrates Annual Fellowship’ and exhibition, and incorporates an extended selection process and production timeline as well as inclusion in an exhibition publication.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;These monument prototypes for New York City will be presented alongside three new commissions for speculative monuments for America by major artists, and a collective monument for Queens created by participants in the Park’s after-school program for teenagers: Socrateens.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fellowship recipients will receive a $5,000 production grant to support their project a $1,000 honorarium and four-months of seven-days-a-week access to the resources and fabrication facilities of the Park’s outdoor artist studio.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist Fellows are responsible for the fabrication, transportation (if necessary) and installation of their works. Socrates will provide limited technical and installation assistance during a three-week installation period, M-F, 10AM – 6PM. Specifics of installation assistance will be discussed with each artist selected.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT DATES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline&lt;br/&gt;Monday, November 25, 2019 by 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notification&lt;br/&gt;January 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fellowship&lt;br/&gt;April 2020 – September 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;October 2020 – March 2021&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DOCS TO DOWNLOAD&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Instructions: bit.ly/2NqoZML&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FAQs: bit.ly/2PVybKN&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Equipment List: bit.ly/2qAeYUc&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SITE &amp; CONTEXT&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Before preparing their applications, artists are strongly encouraged to visit Socrates – a unique New York City public park located on the East River waterfront in an industrial area of Long Island City, Queens – and to explore Socrates’ website and exhibition archive to learn about the history and context of the organization. Visiting the Park will give applicants a better sense of the factors that effect installations in the Park and help impart insights into the available facilities – from the tools and equipment in Socrates’ artist studio to the resources of the surrounding neighborhood.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;REVIEW PROCESS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;‘The Socrates Annual’ fellowship program is based on a competitive, open application process. Completed on-line applications must be submitted by the deadline (Monday, November 25, 2019 by 11:59pm) and will be reviewed by the Socrates exhibition department and outside curatorial advisors. Ten to twelve artists will be selected for the 2020 program. Artists are selected based on the compelling nature of the project proposed, clarity of intent, unique approach to the site, and public context.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Following the recommendations of the curatorial advisors, Socrates staff will contact applicants individually to discuss proposed projects before confirming the final selection in early 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FELLOWSHIP&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Once accepted, Socrates staff members will meet with each Artist Fellow to discuss project proposals in detail and begin to assist with the development, engineering, and installation of the work. A group meeting for all Artist Fellows and Socrates staff will take place one evening in late winter of 2020, followed by an on-site orientation and individual progress meetings throughout the Fellowship to assess progress, troubleshoot issues, and review next steps. Selected works are subject to final approval by Socrates staff and must meet safety requirements to be able to withstand the effects of weather and public use.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fellowships are awarded to artists whose careers and artistic practices would benefit from the opportunity. Artists who are enrolled in a school, college, or university at the time of application are NOT eligible for ‘The Socrates Annual’ fellowship program. Artists who have applied before, but never shown at Socrates, are eligible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The fellowship stipends and honoraria of three out of the 10+ artists selected for The Socrates Annual will be paid for through support from The New York Community Trusts’s Edward &amp; Sally Van Lier Fund. Applicants who meet the following criteria would be eligible to receive their fellowship funding through Van Lier:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Are 30-years-old or younger as of April 15, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Identify with a historically underrepresented community&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Are a New York City-resident&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Have not previously received a Van Lier Fellowship&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We only accept proposals submitted through our online portal: bit.ly/2Cpgprv&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;QUESTIONS?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email jw@socratessculpturepark.org with questions or concerns.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUPPORT&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are eternally grateful for longstanding support from the Jerome Foundation, National Endowment for the Arts, and The New York Community Trust, which has enabled the Emerging Artist Fellowship program to grow and evolve since its founding in 1995.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And special thanks goes to our public partners, including the City of New York, Mayor Bill de Blasio, Queens Borough President Melinda R. Katz, City Council Speaker Cory Johnson, City Council Members Jimmy Van Bramer and Costa Constantinides, the NYC Department of Parks and Recreation, Commissioner Mitchell Silver, and the NYC Department of Cultural Affairs, Commissioner Tom Finkelpearl.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Socrates Sculpture Park has been a model of public art production, community activism, and socially inspired place-making for more than 30 years. Known for fostering ambitious and visionary artworks, Socrates has presented more than 1,200 artists on its five waterfront acres, providing them the financial support, materials, equipment, and space necessary to create large-scale works in the public realm. Open 365 days a year from 9am till dusk, the Park is a center of cultural programming – as a producer of contemporary sculpture exhibitions, a presenter of a multi-disciplinary performances, an arts educator, and a venue for healthy outdoor activities  – all offered completely free of charge to the public. The Park’s existence is based on the belief that reclamation, revitalization and creative expression are essential to the survival, humanity and improvement of our urban environment.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply Now: bit.ly/2Cpgprv&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While our system automatically saves your work as you go, we recommend that you prepare your up-loadable application materials – detailed below – in advance and prior to entering the online application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: Required fields are noted with an asterisk (*).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. PERSONAL INFO*&lt;br/&gt;Complete the first section that asks: 1) name*; 2) date of birth*; 3) place of birth*; 4) mailing address*; 5) telephone number*; and 6) email address*. Please also indicate your 8a) gender (optional); and 8b) ethnicity (optional); 9) whether you previously submitted a proposal to Socrates Sculpture Park*; and 10) whether you are currently based in New York City.* We ask for information about gender and ethnicity because many of our funders inquire.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2. RESUME*&lt;br/&gt;Upload your most current resume as a PDF. Resume should include information&lt;br/&gt;about your education; exhibition history; awards, grants, and residencies; and details of any published writings. File formats accepted: PDF, DOC, or DOCX&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3a. WORK SAMPLE LIST*&lt;br/&gt;Upload a numbered list that corresponds to each of the 10 files submitted. For each image, include the title, date, materials, and dimensions. A two-sentence description of each work is optional. File formats accepted: PDF, DOC, or DOCX, Must by under 1MB&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3b. WORK SAMPLES IMAGES*&lt;br/&gt;Work samples should be of ten recent works, particularly work that relates to your proposal for Socrates Sculpture Park. These images are in addition to any images submitted as part of the project proposal. File formats accepted: JPG, TIFF, MP3, WAV, MP4 and MOV.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4a. ARTIST STATEMENT&lt;br/&gt;Use this section to briefly describe the interests and concerns of your artistic practice. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4b. PROPOSAL*&lt;br/&gt;You may submit one proposal. Enter a written description of the monument - up to 500 words - that you would like to produce and exhibit at Socrates Sculpture Park. This written description should include overall concept, dimensions and materials, and demonstrate a general familiarity with the Park’s site, hours, operations, and audience.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4c. QUESTIONS&lt;br/&gt;There are two prompts that allow you to further contextualize your project:&lt;br/&gt;1) What history does your proposed monument address? How does this project relate to existing monuments in the world?&lt;br/&gt;2) Describe the production process including durability of materials for an&lt;br/&gt;outdoor environment and the relationship to your practice, as you are invited to produce work on-site at the Park’s open-air studio space.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4d. PROPOSAL IMAGES AND MATERIALS*&lt;br/&gt;Upload a single file of up to three pages with drawings, plans, or renderings. File formats accepted: PDF, DOC, or DOCX, JPG, or TIFF.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;5. PROPOSAL BUDGET*&lt;br/&gt;Upload a realistic budget for materials and production with a thorough breakdown of anticipated expenses. This should include the cost of fabrication assistance if necessary within the $5,000 budget total. Please note that there is a separate artist honorarium of $1,000. File formats accepted: PDF, DOC, or DOCX.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;6. POTENTIAL PROGRAMMING&lt;br/&gt;Please share ideas for potential public programing or performance elements that may complement the Park’s already existing special event and public programming that occur throughout the summer and fall. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;7. REFERENCES*&lt;br/&gt;Provide two names, emails and phone numbers of people familiar with your work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;8. SUBMIT*&lt;br/&gt;Once all material is entered and uploaded, click SUBMIT. You will receive an email confirming receipt of the application after completion.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;QUESTIONS?&lt;br/&gt;Email jw@socratessculpturepark.org with questions or concerns.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATIONS WILL NOT BE ACCEPTED AFTER 11:59PM ON MONDAY, NOVEMBER 25, 2019. SELECTED ARTISTS WILL BE NOTIFIED IN JANUARY 2020.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f0e235d6-7f02-4cc3-bfb8-29815833a07b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>622c8652-acad-4995-9fdc-3d2d4ba257df</id><title>12/5 - INTERNATIONAL CALL FOR ART, ArtMaze Magazine Winter Edition 2020: Issue 16</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903950+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtMaze Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍  , United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/05/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artmazemag.com/call-for-art/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art Maze Magazine is an independent artist-run and ad-free international print and online publication dedicated to showcasing and promoting experimental and progressive contemporary art, which reflects modern society and its environment, provokes conversation and action; fosters innovation and diversity of mediums which make today’s art scene so intriguing and versatile.&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: Artists are welcome to submit works in any medium: painting, drawing, sculpture, ceramics, printmaking, photography, textile, installation, mixed media, digital, film (only jpg + link to video) etc. All visual art mediums are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists or any art organisations on behalf of artists from all countries are welcome to submit their works for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each submitted artist, whether selected for a publication or not, will receive a digital copy of the magazine's issue which they applied for.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: December 5th, 2019 (12:00 AM, midnight: end of the day 5th December - Eastern Standard Time)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUEST CURATOR: Scott Ogden, founder and curator of Shrine Gallery, NYC&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO APPLY: www.artmazemag.com/call-for-art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DISTRIBUTION: Physical and digital copies of ArtMaze Mag are distributed worldwide via bookshops, galleries and online. More info: &lt;a href="http://artmazemag.com/shop/" target="_blank"&gt;http://artmazemag.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selected artists will be asked for high resolution images and will be published in the next print and digital issue of ArtMaze Magazine. Each (selected) artist will receive a 1 or 2-page spread in print and digital (PDF) magazine including bio, statement, website, and 1-5 featured artworks. All submitted artists will receive a complimentary PDF copy of the magazine and all published artists will be promoted on our website/social media. Physical copies of Art Maze Magazine are printed to the highest quality in London, UK.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/622c8652-acad-4995-9fdc-3d2d4ba257df" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e5cb7124-ada7-4e57-a88d-c4142e0d026a</id><title>11/30 - Atlantic Gallery Juried Exhibition 2020 SEEING THE UNSEEABLE</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903918+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Atlantic Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://atlanticgallery.org/juried-exhibition-2020-seeing-the-unseeable/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried Group Show with Grand Prize: a Solo Show at Atlantic Gallery in NYC’s Chelsea art district.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In 1947, Mark Rothko wrote:&lt;br/&gt;“Pictures must be miraculous: the instant one is completed, the intimacy between the creation and the creator is ended. He is an outsider. The picture must be for him, as for anyone experiencing it later, a revelation…”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The artist makes the work and the viewer sees it consciously and unconsciously without knowing quite how.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTIST ARE ASKED TO SUBMIT WORKS THAT CHALLENGE THE VIEWER TO QUESTION HOW IDEAS, PLANS AND MATERIALS HAVE BEEN TRANSFORMED IN THE ACT OF CREATION.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Works may be 2- or 3-dimensional.&lt;br/&gt;Juror is a NY-based curator, art consultant and visual artist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To submit your application please visit &lt;a href="http://atlanticgallery.org/juried-exhibition-2020-seeing-the-unseeable/" target="_blank"&gt;http://atlanticgallery.org&lt;/a&gt; and apply through Entrythingy.&lt;br/&gt;JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Judith Krugeris a visual artist whose paintings, prints and mixed media works address Human-Environment connectivity and their shared vulnerabilities. She is recognized internationally for her advocacy of natural painting materials and historic, ecological processes.  Judith’s work is held in private and public collections including Hammond Museum, North Salem, NY, Mattatuck Museum, Waterbury, CT, Jefferson Hospital, Philadelphia, PA, Savannah College of Art and Design, Hong Kong and Phipps Conservatory’s Center for Sustainable Landscapes, Pittsburgh, PA.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Solo exhibitions include Richardson Art Museum, Wofford College, Spartanburg, SC, Mattatuck Museum, Waterbury, CT, Hammond Museum, North Salem, NY, Bentley Gallery, Phoenix, Arizona and Morrison Gallery, Kent, CT. Select group exhibitions include Agawami Museum Hall, Tokushima, Japan, Sato Museum, Tokyo, Japan, Mass MoCA, North Adams, MA, New Britain Museum of American Art, New Britain, CT, Manifest Gallery, Cincinnati, OH, Blue Spiral Gallery, Asheville, NC, John and Robyn Horn Gallery, Penland, NC, Perimeter Gallery, Chicago, IL, Gallery G, Hiroshima, Japan, Pallazo Dell’Anunziata, Matera, Italy, Chicago Cultural Center, Chicago, IL and The Muckenthaler Cultural Center, Fullerton, CA.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Judith received her BFA from Syracuse University and MFA from Savannah College of Art and Design. She has been awarded professional development grants from the Chicago Dept of Cultural Affairs, Target Corporation, Mass MoCA and most recently, a fellowship grant from the Connecticut Office of the Arts. Her studio is located in an old hosiery mill 125 miles North of New York City, at the foothills of the Berkshire Mountains.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;www.judithkruger.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;TIME LINE FOR EXHIBITION&lt;br/&gt;November 30, 2019: Deadline for entry&lt;br/&gt;December 1-4, 2019: Juror reviews work&lt;br/&gt;December 5-7, 2019: Notifications go out to accepted (and not accepted) artists&lt;br/&gt;December 16 – 21, 2019: Work shipped to the gallery&lt;br/&gt;December 16 – 21, 2019: Hand deliver work to gallery between 1pm-6pm&lt;br/&gt;January 7 – 25, 2020: Exhibition Dates&lt;br/&gt;January 9, 2020: Opening reception&lt;br/&gt;January 25, 2020: Pick up hand delivered work 5pm – 7pm&lt;br/&gt;January 28, 2020: Pick up hand delivered work 12pm – 6pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CATEGORIES:&lt;br/&gt;oils, acrylics, watercolors, pastels, drawings, prints, photography, mixed media, and sculpture in any medium&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY INSTRUCTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Open to all artists at least 18 yrs. old&lt;br/&gt;Work, including the frame, may not exceed 24 inches in width and height including frame. All work must be suitably framed (or sides cleanly finished or painted), wired and ready for hanging.&lt;br/&gt;Standing Sculptures maximum width or depth of sculpture is 24 inches x 24 inches height.&lt;br/&gt;ALL 3D WORK MUST FIT ON A 19″ SQUARE PEDESTAL OR ARTIST MUST PROVIDE THEIR OWN APPROPRIATE STAND.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEE:&lt;br/&gt;The fee is $45 for 1 – 3 works.&lt;br/&gt;$5 for each additional work, up to 5 works total. Entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PAYMENT:&lt;br/&gt;Please make payment via Paypal or mail check to&lt;br/&gt;Atlantic Gallery&lt;br/&gt;548 West 28th St, Suite 540&lt;br/&gt;New York, NY 10001&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Be sure to include your printed entry form with check.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Gallery will take 30% commission on any work sold.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LABELING IMAGES:&lt;br/&gt;JPEG images MUST BE labeled as below: Files which are mislabeled or lack the artist’s name will not be viewed by juror.&lt;br/&gt;FILE LABEL FORMAT&lt;br/&gt;YOUR LAST Name_ FIRST Name_&lt;br/&gt;smith_joe_1.jpg&lt;br/&gt;smith_joe_2.jpg etc.&lt;br/&gt;Sculptors must submit two views of EACH work, at no extra cost, and label each work: smith_joe_1a.jpg&lt;br/&gt;smith_joe_1b.jpg&lt;br/&gt;smith_joe_2a.jpg&lt;br/&gt;smith_joe_2b.jpg etc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Delivery and Pick-up Instructions for Artwork to Atlantic Gallery &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shipping Address:&lt;br/&gt;Atlantic Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Attn: Martha Jasopersaud&lt;br/&gt;548 West 28thSt; Suite 540&lt;br/&gt;New York, NY 10001&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contact Information:&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Manager: Martha Jasopersaud&lt;br/&gt;(212) 219-3183&lt;br/&gt;atlanticgalleryinfo@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FOR SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Packages need to be Delivered: December 16 – 21, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Please be sure to tell preferred carrier service that packages need to arrive during our business hours:Tuesday – Saturday; 12:00pm – 6:00pm.&lt;br/&gt;Please include (AND email ahead) DETAILED instructions for unpacking and re-packing work, as well as any specific installation instructions.&lt;br/&gt;Work should be shipped in the smallest reusable container that will safely transport the piece.&lt;br/&gt;Please DO NOT use packing peanuts.&lt;br/&gt;A computer-generated return label for return of work MUST be enclosed in an envelope taped to the back of your artwork or email label to atlanticgalleryinfo@gmail.com.NO EXCEPTIONS. Pre-paid shipping arrangements must be made through UPS or FedEx websites or with other shippers who will pick up work at the gallery. No U.S. Postal Service or COD returns. DO NOT send check, stamps, or credit card information for return of work.&lt;br/&gt;If you are shipping via UPS please be sure to pay for pickup of your piece. It is a separate fee when you purchase your return label.&lt;br/&gt;The gallery will do its best to repack work in shipped packaging, but responsibility for providing adequate packaging and instructions rests with the artist.&lt;br/&gt;FOR HAND DELIVERY:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Hand Delivered: December 16 – 21, 2020; 12pm-6pm&lt;br/&gt;Please wrap artwork in bubble wrap if you choose not to package it in a box.&lt;br/&gt;Hand-delivered packaging must be removed from the gallery upon delivery. Floor stands must be brought with sculpture unless arrangements are made to use a gallery stand. Gallery stands are 19”x19”.&lt;br/&gt;Hand-delivered work must be picked up on Saturday, January 25, 2020: 5pm – 7pm and Tuesday, January 28, 2020: 12pm – 6pm&lt;br/&gt;The gallery accepts no responsibility for work not retrieved on pick-up date. If other arrangements need to be made please contact gallery manager via email atlanticgalleryinfo@gmail.comor phone (212) 219-3183. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Terms of Entry for Entrants:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All works must be for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Accepted work may be refused if it does not conform to the entered image. Absolutely NO substitutions of accepted works will be allowed. All accepted work must remain in the gallery for the duration of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission to this juried exhibition constitutes an agreement on the part of the entrant to the conditions set forth in this prospectus. Atlantic Gallery reserves the right to final curatorial, educational, installation and marketing decisions. Entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Great care will be taken with all work, but artists are responsible for insuring their own pieces if they wish. Atlantic Gallery will not be responsible for any loss or damage to work while on the premises or in transit to or from the gallery. The payment of the entry fee will serve as your acceptance of the terms and conditions stated in this prospectus. Acceptance of a work of art to this exhibition shall be understood to constitute an agreement on the part of the artist to the terms and conditions stated in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e5cb7124-ada7-4e57-a88d-c4142e0d026a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>62651f35-d971-4127-a10b-c993dfe13d27</id><title>11/15 - Engaging Artists: Fellowship and Residency</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903890+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;More Art&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://moreart.org/projects/engaging-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ENGAGING ARTISTS (EA) is More Art’s 2-tiered, Fellowship and Residency program for artists seeking to both develop and sustain their public art and socially-engaged practice. The program curriculum encompasses a professional development series, public art commission opportunities, mentorship, and peer networking. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FELLOWSHIP&lt;br/&gt;The twelve-month Fellowship provides an infrastructure and laboratory for NYC-based emerging and underrepresented artists to gain a deeper understanding of the history of the field of public art, incubate and develop their early-stage research and project, collaborate with communities in shaping society, and build sustainable careers. The EA Curriculum is valued at $25,000 per participant. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RESIDENCY&lt;br/&gt;The nine-month Residency provides an opportunity for NYC-based early career and underrepresented artists to gain a deeper understanding of the history of the field of public art, and is focused on the incubation and commissioning of  a public art project. The Residency carries a $8000 award to realize the project.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are currently accepting applications for the 2020 season. The deadline to apply is 11:59pm on November 15, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications for the Fellowship and Residency are accepted once annually.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and to apply, go to: &lt;a href="http://moreart.org/projects/engaging-artists/" target="_blank"&gt;http://moreart.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/62651f35-d971-4127-a10b-c993dfe13d27" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>fb62fce7-4fc9-4290-9b49-0aa0d37f0be5</id><title>12/31 - ARTIST CALL - Habitat California: Flora &amp;amp; Fauna - Traditional and Digital Media Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903861+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Palos Verdes Art Center / Beverly G Alpay Center for Arts Education&lt;br/&gt;📍 Rancho Palos Verdes, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://pvartcenter.org/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Habitat California: Flora &amp; Fauna&lt;br/&gt;February 8 – April 18, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Traditional and Digital Media Juried Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Tulsa Kinney, Editor of Artillery (artillerymag.com)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply at callforentry.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This invitational and juried all-media exhibition focuses on the plants and wildlife of California in the shifting ecosystems they inhabit. Entry is not restricted to California-based artists. Traditional media including painting en plein air is welcome, as well as sculpture, photography, video, and new media including VR (virtual reality), AR (augmented reality), and internet-based art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Welcome areas of inquiry include, but are not limited to:&lt;br/&gt;* Continuing the California Landscape and California Impressionist traditions.&lt;br/&gt;* The intersections of urban, suburban, and wildlife habitats.&lt;br/&gt;* The effects of climate change on wildlife and botanical habitat and species.&lt;br/&gt;* Explorations in new media featuring California flora and fauna.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contemporary juried-in works will be accompanied by works by select invited artists, as well as historic pieces by noted California painters.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Tulsa Kinney is the editor and co-founder of Artillery, a contemporary art magazine based in Los Angeles established in 2006. She received her MFA at USC in 1988 and has been in numerous solo and group art exhibitions for over two decades. At that time she was teaching digital imaging at various Southern California colleges along with her graphic design career at the LA Weekly. Tulsa started writing about 20 years ago and her articles have been published in the Los Angeles Times and LA Weekly. She continues to write about art and stay deeply immersed in the contemporary art world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: December 31, 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On-Line Submission Procedure:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Go to callforentry.org, click FIND CALLS, search "Habitat California: Fauna &amp; Fauna" &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Create a CaFE profile.&lt;br/&gt;Follow step-by-step instructions in CaFE for creating a profile. Please be sure to identify your media and substrate, i.e. oil on canvas, digital print on Arches paper, etc.&lt;br/&gt;Apply to call,. You may submit up to 3 pieces of art once your profile in CaFE is complete.&lt;br/&gt;2-Dimensional and 3D artists may submit 3 jpegs, one for each piece of art entered.&lt;br/&gt;Video, VR, and AR artworks may be represented by an MP4 in addition to a jpeg.&lt;br/&gt;VR may be submitted via URL in Oculus or Google apps.&lt;br/&gt;AR may be submitted via URL in Android and Apple app.&lt;br/&gt;All work must be original to the artist and the source material must be original to the artist or from a permitted source.&lt;br/&gt;For assistance with CaFE submission, call CaFE support at 1-303-629-1166 or contact Scott Andrews, Palos Verdes Art Center, at 310-541-2479 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Requirement for Entry: Artworks must focus on California wildlife or plants in their habitat. Artists are not restricted to being California residents.&lt;br/&gt;Selection Process:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror selections will be announced by CaFE via email by Janu. If you haven’t heard from CaFE by January 9, 2020, check your spam and trash. You can also go to your CaFE portfolio and check there.&lt;br/&gt;Media: All media is eligible.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fb62fce7-4fc9-4290-9b49-0aa0d37f0be5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ad36a03c-6450-45b1-81ed-393566525fc2</id><title>12/2 - National Exhibition of American Art.</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903834+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Pleiades Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/02/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://pleiadesgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submissions are now open for Pleiades Gallery first National Exhibition of American Art. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The theme for this exhibition is “Altered States: A state of mind that deviates from what is thought to be a normal state of consciousness.”  Artists often reinterpret reality in their art, using their own visions to create new possibilities. We are interested in seeing artist’s of the world, as interpreted in their own work. We are looking for a variety of styles and approaches from total abstraction or hyperrealist or anything in between. Send us your best works. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Jurors for this exhibition are members of Pleiades Gallery: Denise Adler, Al Benkin and Joseph O’Neill &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition will consist of two-dimensional and three-dimensional art works in all media. The size limitation for wall-hung work is 60 inches high by 40 inches wide (including frame.) Free-standing work may not exceed 30 inches wide by 30 inches deep by 96 inches high. Sorry no performance or video art. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Deadline is December 2nd, 2019 (11:59pm) EST. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee: $35 for 2 works, $5 each additional work up to a maximum of 10.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus at &lt;a href="http://pleiadesgallery.com/call-for-artists-2/" target="_blank"&gt;http://pleiadesgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ad36a03c-6450-45b1-81ed-393566525fc2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>17c2adbc-17ce-424e-a58d-b86d26ed1c34</id><title>11/19 - Call for Artists + Photographers - $550.00 Innovate Grants</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903805+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Innovate Grant&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://innovateartistgrants.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Innovate Grant is now accepting submissions for Fall 2019. Innovate Grant awards (2) $550.00 grants each quarter, to one Visual Artist and one Photographer. In addition to receiving a grant award, winners will be featured and recognized on our website and join a growing community of vibrant and talented artists. For more information and to apply visit &lt;a href="https://innovateartistgrants.org" target="_blank"&gt;https://innovateartistgrants.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Innovate Grant is a new grant program initiative that supports photographers and artists through quarterly grants. We've simplified the grant process, so that artists and photographers can focus on making their innovative work. The work should speak for itself and our application reflects that.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Innovate Grant Winners  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Joe Hedges&lt;br/&gt;Pullman, WA Summer Grant Recipient – Art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Leafy Yeh&lt;br/&gt;Los Angeles, CA Summer Grant Recipient – Photography&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Margaret Jacobs&lt;br/&gt;Enfield, NH Spring Grant Recipient – Art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ceaphas Stubbs&lt;br/&gt;Newark, NJ Spring Grant Recipient – Photography&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Taylor O. Thomas&lt;br/&gt;Tampa, FL Winter Grant Recipient – Art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shane Lavalette&lt;br/&gt;Syracuse, NY Winter Grant Recipient – Photography&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Category: Multiple disciplines and genres accepted&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: November 19, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Region: US &amp; International&lt;br/&gt;Awards: $550.00 Grants&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply Online Today&lt;br/&gt;https://innovateartistgrants.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Innovate Grant is an international grant program. Visual Artists and Photographers 18 years and older, from all around the world, are eligible to apply. All media and genres are accepted. All applicants retain the right to the work they submit. Apply today at &lt;a href="https://innovateartistgrants.org" target="_blank"&gt;https://innovateartistgrants.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/17c2adbc-17ce-424e-a58d-b86d26ed1c34" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6c7b2746-fa2e-4c87-b95f-c95f163f5413</id><title>11/15 - Open Call- Juried 3 Person Exhibition</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903775+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tiger Strikes Asteroid&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.tigerstrikesasteroid.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEN CALL FOR A 3-PERSON JURIED SHOW&lt;br/&gt;JANUARY 9 – FEBRUARY 15, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Entry Deadline: November 15, midnight &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Link: &lt;a href="https://tigerstrikesasteroid.submittable.com/submit/2ab82685-9e3c-4d98-a17f-1c7ff3f58c5a/phl-open-call-2019-three-person-exhibition" target="_blank"&gt;https://tigerstrikesasteroid.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Tiger Strikes Asteroid is a network of artist-run spaces with locations in Philadelphia, New York, and Los Angeles. Each space is independently operated and focuses on presenting a varied program of emerging and mid-career artists. Our goal is to collectively bring people together, expand connections and build community through artist-initiated exhibitions, projects, and curatorial opportunities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CALENDAR&lt;br/&gt;September 22: Submissions begin&lt;br/&gt;November 15: Submission deadline, midnight &lt;br/&gt;December 6: Notification of accepted works&lt;br/&gt;January 4-5: Delivery of accepted works, 12noon-7pm&lt;br/&gt;January 9- February 15: Exhibition dates&lt;br/&gt;January 9: Opening reception, 6-9pm&lt;br/&gt;February 13: Closing reception, 6-9&lt;br/&gt;February 16: Pick up of all work, 12noon-7pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEE: $25 &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition is open to artists age 18 and older. International artists are also welcome to apply but are responsible for all shipping costs. At least one of three artists included in this exhibition will be local to the Philadelphia area.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SPECIFICATIONS&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition is open to works in all media. Wall pieces must be wired for hanging. Installation pieces must be received ready for installation with proper hanging devices attached and thorough instructions where necessary. Audio/Video artists need to provide a monitor and/or other equipment. Accepted work cannot be substituted and must be available for the duration of the exhibit. All work must be ready to hang. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;Submit up to 5 JPEG digital images to Submittable. &lt;br/&gt;¥	File dimensions: no smaller than 1920 pixels on the longest side&lt;br/&gt;¥	File resolution: 72 ppi/dpi (standard web resolution)&lt;br/&gt;¥	File size: 5 MB maximum&lt;br/&gt;¥	Video: upload a still image and provide a link to the video in the image description box.&lt;br/&gt;¥	File labeling: Each image should be numbered and include your first and last name and the image title. Example: 1_Toni_Basil_Untitled.jpg; 2_Toni_Basil_DreamBoat.jpg; etc&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HONORARIUM&lt;br/&gt;Each artist will receive $150 honorarium.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING/DELIVERY OF ARTWORK&lt;br/&gt;The artist is responsible for the cost of shipping or mailing artwork to and from Tiger Strikes Asteroid using Fed-X, UPS or Post. A return shipping label and return postage must be included with the artwork. Artwork may also be hand-delivered to and picked up from Tiger Strikes Asteroid on the appropriate dates during the scheduled times.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SALE OF ARTWORK&lt;br/&gt;Tiger Strikes Asteroid retains a 30% commission on all art sales made during the exhibition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://tigerstrikesasteroid.submittable.com/submit/2ab82685-9e3c-4d98-a17f-1c7ff3f58c5a/phl-open-call-2019-three-person-exhibition" target="_blank"&gt;https://tigerstrikesasteroid.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;email philadelphia@tigerstrikesasteroid.com with questions&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6c7b2746-fa2e-4c87-b95f-c95f163f5413" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>5e78dcea-33b9-4545-a880-a27f5b6ab434</id><title>11/22 - CURATORIAL APPLICATION NOW OPEN | SPRING/BREAK Art Show NYC + Los Angeles 2020</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903738+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SPRING/BREAK Art Show&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/22/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $100.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.springbreakartshow.com/2020-application/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SPRING/BREAK Art Show is now accepting submissions by curators until November 22, 2019, midnight (your time), for the upcoming 2020 New York City and Los Angeles exhibitions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2020 THEME | IN EXCESS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“The more the merrier.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;                          - Traditional&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The term ‘tipping point’ is used frequently in current affairs in regards to a variety of topics. Environmental extinction predominantly first and foremost, but also resumed economic stability, political divisiveness, information overloads, cancel culture mania, all are together thought to be at every manner of places along an axis of toppling the heck over, with varying ideas circulated as to which side of their scales are too overstuffed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art and entertainment feel indistinguishable from one another, piled together as “content”, which is consistently billed as in overwhelming supply from creators both amateur and professional; News peppers everyday moments through our devices’ push notifications and peer updates; tech-aided romantic possibilities appear infinite, as do all the other seductions of a globalized world—people to meet, people to follow, things to buy and eat and do. (Should one be able to afford it…For better or worse, then, the ‘too much’-ness of everything is certainly on the mind. In line with these grumblings of overmuch, SPRING/BREAK Art Show 2020 seeks similar inquiries into the paradoxes and nuances of ‘more’. For both upcoming New York and Los Angeles shows, IN EXCESS is actively searching for exhibitions dealing with virtues and/or limitations of maximalism, materialism, digression, hysterical realism, capitalism, encyclopedii, redundancy, consumerism, the over-foot-noted and the overlabored. Submissions may or may not include touchstones on multimedia, multiracial, or multiverse theories and perspectives; environmentalism, globalization, and future shock; the baroque, the Simulacrum, the epic, human play, the hall of mirrors, or any manner of other meditations on the Anthropocene and its anxieties; and, maybe—where we can find them—joys.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The pleasure of ‘more is more’ may be explored through the joyously overindulged overabundance of ideas, forms, perspectives. Aesthetically, ‘the bigger, brighter, busier, the better’ was once the zeitgeist with the intent to create, not a nauseous geegaw of consumer pleasures, but an impression that rattled complacency—generating, instead, awe, surprise, wonder; a sense of the infinitude of our World. Where is our awe now in all this excess? Where is the new Rocaille? Is it any good? Is it a spectre of Greed or Good? How much is not enough, and when is too little too soon?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;References in the current and former art landscape include, but are not limited to, Peter Saul’s rambunctious hypercolor paintings of interwoven political brutality, Joyce Kozloff’s reframing of “women’s work” in her P &amp; D movement pieces and their extension over into, and reframing by, artist Liz Collins, William Powhida’s art world cartography of complicit capitalism. Marco Brambilla crafts sprawling video pop cultural hells and heavens, packed with re-appropriated movie characters all fighting each other for a place in the pantheon, Mickalene Thomas constructs dizzying pastiche domiciles where tactile textiles, personal experience, and the figure from memory converge, authors like Thomas Pynchon and Zadie Smith jam-pack characters into stories teeming with a dance of detritus both intimate and historical; Stan Brakhage deploys the barrage for the sake of recalibrating our vision, Anselm Kiefer, with his fussy gigantic meditations, employs scale to save our soul. Robert Breer’s lightning speed animations stagger in their short running time pummel, Azikiwe Mohammed toils to find overstocked thrift store tapestries of Black utopias, and for Alison Zuckerman, art history, digital self-documentation, and Photoshop fiddling all find themselves locked, arm-in-arm, in triplicate.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Wilde suggested moderation in art and life was a fatal thing. But how does it support or subvert our consumptive excesses? Like Gittes once said to Mulwray, “how much better can you eat? What can you buy that you can’t already afford?”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;People, go for baroque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION GUIDELINES + CURATORIAL REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There are separate applications for the New York City and Los Angeles shows. Please note that curators may apply to both the New York City and Los Angeles shows and will need to submit separate applications for each show to be considered for either and/or both. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications will be accepted by independent curators, galleries and non-profit organizations during the application period between October 1 - November 22, 2019. The online application form will be available during those dates until November 22, 2019 at 11:59pm your time. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;No proposals nor applications will be accepted via email.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION FEE&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is a non-refundable application fee of $100.00 per application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our mission is to create an unique environment for showcasing independent curators by providing free exhibition space to each selected curator, and therefore, require an application fee to cover our administrative fees for processing the applications.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHO MAY APPLY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1) INDEPENDENT CURATORS: Independent Curators may submit an application for the 2020 SPRING/BREAK Art Show, including a curatorial proposal related to the theme of IN EXCESS, sample images of art work, a curatorial statement and additional information necessary to complete the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that artists may apply as an Independent Curator only if they are applying with a group show or a solo show of another artist's work. An artist may not apply with their own art work in a solo show, but must have a curator who applies on behalf of him/her/they.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is NO FEE for the exhibition space if you are selected as an independent curator.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2) GALLERIES + PROJECT SPACES + NON PROFIT ORGANIZATIONS: Applicants affiliated with a gallery or project space/non-profit organization may submit a curatorial proposal comprised of artists from the gallery's roster and this curatorial proposal will fall into our SPECIAL PROJECT section. If you have an affiliation with a gallery, project space or non-profit organization, please define your affiliation/title and include the full roster of artists in the application below for our reference.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Special Project section was initated in 2015 as a way to invite established, new and recently closed galleries to participate in the show. We encourage participants in the Special Project section to explore the theme in full and to go beyond what they typically would do in a traditional art fair environment. In 2019, there were 26 Special Projects as part of the program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each Special Project contributes a fee to participate, which helps to cover the production costs of the event.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information on applying at an Independent Curator, Gallery or a Non-Profit Organization, please visit our website for more details:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;http://www.springbreakartshow.com/2020-application/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED CURATORIAL APPLICATIONS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission of an application does not guarantee participation. We will review applications in December and notify selected curators by the beginning of January, if not before. If we have any questions about your proposal, we will contact the primary curator listed on the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each curatorial proposal will be given one (1) room/space for exhibiting artworks. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected curators will receive a consignment agreement to review and complete. All artworks included in the show must be included in and subject to the terms of the consignment agreement. Artworks that are not listed on the consignment agreement will not be permitted on the show premises. If you have any questions about the consignment terms, please contact us for details.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5e78dcea-33b9-4545-a880-a27f5b6ab434" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0409a215-163f-449b-a30c-5fe4bcabd290</id><title>12/1 - Renewal: Upstream Gallery Small Works Show 2020</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903705+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Upstream Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hastings on Hudson, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.upstreamgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call for Artists:   Renewal: Upstream Gallery Small Works Show 2020&lt;br/&gt;We invite artists to submit small works interpreting the concept of Renewal for a national juried exhibit to be held at Upstream Gallery, a well-known, beautiful venue only 20 minutes from Manhattan in Hastings on Hudson NY.  The exhibit will hang from January 2nd to January 26th, 2020. Artists’ reception will be on January 5th, 2020. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible work: Entries in all media are welcome including drawing, painting, printmaking, collage, photography, digital and sculpture. The size limit is 20" in any direction including the frame or base. Please note: this size is slightly larger than in previous years. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee: Minimum entry of 3 pieces $45.00; $5.00 for each additional entry up to a maximum of 6 pieces. The jury may select one, all, several or none of your submissions. For work selected, the gallery will retain a 30% Commission on all sales; all work must be for sale. All accepted works must be framed and ready to hang from a wire. Sculptures must include their own base. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for entries: December 1, 2019. All entries must be made via Submittable. &lt;br/&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Other Key Dates: &lt;br/&gt;Show opens January 2rd, 2020 &lt;br/&gt;Artists Reception January 5th 2020 2-5 pm &lt;br/&gt;Last day of show January 26th, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Upstream Gallery&lt;br/&gt;8 Main Street, Hastings on Hudson, NY 10706&lt;br/&gt;www.upstreamgallery.com &lt;br/&gt;914-674-8548&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit" target="_blank"&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0409a215-163f-449b-a30c-5fe4bcabd290" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1003fd76-f045-4f5c-85fe-838a7630068e</id><title>12/20 - Japan Day Art Contest 2020</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903674+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Japan Day Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.japandaynyc.org/artcontest2020"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan Day is inviting all visual artists to submit their work to Japan Day Art Contest to select our Japan Day Official Artist 2020. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are accepting submissions that incorporate all of the three themes of New York, Japan, and Central Park. The chosen artwork will become the official image of Japan Day @ Central Park 2020, and will be used for collateral materials including poster, program, flyer, and T-shirts. Several artists will receive honorable mentions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Japan Day Official Artists will receive a round trip ticket for two (2) to Japan, provided by ANA and Digital camera, provided by Nikon Inc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All winners will be announced in late March/early April 2020. The awards will be presented on the day of event in May 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RULES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Art must incorporate all of the following three themes: “New York,” ”Japan,” and “Central Park.”&lt;br/&gt;- Size must be 24" tall x 18" wide.&lt;br/&gt;- Only two-dimensional media is accepted.&lt;br/&gt;- Only one submission per artist will be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;- All entries must be the original work of the entering artist.  &lt;br/&gt;- Artwork which has been submitted to previous contests and/or previously shown or published is not eligible. &lt;br/&gt;- Artwork does not need to include the Japan Day logo or any text related to the event.&lt;br/&gt;- Artwork that violates copyrights, intellectual property rights, and/or any related rights of a third party, is not eligible. (For example, the use of existing anime characters would be a violation of copyrights.)&lt;br/&gt;- Art must not contain explicit sexuality, violence, or any discriminatory elements.&lt;br/&gt;- The final layout and design of the poster, flyer and other publicity materials will be created and approved by Japan Day Inc.  Artist’s approval is not required for publication.&lt;br/&gt;- By submitting their artwork, artists grant Japan Day Inc. the right to use their work for the purpose of marketing, exhibition and other Japan Day-related uses. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please visit the website (http://www.japandaynyc.org/artcontest2020) for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1003fd76-f045-4f5c-85fe-838a7630068e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4ff24684-9e28-429f-83de-f8f1c08e1879</id><title>1/6 - Beam Center Seeks Ambitious Project Proposals for New Hampshire and Brooklyn</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903647+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Beam Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/06/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://beamcenter.org/updates"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the last 15 years, Beam has conducted an international search for spectacular project ideas to be built at Beam Camp in New Hampshire. For the first time this year, we are putting out calls for two big ideas for two places: one for camp in New Hampshire and one to be built in Brooklyn as our 2020 NYC Beam Project.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Beam Projects are spectacular collaborations between visionary big thinkers and the Beam Community of youth and creative and technical experts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What we’re looking for in Beam Project Proposals:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Projects coming from creative individuals and teams, including but not limited to Artists, Designers, Architects, Builders, Engineers, Musicians, Fabricators &amp; Technologists.&lt;br/&gt;• Big ideas that culminate in a unique, ambitious, and spectacular artwork in a public space&lt;br/&gt;• Utilize a range of materials and a range of fabrication processes&lt;br/&gt;• Proposals that communicate a clear vision (sketches, diagrams, and other visuals are always helpful) and represent your/your team’s expertise&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For details on each call and to submit a proposal:&lt;br/&gt;New Hampshire Project Call -  &lt;a href="https://beamcamp.org/projectproposal" target="_blank"&gt;https://beamcamp.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;New York City Project Call - &lt;a href="https://beamcenter.org/nycbeamprojectproposal" target="_blank"&gt;https://beamcenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Individuals and teams can apply for one or both projects. Proposal deadline for both is Monday, January 6, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://beamcenter.org/updates" target="_blank"&gt;https://beamcenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4ff24684-9e28-429f-83de-f8f1c08e1879" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0dd25bc4-2205-4268-aeae-8961f1c8356d</id><title>11/3 - Light The Night – Pink  Fundraiser  Call For Artists</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903612+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Lighthouse Court Reporting Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 Remsenburg, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/03/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When:&lt;br/&gt;November 16, 2019 from 6:00 – 9:00 pm &lt;br/&gt;Where:&lt;br/&gt;2 Main Street, Sayville NY 11782- THORNHILLS BUILDING&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Call for artists to showcase their art for a local fundraiser. A one-night fundraiser where a portion of the art sale proceeds will go to &lt;br/&gt;           The Carol M. Baldwin Breast Care Center, Stony Brook, NY 11790.&lt;br/&gt;•	Special attention given for Long Island artists who’ve been affected by breast cancer that would like to help families and communities understand the impact of breast cancer. &lt;br/&gt;•	Additionally,  opencall extended to Long Island and NYC artists interested in this one-night exhibit in Sayville.&lt;br/&gt;•	Deadline for entries is Sunday, November 3rd, 2019. Artists must be able to transport and pick up unsold artwork to the gallery space in Sayville independently.&lt;br/&gt;•	Lighting ceremony accompanies the fundraiser, lighting the iconic neon Thornhill’s Pharmacy sign for the first time nearly 70 years. The Thornhill’s Pharmacy building has been renovated and will host the fundraiser.&lt;br/&gt;•	Call Matthew LaPiana at 716-812-7504 for details.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call Matthew LaPiana at 716-812-7504 for details.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0dd25bc4-2205-4268-aeae-8961f1c8356d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cd6d55fb-432b-41a8-94ec-14c5d2ece214</id><title>12/10 - Portrait: Identity and Expression</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903530+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $37.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Portrait: Identity and Expression&lt;br/&gt;January 31– February 29, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Portraiture hinges on the question of whom deserves to be shown. Beginning with religious and royal iconography, produced under systems of patronage, portraits were meant to immortalize the divine, powerful, and wealthy. However, what it means to make a portrait — its subject, form, method, and medium — has expanded beyond those previous confines. There has been a democratization of both subject matter, and practitioners. In reconceptualizing many of the old categories, as well as ushering in a variety of new ones, successive generations of artists have interrogated our received images of race, class, beauty, gender, sexuality. Site:Brooklyn is calling for works, across all mediums, that engage with the increasingly complex intersection between portrait and identity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Claire Voon is a freelance arts journalist and critic who lives in Chicago. Her writing has appeared in publications including the New York Times, ARTnews,The Art Newspaper, Artsy, New York magazine, and Garage. She was formerly an assistant editor at Chicago Magazine and a staff writer at Hyperallergic.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: October 26, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: December 10, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: December 19, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: January 31– February 29, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, January  31, 2020 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in drawing, painting, printmaking, sculpture, collage. photography, video. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $37.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by December 10, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2orZdhz" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 72” X 60” X 24” D&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;4. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the Ink “Portrait: Identity and Expression, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2orZdhz" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cd6d55fb-432b-41a8-94ec-14c5d2ece214" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6971b7c7-84c7-4bb7-b79f-a294aedeb532</id><title>11/25 - Summit Public Art:  Call for Artists Spring 2020</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903490+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Summit Public Art&lt;br/&gt;📍 Summit, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://summitpublicart.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call for Artists for Spring, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: November 25, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art&lt;br/&gt;Summit, New Jersey&lt;br/&gt;summitpublicarts@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art is a volunteer-based, city organization whose mission is to bring public art to public spaces in Summit. Since its inception in 2002, Summit Public Art has installed over 100 diverse temporary works of art from artists of national and international renown, as well as emerging artists. The artists’ works span across a broad range of media from metal to glass, from stone to wood to fiber. Summit Public Art has also installed four permanent public art works, including stained glass panels in the bus shelters and the gateway project, Silver Sentinel by Douwe Blumberg.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SPA’s Artwork Theme for 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The theme for artwork installations for 2020 is Light and Motion. This theme should be viewed as a general direction, and we welcome interpretation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art’s Temporary Art Program&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork for the 2020 cycle will be installed from April - early July.&lt;br/&gt;Installations typically remain in place for twelve months.&lt;br/&gt;Installation sites are typically situated in downtown Summit, in city parks, and other high visibility locations. &lt;br/&gt;SPA provides identifying signage for artwork at the site.&lt;br/&gt;SPA provides public relation opportunities.&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art provides an honorarium to support the artist’s project and related expenses, including installation and de-installation.  For this call, honorariums of up to $5000 are being offered. &lt;br/&gt;Artwork is insured by the City of Summit while on display.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Review Process&lt;br/&gt;All art installation proposals are reviewed by the Art Selection Committee with subsequent approval required by the full Summit Public Art Board. Once approved, finalists’ proposals are submitted to the City of Summit for final approval. Upon final approval by the City, the artist enters into a contractual agreement with the City of Summit. &lt;br/&gt;The deadline for submission is November 25, 2019.  All artists will be notified of SPA’s decision by the end of December, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Requirements&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art welcomes proposals for our upcoming installation cycle and asks artists to provide the following, using our Artist Proposal Form found online here.  Please submit your proposal by email to summitpublicarts@gmail.com by November 25, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s résumé or CV, including information and details about educational background, previous work, gallery showings, and past experience in public art exhibits.&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s Statement conveying your vision as an artist and your body of work in 150 words or less.&lt;br/&gt;Project Description highlighting your creative intentions, including how your artwork interprets the theme. &lt;br/&gt;Digital images of proposed artwork, as well as 3 to 5 images of past work in jpeg format.  Include an associated image list including title, date of completion, medium, dimensions, and location. Each image should be no larger than 500 MB, with the total digital presentation not to exceed 1 GB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork for consideration should avoid:&lt;br/&gt;Fragile and easily damaged or breakable materials such as paper or glass.&lt;br/&gt;Sharp edges, points, projections, or pinch-points, which may cut, puncture or cause injury by impact, catching passing pedestrian clothing or entrapment of limbs.&lt;br/&gt;Overhead parts, which present a hazard to pedestrian traffic. Artwork should follow minimum sign height requirements in areas where pedestrian traffic is likely.&lt;br/&gt;Unsafe climbing opportunities for children/adults.&lt;br/&gt;Obstruction of any traffic control device.&lt;br/&gt;Cynical, pornographic, and otherwise obscene artwork deemed inappropriate for general audiences.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All work must be suitable for outdoor display in the Northeastern United States, with its variety of climatic conditions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following non-artistic items will not be considered: &lt;br/&gt;Reproductions of original works of art&lt;br/&gt;Decorative, ornamental, or functional elements.&lt;br/&gt;“Art objects” which are mass-produced of standard design.&lt;br/&gt;Directional or other functional elements such as super-graphics, signs, color coding, or maps.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s Responsibilities&lt;br/&gt;Fabrication, transportation, installation, and deinstallation. Tools, materials and equipment are not provided by Summit Public Art.&lt;br/&gt;Timely and proper installation and removal of artwork. &lt;br/&gt;Technical reports prepared by a licensed engineer, if needed.&lt;br/&gt;Maintenance of artwork, if necessary.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the City of Summit&lt;br/&gt;Summit is home to more than 21,000 with approximately 175,000 people who live within a five mile radius.&lt;br/&gt;The city is a major transport hub visited by over 17,000 visitors daily.&lt;br/&gt;Summit is a diverse community with residents who speak more than 35 languages.&lt;br/&gt;The city is an economically and culturally diverse community -- the Visual Arts Center of NJ, Reeves-Reed Arboretum, Summit Playhouse, plus many other arts and cultural organizations call Summit home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Requirements&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art welcomes proposals for our upcoming installation cycle and asks artists to provide the following, using our Artist Proposal Form (found on Summit Public Art website:  summitpublicart.com).  Please submit your proposal by email to summitpublicarts@gmail.com by November 25, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s résumé or CV, including information and details about educational background, previous work, gallery showings, and past experience in public art exhibits.&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s Statement conveying your vision as an artist and your body of work in 150 words or less.&lt;br/&gt;Project Description highlighting your creative intentions, including how your artwork interprets the theme. &lt;br/&gt;Digital images of proposed artwork, as well as 3 to 5 images of past work in jpeg format.  Include an associated image list including title, date of completion, medium, dimensions, and location. Each image should be no larger than 500 MB, with the total digital presentation not to exceed 1 GB.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6971b7c7-84c7-4bb7-b79f-a294aedeb532" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>670f34d1-7077-4d0a-88f2-512f9236c352</id><title>11/17 - CALL FOR ART  THE BIG SHOW: ALL ANIMALS WELCOME, Deadline for Submission: 11/17/19</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903461+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Drawing Rooms&lt;br/&gt;📍 Jersey City, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.drawingrooms.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All professional artists, anywhere, are invited to submit work for consideration in Drawing Rooms 2019 year-end fundraiser exhibit, THE BIG SHOW: All Animals Welcome, 12/13/19 - 2/8/20.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THEME: The earliest art images known to man were cave paintings which depicted animals to help tell the story of their lives, giving animals a mythic and symbolic presence. Artists have continued to be interested in animals as subject matter. Peaceable Kingdom by Edward Hicks takes its theme from a passage in the bible which tells of the animals gathering together in harmony, Guernica by Picasso tells a story of war, Deborah Butterfield’s horses are a metaphorical substitute for herself, Louise Bourgeois’ spiders allude to the strength of her mother, and were used as a symbol of nurturing and protection. Animals are of great importance as companions to humans, bringing joy and comfort into our lives. We cherish animals as part of our families, and also consider them our friends and protectors. Animals, insects and even micro-organisms have important roles in the ecosystem, co-existing and balancing each other out. Some animals and insects help to reduce negative impacts on the globe, addressing issues such as global warming and pollution. Animals deserve our respect. Issues around extinction and the care and treatment of animals are of the utmost importance. How are artists incorporating animals into their artwork today? What meaning is placed upon animals and how are animals used as image, symbol and metaphor in artists works today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All media accepted, up to 30-inches, although a few larger works may be considered.&lt;br/&gt;No fee to submit. $40 hanging fee for accepted artists which includes a copy of Drawing Rooms 2019 Yearbook.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please learn more about the call here and how to submit: &lt;br/&gt;http://www.drawingrooms.org/the-big-show-2019-call.html&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/670f34d1-7077-4d0a-88f2-512f9236c352" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>37afdce1-0425-4ac4-87e8-74c9aa4ad010</id><title>12/31 - Artfare Submissions Program</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903428+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Artfare, Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artfare.com/for-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artfare is a platform that allows artists and patrons to connect through our iPhone app (artfare.com/app).  Patrons can follow artists, request studio visits, and purchase work posted by our curated group of professional artists. We started out in NYC early 2019 and have recently started accepting submissions from LA, Chicago, and Miami.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artfare allows artists to present their work to a broad audience and connect with patrons both digitally and in person through studio visits, exhibitions and events. Using our app, artists can also discover and communicate with other artists and curators, and work together to independently organize exhibitions and events.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artfare artists are based in NYC and actively make and show their work. Our group is carefully curated and  selective. In addition to quality and maturity in the work, we seek artists with professional track records and career ambition. We aim to create a well rounded program that represents all voices and mediums. Please browse the app and artfare.com to get a sense of our mission and artist list. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our tools and services allow artists to:&lt;br/&gt;1. Easily share links to your available works and facilitate sales from your studio, both on and offline&lt;br/&gt;2. Build a following of potential patrons and curators in a professional context&lt;br/&gt;3. Receive tax documents at year end and let Artfare collect, file, and pay sales tax on your behalf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you would like to submit your work for consideration please do so by September 30 via this link (please choose you city from the menu):&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://artfare.slideroom.com/&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/37afdce1-0425-4ac4-87e8-74c9aa4ad010" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6c4295ac-eb8a-4752-9610-c85536bbbcdf</id><title>Open Call All Mediums! WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!  Friday 8th 2019</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903351+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our Nov 8th Open Call Juried Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, Nov 8th , 2019 from 8pm- 12am.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, Nov. 7th, 2019 at 8pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is a Juried Salon style show. We have a panel of esteemed judges who will choose the winners! &lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We'll have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup ofMusicalGuests &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/394062041476736/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up their work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINES:&lt;br/&gt;Submissions must be received by 8pm Thurs Nov 7th &lt;br/&gt;REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF DEADLINE IS THURSDAY, Nov. 7th at 11pm. &lt;br/&gt;Works must arrive to the gallery by 11pm. We do not accept works shipped in the mail and must be dropped off in person.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces already this past year. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com  Instagram: @ Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/394062041476736/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6c4295ac-eb8a-4752-9610-c85536bbbcdf" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c5ba5985-af38-4516-a6f8-ce0f7a2e3aed</id><title>12/15 - Open Call for Papers: 2020 Nasher Prize Graduate Symposium</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903314+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Nasher Sculpture Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Dallas, TX, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.nashersculpturecenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nasher Sculpture Center Announces the 2020 Nasher Prize Graduate Symposium Open Call for Papers&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Symposium to address the work of 2020 Laureate, Michael Rakowitz; University of North Texas’s Dr. Nada Shabout to moderate&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DALLAS, Texas (October 28, 2019)—Nasher Sculpture Center announces an open call for participation in the 2020 Nasher Prize Graduate Symposium, which aims to expand scholarship on the field of contemporary sculpture in its many forms. Submissions should address themes related to the work of the 2020 Nasher Prize Laureate Michael Rakowitz. This year’s symposium will be moderated by Dr. Nada Shabout of University of North Texas, founding president of the Association for Modern and Contemporary Art from the Arab World, Iran and Turkey.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The Nasher Prize Graduate Symposium, addresses a broad audience of art historians and museum professionals, allowing symposium participants to receive feedback from fellow presenters, the moderator, the keynote speaker, and audience members. Students selected to present papers will also have their work published in the annual symposium compendium, together with the paper delivered by the keynote speaker, yet to be announced.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Since his career began in the late 1990s, Michael Rakowitz’s dynamic body of work has involved intensive research, resulting in an array of objects, environments, films, and publications that seek to reclaim, reposition, or refocus complicated aspects of material and cultural histories or events. He has especial interest in refugee and migrant populations, particularly from the Middle East. Often durational in nature, his projects frequently enlist the participation of collaborators or the public to create objects or events, making the work as much participatory as it is material.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Since 2003, Rakowitz’s work has considered his own heritage as an American descendent of the Iraqi Jewish diaspora with projects that include, among other efforts, research into the archeological artifacts and sites that have been destroyed or compromised due to political conflict. His ongoing project The invisible enemy should not exist, begun in 2007, seeks to recreate the thousands of artifacts that were looted or destroyed in the raiding of the National Museum of Iraq, Baghdad in 2003, as well as artifacts decimated by ISIS in 2015 during a destructive spree on cultural sites and institutions throughout Iraq. For this, Rakowitz solicits the help of communities of people to remake each of the artifacts, at their original scale, using images and information from the University of Chicago’s Oriental Institute database. Employing packaging from Middle Eastern food products and Arabic newspapers in combination with simple sculptural means, such as papier-mâché, the ancient objects are recreated as colorful, text- and image-laden sculptures that the artist has described as “ghosts”.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Suggested Topics for the 2020 Nasher Prize Graduate Symposium:&lt;br/&gt;–Provisional architecture within sculpture&lt;br/&gt;–Archaeology and the politics of cultural heritage&lt;br/&gt;–Food in social practice and community-healing&lt;br/&gt;–Traditional sculptural methods in contemporary sculptural practice&lt;br/&gt;–Transmissions of skill or expertise as forms of resistance to cultural erasure&lt;br/&gt;- Social media and e-commerce sites as paths of research&lt;br/&gt;- Artistic responses to the destruction of cultural patrimony&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Complete proposals must include the following:&lt;br/&gt;–Contact information, participant’s field and university affiliation, and CV&lt;br/&gt;–Paper title and abstract of no more than 200 words, and 3 to 5 keywords&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposals are due by Sunday, December 15, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;Send submissions and questions to symposium@nashersculpturecenter.org&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;We hope to notify successful applicants by January 13, 2020. Registration information will follow.&lt;br/&gt;With proof of need, eligible candidates may be considered for scholarship funding to offset travel costs.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;About Michael Rakowitz, 2020 Nasher Prize Laureate&lt;br/&gt;Michael Rakowitz was born in 1973 in Great Neck, New York; he lives and works in Chicago, Illinois and is professor of art theory and practice at Northwestern University. He studied at Purchase College, State University of New York, where he received a BFA in 1995 and at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, graduating with a Master of Science in Visual Studies in 1998. His recent retrospective opened at the Whitechapel Gallery, London, in 2019, traveling to Castello di Rivoli Museo d’Arte Contemporanea, Rivoli-Torino and, in 2020 is scheduled to open at the Jameel Art Centre, Dubai. It was preceded by Backstroke of the West, a survey exhibition at the Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago in 2018.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;He has exhibited in venues including dOCUMENTA(13), The Museum of Modern Art, New York; MoMA/PS1, New York; Tate Modern, London; MassMOCA; Castello di Rivoli; the 10th and 14th Istanbul Biennials; the Sharjah Biennials 8 and 14 ; the Tirana Biennale; and Transmediale 05.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Rakowitz is the recipient of many awards and honors, including the 2018 Herb Alpert Award in Visual Arts, a 2012 Louis Comfort Tiffany Foundation Biennial Award, a 2008 Creative Capital Grant, the Sharjah Biennial Jury Award, a 2006 New York Foundation for the Arts Fellowship Grant in Architecture and Environmental Structures, the 2003 Dena Foundations Award, and the 2002 Design 21 Grand Prix from UNESCO.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;About Nada Shabout, moderator&lt;br/&gt;Nada Shabout is a Professor of Art History and the Coordinator of the Contemporary Arab and Muslim Cultural Studies Initiative at the University of North Texas, Denton, Texas, U.S.A. She is the founding president of the Association for Modern and Contemporary Art from the Arab World, Iran and Turkey. Shabout is the Project Advisor for the Saudi National Pavilion, Venice Biennale 2019. She is the author of Modern Arab Art: Formation of Arab Aesthetics, University of Florida Press, 2007; co-editor with Salwa Mikdadi of New Vision: Arab Art in the 21st Century, Thames &amp; Hudson, 2009; and co-editor with Anneka Lenssen and Sarah Rogers of Modern Art in the Arab World: Primary Documents, Museum of Modern Art, New York, 2018.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Shabout was the curator of Sajjil: A Century of Modern Art, Interventions: A dialogue between the Modern and the Contemporary, 2010; co-curator of Modernism and Iraq, Wallach Art Gallery, Columbia University, 2009, and curator of the traveling exhibition, Dafatir: Contemporary Iraqi Book Art, 2005-2009. Her awards include: Writers Grant, Andy Warhol Foundation 2018; The Presidential Excellency Award, UNT 2018; The American Academic Research Institute in Iraq fellow 2006, 2007; MIT visiting Assistant Professor, spring 2008, and Fulbright Senior Scholar Program, 2008 Lecture/Research fellowship to Jordan.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;For images, please follow this link: &lt;a href="https://www.dropbox.com/sh/el7d53y01em6edf/AABXzijbOsied5R-hCI53MOEa?dl=0" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.dropbox.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;About the Nasher Sculpture Center&lt;br/&gt;Located in the heart of the Dallas Arts District and designed by architect Renzo Piano, the Nasher Sculpture Center is home to the Raymond and Patsy Nasher Collection, one of the finest collections of modern and contemporary sculpture in the world, featuring more than 300 masterpieces by Calder, de Kooning, di Suvero, Giacometti, Gormley, Hepworth, Kelly, Matisse, Miró, Moore, Picasso, Rodin, Serra, and Shapiro, among others. On view in the light-filled galleries and amid the garden grounds is a rotating selection of works from the Collection, as well as important exhibitions of modern and contemporary sculpture, including Sightings, a series of small-scale exhibitions and site-specific installations that explore new work by established and emerging artists. In addition to the indoor and outdoor gallery spaces, the Center contains an auditorium, education and research facilities, a cafe, and a store. For more information, visit www.NasherSculptureCenter.org.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Media Contact:&lt;br/&gt;Lucia Simek&lt;br/&gt;Manager of Communications and International Programs&lt;br/&gt;Nasher Sculpture Center&lt;br/&gt;LSimek@nashersculpturecenter.org&lt;br/&gt;+1 214 242 5177&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete proposals must include the following:&lt;br/&gt;–Contact information, participant’s field and university affiliation, and CV&lt;br/&gt;–Paper title and abstract of no more than 200 words, and 3 to 5 keywords&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposals are due by Sunday, December 15, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;Send submissions and questions to symposium@nashersculpturecenter.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c5ba5985-af38-4516-a6f8-ce0f7a2e3aed" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3ee34df3-5600-442d-8dfd-cf1834abc49f</id><title>11/10 - stARTup Art Fair Los Angeles 2020: Call for Artists</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903280+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Startup Art Fair LLC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Venice, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.startupartfair.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;stARTup Art Fair Los Angeles is a contemporary hotel art fair for independent artists.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our three-day fair is February 14-16, 2020 at the hip and stylish The Kinney in Venice, with easy access to Venice Beach, Santa Monica and Marina Del Rey. stARTup LA takes place concurrently with Frieze LA and the Art Los Angeles Contemporary gallery fairs nearby. Participating artists will have a fantastic opportunity to expose new work to a myriad of collectors, curators, gallery owners, art consultants, and writers who will be coming to the city for a weekend of contemporary art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The core mission of stARTup Art Fair is to provide a marketplace that gives artists the power to present and sell work on their own terms. All sales proceeds belong 100% to the artists.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications for stARTup Art Fair Los Angeles will be accepted through November 10, 2019. Those selected from the open application process will each take over a hotel room for the course of three days to present a solo show of their work. Through its democratic, online application, artists get the opportunity to have their work reviewed by an impressive Selection Committee of diverse art world professionals.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There are application and exhibitor fees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and to apply, visit: &lt;a href="https://www.startupartfair.com/apply-for-la-2020" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.startupartfair.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3ee34df3-5600-442d-8dfd-cf1834abc49f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3faaf5a2-6807-4290-970e-7295e56fdc4b</id><title>Open Call For Artists</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903169+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Mahlstedt Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Rochelle, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://jam415.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEN CALL FOR ARTISTS - INTERNATIONAL&lt;br/&gt;Mahlstedt Gallery is currently accepting submissions for 2019-2020 and is sending out a call to artists, at all stages in their art careers, from around the world to submit their portfolios for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;We are accepting submissions from  visual artists, digital artists, illustrators, and photographers.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Mahlstedt Gallery is proud to represent talented, international artists, helping them achieve success in one of the most exciting regions of the global art community. Representation is offered to talented artists at every stage of their career, and acceptance is granted on the basis of a portfolio review carried out by the Mahlstedt Gallery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit 6-8 jpegs of work to opencall@jam415.com Artwork should be accompanied by title, medium, and dimensions.&lt;br/&gt;First and Last Name&lt;br/&gt;Direct Phone&lt;br/&gt;Email&lt;br/&gt;Artists website&lt;br/&gt;Links to any of your social media platform&lt;br/&gt;Your biography&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3faaf5a2-6807-4290-970e-7295e56fdc4b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>485ecf1c-1834-4d96-bab5-514a271626d9</id><title>12/9 - Ink:New Prints</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903135+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Printmaking&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $37.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ink: New Prints&lt;br/&gt;January 31– February 29, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is seeking work for its upcoming printmaking exhibition. We are looking for a wide variety of work, in order to best represent that state of contemporary printmaking. We are accepting work in a number of mediums, including serigraphy, letterpress, calligraphy, etching, woodcut, lithography, linocut, drypoint, mezzotint, mono-print, solar plates and book-making. Digital and photographic elements may be used only as a supporting element.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Laura G. Einstein is currently Manager of the Mezzanine Gallery at The Metropolitan Museum of Art. She has more than thirty years’ experience in curating and museum work. Einstein has worked as Interim Head and Assistant Curator of the Asian Art Department at Yale University Art Gallery and lecturer at The Metropolitan Museum of Art and at the IBM Gallery of Science and Art, among other institutions. Einstein served as Executive Director at the Center for Contemporary Printmaking in Norwalk, Connecticut. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: October 25, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: December 9, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: December 18, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: January 31– February 29, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, January  31, 2020 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in printmaking,  This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $37.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by December 9, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:  &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2pR5bZT" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 72” X 60” X 6” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. &lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;4. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Ink:New Prints” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:  &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2pR5bZT" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/485ecf1c-1834-4d96-bab5-514a271626d9" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>59a017da-d9c5-42d0-b2dc-744b7df56c8e</id><title>11/15 - OPEN CALL - WINTER MARKET - VENDORS - ARTISTS - ARTISANS - MAKERS - CREATIVES</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903102+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Local Project&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://localproject.org/winter-market-open-call-2019/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking for artists and artisans to sell original hand-made or designed objects at our 3rd Annual Winter Market that will take place on Saturday December 7, 2019 from 12pm-7PM at THE LOCAL HOSTEL in LIC 1302 44th AVE.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no fee for application.&lt;br/&gt;Application DEADLINE: Nov 15, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Artist will be notified in a few days as they submit.&lt;br/&gt;Local Projects takes NO commission on any sales unless other wise.&lt;br/&gt;LP will:&lt;br/&gt;– Provide tables and chairs (you must bring your own tablecloth if you want one).&lt;br/&gt;– Provide promotional material, printed posters, hashtags, newsletter, FB Event.&lt;br/&gt;– Help provide an audience but vendors are encourage to help spread the word.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMIT :&lt;br/&gt;– 2-5 low res images&lt;br/&gt;– Your website or social media platforms, and explain what will you like to sell and your preference for either full or half table,&lt;br/&gt;$100 One table 2 chairs&lt;br/&gt;$50 Half table one chair&lt;br/&gt;(wall space NOT included)&lt;br/&gt;to OPENCALL@LOCALPROJECT.ORG including WINTER MARKET 2019 in the subject&lt;br/&gt;Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;– Vendor is responsible for the transportation in and out on time provided.&lt;br/&gt;– Commit to be present for the market from 11:00 till end&lt;br/&gt;– Sell original art, handmade or designed objects by you.&lt;br/&gt;– Pay Table fee as soon as accepted&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/59a017da-d9c5-42d0-b2dc-744b7df56c8e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>371a2da8-278b-433e-bcbf-d9b7f776f014</id><title>1/6 - Operator for the Harlem African Burial Ground Memorial &amp;amp; Cultural Center RFEI</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903065+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;NYCEDC&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/06/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://edc.nyc/operator-harlem-african-burial-ground-memorial-cultural-center-rfei"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York City Economic Development Corporation (NYCEDC) in collaboration with the NYC Department of Cultural Affairs (DCLA) released a Request for Expressions of Interest (RFEI) to select a non-profit arts or cultural organization to operate a memorial and cultural education center at the site of a historical African Burial Ground associated with the former Reformed Low Dutch Church of Harlem dating back to the late 17th century.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The historical burial ground was discovered in the early 2000s beneath the East 126th Street Metropolitan Transportation Authority Bus Depot. The public memorial will be located outdoors at the location of the historical burial ground and the cultural education center will be housed in an adjacent building. The cultural education center could include elements such as a visitor center, exhibitions explaining the history of the site, and community space for programming inspired by the Burial Ground. The cultural education center is intended to offer a variety of public programming and activities, which may include artist workshops, artists-in-residence, visiting scholars and thought leaders in arts and culture, advocacy, literacy and social justice.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NYCEDC plans to designate an operator for the Cultural Education Center and Outdoor Memorial to participate in the Project on the basis of factors stated in the RFEI which include, but are not limited to: the quality of the proposal, experience of key staff identified in the proposal, demonstrated successful experience in performing services similar to those encompassed in the RFEI, and the financial capacity of the respondent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;INQUIRIES&lt;br/&gt;Optional informational sessions will be held at 12pm at NYCEDC and at 6:30pm at The Silberman School of Social Work at Hunter College on Thursday, November 7, 2019. Those who wish to attend either session should RSVP by email to HABG_RFEI@edc.nyc on or before October 31, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Respondents may submit questions and/or request clarifications from NYCEDC no later than 5pm on Thursday, November 14, 2019. Questions regarding the subject matter of this RFP should be directed to HABG_RFEI@edc.nyc. For all questions that do not pertain to the subject matter of this RFEI please contact NYCEDC’s Contracts Hotline at (212) 312-3969. Answers to all questions will be posted by Friday, November 22, 2019, to edc.nyc/rfps.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;Detailed submission guidelines and requirements are outlined in the RFEI, available as of Monday, October 21, 2019. The RFEI is available for in-person pick-up between 9:30am and 4:30pm, Monday through Friday, from NYCEDC, One Liberty Plaza, 165 Broadway, 14th floor, New York, NY 10006. To download a copy of the solicitation documents please visit edc.nyc/rfps. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RESPONSES ARE DUE NO LATER THAN 4pm on Monday, January 6, 2020. Please submit five (5) sets of your expression and one (1) digital copy USB flash drive of your expression of interest to:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NYCEDC, One Liberty Plaza, 165 Broadway, New York, NY 10006&lt;br/&gt;Attention: Maryann Catalano, Chief Contracting Officer, Contracts.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/371a2da8-278b-433e-bcbf-d9b7f776f014" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f309d1dd-e853-4fc0-8423-cdf58e61c738</id><title>11/15 - Mobius Photo Winter Portfolio Competition</title><updated>2019-11-20T21:28:04.903005+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Mobius Photo LLC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.mobiusphoto.co/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;8-10 images surrounding a specific theme, vision or story&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About :: Mobius Photo is an online platform dedicated to the curation of emerging and established photographers through quarterly photography competitions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;How It Works :: Submissions are open for 6 week periods. Winners are announced 2 weeks after the closing date. Selected works live on the website for the following year.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Follow us on social at @mobiusphoto (instagram) &lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/MobiusPhotoCo/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.mobiusphoto.co/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply at &lt;a href="https://www.jotform.com/MobiusPhoto/winter-2019-portfolio-submission" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f309d1dd-e853-4fc0-8423-cdf58e61c738" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>