<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-14T03:16:38-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>d8f1a096-58d1-411c-a3e7-00e81601fa2f</id><title>6/25 - 16th Annual Betsy Meyer Memorial Exhibition and Meyer Family Award for Contemporary Art</title><updated>2019-05-14T03:16:38.864877+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Main Line Art Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Haverford, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.mainlineart.org/exhibitions/artist-opportunities/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Meyer Family Award for Contemporary Art, presented by Main Line Art Center in conjunction with the Betsy Meyer Memorial Exhibition, honors approximately three artists annually with an exhibition in the Center's gallery and an award of $1000. This award and associated exhibition program is an effort to support talented contemporary artists, to honor deserving artists in the field, and to encourage excellence and experimentation in artistic practice, presentation, and community involvement. Winners are selected by Main Line Art Center's Board of Artistic Advisors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All adult fine artists are eligible to apply. All mediums are welcome. Artists must attend the opening reception and be present for installation. The application deadline is June 25, 2019. Artists selected to receive the award will be notified in August 2019 and the exhibition will take place in November/December 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLY HERE:  mainlineart.slideroom.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Tuesday, June 25 by 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;QUESTIONS: Paige Cherrington, Exhibitions Manager, pcherrington@mainlineart.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PROSPECTUS: &lt;a href="https://www.mainlineart.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/16th-Annual-Betsy-Meyer-Memorial-Exhibition_FINAL.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.mainlineart.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d8f1a096-58d1-411c-a3e7-00e81601fa2f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0d80943d-4671-42b8-a30b-9d4d286c7927</id><title>6/11 - Field Work: Landscape and Architecture</title><updated>2019-05-14T03:16:38.864846+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on landscape and architecture in photography.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0d80943d-4671-42b8-a30b-9d4d286c7927" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>25a45b2b-8895-4066-addc-e85d752e15f7</id><title>5/24 - Upstream Gallery PaperWorks 2019-Theme &amp;amp; Variation</title><updated>2019-05-14T03:16:38.864800+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Upstream Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hastings on Hudson, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/24/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.upstreamgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL FOR ARTISTS&lt;br/&gt;Upstream Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Hastings on Hudson, NY&lt;br/&gt;PaperWorks 2019- Theme &amp; Variation&lt;br/&gt;Deadline May 24, 2019. Multiple price options&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As artists, most of us find our voices through examining similar ideas over time.  Ultimately, these become our “thematic materials”.  Upstream Gallery invites artists working on paper or making paper based constructions to submit work from their own practice that speak to the idea of theme and variation for our 7th Annual Juried PaperWorks exhibition.  The exhibition will be at Upstream Gallery, Hastings on Hudson, NY from June 27th to July 28th, 2019. Reception: Sunday, June 30th 2-5 pm. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Work: Artists are invited to submit 2-D or 3-D work that is primarily paper based.  Successful entries will demonstrate thematic relationships among two or more pieces.  Photography is not eligible for this exhibition; we hold a separate show for photographic work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Specifications: Maximum framed size may not exceed 20 x 24 inches. Accepted pieces must be able to be hung and properly wired or mounted for hanging. The gallery reserves the right to reject poorly presented pieces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jurors: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Antonio Alvarez:  Cuban born Alvarez is a both a remarkable abstract painter and a world-renowned art conservator specializing in the restoration of works on paper. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Nancy Egol Nikkal:  Nikkal is a graduate of Hunter College in Art with postgraduate work in printmaking.  She is a painter who works on canvas and in collage, where she uses papers she paints herself as the foundation for her elegant and witty work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Rachel Weatherford Whitlow:  Whitlow is a graduate of Cooper Union in fine art who also studied painting, lithography and print making at Academie Minerva in Groningen, Netherlands.  She is a master printer of both Tamarind and Paris methods of lithography.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee: Minimum entry of 3 pieces $45; each additional entry $5 up to a maximum of 6 pieces ($60) The jurors may select two, several, all, or none of your submissions.  All pieces must be for sale. The gallery will retain a 30% commission on all sales. To enter please go to:&lt;br/&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT DATES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Entries, Friday, May 24th 2019.  All entries must be made via Submittable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, June 21st by 5 pm deadline for delivered work if shipping&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Monday, June 24th 10 a.m. to 2 pm: Delivery of artwork to gallery if local;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thursday, June 27th: Opening of exhibition &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sunday, June 30th, Opening reception – 2 to 5 pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sunday, July 28th, Last day of exhibition&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Monday, July 29th, Local Artists pick up work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please go to upstreamgallery.com &amp; click on juried shows, or go to&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href="https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit" target="_blank"&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/25a45b2b-8895-4066-addc-e85d752e15f7" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>fdbc1078-e761-49f3-bae8-6d0e4530b68c</id><title>5/16 - May 17th People&amp;#39;s Choice Open Call Salon Show- WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!</title><updated>2019-05-14T03:16:38.864767+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/16/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our May 17th People's Choice Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, May 17th, 2019 from 8pm- 12am.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, May 16th, 2019 at 11pm  &lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/2509536149091781/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For this show, we let the people decide, which means everyone who attends votes for the winners! We pass out ballots at the door and guests who attends choose the winners! It is always one of our most well attended nights, boasting record art sales and a large community of fellow artists and art lovers!&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of local bands!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, May 16th  at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces in the $150-$500 range. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2509536149091781/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fdbc1078-e761-49f3-bae8-6d0e4530b68c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>34d555bb-a76d-46d6-9202-d829a510e91c</id><title>5/17 - Call for Artists! Juried Exhibition on the theme of &amp;quot;Light&amp;quot;</title><updated>2019-05-14T03:16:38.864728+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;440 Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://gallery440.squarespace.com/call-for-artists"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Light&lt;br/&gt;Juried Exhibition, Brooklyn, NY&lt;br/&gt;June 26 - July 26, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Whether we seek light as a physical object or observe it as a metaphysical presence, it is the play of light and shadow that uniquely informs our human vision. In simpler terms, light gives life; under certain circumstances light also facilitates destruction. Capturing light in visual terms has always been a crucial element in traditional painting. With multi-media, installation, and conceptual-based artwork, light takes on an equally important role for the artist.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jurors for the “Light” show are Lauren Hirshfield and Kat Ryals, &lt;br/&gt;Co-Directors of Paradice Palase in Bushwick, Brooklyn, NY.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JURORS:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lauren Hirshfield is an independent curator and artist living and working in NYC. She received a BFA in painting, arts management and art history from SUNY Purchase. Over the past five years she has freelanced as an arts administrator, assistant, and curator for organizations such as Superchief Gallery, 4Heads/Portal, POWRPLNT and ArtMoney. Her curatorial practice is fueled by the ephemeral, the ethereal and the tactile. She is interested in further democratizing the art world and strives to consider accessible ways the public can engage with art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Kat Ryals is an artist, curator and photographer based in Brooklyn, NY. She received a BFA in photography in 2010 from Savannah College of Art and Design, and an MFA in Visual Art and Museum Education from Brooklyn College. She has worked in the education department of several NYC museums and non-profits, including the Rubin Museum, the Museum of Arts and Design, and ArtsConnection. Ryals has shown her work nationally, and was included in recent group exhibitions with the Holocenter on Governor’s Island, Temporary Storage Gallery at Brooklyn Fireproof, and the Wassaic Project. She was a Fellow at Vermont Studio Center in January 2018, and a resident at the Wassaic Project in January 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;440 Gallery is an artist-run space in Park Slope, Brooklyn, dedicated to the creation, exhibition and sale of a wide range of work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Open to U.S. resident artists at least 18 yrs. old. All 2-D work must be suitably framed, wired and ready for hanging. Works on paper must be framed under plexiglass or glass. Canvases must be wired for hanging. All 3-D work must be able to hang securely on the wall, sit on a shelf, pedestal or the floor. Size limit for this exhibition is 40 x 40 inches.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ACCEPTANCE:&lt;br/&gt;Accepted work may be refused if it does not conform to the entered image. Absolutely NO SUBSTITUTIONS of accepted works will be allowed. All accepted work must remain in the gallery for the duration of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SALES:&lt;br/&gt;The gallery will take 40% commission on any work sold. Work not for sale must be marked “NFS"; no Price on request, ”POR" sales.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEE:&lt;br/&gt;The fee is $40 for 1 - 3 works, $5 for each additional work up to 6 works total. Entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY REQUIREMENTS: All entries must be submitted electronically. Judging will be done entirely from JPEGs. No other formats will be accepted. JPEGs should be at least 600 pixels but not greater than 1200 pixels in either direction. Maximum file size for any individual image is 2 MB. The size given for works should be the framed size. *Height must be given before width regardless of whether the work is a vertical or a horizontal. Entry form must be filled out completely. Your payment will serve as your acceptance of the terms and conditions stated in this prospectus. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMAGE LABELING: JPEG images MUST BE labeled as follows:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LAST Name_FIRST Name_The number that corresponds with that work's placement on the Entry Form (1st, 2nd, 3rd, etc.) smith_joe_1.jpg&lt;br/&gt;smith_joe_2.jpg&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Files mislabeled or lacking the artist's name will not be viewed by the juror.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DELIVERY OF WORK: Hand-delivered work will be accepted at the gallery ONLY on Saturday June 22, 12-6 and Sunday, June 23, 12 - 6 PM. Packaging must be removed from the gallery at the time of delivery. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shipped work must arrive at the gallery between Wednesday June 12 - Saturday, June 22, in a reusable container. A computer-generated return label for return of work MUST be enclosed. NO EXCEPTIONS. Pre-paid shipping arrangements must be made through UPS or FedEx websites. NO U.S. POSTAL SERVICE OR COD RETURNS. DO NOT SEND CASH, CHECK, STAMPS, OR CREDIT CARD INFORMATION FOR RETURN OF WORK. Keep in mind the gallery is closed on Monday and Tuesday and will not be able to accept deliveries on those days.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artworks that do not arrive by June 23 will not be hung.  No exceptions will be made.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RETURN: Hand-delivered work must be picked up on July 27-28, 12-6 PM. Shipped works will be returned the week of July 29th. The gallery accepts no responsibility for work not retrieved on pick-up date, after 30 days the gallery may dispose of the work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY: Great care will be taken with all work, but artists are responsible for insuring their own pieces if they wish.  440 Gallery will not be responsible for any loss or damage to work while on the premises or in transit to or from the gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The submission of a work of art to this exhibition shall be understood to constitute an agreement on the part of the artist to the conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EVENT SCHEDULE:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;May 17                          Entry deadline at midnight&lt;br/&gt;June 9                            Notifications sent out by this date&lt;br/&gt;June 12-22                    Receipt of shipped work via UPS or FedEx&lt;br/&gt;June 22-23                   Hand delivery of work:  11-4 PM&lt;br/&gt;June 24                         Installation&lt;br/&gt;June 26                         Exhibition opens&lt;br/&gt;June 29                         Opening reception 5-8 PM&lt;br/&gt;July 26                           Exhibition closes &lt;br/&gt;July 27                           Pickup of hand-delivered work: 12-6 PM&lt;br/&gt;July 28                           Pickup of hand-delivered work: 12-6 PM&lt;br/&gt;Week of July 29            Return of shipped work via UPS or FedEx&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/34d555bb-a76d-46d6-9202-d829a510e91c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>667bb88a-3f18-4c01-b732-a0b5c3dcaeb1</id><title>9/9 - Nocturne National Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-05-14T03:16:38.864672+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arc Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 San Francisco, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.arc-sf.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The word “Nocturne” conveys a dreamy, pensive composition or works of art dealing with the coming of darkness. We are seeking works that are evocative of the night, subjects as they appear in a veil of light, twilight or the absence of direct light. This theme lends itself to works that are tonal in nature, so works using soft, diffused light, muted tones and hazy outlined objects are welcome. We also invite artists to explore subjects associated with the night such as nocturnal animals and birds, people working the night shift, landscapes and cityscapes at night, and nocturnal fantasy creatures such witches, vampires and ghosts. And finally, artists whose favorite color is black are invited to submit works in that tone. Juror: Jennifer Perlmutter, Jennifer Perlmutter Gallery, LaFayette, CA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online submission only. Read prospectus and apply here: &lt;a href="https://www.arc-sf.com/nocturne.html#dashboard" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.arc-sf.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email questions to arcgallerysf@gmail.com.  If you would like to talk to us by phone, please include your phone number in your email.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/667bb88a-3f18-4c01-b732-a0b5c3dcaeb1" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>