<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-02T13:17:46-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>0beb4eee-54ea-40dc-a150-665b917499e9</id><title>10/1 - Open Call for Proposals: Syracuse Area</title><updated>2019-07-02T13:17:46.348564+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Darling Green&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://darlinggreen.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An international and well recognized corporate art collection is seeking proposals for site- specific works for its Syracuse, NY campus. The works will be displayed in and throughout the office space and will expand upon this multi-national corporation’s tradition of collecting and displaying art as a benefit to both its employees and the community.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This project is limited to New York-based artists living and working within 150 miles of Syracuse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This call is an exploratory search to assess the interest of New York artists in working within an office environment, as well as their interest in engaging with both employees and the surrounding communities through site- specific works of art. We hope this will create a specific sense of place and identity within and around the office space and encourage dialogue between the artist, employees and the community.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please send us an email for more information. &lt;br/&gt;info@darlinggreen.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0beb4eee-54ea-40dc-a150-665b917499e9" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6e6055c3-8ef1-42c2-a815-c29b305a6a56</id><title>7/15 - 1708&amp;#39;s InLight 2019 Call for Entries</title><updated>2019-07-02T13:17:46.348532+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;1708 Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Richmond, VA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.1708gallery.org/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1708 Gallery invites national and international artists working in all media and disciplines to submit entries for the 12th annual InLight Richmond. InLight is a public exhibition of contemporary light-based artworks— multimedia and interactive projects, video, projection, sculpture, installation, and performance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;InLight 2019 will take place at Chimborazo Park in the Church Hill neighborhood of Richmond on Friday and Saturday, November 15 and 16. Artists are invited to propose projects that critically engage with the social and geographic history of this site. Two key moments in the park's history include being the location of the largest Confederate military hospital during the Civil War and following Emancipation, hosting a Freedmen’s community for formerly enslaved African-Americans. 1708 seeks artists and projects that respond to, elaborate on, and propose new ways of understanding these complex histories.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE TO APPLY: Midnight (EST), Monday, July 15, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Potential sites for installations and performances include pathways, sidewalks, green spaces, trees, and more. There are no interior sites available. Artists may propose a specific site for both pre-existing and site-responsive works. Please indicate if your work is site-specific on your entry form. 1708 Gallery reserves the right to make final site assignments.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more details about InLight 2019 and to apply, visit www.1708gallery.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applications are accepted via our online form at &lt;a href="https://fs2.formsite.com/1708gallery/7vprjoxmvh/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;https://fs2.formsite.com&lt;/a&gt; or by visiting our website. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For questions, please contact Erin Willett at info@1708gallery.org or 804-643-1708&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6e6055c3-8ef1-42c2-a815-c29b305a6a56" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>574207e3-4b90-498b-87d6-f3207677a710</id><title>7/5 - Tool Book Project Volume III: Work Book Open Call</title><updated>2019-07-02T13:17:46.348492+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Tool Book Project&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/05/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.toolbookproject.org/submissions"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tool Book Project Volume III: Work Book&lt;br/&gt;Open Call, Due Friday, July 5, 2019, 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;The ways in which we work cut across intersections of all parts of identity, individual and community well-being and social and political power. We face increasingly complex local and global economies, war, environmental disasters and their resulting human migrations, alongside increasing concentrations of wealth and weakened worker protections. How, as artists and cultural producers, do we address the multiplicities of factors that impact our own survival? To what extent do contemporary technologies shape our work experiences? How are artists activating contemporary dialogues around labor history, interdependence, interconnectivity and communalism? The artworld has many historic examples of protests against unfair wages and unfair institutional representation that impact artist survival, including Art Workers Coalition, United Black Artists, Guerrilla Girls, Artists of Color Organization, the New York Artists Strike, Gran Fury and Act Up. More recent examples include W.A.G.E., Arts and Labor working group, Occupy Museums, MoMA Union Workers and protests demanding MoMA, the Whitney Museum and other large museums divest from the Prison Industry, Weapons Manufacturing and Big Pharma. What is the future of institutional critique and direct social action, and what can we glean from revisiting past Art and Labor movements?&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The Tool Book Project is seeking submissions for its third publication: Work Book. Work Book will be a risograph magazine featuring art and writing that responds to contemporary labor issues. Work Book seeks artwork and writing that address the labor of art, art production and artworld workers, as well as art and writing that broadly considers labor, leisure and its cultural intersections. Topics may include but are not limited to: prison labor, postwork imaginaries, cultural workers, invisible labor and emotional labor in light of gender, race, ethnicity, sexuality and masculine/feminine spectrums, museum labor, institutional labor practices, exchange and gift economies, manual labor, collective work and living, financial precarity, retirement and aging, ableism and mental health in art, academic and other work worlds, marxism, techno-labor, unpaid domestic labor, performing leisure, labor and land, environmental collapse and the economy, de-colonialist action, and the labor of craft and studio practice. We are especially interested in projects that examine and re-center the histories and contemporary labor/leisure from a feminist perspective that addresses the intersectional and transnational complexity of race, ethnicity, gender, class, age, body size, disability, transgender and non-binary experience and sexual orientation.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The Tool Book Project is a semi-annual publication that showcases art, writing, dialogue and critical discourse from an international group of artists and cultural producers. Tool Book is also a platform for sharing resources via curated gallery shows, readings, roundtable discussions, and other public events. Sales from each publication are donated to specific social and environmental justice organizations, providing a mode of direct action for artists and writers to exchange ideas and affect positive social change.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Deadline: July 5, 2019 by 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;Editing will begin soon and earlier submissions are encouraged&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply here: &lt;a href="https://www.toolbookproject.org/submissions" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.toolbookproject.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contact: toolbookproject@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;-CV&lt;br/&gt;-Artist Bio (150 Words)&lt;br/&gt;-Project Description or Writing Abstract (350 Words)&lt;br/&gt;-5 Images and/or 3 time-based media clips (see details below)&lt;br/&gt;-OR-&lt;br/&gt;-Essay, Fiction, or Poetry up to 2,500 words (see details below&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;Project Description: This can be a project statement for the artwork you are submitting or an abstract for written submissions. Your statement should address how your submission reflects the themes of Work Book and may also discuss how your submission relates to your larger practice.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Artwork requirements: We seek works of art that can be reproduced via Risograph. If your work is chosen for publication we will work with you to prepare files. There will be a companion web page where time-based media can be viewed. If you are applying with audio, video, AR, VR we suggest including video or film stills, screenshots, audio transcripts or scores and/or text about the project.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Each applicant may submit up to five images and/or up to three video or audio clips, 5 minutes max each.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Image requirements:&lt;br/&gt;-Up to 5 images&lt;br/&gt;-Files should be labeled Lastname-firstname-number.jpeg (i.e. Ono-Yoko-1.jpeg)&lt;br/&gt;-No larger than 1MB (HIgher res images may be required for publication.)&lt;br/&gt;-Files should be .jpegs, .png or pdf&lt;br/&gt;-Descriptions should include Title, Year, Dimensions, Medium&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Video/Audio requirements:&lt;br/&gt;-Up to three clips.&lt;br/&gt;-No more than 5 minutes in length.&lt;br/&gt;-Must be shared via weblink (SoundCloud, Vimeo, YouTube, etc.)&lt;br/&gt;-Descriptions should include: Title, Year, Media, Length&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;Writing requirements:&lt;br/&gt;Work Book is interested in publishing long form critical and analytical essays, fiction and poetry up to 2,500 words. Materials should be submitted as MS-Word (.doc, .docx) or PDF.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Formatting requirements:&lt;br/&gt;-Use single line spacing, 12-point Times font, headings and subheadings should be boldfaced.&lt;br/&gt;-Please use guidelines published by the Modern Language Association (MLA).&lt;br/&gt;-Images (72 dpi, minimum, 1000 px wide) should be placed within the text at the appropriate points not at the end of the article. Credit images with author, copyright, title, and caption information when necessary. Please do not include more than a total of 6 images with your submission. If your text uses images not created by the author, include publication permissions from the original creator with your submission. Where available, include URLs for the references.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/574207e3-4b90-498b-87d6-f3207677a710" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1f1bb230-f672-4d38-a7db-64c9d0d3a050</id><title>7/13 - Chelsea Gallery OPEN CALL</title><updated>2019-07-02T13:17:46.348411+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Field Projects&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/13/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com/open-call/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Field Projects is pleased to announce our Summer 2019 Open Call! Emerging and mid-career artists are invited to submit their work for consideration.. All submissions will be considered by our Guest Curators: Tess Schwab, Diretor Jenkins Johnson Projects. Simultaneously, Field Projects Panel (4-5 curators) will be considering the submissions for future solo exhibitions, group exhibitions, 2 person exhibitions, art fairs, pop-up shows, off-site exhibitions and our studio visit program, where we invite outside curators to accompany us to your studio. (85% of the artists we have shown in the last 8 years have been discovered through the Open Call.) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With your submission you will get several opportunities:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. Summer Exhibition by our Guest Curator: Tess Schwab, Director Jenkins Johnson Projects&lt;br/&gt;2. Online Exhibition &lt;br/&gt;3. Future Solo and Group Exhibitions at Field Projects.&lt;br/&gt;4. Future Art Fairs with Field Projects.&lt;br/&gt;5. Outside Exhibitions by our FP panel members.&lt;br/&gt;6. Studio Visit pool for NYC Artists.&lt;br/&gt;7. Field Magazine&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Field Projects is an NYC-based project space located in the heart of Chelsea's gallery district. As an artist run space, we are committed to opening the field of exhibition opportunities to other working artists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow our website link above or cut and paste : &lt;a href="http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com/open-call/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit :&lt;br/&gt;up to 5 images of your work&lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement&lt;br/&gt;CV&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline : July 13th, 11:59 PM !!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Summer Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;The theme of the show will come from the work submitted. &lt;br/&gt;Selected artists will be notified by July 22nd, 2019&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must arrive at Field Projects by Thursday, August 1st, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;Summer Exhibition opens August 8th, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Summer Exhibition closes August 31th, 2019&lt;br/&gt;All artwork in the exhibition will be for sale, with artists receiving 50% of final sale. &lt;br/&gt;We look forward to seeing your work!!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Field Projects&lt;br/&gt;526 W 26th Street, &lt;br/&gt;#807&lt;br/&gt;New York, NY 10001&lt;br/&gt;info@fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;www.fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1f1bb230-f672-4d38-a7db-64c9d0d3a050" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>