<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-21T11:16:48-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>4484575b-509c-44e2-bad6-a6c30811641f</id><title>8/9 - Open Call for Artist Submissions: Group Exhibition in New York City</title><updated>2019-05-21T11:16:48.987838+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;MW Projects&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.MWprojects.art"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEN CALL FOR ARTIST SUBMISSIONS&lt;br/&gt;Inversions: Contemporary Art Inspired by the Architecture of Louis Kahn&lt;br/&gt;October 19 – November 10, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Organized by MW Projects&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: Friday, August 9, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Please submit online at &lt;a href="https://mwprojects.typeform.com/to/DMmZdo" target="_blank"&gt;https://mwprojects.typeform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Kahn’s architecture is full of inversions: masses which suddenly seem weightless, materials which dissolve into immateriality; structures which reverse load and support; rays of light which reveal the realm of shadows; solids which turn out to be voids.”&lt;br/&gt;-- William J.R. Curtis&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists are invited to submit works for a group exhibition of contemporary art inspired by the architecture of Louis Kahn and the idea of inversions.  The exhibition is organized by MW Projects, with support from the Consulate General of Estonia in New York, and will be held in New York City in Fall 2019.  The main exhibition will be presented at Gallery RIVAA on Roosevelt Island and will be complemented by an outdoor exhibition of Arne Maasik’s Kahn-related photographs in partnership with Four Freedoms Park and a weekend pop-up exhibition focused on performance in downtown Manhattan.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Born in Estonia in 1901, Louis Kahn was one of the most important architects of the second half of the 20th century.  His work includes the Salk Institute (La Jolla, CA), National Assembly Building (Dhaka, Bangladesh), Phillips Exeter Academy Library (Exeter, NH) and Four Freedoms Park (New York, NY).   Known for combining Modernism with the weight and dignity of ancient monuments, Kahn used simple shapes and simple materials to build preternaturally beautiful structures that sought to create transcendent experience.  He believed that structure, space and light must always be in harmony, and that it is through the material that we can understand the immaterial and universal.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All art forms will be considered for the exhibition, including painting, drawing, photography, sculpture, music, performance art, dance and media art.  There are also opportunities for live performances during the run of the main exhibition and the pop-up exhibition.  Artists are encouraged to investigate the conceptual underpinnings of Kahn’s works and words, rather than using images of Kahn’s designs and buildings.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All entries will be reviewed, selected and notified by Monday, September 9, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;Please see website for details.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Details: www.MWprojects.art&lt;br/&gt;Application instructions: &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/inversionskahn" target="_blank"&gt;http://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application: &lt;a href="https://mwprojects.typeform.com/to/DMmZdo" target="_blank"&gt;https://mwprojects.typeform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email: info@mwprojects.art&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4484575b-509c-44e2-bad6-a6c30811641f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b7998912-306a-49e2-b5b4-ec15c4ff4083</id><title>6/7 - GET FEATURED in the next issue of Artqol Magazine 6th edition</title><updated>2019-05-21T11:16:48.987804+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Artqol&lt;br/&gt;📍  , Netherlands&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/07/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artqol.com/magazine-call"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your art doesn't speak for itself, we help you to tell its story by writing about you and your artistic practice.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artqol magazine is a curated collection of stories behind artists and their works, promoting Artqol's contemporary artists and curator members, with focuses on conceptual, expressive, social, political and environmental art practices. The magazine is digitally distributed directly to international art professionals, including curators, artists, galleries and art institutions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application deadline for the next issue:&lt;br/&gt;June 7th 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The magazine is exclusive for Artqol members.&lt;br/&gt;There is a $55.00 yearly membership fee.&lt;br/&gt;To Join: artqol.com/magazine-call&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists receive:&lt;br/&gt;Artist Profile Page&lt;br/&gt;2-4 page spread including introduction, images and Q&amp;A&lt;br/&gt;Regular coverage through out the year&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The magazine is exclusive for Artqol members.&lt;br/&gt;You can join here artqol.com/magazine-call&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b7998912-306a-49e2-b5b4-ec15c4ff4083" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b5d31968-3cb7-4206-9431-8cb3c63ada61</id><title>6/18 - Transformations: Figures of our Other Selves</title><updated>2019-05-21T11:16:48.987769+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Smithtown Township Arts Council-Mills Pond Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 St. James, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Painting&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/18/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.millspondgallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mills Pond Gallery invites artists to submit works for a juried exhibition August 17 - September 14, 2019. Juried by Carol Fabricatore, Transformations seeks visual works that explore the artist’s take on what persona or alter ego is present in their artwork. Transform into something you would like to present as a public image of yourself.  It could be a self-portrait that transforms you into who, what, or how you would like the public to see you, or whatever your alter ego may be., The exhibition will accept drawing and/or painting in any 2D mediums traditional or digital. No Photography Entry Fee $45/3 images. Awards: $700 Best in Show, $500 Second Place, $300 Third Place. Entry Deadline June 18&lt;br/&gt;https://www.millspondgallery.org/calls-for-entry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;gallery@stacarts.org&lt;br/&gt;Entry form, entry images, entry payment required.&lt;br/&gt;https://www.millspondgallery.org/calls-for-entry#/transformationsfigures-of-our-other-selves&lt;br/&gt;631-862-6575&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b5d31968-3cb7-4206-9431-8cb3c63ada61" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c4ed1c55-a90a-4076-b5aa-397d89a0f42a</id><title>6/10 - Summer Exhibition - Open Call for Submissions</title><updated>2019-05-21T11:16:48.987713+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open is seeking work that is reflective of the moods and feelings engendered by Summer. The Ancients described the season as one of growth, it is also frequently associated with fertility and abundance.  We have 2 large spacious galleries offering around 10,000 square foot of space.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Work can be in any medium from Painting to Sculpture to Ceramics to Installations and more.   The exhibition will open on June 20th and close on July 19th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply using this form:  &lt;a href="https://form.jotform.com/91385192077968" target="_blank"&gt;https://form.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you are a previous participant in LIC Arts Open you pay a reduced application fee of $15.  Work must be ready to hang with fixings, wire and hanging systems installed. Also, all work must have the artists name on the back of the piece.  Please note also that when you apply please make a note of the pieces you have submitted.  Work must be dropped off and picked up at the appropriate listed times. Work must be as submitted we cannot accept substitutions.   Deadline is June 10th and if successful the drop off is June 15 &amp; 16 between 3 - 6 pm.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c4ed1c55-a90a-4076-b5aa-397d89a0f42a" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>