<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-16T16:16:42-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>91fafc5b-e3da-4962-ab3c-c9c6cb24a215</id><title>6/15 - Open Call for a juried exhibition open to all artists working in Queens NY!</title><updated>2019-05-16T16:16:42.526939+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LiC-A @ THe Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 LIC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_creative_mosaic"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creative Mosaic curated by NYC based curator Osman Can Yerebakan&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Description of Exhibition: &lt;br/&gt;LIC-A’s  aim is to increase awareness and appreciation of the richly diverse art produced throughout Queens. Included will be a continuous  digital presentation with images of participating artists in their studios and workshops, describing  how the growth of art studios and the presence of artists in every area of Queens has enriched all aspects of community life wherever they occur.  Meet-the-Artists event will be scheduled to enable conversation and connection between  the artists and  community residents  and businesses.    We also plan to create a video documentary on the various arts groups we connect with in the Borough.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, go to LIC-A’s website, www.licartists.org.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Osman Can Yerebakan is a curator and art writer based in New York. His writing has appeared on T: The New York Times Style Magazine, The Paris Review, Vulture and The Cut (both New York Magazine), The Brooklyn Rail, BOMB, Village Voice, Harper’s Bazaar Arabia, Wallpaper*, L’Officiel, Flaunt, Galerie Magazine, Cultured, and elsewhere.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Osman previously organized exhibitions at The Clemente Center (Residual Impression; A Room of One's Own), La MaMa Galleria (Party Out Of Bounds: Nightlife As Activism Since 1980), Radiator Gallery (Works: Reflections on Failure), Equity Gallery (Like Smoke), AC Institute (My Nights Are More Beautiful Than Your Days), Center for Book Arts (En Masse: Books Orchestrated), Local Project (Hopscotch), UrbanGlass (Glass Ceiling: Art of Resilience and Fragility), Leslie Lohman Museum Project Space (Alternate Routes), the Queens Museum (Executive (Dis)Order: Art, Displacement &amp; the Ban), and Residency Unlimited (Contingencies).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit through the link below:&lt;br/&gt;http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_creative_mosaic&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/91fafc5b-e3da-4962-ab3c-c9c6cb24a215" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>