<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-01T06:17:03-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>72596ad4-caa1-4aa0-ba86-6f93535f0b00</id><title>7/12 - Call for Artists- 2019 Creative Climate Awards</title><updated>2019-06-01T06:17:03.613512+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Human Impacts Institute&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/12/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.humanimpactsinstitute.org/creative-climate-awards"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Human Impacts Institute’s Creative Climate Awards are an annual&lt;br/&gt;series of events that showcase artists creating climate-inspired, public&lt;br/&gt;works. In an effort to inspire us to think more critically about our actions&lt;br/&gt;and their impacts, the Creative Climate Awards program uses the arts&lt;br/&gt;and creativity to share knowledge, broaden the climate conversation,&lt;br/&gt;educate, and incite action.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What We Accept:&lt;br/&gt;All 2D works, including graphic design, drawings, painting, photographs,&lt;br/&gt;collage, and mixed media&lt;br/&gt;Films (both shorts and feature length)&lt;br/&gt;Performative works , including dance, theatre, music, and other works&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What You Get:&lt;br/&gt;Cash prizes of $1,100, $600, and $360&lt;br/&gt;Month long exhibit at 42nd St. gallery in Manhattan, NYC&lt;br/&gt;Work viewed by our judges&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*NOTE: Artists are responsible for costs of shipping works to and from NYC. All&lt;br/&gt;performers must be able to perform in NYC November 6th - December 4th 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Timeline:&lt;br/&gt;Submissions Due: 11:30 pm EST, July 12th&lt;br/&gt;Selections Announced: August 16th&lt;br/&gt;Exhibit Dates: November 6th - December 4th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSIONS DUE 11:30PM EST JULY 12TH, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply for FREE online at:&lt;br/&gt;www.humanimpactsinstitute.org/creative-climate-awards&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/72596ad4-caa1-4aa0-ba86-6f93535f0b00" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3c436ab4-aa25-41f6-9f08-e4f290fd86d1</id><title>7/7 - OPEN CALL: Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists</title><updated>2019-06-01T06:17:03.613473+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Friend of The Artist&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/07/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.friendoftheartist.com/apply/vol10"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FOA is a quarterly book dedicated to elevating the work of emerging artists around the world. Our publication releases in a hardcover art book every quarter and includes the work of artists who work in a variety of mediums, informative articles, and interviews. Accepted artists will have a four-page spread of their work, information, and artist statement. Volume 10 will be juried by Diana Cerezino, Michael Dewberry, and Tim Ralston and will be available in our store and online retailers including Amazon and Barnes and Noble.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted Artists Receive&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3 works published in Volume 10, complimentary digital copy of the publication, social media post of work, discounts on books for family and friends, and free digital access to future publications&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$30 for 5 Images&lt;br/&gt;or&lt;br/&gt;$50 for 5 Images + Book&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;July 7, 2019 (midnight, CST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists of all academic disciples are welcome to apply. This includes painting, sculpture, photography, installation, and performance art. Works must be submitted in a printable format.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guest Jurors&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Diana Cerezino&lt;br/&gt;Michael Dewberry&lt;br/&gt;Tim Ralston&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Diana Cerezino &amp; Tim Ralston&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Diana Cerezino and Tim Ralston are founding directors of PADA, an artist-led, non-profit arts organisation based in Barreiro on Lisbon’s South Bay. Set within a derelict industrial Park, PADA is a studio provider, international residency and gallery promoting interaction between national and international artists. Both practicing artists, Tim and Diana set up PADA with the aim of creating a unique resource for artists, to provide excellent studios and fabrication facilities alongside the opportunity to exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Having both graduated with BA Hons they have worked in the London art scene for the last 15 years and gained a wealth of experience that they bring to this new project in Lisbon. In this time they have worked for artists such as Damien Hirst, Raqib Shaw and Julian Opie, galleries Alison Jacques and Hauser and Wirth as well as institutions including The Tate, ICA and BFI. The knowledge from assisting and working with these established and well known artists, galleries and institutions informs PADA as a residency that encourages and supports artists development. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As PADA they have curated exhibitions in London and Lisbon, the latest exhibition at AMAC in Lisbon, included 40 artists over 4 galleries. 'Out of Office' curated by Alice Bonnot opens on the 11th May at PADA gallery and Recreational Grounds V opens on 17th May in the project space Tim still co curates in London.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Michael H. Dewberry&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A native of Dallas, TX, Michael H. Dewberry is an emerging curator who has coordinated and collaborated on international traveling exhibitions in Mexico, Dallas, and New York City. He has held positions at the Crow Museum of Asian Art, Brooklyn Museum, Wadsworth Atheneum, Academia Nazionale di San Luca, Museo Internacional del Barroco, and the Bard Graduate Center Gallery. His mission is to curate exhibitions and programming that bridges cultures and creates communities united around art and action. Prior to attending graduate school to focus on decorative arts he studied product design at the Scuola Politecnico di Design in Milan, Italy. Michael earned his master’s degree in Decorative Arts, Design History, and Material Culture from the Bard Graduate Center in New York City and a holds a Bachelor of Arts with honors in Art History from Trinity College in Hartford, Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at friendoftheartist.com/apply/vol10&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Email contact@friendoftheartist.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3c436ab4-aa25-41f6-9f08-e4f290fd86d1" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0224217a-5558-49db-b3e2-6cfc9fc8eb45</id><title>6/30 - Open Call for Midnight Moment—chance to show moving-image art on 60+ screens in Times Square!</title><updated>2019-06-01T06:17:03.613419+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.TSq.org/Arts"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts invites you to submit original moving-image artwork to Midnight Moment, the world’s largest, longest-running digital art exhibition synchronized on electronic billboards and newspaper kiosks throughout Times Square nightly from 11:57pm to midnight. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for submissions: June 30, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;Learn more about submission guidelines here: TSq.org/MMSubmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open applications for the Midnight Moment program are accepted through the online Slideroom portal. Please review submission guidelines and access the portal here: TSq.org/MMSubmission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have any questions about your proposal, please email Public Art Manager Hillary Dvorkin at hdvorkin@tsq.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0224217a-5558-49db-b3e2-6cfc9fc8eb45" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>