<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-22T13:16:50-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>2558a228-b6db-49fe-a107-1d486efdb1d7</id><title>7/15 - Animals</title><updated>2019-05-22T13:16:50.421982+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Animals&lt;br/&gt;September 20– October 20, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The varied aesthetic uses of animals has often been captured through visual art, both subjects of study themselves and as reflections of humanity. Site:Brooklyn wants to give artists an opportunity to show works, across subject matter, medium, form, that focus on the interplay between animals and art. You might focus on, but are by no means limited to, personal connections with animals, the use of animal materials in art, how animals represent social, political, and aesthetic ideas, and how artists use animals in imaginative or formally innovative ways.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Alina Cohen is a staff writer at Artsy. She has written on a freelance basis for The&lt;br/&gt;New York Times, Vanity Fair, Art in America, New York Magazine, Hyperallergic,&lt;br/&gt;and a number of other publications. She previously worked at Nadine Johnson,&lt;br/&gt;The Pulitzer Arts Foundation, and the Contemporary Art Museum St.&lt;br/&gt;Louis.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: May 20, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: July 15, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: July 23, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: September 20– October 20, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, September 20, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in drawing, painting, printmaking, sculpture, collage.&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $35.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by July 15, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:  &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2HIodqB" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 60” X 60” X 24” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;4. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Animals” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2HIodqB" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2558a228-b6db-49fe-a107-1d486efdb1d7" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e26d0cc7-f1ba-4ff7-8a1a-1dffcc358da5</id><title>6/15 - CAUSE FOR PAWS T-SHIRT DESIGN OPEN CALL</title><updated>2019-05-22T13:16:50.421953+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Artrepreneur&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://opencall.artrepreneur.com/tiny-tim-rescue/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALLING ALL GRAPHIC ARTISTS&lt;br/&gt;THE TINY TIM RESCUE FUND WANTS YOU TO DESIGN A NEW OFFICIAL T-SHIRT!&lt;br/&gt;The new t-shirt and other accessories will be sold to raise funds in support of Tiny Tim’s mission to remove innocent animals from high-kill shelters, provide for their proper medical care and to find them a loving, forever home. 100% of all proceeds will be used for this important cause. &lt;br/&gt;YOU CAN BE A PART OF THIS IMPORTANT MISSION. One Grand Prize winner will receive a $500 cash prize and have the opportunity to work with famed fashion designer and animal rights champion, John Bartlett. You’ll work with Bartlett to design a beautiful and compelling t-shirt graphic that will be used to help these animals in need. Your contribution will save the lives of hundreds of cats and dogs through t-shirt sales. Five Runners up will receive additional prizes along with promotion of their entries to animal lovers across the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALLING ALL GRAPHIC ARTISTS&lt;br/&gt;THE TINY TIM RESCUE FUND WANTS YOU TO DESIGN A NEW OFFICIAL T-SHIRT!&lt;br/&gt;The new t-shirt and other accessories will be sold to raise funds in support of Tiny Tim’s mission to remove innocent animals from high-kill shelters, provide for their proper medical care and to find them a loving, forever home. 100% of all proceeds will be used for this important cause. &lt;br/&gt;YOU CAN BE A PART OF THIS IMPORTANT MISSION. One Grand Prize winner will receive a $500 cash prize and have the opportunity to work with famed fashion designer and animal rights champion, John Bartlett. You’ll work with Bartlett to design a beautiful and compelling t-shirt graphic that will be used to help these animals in need. Your contribution will save the lives of hundreds of cats and dogs through t-shirt sales. Five Runners up will receive additional prizes along with promotion of their entries to animal lovers across the globe.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applicants must be 18 years or older.&lt;br/&gt;Submission must be by the copyright holder. (Applicants retain the copyright in any submitted work.)&lt;br/&gt;Employees of Artrepreneur or Tiny Tim Rescue Fund are not eligible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You should submit examples of your graphic design or illustration work that will show off your talent and technical capabilities. These designs DO NOT need to be a potential design for the t-shirt. The Grand Prize winner will create a new graphic for the shirt through consultation with John Bartlett. Your submission should focus on the breadth of your design style so that he can evaluate your ability to create a stunning graphic that will help the Tiny Tim Rescue Fund fulfill its mission.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CASH PRIZES&lt;br/&gt;One Grand Prize Winner will be selected along with a cash prize of $500 and the opportunity to work directly with John Bartlett.&lt;br/&gt;Five runners-up will receive a $100 Amazon gift card.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The announcement of the winner and other contest updates can be found on Instagram, so please follow us to receive these notifications. (@artrepreneur_og)&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e26d0cc7-f1ba-4ff7-8a1a-1dffcc358da5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0d7aafcf-5a2d-481e-99fa-86889389f55b</id><title>6/15 - Museum of Exploration and Innovation 2020</title><updated>2019-05-22T13:16:50.421919+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;MOXI (The Wolf Museum of Exploration + Innovation)&lt;br/&gt;📍 Santa Barbara, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/15/2018 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=6603"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MOXI (The Wolf Museum of Exploration and Innovation) opened in 2017 and was listed by Fodor's Travel as one of the top 10 new museums in the world. Based in Santa Barbara, CA, MOXI has two spaces dedicated to rotating 3-month interactive media art installations. This call represents MOXI's second open application for artists and art collectives to propose works, for the year 2020.  Artworks should be interactive and designed to be highly robust to accommodate active children and family visitors.  Total budget of a large-scale interactive artwork can be up to $10,000.  At the close of this call, up to 8 applications will be chosen and applicants will be paid $200 each to develop more detailed exhibition proposals and interview with the MOXI staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply on CaFE at:&lt;br/&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=6603&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0d7aafcf-5a2d-481e-99fa-86889389f55b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>129ef535-892a-4607-b72f-4b19971f4eb0</id><title>5/28 - OPEN CALL: SHIM Invitational 7</title><updated>2019-05-22T13:16:50.421879+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SHIM Art Network&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/28/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.shhhim.com/invitational"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call for Submissions:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIM Art Network is pleased to announce an open call to visual artists in all media for the next iteration of SHIM’s Invitational program: SHIM Invitational 7.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIM is an arts exhibition company that fills the gaps in the art world, providing exhibition opportunities to artists, curators, and other organizations. In partnership with Artsy.net, we are thrilled to be able to expand our programming to include professional digital services to our artist members under a new, improved, and sustainable model for artists. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIM Invitational 7 will take place June 7th - 30th at SHIM’s partner gallery at ODETTA in Brooklyn, NY and will feature work by 12-18 artists curated by SHIM’s team. To be considered for SHIM Invitational 7, the deadline for submissions is May 28th, 2019. Applications received after May 28th will be kept for consideration for 12 months of future iterations of our membership and exhibition programs, including planned presentations at Superfine! DC art fair and Aqua Art Fair Miami this fall/winter. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;TO APPLY:&lt;br/&gt;Please visit the link below and submit your info, image samples, and non-refundable application fee via SHIM’s Artist Application, where you can also find more info about SHIM’s full range of programs for individual artists. Application Fees through our streamlined Artist Application, where you can apply your application to multiple opportunities in our network, are $10 per program, plus SHIM’s $10 Processing Fee. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MEMBERSHIP BENEFITS:&lt;br/&gt;Artists selected to exhibit in SHIM Invitational 7, in addition to having their work exhibited in our June show, will receive membership in SHIM’s permanent Invitational Exhibitor Group with annual year-round benefits that include access to SHIM Art Network’s Artsy.net platform, exclusive early invitations to gallery and art fair exhibitions, and additional professional development resources.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MEMBERSHIP + EXHIBITOR FEE: $300&lt;br/&gt;Artists selected for the exhibition and membership will be subject to a one-time fee, which covers the exhibition production and promotion, and annual digital content hosting on SHIM’s Artsy.net platform. Like all of our programs, SHIM Art Network applies no commissions to sales from our exhibitions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLY HERE: &lt;a href="https://shhhim.wufoo.com/forms/z1um3hgw0meie7e/" target="_blank"&gt;https://shhhim.wufoo.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To learn more about SHIM’s Invitational program, please visit www.shhhim.com/invitational or send us an email at info.shhhim@gmail.com. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Follow us on Facebook at fb.com/SHIMartnetwork and on Instagram at @SHIMartnetwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLY HERE: &lt;a href="https://shhhim.wufoo.com/forms/z1um3hgw0meie7e/" target="_blank"&gt;https://shhhim.wufoo.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To learn more about SHIM’s Invitational program, please visit www.shhhim.com/invitational or send us an email at info.shhhim@gmail.com. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Follow us on Facebook at fb.com/SHIMartnetwork and on Instagram at @SHIMartnetwork.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/129ef535-892a-4607-b72f-4b19971f4eb0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>fd5fdee2-31c3-4bd0-ab95-cdd797433ede</id><title>6/9 - HEIRLOOM (Deadline Extended): An OPEN CALL to Help Reunite Immigrant Families</title><updated>2019-05-22T13:16:50.421823+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ground Floor Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 BROOKLYN, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://groundfloorbk.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Spring Pop-up Exhibition HEIRLOOM: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ground Floor Gallery is pleased to announce our spring open call for "HEIRLOOM,"  a pop-up show in honor of the season and the significance of family! As defined by Merriam-Webster Dictionary, an heirloom is: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1: a piece of property (such as a deed or charter) that descends to the heir as an inseparable part of an inheritance of real property&lt;br/&gt;2: something of special value handed down from one generation to another&lt;br/&gt;3: a variety of plant that has originated under cultivation and that has survived for several generations usually due to the efforts of private individuals.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In true Ground Floor Gallery fashion, "HEIRLOOM" is an extension of our mission to connect emerging artists to new art buyers while - in our small way - supporting a cause we deem urgent. Each original artwork will be sold for $225; all sales will be accompanied by a certificate of authenticity; and, in honor of election year and the prospect of new beginnings - $20.20 from each sale will benefit RAICES: (The Refugee and Immigrant Center for Education and Legal Services) in their continued efforts to reunite immigrant families separated at the border. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline EXTENDED: Sunday, June 9th, 2019, 12pm. No fee to enter. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SAVE THE (NEW!) DATE for the Opening Reception: Wednesday, June 12th, 5-9pm &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Two years ago, you all helped us raise over $1,000 for the Committee to Protect Journalists and we’re hoping your passion and sense of urgency to address this most pressing of issues resonates as strongly!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No phone calls. Submission Details on our Website: &lt;a href="http://groundfloorbk.com/news/1/" target="_blank"&gt;http://groundfloorbk.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Looking forward!&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fd5fdee2-31c3-4bd0-ab95-cdd797433ede" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>