<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-03T19:17:07-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>223aec2f-09fc-42e5-a795-0eccb3cfbd74</id><title>7/12 - Call for Proposals:  Take A Seat Exhibition</title><updated>2019-06-03T19:17:07.956857+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtsWestchester&lt;br/&gt;📍 White Plains, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/12/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artswestchester.submittable.com/submit/133709/call-to-artists-and-designers-submit-your-chairs-to-take-a-seat-exhibition-at"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"TAKE A SEAT": An exhibition that explores the form, function, creativity, and tradition of seating.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ArtsWestchester invites artists and artist collectives to submit originally designed and handcrafted chairs, alternative forms of seating, or artwork that represents or incorporates chairs for its exhibition, “TAKE A SEAT”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected work will be on view in ArtsWestchester’s “TAKE A SEAT” exhibition, which will open with a reception on September 28, 2019, and be on view to the public through October 19, 2019.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BACKGROUND: "TAKE A SEAT" explores the forms, functions, traditions, and creative frameworks of seating. For the exhibition, ArtsWestchester will consider work in all media including, but not limited to: sculptural, conceptual, functional (and dysfunctional) seating, 2-dimensional artworks, and installations using chairs/seating. &lt;br/&gt;As with all exhibitions at ArtsWestchester's Gallery, "Take a Seat" will be free to the public. The exhibition will address an audience of all ages and backgrounds.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Applicants must be at least 18 years old, and must live, maintain a studio or be enrolled in an undergraduate or graduate program in New York State.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR SUBMISSIONS:  July 12, 2019 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be notified of their submission status on or around July 31, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION PERIOD:&lt;br/&gt;“TAKE A SEAT” will open with a reception on Saturday, September 28, and be on view through October 19, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;ArtsWestchester Gallery hours are Tuesday - Friday, 12-5PM, and Saturday, 12-6PM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION REQUIREMENTS:&lt;br/&gt;All Submissions must be submitted digitally via Submittable. E-mailed or mailed submissions will not be considered. Artists must submit a separate statement for each piece. &lt;br/&gt;Complete applications must include:&lt;br/&gt;Artist Bio and/or CV (word document)&lt;br/&gt;High Resolution Images of each work (artists may submit up to 5 unique works, with no more      than 3 images per work.) (jpeg, tiff, pdf)&lt;br/&gt;Submission checklist (word document). Checklist should include the following information: title, date, materials, dimensions,  sale price, insurance pricem and installation/display details. &lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement for each submitted work (word document) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Note:  ArtsWestchester reserves the right to use any High Resolution Images of selected works for promotional purposes of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Further Questions: Contact Amy Kurlander, Curator: Akurlander@ArtsWestchester.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/223aec2f-09fc-42e5-a795-0eccb3cfbd74" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4b4fab2f-d67f-4c24-a57d-cab7c17e399c</id><title>7/10 - Haverstraw Riverwide Arts and Music Festival Projex: 6 • Juried</title><updated>2019-06-03T19:17:07.956812+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Haverstraw Riverwide Arts &amp;amp; Music Festival&lt;br/&gt;📍 Haverstraw, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http:/www.haverstrawriverwidearts.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;$400 Honorarium per accepted submission&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JURIED BY: Kathleen Rickling, Director of Public Arts Programs and former Curator at ArtsWestchester, White Plains, NY. Research assistant at Museum of Modern Art, NYC &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ADELANTE, THE FUTURE:  Water-Front-Parklets • Pop-up Art Event&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Haverstraw Riverwide Arts &amp; Music Festival is excited to announce a Call for Entry, to its HAVERSTRAW RIVERWIDE ART PROJEX: 6, Pop-Up Parklets. The theme is: Adelante, the Future. To be held in Emeline Park, located on the shore of the Hudson River in the Village of Haverstraw, September 14th, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In an experimental spirit, we welcome artists interested in moving from the traditional studio, gallery and museum space into the freedom of an outdoor landscape setting with site specific and community accessible art, by making a themed-seating-parklet or vignette, sited on the water front of the Hudson. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PARKLETS: traditionally started by taking a lowly parking spot, encouraging their transformation into parks, playgrounds, pop-up cafés – anything other than their intended use. We are redefining the concept by asking artists to create a small themed seating vignette within our park. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Parklets should be an interactive art seating project assembled on-site with a mission to reference any aspect of the “cultural landscape” of this vibrant river town, celebrating the strength of melding its diverse cultural heritage, while it moves future forward over time. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The PARKLET may take form, in any media that can withstand the weather, and site conditions for one day. Re-cyclables are encouraged but not required. Immersive mixed media parklet installations of seating with sculpture, painting, mixed media, tactical and site performance, temporal installations, video, sound projections, or multimedia digital platforms are acceptable. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The festival will include live music, food, craft venders along with NYC, South Street Sea Port's Schooner, Pioneer.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Requests for proposals.  Full description:  &lt;a href="http://www.haverstrawriverwidearts.org/call-for-artists-entry" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.haverstrawriverwidearts.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Up to 4 individual artists or adtist team will be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;$400 Honorarium per accepted submission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSION DEADLINE:                                                   July 10, 2019&lt;br/&gt;WINNER ANNOUNCED:                                                   July 22, 2019&lt;br/&gt;DATE OF HAVERSTRAW RIVERARTS PROJEX: 6     September 14, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HONORARIUM:  $400 for individual artists or artists teams per selected submission&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:  Professional visual, sculptors, painters, video, sound projections, multimedia and digital artists, architects, designers and performance artists, are invited to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Required: A digital folder with:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1.	A 300 word or fewer proposal that includes the media and scale.&lt;br/&gt;2.	Resume&lt;br/&gt;3.	Up to 8 images of recent work. (Digital specifications can be found on &lt;a href="http://www.haverstrawriverwidearts.org/call-for-artists-entry/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.haverstrawriverwidearts.org&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br/&gt;4.	An image script, which should include title, medium, dimension, and date.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOTE: Please size your images no larger than 2000 pixels max H or W, at a resolution of 72 dpi and format them as RGB JPGs. You may send up to 8 images. Describe your images in your proposal. Digital images should be in a folder and clearly labeled so that they match the description using two digits (01, 02, 03, etc.) and your name in the following format: LastName_FirstName_01.jpg. Do not submit CDS. All images must be uploaded digitally. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For additional questions about the application, or for specifics of Haverstraw Riverwide Arts &amp; Music Festival Call for Entry, please contact us at: www.haverstrawriverwidearts.org •haverstrawriverarts@gmail.com •(845) 708-5098.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4b4fab2f-d67f-4c24-a57d-cab7c17e399c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f8ada703-4c1e-4233-bf6d-a81431717f4a</id><title>8/1 - Superposition Gallery Artist Roster Application</title><updated>2019-06-03T19:17:07.956781+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Superposition Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Los Angeles, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://superpositiongallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Superposition is turning 1 year old in August, and we are celebrating with our annual show in Los Angeles. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Join a roster of multidisciplinary artists, mentors, and a community focused on a socially conscious approach to art. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://form.jotform.com/91425573540153&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit SuperpositionGallery.com and click APPLY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;or use the JotForm link provided &lt;a href="https://form.jotform.com/91425573540153" target="_blank"&gt;https://form.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f8ada703-4c1e-4233-bf6d-a81431717f4a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c114f16a-15ef-4cc5-8c70-a784051ae683</id><title>7/19 - **Call For Artists: The Other Art Fair Brooklyn**  Brooklyn Expo Center, Nov. 7-10, 2019</title><updated>2019-06-03T19:17:07.956730+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Other Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://nyc.theotherartfair.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Other Art Fair returns to the Brooklyn Expo Center to present its final edition of 2019 (Nov. 7-10, 2019). The Other Art Fair provides a unique platform for artists to showcase their work to gallerists, curators, critics and collectors. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Presented by leading online gallery Saatchi Art, the fair is recognized as the definitive place for buyers to discover exciting and emerging talent. In addition to artwork sales, these four days enable artists to launch their work in the contemporary art world, gauge the public’s response to their pieces and meet fellow artists for potential future collaborations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Other Art Fair in Brooklyn in November 2018 welcomed over 12,300 visitors and attracted representatives from many esteemed New York galleries and cultural institutions such as Gagosian Gallery, Pace Gallery, Elizabeth Dee Gallery, The Museum of Modern Art, The Metropolitan Museum of Art and Christie’s. This reception was met with numerous sales, commissions and post fair collaborations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply online now: &lt;a href="http://nyc.theotherartfair.com/applications" target="_blank"&gt;http://nyc.theotherartfair.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for applications: January 18&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no application fee. Stand fees start at $1,880 + sales tax.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As part of our exciting collaboration with leading online gallery Saatchi Art, exhibitors will be presented as fair artists to an extensive network of curators, collectors, interior designers and international buyers via saatchiart.com/theotherartfair, social media and the Canvas blog.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions? Please contact Sasha Ali, Events Assistant, sasha@theotherartfair.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online now: &lt;a href="http://nyc.theotherartfair.com/applications" target="_blank"&gt;http://nyc.theotherartfair.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for applications: January 18&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no application fee. Stand fees start at $1,880 + sales tax.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c114f16a-15ef-4cc5-8c70-a784051ae683" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>