<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-23T21:16:52-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>9cb8185f-32ff-440e-9e30-847790fb998e</id><title>12/31 - Seeking Curatorial Proposals for LIC Arts Open Gallery at The Factory</title><updated>2019-05-23T21:16:52.381921+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The LIC Arts Open Gallery is seeking proposals from curators for shows at our two galleries in The Factory LIC.  The LIC  Arts Open operates two gallery spaces at The Factory -  the smaller gallery is approximately 50 x 50' and the larger one is over 6000 sq ft with one wall being over 100' long. Accordingly, we are seeking all kinds of proposals from solo shows all the way to large group exhibitions that could feature 40+ artists.    Certain proposals from curators may have a stipend attached which depends on certain factors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist's collectives and individual curators are all welcome to submit. Shows will usually run for a month, receptions are held on Thursdays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send your proposals indicating whether you are able to supply the necessary technology if working in the video or technology field. Please also tell us if any of the materials are toxic or hazardous. There are no restrictions on the subject matter.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9cb8185f-32ff-440e-9e30-847790fb998e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>25338a92-417c-4464-8573-1c4d2c75277d</id><title>7/1 - IVERSEN CENTER FOR FAITH ARTWORK REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS</title><updated>2019-05-23T21:16:52.381864+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;University of St. Thomas&lt;br/&gt;📍 St. Paul, MN, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.stthomas.edu/media/collegeofartsandsciences/arthistory/ICFCalltoArtists.pdf"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The University of St. Thomas invites artists’ proposals for new integrated artworks for the Iversen Center for Faith. Designed by Opus Design Build, L.L.C., this 23,000 square foot subterranean glass addition will create a contemporary touch to the Classical Revival architecture of the Chapel of St. Thomas Aquinas, designed by Emmanuel Masqueray in 1916. The expansion puts the original chapel on a lighted pedestal and adds expanded space and amenities to better serve the contemporary needs of the campus community. This space will centralize all campus ministry offices and serve as the spiritual heart of the campus. It will include a multi-faith meditation room, sacred arts gallery, multipurpose gathering room for receptions and events, new bride and groom facilities, and an outside amphitheater. The dedication for the Iversen Center for Faith is planned for fall 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For complete information, including how to apply, please see: &lt;a href="https://www.stthomas.edu/media/collegeofartsandsciences/arthistory/ICFCalltoArtists.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.stthomas.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For further questions, please contact: ArtHistoryGallery@stthomas.edu&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/25338a92-417c-4464-8573-1c4d2c75277d" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>