<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>e47c593b-a393-4c41-988e-5ca9f0bfc0ac</id><title>2/15 - Northern Regional Recreation Center – Lighting Installation</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.489393+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arts and Science Council&lt;br/&gt;📍 Charlotte, NC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Arts &amp; Science Council (ASC) is accepting qualifications from professional artists or teams of artists in response to a public art opportunity for Mecklenburg County’s Northern Regional Recreation Center. ASC is seeking artists or teams of artists with a demonstrated record of integrating dynamic lighting into architectural space, while responding to infrastructure and community input.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The selected artist/s will be asked to create an artwork that can interact and activate specific architectural features through integrated lighting and pattern. The “silo”, a 30’ OD perforated metal cladding housing indoor water slides, highlighted in accompanying renderings has been identified as the main artwork site. Further opportunities identified by the selected artist will be considered. The lighting for the artwork can be colorful, programmable, and interactive, and should respond to the design of the silo and water slides it houses. Artists are also encouraged to consider the relationship to the integrated lighting and the perforated cladding. Specific sections of the silo’s metal cladding could be customized to interact with and enhance the experience of the integrated lighting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To view/begin the application, go to &lt;a href="https://asc.slideroom.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://asc.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt; and sign up for an account. Applications must be received via SlideRoom by 11:59 p.m. Eastern Savings Time on February 15, 2019. There is no application fee to apply or use the SlideRoom online application system. The following materials will be required to be uploaded to SlideRoom:&lt;br/&gt;- Credentials: Resume or Curriculum Vitae (CV)demonstrating professional history and skills or experience as a professional artist (maximum two pages)&lt;br/&gt;- Statement of Interest: a brief introductory narrative that also provides insight about your interest in the project&lt;br/&gt;- Images: up to eight (8) images or three (3) digital video or movie files limited to two minutes each – of recent work completed within the past five (5) years&lt;br/&gt;- Annotation: titles, date, media and dimensions of artwork&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e47c593b-a393-4c41-988e-5ca9f0bfc0ac" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>381c9594-2e6b-42dc-98b1-295e7287cf0c</id><title>3/27 - ROLLING SUBMISSIONS: Superfine! Art Fair | New York 2019</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.489363+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Superfine! Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/27/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.superfine.world/exhibit-nyc"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rapidly growing art fair that has spread its "make art yours" mantra to Washington DC, Miami, and Los Angeles returns for the third year to its easy-to-get-to, high traffic Meatpacking location in Manhattan. Superfine! NYC '19 applications close on Wednesday, March 27th, however applications are reviewed and accepted on a rolling basis. 60% of artist booths and 30% of gallery booths are already reserved by other cutting-edge, new contemporary exhibitors, and all booths will likely be sold out before the application deadline. Here's what's still available:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GALLERIES:&lt;br/&gt;• 18 booths in our Gallery Pavilion ranging from 16 - 32 linear feet of wall ($4,000 - $8,000)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SOLO ARTISTS:&lt;br/&gt;• 4 Elevate Booths: 12-foot artist booths; the fair's most popular size ($3,000)&lt;br/&gt;• 13 Immerse Booths: 16-foot artist booths for artists wishing to have a larger footprint in the fair ($4,000)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! receives frequent and consistent media coverage in outlets like Washington Post, New York Post, and Artnet, and the fair holds the key to the growing, "maturing", and engaged young collector masses. About 20% of visitors make a significant purchase of at least $500, and 90% of past exhibitors report selling to almost exclusively new clients outside of their existing collector network.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! NYC will be hosted from May 1-5 on 14th Street in the Meatpacking District (at the foot of the bustling High Line Park). Superfine! is an art fair engineered for galleries who recognize a needed shift in the art market and for artists treating their talents as a serious art business.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GET A BETTER SENSE OF THE FAIR:&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! on Artnet: &lt;a href="https://news.artnet.com/partner-content/superfine-la" target="_blank"&gt;https://news.artnet.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! NY '18 Recap Video: &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/_vyyZ8LQjOk" target="_blank"&gt;https://youtu.be&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibitor Testimonials: &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/testimonials/" target="_blank"&gt;https://superfine.world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Review our floor plan and decide which available space you would like (link below).&lt;br/&gt;2. Fill out and submit your application (~10-15 min., link below).&lt;br/&gt;3. Email five high-quality artwork images to exhibit@superfine.world (these are only examples for initial promotion, you may show different/more works for the fair itself).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FLOOR PLAN + EXHIBITOR INFO:&lt;br/&gt;https://superfine.world/exhibit-nyc&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DIRECT LINK TO APPLICATION:&lt;br/&gt;https://na3.docusign.net/Member/PowerFormSigning.aspx?PowerFormId=7ef148e8-58c5-4885-896a-a3b157674304&amp;env=na3&amp;v=2&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/381c9594-2e6b-42dc-98b1-295e7287cf0c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>284e490c-34a7-4f22-b577-fa610bf6f0c2</id><title>3/1 - Call for Work: Art Stands Still</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.489331+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Collar Works&lt;br/&gt;📍 Troy, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artstandsstill.wixsite.com/home"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call for Work: Art Stands Still &lt;br/&gt;May 31 – July 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;In the United States, freedom has historically been linked to the right to move as one pleases.  This limited understanding of freedom has led to the creation of a system that constrains the movement of the many to reinforce the supposed freedom of the few. Policies of containment can be found throughout the history of the United States: Japanese internment camps, Native American reservation systems, the Chinese Exclusion Act, and Jim Crow segregation, not to mention today’s mass incarceration of people of color, the travel ban blocking entry to those from majority-Muslim nations, and the shutdown of the government over the funding of a border wall between the United States and Mexico.  &lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;In our modern history of art, freedom has also been conceptualized as movement: the avant-garde push our society forward through their new and unconventional choices.  Like the first line of an army charging into battle, these artists attempt novel works of art while denying any previous influences or collaborators. This concept of freedom has restricted our understanding of what artistic genius looks like to the domain of white men, who, as art historian Linda Nochlin famously pointed out, have suffered from less societal restrictions to their claims of independence and exceptionality. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Contemporary artists and historians working in disability studies, gender studies, critical race theory, and queer theory, among other fields, have begun the important work of dismantling the conflation of freedom with movement.  How does our current limited definition of freedom support hegemonic capitalist, nationalist, sexist, racist, ablest, homophobic, transphobic systems of power in the art world and beyond? How can we visualize alternative notions of freedom through art? How can mobility participate in the limitation or denial of such freedoms? And what happens when artists and viewers not only resist moving forward, but choose to stand shockingly still? &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The group exhibition, Art Stands Still, will open at Collar Works, a repurposed textile factory, within Troy, New York, a city that was once celebrated for its position at the forefront of American industrial achievement. Like many Rust Belt economies, it experienced a sharp economic decline in the late twentieth century. What is forward for cities like Troy? Art Stands Still looks to create a place for a community of alternatives to spatial, temporal, and social advancement.  Works may be connected to the theme broadly and all media will be considered.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Just for a moment, let’s not go anywhere, together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit application to ArtStandsStill@gmail.com by Friday, March 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;Submission Guidelines&lt;br/&gt;o     Only one application per artist will be accepted; however, artists may submit up to three works for consideration, and up to five images of the work or one video clip per each work on the application. File formats accepted are JPEG, TIFF, PDF, and MOV. ​&lt;br/&gt;o     Image files should be no larger than 5 MB; video clips may exceed this size requirement but should be no longer than 5 minutes in duration. &lt;br/&gt;o     Please include your name, a brief artist statement, a description of each submitted work, a CV, and a link to your artist website.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Dates&lt;br/&gt;o     Submissions due Friday, March 1, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;o     Artists will be notified by e-mail of decisions by Sunday, March 17, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;o     Confirmation by accepted artists and commitment to show work will be required by Friday, March 29, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;o     Work must be received by Friday, May 10, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;o     Work will be returned by July 20, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/284e490c-34a7-4f22-b577-fa610bf6f0c2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>76881a8d-18a9-4f1e-875f-7f129098e7bc</id><title>2/14 - 32nd Annual McNeese National  Works on Paper Exhibition</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.489288+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;McNeese State University/Dept. of Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Lake Charles, LA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.mcneeseartonline.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUROR&lt;br/&gt;Stephanie Mitchell, Executive Director&lt;br/&gt;Lawndale Art Center, Houston, Texas&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CALENDAR 2019&lt;br/&gt;February 14......Deadline for receiving all entry submissions&lt;br/&gt;February 28.....Notification of acceptance&lt;br/&gt;March 12.........Deadline for receipt of accepted works&lt;br/&gt;March 21.........Opening reception (6 to 8 p.m.)&lt;br/&gt;May 9..............Exhibition concludes&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AWARDS&lt;br/&gt;$3,000 will be available for the purchase of works for the McNeese State University Works on Paper Permanent Collection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MEDIA SPECIFICATIONS&lt;br/&gt;Work in any medium using paper as a component part is eligible. Artwork, including frame, should not exceed 40” in any dimension.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;Open to all artists living in the United States. All artwork should be original and completed in the last two years.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION&lt;br/&gt;Accepted artwork must be suitable for formal gallery presentation as well as the rigors of packaged shipping.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRIES&lt;br/&gt;Artists may submit no more than three entries. &lt;br/&gt;Entries are submitted using the CaFÉ™ website (www.callforentry.org). &lt;br/&gt;You may prep your materials in advance by following these specifications:&lt;br/&gt;File format - JPEG or JPG&lt;br/&gt;File dimension - minimum 1,200 pixels on the longest side File size - under 5 MB &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEE&lt;br/&gt;A non-refundable entry fee of $35 is charged each entrant. &lt;br/&gt;This fee entitles the artist to a maximum of three entries. &lt;br/&gt;Credit card payments are accepted using the CaFÉ™ website.&lt;br/&gt;Entries will be marked complete upon receipt of payment.&lt;br/&gt;The prospectus may be copied or downloaded from: www.mcneeseartonline.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION&lt;br/&gt;March 21 - May 9, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Awards will be announced at the opening reception March 21.&lt;br/&gt;Accepted artworks required to remain in the Grand Gallery for the duration of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DELIVERY OF ACCEPTED WORK&lt;br/&gt;Please ship work to:&lt;br/&gt;32nd Annual McNeese National Works on Paper Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;McNeese State University/Dept. of Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;4205 Ryan St. &lt;br/&gt;Lake Charles, LA 70609&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Works must be received by March 12.&lt;br/&gt;• C.O.D. deliveries will not be accepted. &lt;br/&gt;• All accepted works must include prepaid return shipping label.&lt;br/&gt;• Late or damaged shipments will be returned collect.&lt;br/&gt;• Works must be shipped in reusable packing cartons.&lt;br/&gt;• NO PACKING POPCORN.&lt;br/&gt;• Hand deliveries accepted March 12-15 (9 a.m. to 4 p.m.).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RETURN OF ACCEPTED WORKS&lt;br/&gt;Return of artwork begins:...May 14&lt;br/&gt;Hand delivery pick up:.........May 18 (9 a.m. to 4 p.m.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY&lt;br/&gt;All reasonable care will be given to objects in the custody of the Department of Visual Arts. Works are insured while on exhibition in the Grand Gallery. The Department of Visual Arts cannot assume responsibility for the damage or deterioration incurred before or after exhibition, or for possible loss in transit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SALES &amp; REPRODUCTION&lt;br/&gt;While no commission will be charged on purchase prize awards, a 40 percent commission will be charged on all other artists’ sales by the Grand Gallery. The exhibition committee reserves the right to reproduce accepted entries in press releases, catalog and on the website.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CONTACT INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;McNeese State University, Department of Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Coordinator: Heather Ryan Kelley&lt;br/&gt;Phone: 337-475-5060 (office), 337-475-5927 (fax)&lt;br/&gt;Email: hkelley@mcneese.edu&lt;br/&gt;Mailing address:&lt;br/&gt;32nd Annual McNeese National &lt;br/&gt;Works on Paper Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;McNeese State University/Dept. of Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;4205 Ryan St.&lt;br/&gt;Lake Charles, LA 70609&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/76881a8d-18a9-4f1e-875f-7f129098e7bc" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>49c95674-9918-434f-b365-1412b1754f39</id><title>2/6 - 76th Regional Exhibition Call for Entries</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.489261+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arnot Art Museum&lt;br/&gt;📍 Elmira, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://76thregional.artcall.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Arnot Art Museum in Elmira, New York announces a call for artists for their 76th Regional Exhibition. Artists must be 18 or older and live in Connecticut, Delaware, Maine, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, New Jersey, New York, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, or Vermont. Work over five years old or shown before in any Arnot Art Museum exhibition is not eligible. There is a maximum of two entries per artist. Please visit &lt;a href="https://76thregional.artcall.org" target="_blank"&gt;https://76thregional.artcall.org&lt;/a&gt; for more information and to submit your entries. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The 76th Regional Exhibition offers up to $8,000 in cash awards to be distributed among the juror selections. Work selected for the exhibition will be on display in the Museum's galleries from 15 March through 14 June 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The non-refundable entry fee is $40 for one or two entries ($25 for Museum members). You must use the secure website ArtCall.org to participate. Please visit &lt;a href="https://76thregional.artcall.org" target="_blank"&gt;https://76thregional.artcall.org&lt;/a&gt; to complete the registration, payment, and submission process by 6 February 2019. Contact engagement@arnotartmuseum.org if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/49c95674-9918-434f-b365-1412b1754f39" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>fb480ae1-46c4-44e5-bc88-c60308e42528</id><title>2/24 - 20/92 Video Festival at Icebox Project Space</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.489230+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Icebox Project Space&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/24/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://iceboxprojectspace.com/20-92-annual-video-festival/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 20/92 Video Festival, now in its fifth year, presents collected short videos curated form a national open-call and screened at an immersive scale over the course of a week.  20/92 is unlike any other video festival, as the Icebox Project Space is one of the largest exhibition spaces Philadelphia at nearly 3,500 sq.ft. and has a dedicated projection system which allows for a continuous image to be cast upon its eastern and northern walls, at a maximum size of 20’ x 92’. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;There is no yearly theme, but we are a project space, and our mission is dedicated to artists who push against something, whether it is oppressive institutions, construction of identity, or even the creative process itself. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;This year we are looking for video shorts with a maximum run time of 15 minutes. All video ratios (4:3, 16:9, multi-video) are accepted and we encourage artists to explore the unique projection layout and scale.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Your submission supports our year-long programming focused on collaboration, experimentation, and opportunity.  Submissions are juried by Icebox directors Timothy Belknap and Ryan McCartney, and all participating artists will be provided with still image documentation. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline - February 24th&lt;br/&gt;Notification – February 28th&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception – March 14th  // 6 – 9pm&lt;br/&gt;Screening – March 15th – 17th  // 12 - 6pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;http://iceboxprojectspace.com/20-92-annual-video-festival/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit us online at:&lt;br/&gt;http://iceboxprojectspace.com/20-92-annual-video-festival/&lt;br/&gt;For full application instructions&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fb480ae1-46c4-44e5-bc88-c60308e42528" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e30c6096-7e64-4615-8b0e-3628a55c952f</id><title>3/15 - Art New England Artist in Residence</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.489199+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Art New England&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://opencall.artrepreneur.com/art-new-england-artist-residence/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art New England, in celebration of its 40th Anniversary and in collaboration with Artrepreneur, announces an Open Call for an Illustrator/Artist-in-Residence. Three finalists will be chosen, with the winner’s work appearing in three issues of Art New England in 2019 in addition to a $500 cash prize and $300 dollars per issue. Work will help illustrate the Publisher’s Letter and other editorial as needed, with specifics and instructions provided to the artist per issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply via this link: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://opencall.artrepreneur.com/art-new-england-artist-residence/&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e30c6096-7e64-4615-8b0e-3628a55c952f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6889bcb1-91fd-4443-898f-022ade065527</id><title>4/1 - Call for Artists and Designers- Azarian McCullough Art Gallery - 2019 - 2020</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.489157+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Azarian McCullough Art Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Sparkill, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://stac.edu/amag"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Azarian McCullough Art Gallery invites art and design applications for our 2018 – 2019 exhibition calendar.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AMAG is located on the campus of St. Thomas Aquinas College in Sparkill N.Y.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists in the tri-state area  (NY.NJ.CT.) are eligible. There is no application fee. All media will be considered.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AMAG assumes the expenses of insurance, the opening and a postcard, handles publicity in the Rockland/Bergen areas and takes a 20%  “commission” on sales  (see below).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION DEADLINE: April 1, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY AND TERMS&lt;br/&gt;- Because AMAG serves the educational community of St. Thomas Aquinas College, exhibiting artists agree to meet with our students (on one occasion) at a mutually convenient time to discuss their work.    &lt;br/&gt;- Works selected for exhibit must be assigned a dollar value and listed for insurance purposes. AMAG should have this list two weeks prior to delivery.  Works delivered in good condition are insured against loss or damage while in the gallery, from the date of delivery through the last date of retrieval.   (These dates will be specified in a letter of agreement between the artist &amp; AMAG.).    &lt;br/&gt;- AMAG inspects all delivered works for damage. AMAG and St. Thomas Aquinas College are not responsible for loss or damage of:  works in transit; works not listed for insurance purposes; works exhibited outside of the gallery; works left in the gallery beyond the last date of retrieval.  &lt;br/&gt;- Artists must hand deliver and retrieve works.   &lt;br/&gt;- Delivered works should be ready for hanging and/or installation.     &lt;br/&gt;- Artists are responsible for transportation costs to and from the gallery.  &lt;br/&gt;-  Artists who accept an invitation to exhibit at AMAG, grant AMAG and St. Thomas Aquinas College the right to use images of their work, as well as submitted biographical information, for educational and publicity purposes.&lt;br/&gt;- Artists who sell works while displayed at AMAG, agree to donate 20% of these sales to St. Thomas Aquinas College.    &lt;br/&gt;- Artists who accept an invitation to exhibit at AMAG agree upon the specified dates for: delivery, set up, display, reception and retrieval.&lt;br/&gt;- Artists who accept an invitation to exhibit at AMAG will be asked to donate a small work, sketch or example of process to the AMAG Archive to be used in future academic capacities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION PROCEDURE  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE SUBMIT&lt;br/&gt;A single, compressed (Reduced Size) PDF with the following: &lt;br/&gt;1.   20 images with titles, dimensions and dates underneath &lt;br/&gt;(It is preferred if the submitted work is representative of the work you would like to exhibit)    &lt;br/&gt;2.   Contact information &lt;br/&gt;3.   Artist's Statement OR description of proposed exhibition (1-2 pages)  &lt;br/&gt;4.   CV or Resume indicating exhibition history and education &lt;br/&gt;5.  One page description of how your work could enhance the curriculum of departments outside of art (eg. political science, biology, English, history)&lt;br/&gt;NOTE: Time-based artists can include a link in their submission email to videos online in addition to the above information  &lt;br/&gt;PLEASE SEND MATERIALS TO amag@stac.edu with &lt;br/&gt;2019 – 2020 Submissions in the subject line&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Visit AMAG on the web:  stac.edu/amag&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6889bcb1-91fd-4443-898f-022ade065527" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f6d1d0b2-ae51-4f94-b1b0-006b7ae899cd</id><title>3/1 - CALL TO ARTISTS - NYA gallery | newyorkart.com grand opening group show.</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488400+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;NYA gallery, newyorkart.com&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://newyorkart.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around for the past 8 years as an iPhone app and website newyorkart.com is opening a 9000 sq ft arts center, with storage, art studios and a white box gallery called NYA gallery in TriBeCa on Broadway.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;TRIBECA ARTS CENTER.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CALL TO ARTIST -  for a group show for the grand opening happening Thursday, March 7 2019 (6-9pm) (During Armory week)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Subject: any&lt;br/&gt;Medium: any&lt;br/&gt;Size restriction: under 36"X48"&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$45 application fee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;log onto newyorkart.com and click on "Artist Submit" - application $45.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f6d1d0b2-ae51-4f94-b1b0-006b7ae899cd" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>bb01dc28-5d8d-496a-a270-db1bf2019ca9</id><title>2/28 - Cortex Garage Artwork</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488355+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Cortex Innovation Community&lt;br/&gt;📍 St. Louis , MO, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/28/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://cortexstl.com/call-for-artists-cortex-garage-artwork/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cortex is interested in commissioning an artist to create an iconic artwork for an important and visible new parking facility in the Cortex Innovation Community in St. Louis, Missouri. This new, site- specific exterior mural or graphic treatment will embrace creative design solutions and reflect Cortex’s spirit of energy, innovation and community collaboration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Cortex is working with Via Partnership to help manage the selection process which is open to artists and designers with the capacity to successfully complete design and installation/fabrication of the project within the timeline.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE CORTEX INNOVATION COMMUNITY&lt;br/&gt;The Cortex Innovation Community is a vibrant 200-acre innovation hub and technology district in the heart of St. Louis City. It sits between St. Louis’ Central West End and Forest Park Southeast neighborhoods and is surrounded by nationally ranked universities and medical centers, cultural assets, historic neighborhoods, and public spaces, including the Grand Center Arts District, Forest Park, and the Grove. The complete Cortex development plan includes support for $2.3 billion of development: 4.5 million square feet of mixed-use buildings (research, office, clinical, residential, hotel, and retail), as well as a MetroLink light-rail station, a publicly-accessible park, and 15,000 permanent technology-related jobs for the St. Louis region. Currently, over 390 companies call the Cortex Innovation Community home. The Community is an open place for big thinkers and risk takers, home to tech startups, manufacturers, corporate research and development teams, nonprofit organizations, and local restaurants, as well as entrepreneurs, artists, designers, side-hustlers, researchers, chefs, and students -- anyone who wants to build a product, grow a business, throw a party, or make connections.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT CORTEX&lt;br/&gt;Cortex is a 501(c)3 nonprofit organization that oversees development of the Cortex Innovation Community, founded by Washington University in St. Louis, Saint Louis University, University of Missouri - St. Louis, BJC Healthcare, and the Missouri Botanical Garden. Cortex staff and leadership are committed to creating a community in which everyone has access to office space, capital investment, business education, mentoring, and community events. We are building a dynamic, 24/7 neighborhood of restaurants, nightlife, shops green spaces, and apartments. Cortex is committed to fostering an innovation community in which the benefits of new company formation, capital investment, job creation and wealth generation extend to all. We work closely with our District innovation centers, founding partners, and other entrepreneur support organizations across the region to create and strengthen that community. We recognize that we are part of a larger movement for inclusive economic transformation of the St. Louis region. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ART PROJECT DESCRIPTION&lt;br/&gt;The Cortex Parking Garage is currently under construction. It is located in the center of the Cortex Innovation Community to the east of the 4220 Duncan building. The south façade of the garage will face the future Chouteau Greenway urban trail and a recently opened MetroLink light rail station. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Phase 1 of the garage will have five levels made up of three bays that together are 179 feet long. The construction of Phase 1 is scheduled to be completed in May 2019. A future expansion of the garage to the east would add another two to three bays and five to six levels. While the artwork installation for Phase 2 of the garage will not occur within the current timeline, finalists will create a design for both portions of the structure, as explained below. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The new artwork on the south façade of the parking garage will be viewed by those entering and exiting the garage and will be highly visible to both MetroLink riders and passersby on the Chouteau Greenway. The artwork will also be visible to pedestrians and drivers from many other vantage points throughout the area and from nearby structures. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The artwork should make use of the design of the structure in creating a site-specific piece. Proposals are not requested at this time, but finalists selected to develop a proposal will need to work within the technical constraints of the garage design, phased construction schedule and consideration of additional areas of the garage in their design. Detailed information will be shared with finalists to include the following considerations:&lt;br/&gt;•	Completed artwork should be permanent or semi-permanent with a minimum longevity of ten years. &lt;br/&gt;•	Minimal additional weight can be added to the structure of the garage and the artwork must not hinder air flow through garage openings. A painted mural, graphic treatment, or lightweight attachments to the garage face would be possible. Electricity can be made available. Finalists will be free to explore creative solutions in their concept proposals within the technical constraints. &lt;br/&gt;•	Finalists’ concept proposals will address both Phase 1 and Phase 2 of the garage construction. Because the Phase 1 artwork will be completed before the construction of Phase 2, the first phase of artwork must be both independent and complementary with the design of Phase 2.&lt;br/&gt;•	Finalists have the option to include the south stair concrete element in the scope of their design. The selected artist will also be consulted in selecting a complimentary color treatment for the west façade and northwest stair concrete element and elevator shaft.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ART PROJECT GOALS&lt;br/&gt;The project should achieve the following goals:&lt;br/&gt;•	Build on the image of Cortex as a premier national and international innovation hub.&lt;br/&gt;•	Reflect the spirit of the cutting edge, vibrant and energetic Cortex community. &lt;br/&gt;•	Serve as a gateway and point of arrival into Cortex.&lt;br/&gt;•	Create an iconic point of interest to bring attention to Cortex and help spread Cortex’s message.&lt;br/&gt;•	Use a functional parking infrastructure in a creative, innovative way. &lt;br/&gt;•	Highlight the interplay of movement seen from the MetroLink and the Chouteau Greenway to emphasize energy and activity.&lt;br/&gt;•	As one of the first major public art commissions in Cortex, set a high bar that energizes the community to use public art in future developments and public spaces.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTIST SELECTION PROCESS&lt;br/&gt;•	Artist submissions will be reviewed by an Artist Selection Panel (ASP), made up of regional curators, arts leadership and design professionals from the St. Louis community, as well as Cortex stakeholders. &lt;br/&gt;•	The ASP will select up to three (3) finalists to develop and present concept proposals. &lt;br/&gt;•	Finalists will receive a stipend of $5000 to participate in the concept proposal process, which will include touring Cortex and meeting community members prior to developing a proposal, and to present their proposal. Proposals will include renderings and a short narrative description addressing both Phase 1 and Phase 2, as well as a preliminary budget and timeline for completing Phase 1. &lt;br/&gt;•	Finalists will return to St. Louis to present their concept proposals directly to the ASP in person and to present their design at a Venture Café Gathering, which is open to the public. Feedback from attendees of this presentation will be shared with the ASP.  The ASP will recommend a final artist/design for the project. &lt;br/&gt;•	Artists living more than 100 miles from Cortex will be paid an additional amount up to $2000 for travel and lodging expenses in St. Louis for visits during the selection process, including the finalists’ introduction to Cortex and the presentations of the concept proposal.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FINALIST SELECTION CRITERIA&lt;br/&gt;The following criteria will be used by the Artist Selection Panel to select up to three (3) finalists.&lt;br/&gt;•	Artistic excellence as demonstrated by past work and submitted materials.&lt;br/&gt;•	A clear understanding of the project.&lt;br/&gt;•	A body of work that demonstrates an ability to create an artwork that responds to the goals of the project.&lt;br/&gt;•	Availability to meet the project timeline.&lt;br/&gt;•	Experience executing projects of similar scale and budget.  (If you do not feel like you meet this criteria, please include the reasons why you are right for this project in your letter of interest.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTIST’S ANTICIPATED SCOPE OF WORK&lt;br/&gt;The selected artist’s responsibilities will be to:&lt;br/&gt;•	Work with the project art consultant, garage architects, contractors and production company (if applicable) to finalize the design for both Phase 1 and Phase 2.&lt;br/&gt;•	Work with the project art consultant to coordinate fabrication (if applicable), installation and complete execution of artwork. If the selected artist fabricates and installs the artwork themselves, the selected artist will be responsible for bringing all required materials needed for installation, including approved scaffolding and equipment to be able to safely reach the facade, assistants to complete the process in the agreed-upon timeframe, painting supplies and liability insurance coverage.&lt;br/&gt;•	Recommend a color treatment for the west façade, and northwest stair concrete element and elevator shaft, and, if not included in scope of design, the south stair concrete element to coordinate with the artist’s design.&lt;br/&gt;•	Provide maintenance and conservation instructions for the completed artwork.&lt;br/&gt;•	Work cooperatively and maintain effective communication with all parties involved in the project.&lt;br/&gt;•	Collaborate with Cortex Innovation Community on marketing and promotion of artwork.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BUDGET&lt;br/&gt;The budget for the artwork is not to exceed $250,000. This budget includes all costs of designing, fabricating and installing the artwork, including but not limited to all design fees, fabrication, materials and equipment costs, professional fees, travel and lodging during fabrication and/or installation, insurance, overhead, design, fabrication, site-work, shipping, and installation costs.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;TENTATIVE TIMELINE&lt;br/&gt;February 18, 2019	Last day to submit questions&lt;br/&gt;February 28, 2019	Call for Artists Submissions due&lt;br/&gt;Mid-March, 2019	Up to three (3) finalist artists selected and notified&lt;br/&gt;Late March, 2019	Finalists invited for tour and introduction to the Cortex community&lt;br/&gt;May 30, 2019	Finalists present final concept proposals to ASP &lt;br/&gt;May 30, 2019	Finalists present final concept proposals at Venture Café Gathering series &lt;br/&gt;June 2019	Artist selection finalized&lt;br/&gt;July 2019	Selected artist submits final design for approval&lt;br/&gt;July-November 2019	Fabrication (if applicable) and installation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TO SUBMIT&lt;br/&gt;To apply, go online to the CaFÉ homepage at www.CallForEntry.org and create a free artist account. CaFÉ is free to use and there is no entry fee for this call.  Under “Find Calls” search for “Cortex Garage Artwork.” Follow the instructions for submission, upload the required images and files, and submit. For technical questions about CaFÉ, please click on “Help” on the CaFÉ website.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You will be required to submit the following:&lt;br/&gt;•	A brief letter describing your interest in the project, an explanation of why you are right for this project and confirmation of your ability to meet the project timeline. &lt;br/&gt;•	A CV/resume &lt;br/&gt;•	Contact information for 3-5 references.&lt;br/&gt;•	Up to 10 jpeg images of previously completed projects that show your experience with art projects of this scale. &lt;br/&gt;****PLEASE DO NOT SEND SPECIFIC PROPOSALS AT THIS TIME.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;QUESTIONS&lt;br/&gt;Interested artists may submit questions about this call by 4:00 p.m. CST on February 18, 2019 to Angie Villa at villa at viapartnership.com. Responses to questions will be posted at &lt;a href="https://cortexstl.com/" target="_blank"&gt;https://cortexstl.com&lt;/a&gt; by 4:00 p.m. CST on February 20, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/bb01dc28-5d8d-496a-a270-db1bf2019ca9" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>33f6d3c5-f2b8-4ffb-bbb4-9b4c573c1432</id><title>2/4 - Fashion Week NY- Call  to ARTISTS/SCULPTORS/PHOTOGRAPHERS-  NYC FASHION WEEK!</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488324+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Six Summit Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/04/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.sixsummitgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the largest fine art and fashion platform in NYC, LA and Miami.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;172 Norfolk St (lower east side) Angel Orensanz Gothic Cathedral&lt;br/&gt;New York, NY 10002&lt;br/&gt;917-573-0029&lt;br/&gt;www.sixsummitgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fashion Week: Angel Orensanz Center – Contemporary Art and Gothic Revival for “Art Hearts Fashion”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Six Summit Gallery is a leading multi-platform fine art and entertainment concern.  Art Hearts Fashion is a leading large award winning internationally known exquisite haute couture inclusive fashion platform whose designers dress some of the worlds most notable people. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Over 18  Shows- Thousands expected. Accepted artists will receive complimentary ticket for every show and discount for friends. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;– One of the true extraordinary venues in NYC. Over 30,000 square feet, multiple levels.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art does not have to be directly fashion related.&lt;br/&gt;Six Summit Gallery curates New York Fashion Week&lt;br/&gt;with Art Hearts Fashion.&lt;br/&gt;Art Hearts Fashion” events are a leading platform for artistically inspired emerging, celebrity and couture designers to showcase their collections in a contemporary fashion week setting. AHF events have been held coast to coast as a national showcase for designers to participate in New York, Miami, Mercedes-Benz Fashion Week China and Los Angeles Fashion Week. Founded by Philanthropist and Designer Erik Rosete, Participating designers can be seen on every major Hollywood celebrity including: Beyoncé, Lady Gaga, Katy Perry, Nicki Minaj, Rita Ora, Jennifer Lopez, Shakira, Miley Cyrus, Carrie Underwood, and countless more. The platform is unequivocally intertwined with the causes and organizations it supports.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art Hearts Fashion to Break New Ground during NYFW with over 20 Designers at the Angel Orensanz Foundation&lt;br/&gt;(New York, New York)—Revolutionary bi-coastal fashion platform Art Hearts Fashion hosts New York Fashion Week Feb 8-11th at the Neo-Gothic NYC landmark, the Angel Orensanz Foundation on the culturally flourishing lower east side. The Angel Orensanz Foundation, a replica of the Sistine Chapel in Rome, has long been the home for artistic and performing arts. The Cathedral will serve as the dramatic setting for NYC’s most highly attended shows this season of Art Hearts Fashion. A favorite among press and celebrities alike, this season Art Hearts Fashion brings an impressive lineup of over 20 acclaimed designers to the catwalk during 4 full days of runway shows and exclusive closing gala.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Global Juried Show by Six Summit Gallery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global Juried Show by Six Summit Gallery&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Call to ARTISTS&lt;br/&gt;EMAIL SUBMISSIONS ONLY TO&lt;br/&gt;fashion@sixsummitgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBLE WORK: Paintings, Photos works in all media.This show is open to all artists regardless of place of residence however you must deliver in person and you may be responsible for hanging.  (ceilings are high/see floorplan or google Angel Orensanz Foundation. All work must be wired and ready to hang. SUBMISSIONS: All work will be judged by email entry via fashion@sixsummitgallery.com. You MUST write [YOUR NAME]” IN THE SUBJECT OF EMAIL. YOUR NAME MUST BE THE SAME ON YOUR CREDIT/DEBIT CARD Example: Subject: FASHION SUBMISSION: John Doe. Files must be in .jpg format, 300 dpi, max 900 pixels in any dimension. File name should correspond to the title of the piece. PUT title, medium, artist, price, and size as JPEG FILE EXTENSION NAME.!  No accepted work may be removed prior to the show’s conclusion (unless of course it is sold) ALL work must be for sale. You may use existing hooks and existing metal pole on ceiling which goes around perimeter  (we have the wires) You may not make holes n walls. Sculptors must bring their own pedestals or free standing is ok. You are required to make your own labels. They must include Title, Medium,Price, and Your Name, www.sixsummitgallery.com – with “Purchase or Inquire Now” “Call or text Leo 917-573-0029” clearly visible on the bottom below www.sixsummitgallery.com. Purchases will take place during the show- Customers can leave with art or we can help arrange delivery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: The Show Committee reserves the right to disallow the exhibition of any work which, in the opinion of the Committee, is considered detrimental to the good public image of the show and its sponsors, which is too fragile to handle, or which is not accurately represented by the photo submitted. Six Summit Gallery, Angel Orensanz, or Art Hearts Fashion its officers or agents are NOT responsible for loss or damage or theft of any. We reserve the right to photograph work or use submitted images for publicity. ENTRY FEES: $75 for up to 6 entries. $35 for up to 2 entries.  Only work submitted with fee will be considered. Easily click on www.sixsummitgallery.com online store and go to ONLINE STORE-EVENTS SUBMISSION  &lt;a href="https://sixsummitgallery.com/products/event-submissions-products" target="_blank"&gt;https://sixsummitgallery.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;and choose $35 or $75.- Please call the Gallery for any special situations.&lt;br/&gt;Artist receives 60% on accepted sold work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are a fully insured gallery and represent this is a normal course of business. Six Summit Gallery and partners are not responsible for theft or damage of art. Admission will be made available to artists and guests!&lt;br/&gt;This show and venue is the highlight of NYFW. We expect active participating artists for this show. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;QUESTIONS CAN BE EMAILED ONLY TO: Fashion@sixsummitgallery.com Include your Call Back Number!&lt;br/&gt;DO NOT CALL OR EMAIL ANGEL ORENSANZ OR ART HEARTS&lt;br/&gt;(DATES and TIMES Subject to Change)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Delivery – February 8th,  9AM-NOON (you can stay and hang art or drop off only if pre arranged)&lt;br/&gt;Pick up – Feb 11th  after last show OR Feb 12th 9-10:30AM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Show dates and times- announced on our website www.sixsummitgallery.com (click on Art Hearts Fashion link)&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/33f6d3c5-f2b8-4ffb-bbb4-9b4c573c1432" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1fcc05f8-30a2-4e59-9bb2-8d158b02824c</id><title>1/31 - MvVO ART AD ART SHOW 2019 call for artists on LinkNYC in NY city!</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488296+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;MvVO ART&lt;br/&gt;📍 remsenburg, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $75.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.mvvoart.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Go to www. mvvoart.com to apply!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MvVO ART, creator of AD ART SHOW, is turning the streets of New York’s most art-centric neighborhoods into a revolutionary Art Show, digitally exhibiting contemporary Art on the LinkNYC network on select streets during Frieze Week—May 1 to 4, 2019. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;AD ART SHOW celebrates the ART created by artists currently working in advertising, or with roots in the advertising/design/commercial arts industries, as they follow in the footsteps of Warhol, Magritte, Haring, Dali and the many other world-renowned artists who worked in advertising.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The inaugural AD ART SHOW 2018 was a phenomenal success, bringing the Art, Media and Advertising world together for a 4 day show at Sotheby’s with 92 artists from advertising from around the world. AD ART SHOW 2019 transforms the LinkNYC network into an outdoor art show during the biggest week of the City’s art calendar—Frieze Week.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The selection committee is made up of contemporary art experts and influential collectors.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The Call for Artists submissions is open until January 31, 2019. For more information, eligibility or to submit work to the show, visit www.mvvoart.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please go to www.mvvoart.com to learn more and apply right from home page or via this direct link:&lt;br/&gt;https://mvvoart.submittable.com/submit&lt;br/&gt;for questions: contact info@mvvoart.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1fcc05f8-30a2-4e59-9bb2-8d158b02824c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>57a454c6-df3c-432c-9018-ae46f916bde3</id><title>2/24 - treat gallery nyc | satellite art show (austin, tx)</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488266+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;treat gallery new york&lt;br/&gt;📍 Austin, TX, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/24/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.treatgallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treat gallery, based in New York City, is excited to review your work for consideration for Satellite Art Show during SXSW. Your work would be shown at the fair March 13th - 17th.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our treat america project was an elaborate 2018 fundraiser where one user per state took over the @treatamericaproject instagram handle and posted one image a day for a week. Each user selected a state affiliated nonprofit or charity to benefit from sales. The exhibition premiered at Foley Gallery on January 9th, 2019 and will continue to travel.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your work will be shown alongside this project (which was curated by Jon Feinstein and Jamie Martinez) along with 3-4 other artists. We are in search of work that touches the idea of America, Americans (conceptually or content-wise) and what that means today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By paying the application fee, you will be exempt from paying future call for entry fees throughout 2020.  You may submit up to 5 images. Deadline is February 25th, 2019. Please apply by filling out the form below:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.jotform.com/treatgallery/satelliteapplication&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please reach out to us directly at info@treatgallery.org with any questions or concerns.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/57a454c6-df3c-432c-9018-ae46f916bde3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>86bca55b-2114-4992-824d-6266dac16c79</id><title>1/31 - Upcycle Junction Market: Open Call for Vendors</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488239+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Junction BID&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Crafts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="www.exploreflatbush.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for Brooklyn Based artists who specialize in  jewelry, painting, sculpture ,textiles and wood and are interested in being a street vendor and to develop their own brand.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Requirement: portfolio and online presence.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Upcycle Junction Market is an entrepreneural initiative of the Flatbush Junction BID. It is targeted at creatives in the art and design field, who work with recycled and salvaged materials. The program includes hands on training in product design, branding, pricing and marketing. Candidates who complete the training will participate in the Upcycle Junction Market on Hillel Plaza in May 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://thejunctionbid.submittable.com/submit/130103/upcycle-junction-market-open-call-for-vendors" target="_blank"&gt;https://thejunctionbid.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/86bca55b-2114-4992-824d-6266dac16c79" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>781cec0e-d2b6-450d-bfb4-13b458eb3b09</id><title>2/20 - SATELLITE ART SHOW // SXSW Week // Applications Open</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488209+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SATELLITE ART SHOW&lt;br/&gt;📍 Austin, TX, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.satellite-show.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SATELLITE ART SHOW SXSW&lt;br/&gt;MARCH 13 - 17, 2019&lt;br/&gt;AUSTIN, TX&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SATELLITE is a ground breaking art platform which debuted in Miami during Art Basel in 2015 and has now expanded to SXSW week in Austin. We are currently seeking ambitious applications/proposals from Galleries, Curators, Art Collectives, Non Profits and Solo Artists. By fostering a range of programming, SATELLITE is able to offer patrons and collectors with a unique experience where art is at the forefront of creative expression, activism, and curiosity. Our exhibitors are encouraged to provide our visitors both an opportunity to collect new works of art as well as to present exhibitions that are engaging, experiential and interactive. SATELLITE is expanding perceptions on art and community and providing an inclusive environment for guests to feel comfortable in exploration and discovery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION PLATFORMS: ($13.30 a square foot)&lt;br/&gt;• 100 sq ft space ($1,400)&lt;br/&gt;• 150 sq ft space ($2,000)&lt;br/&gt;• 200 sq ft space ($2,600)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our 2019 SXSW Location is the Museum of Human Achievement which always hosts SXSW events (Jack White's record label has had showcases here). The Museum of Human Achievement is a 7,500 sq foot warehouse with an additional 4,000 square feet of outdoor space. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SATELLITE has received rave reviews from Hyperallergic, Art Net, Financial Times, Artefuse, Observer, ArtSpace, Galore, Two Coats of Paint, Juxtapoz, Miami New Times, White Hot, Art Zealous, Guest of a Guest, BMore Art, Huffington Post, Playboy, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please fill out the Austin/SXSW Application on our website. You will instructed to submit the $50 application fee upon completion. If you have any questions or trouble uploading images to our platform please reach out to us at: info@satellite-show.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/781cec0e-d2b6-450d-bfb4-13b458eb3b09" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>66c3ccb4-17ac-4855-ad55-8769a4c6f93a</id><title>2/18 - REQUEST FOR QUALIFICATIONS (RFQ): THE BOWER: SCULPTURE PARK AND GARDENS</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488173+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Bridgette Mayer Art Advisors and the Bower&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/18/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://bridgettemayerartadvisors.submittable.com/submit/133330/request-for-qualifications-rfq-the-bower-sculpture-park-and-gardens"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OVERVIEW:&lt;br/&gt;Bridgette Mayer Art Advisors in collaboration with The Executive Committee of The Bower is seeking to commission professional artist/sculptor and or artist teams to design, fabricate and oversee fabrication and install permanent site-specific sculptures or permanent land art installations as part of its launch of its Phase I Bower Sculpture Park and Gardens. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SITE DESCRIPTION&lt;br/&gt;THE BOWER: SCULPTURE PARK AND GARDENS is located in Shermans Dale, PA (30 minutes outside of Harrisburg, PA). &lt;br/&gt;The location is a private property that will be turned into a public sculpture park and gardens. The future plans also include an artist studio, an artist residency program, possible gallery/exhibition space and public programming with various museums and collecting groups. There are meadow, garden and woodland settings on the property where the commissioned sculptures and projects would be placed. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is the Owners vision to curate an array of sculptural works, both large scale and intimate, that present visual interest from multiple perspectives. The works shall be designed to complement, enhance or provide interesting contrast within the natural setting. The construction shall be durable to withstand the changing seasons and weather elements and also shall be safe for interaction by visitors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Chosen artwork will be required to withstand a high-traffic, unmonitored outdoor environment with very limited maintenance. Artists should take into consideration the possibility of adverse weather conditions, the wellbeing of pedestrian traffic passing by and through the site and the safety of the audience.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PROJECT DETAILS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Owners are developing “The Bower: Sculpture Park and Gardens”, a rural setting, garden and sculpture park located on their 36-acre wooded and meadow site along the northern slope of the Appalachian Mountains in Perry County, Pennsylvania.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Approximately 5-10 finalists will be chosen from the pool of applicants, those finalists will be provided an honorarium up to $1500.00* to work with Bridgette Mayer Art Advisors and feedback from the Executive Committee to develop a final proposal for the artwork. The chosen artists/teams will then be commissioned to finalize design, fabricate, ship and install the artwork.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists may utilize imported materials of their choosing or landforming, stone, wood or other organics from the natural setting. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*For artists wishing to submit already fabricated sculpture works, they can do so for consideration, however please note if a work is selected that is already fabricated, an honorarium will not be provided in this instance.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*(Please note BMAA and Executive Committee will discern amount of honorarium to be given out based on potential travel and or other expenses of the particular applicant and an amount of up to $1500.00 will be awarded).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BUDGET&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Total project budget is approximately $10K-30K per artist or artist team and the amount awarded will be dependent on the proposed project. It is inclusive of all costs such as artist’s fees, fabrication, travel, and installation time and effort. A separate shipping budget should also be proposed. Sculpture foundation, lighting, hardscape and landscaping requirements will be determined in collaboration with the Owners and will be addressed outside the budget established for the artwork.  &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SCHEDULE OF PROJECT&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Request for Qualifications (RFQ)  January 18, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	RFQ Submittal Date  February 18, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	RFQ Review by Executive Committee/Consultant February 18 – March 4, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	Notification of Artist Long List March 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	Request for Proposals (RFP) March 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	Site Visits (optional) March 12-24, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	RFP Submittal Date April 2, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	RFP Review by Owner/Consultant April 2 – May 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	Notification of Artist Shortlist May 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	Request for Project Specific Proposals (PSP) May 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	Site Consultations (required)  May 15- June 8, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	PSP Submittal Date July 8, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	Notification of Selection   August 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	Negotiation of Project Terms August 5 – September 9, 2019&lt;br/&gt;•	Creation and Installation Period September 9, 2019 – April 30, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Additional photos and documentation about this project can be found on their Instagram site “@gardenbower” and "@bmartadvisors".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Deadline:&lt;br/&gt;Monday February 18, 2019 at 12:00 pm EST &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please click the website link to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications received after the deadline and those that are found to be incomplete will not be reviewed. It is the responsibility of the submitting artist to ensure that applications are complete and submitted by the deadline. Extensions to this deadline will not be granted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTIST ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any professional artist or artist team is eligible to apply. If artists are applying as a team, the team should be declared in the Artist Statement, specifying a team leader to receive notifications. Applicants must be 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTIST SELECTION CRITERIA &amp; PROCESS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Qualifications will be reviewed by Bridgette Mayer, Bridgette Mayer Art Advisors and The Bower Executive Committee based on the following: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	 Aesthetic merit of past projects; appropriateness of artwork medium and artistic concepts; &lt;br/&gt;•	Experience, success and/or interest in creating artworks in collaboration with     architects, design teams, community members, and collectors. &lt;br/&gt;•	Past art commissions are not a prerequisite for review but submitted work should demonstrate potential capacity for completion of artwork for the  project. &lt;br/&gt;•	Bridgette Mayer, Bridgette Mayer Art Advisors and The Bower Executive Committee reserves the right to alter the selection process based on the applications received and/or needs of the project.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FOR FURTHER QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS PLEASE CONTACT:&lt;br/&gt;Bridgette Mayer, Bridgette Mayer Art Advisors: bmayer@bmayeart.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/66c3ccb4-17ac-4855-ad55-8769a4c6f93a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>853b22e8-17d6-4525-8ba8-c70974c17aa0</id><title>2/24 - Open Call: 2019 Public Artists in Residence with the City of New York</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488142+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;New York City Department of Cultural Affairs&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/24/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www1.nyc.gov/site/dcla/publicart/pair.page"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The NYC Department of Cultural Affairs (DCLA) is seeking four artists to join the Public Artists in Residence (PAIR) program in 2019: one selected artist will be placed in residence with the following City agencies and offices: the Department of Mental Health and Hygiene, Department of Aging, Department of Records and Information Services, and the Mayor’s Office of Sustainability.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT PAIR&lt;br/&gt;DCLA’s Public Artist in Residence program (PAIR) is based on the premise that artists are creative problem solvers. To that end, DCLA embeds socially engaged artists in New York City municipal agencies in order to use creative, collaborative art practice to propose and implement creative solutions to pressing civic challenges.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Launched in 2015, PAIR takes its name and inspiration from the pioneering work of artist Mierle Laderman Ukeles, the first official artist in residence with the NYC Department of Sanitation (1977- present).  Since establishing the program, DCLA has embedded 10 artists in 8 agencies, including Tania Bruguera at the Mayor’s Office of Immigrant Affairs, The Lost Collective at the Administration for Children’s Services, Tatyana Fazlalizadeh at the Commission on Human Rights, among others. For a full list of PAIRs to date, click here.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All of the PAIR partnerships – some of which are still ongoing – vary greatly in concept, scope, duration, and populations engaged, and their successes are driven by the openness of the partner agencies and the artist-led, collaborative process that the PAIR program framework provides. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RESIDENCY STRUTURE, FEES, and MATERIALS&lt;br/&gt;PAIR residencies begin with a required half-day orientation session, which kicks off a three-month Research Phase.  This Phase is a time for the artist and agency to establish mutual trust through shared exposure to each other’s work and process—the artist shadows agency staff and attends meetings, trainings and site visits, and in turn the agency hosts an artist talk and visits the artist at their studio.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Research Phase ends with the artist proposing a project, designed in collaboration with the partner agency, to produce during the remaining eight months of the residency.  The Implementation Phase of the residency is marked by approval of the project proposal and initiation of the work.  The proposed project must be collaborative in nature and include at least one (1) public-facing event or component. Both DCLA and the partner agency will continue to provide the artist support during the project’s production for the duration of the residency.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Throughout the residency, the artist and agencies have weekly check-ins by phone or in-person to assist in project production.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PAIR funding per residency is $40,000: $20,000 for the Research Phase and $20,000 for the Implementation Phase. Funding is inclusive of related project expenses (e.g., printing, materials, equipment, video production, etc.). The selected artist(s) are responsible for managing the project budget and submitting invoices. No additional funding is provided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://nyculture.submittable.com/submit" target="_blank"&gt;https://nyculture.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/853b22e8-17d6-4525-8ba8-c70974c17aa0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>dd04fff2-708c-4ad9-b7c5-f10f3595f46c</id><title>2/14 - Request for Qualifications - Eight Public Art Opportunities</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488108+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Campus Arts Initiative&lt;br/&gt;📍 University Park, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://campusarts.psu.edu/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Campus Arts Initiative and eight partners from across Penn State’s Commonwealth Campuses are partnering to develop temporary works of public art, one at each partner’s site.  The Pennsylvania State University (Penn State) is one of the country's largest public university systems and Pennsylvania's sole land-grant institution. Penn State's community includes 100,000 students across 24 campuses and 17,000 faculty and staff dedicated to making a positive impact on communities around the world. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The projects will result from collaboration between eight artists and the host sites they are partnered with. The exact vision, form, location, installation duration, and materials for the project will be determined by the artist in collaboration with their university partner.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are seeking visual artists or teams that include a visual artist and there are no residency requirements for this opportunity. Professional and emerging artists who are new to the field of public art are encouraged to apply&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY AND CRITERIA&lt;br/&gt;We are seeking visual artists or teams that include a visual artist. There are no residency requirements for this opportunity, but applicants should be aware that the program requires site visits and in-person collaboration with partners. Professional and emerging artists who are new to the field of public art and/or have experience working with students are encouraged to apply. Faculty and students of Penn State University are eligible to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Penn State is an equal opportunity, affirmative action employer, and is committed to providing opportunities to all qualified applicants without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications will be reviewed on the following criteria:&lt;br/&gt;•	Aesthetic quality of previous work&lt;br/&gt;•	Experience working collaboratively&lt;br/&gt;•	Experience working in the public realm or with communities in interdisciplinary settings&lt;br/&gt;•	Quality and completeness of application materials&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT&lt;br/&gt;The participating partner sites are:&lt;br/&gt;•	Center for Performing Arts at Penn State (University Park)&lt;br/&gt;•	LGBTQA Student Resource Center (University Park)&lt;br/&gt;•	Penn State Abington &lt;br/&gt;•	Penn State Beaver&lt;br/&gt;•	Penn State College of Engineering (University Park)&lt;br/&gt;•	Penn State Erie, The Behrend College&lt;br/&gt;•	Penn State Lehigh Valley&lt;br/&gt;•	Penn State Materials Research Institute (University Park)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;These partners will serve on the selection panel, along with representatives from Campus Arts and additional arts professionals. Once each organization is partnered with an artist, the artist will work with stakeholders at the host site to develop a proposal for the design and implementation of a temporary public art project/intervention. The resulting works will be catalysts for community and student engagement, making the arts central to the Penn State experience.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Temporary artworks are expected to be present at the site, on loan, for up to one year. Please note that the purpose of this program is to provide an opportunity for partners and artists to collaborate on developing new ideas for temporary artworks. It is not a funding stream to implement existing plans or concepts for specific works of art. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The selected artists will enter into a contractual agreement with the university and their partner site. This program is supported by a grant through Penn State’s Strategic Planning Seed Grant.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BUDGET&lt;br/&gt;Each artwork has a budget of $7,000. Artists will be asked to generate a budget within this framework that includes an artist’s fee, materials and fabrication costs, site visits, project management, and installation and de-installation of the work. Artists are required to furnish proof of general liability insurance before funds are dispersed. Projects will be considered on loan from the artist for a period of up to one year. Please note that at least two site visits (one initial visit and one during installation) are required.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Partners will select artists with guidance from Campus Arts. Depending on the scale and scope of the proposed collaborations, additional resources may be sought on a case by case basis.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION PROCESS&lt;br/&gt;Campus Arts will facilitate the artist selection process. Qualifications submitted through this RFQ will be reviewed by a selection committee. A limited number of artists will be invited for an interview. Only one artist or artist team will be chosen for each partner site.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;During the interview process, artists will discuss their past work, their ability to work on the project, their interest in this particular project, and their experience collaborating with communities. The artists who are asked to interview for the project will not be asked to develop a model or proposal.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists may interview with multiple partners, but can only be selected for one project. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;br/&gt;Applications will only be accepted electronically through Submittable at &lt;a href="https://hub-robesongallery.submittable.com/submit." target="_blank"&gt;https://hub-robesongallery.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications must include:&lt;br/&gt;1. A letter no longer than two pages describing why you are interested in this project. Include details about one or two of your experiences collaborating or working with communities. Name the letter using this convention: last name_first name_letter and save the file as a PDF.&lt;br/&gt;2. Work samples of past work, up to 10 images and/or videos. Images should be in JPEG format and videos not longer than 3 minutes. Name work samples with your last name, first name, and numbers 1 – 10. For example: Auerbach_Tauba_01, Auerbach_Tauba_02, etc. TIP: please do not include composite images (multiple images in one file).&lt;br/&gt;3. A script that includes a short description of each image submitted. The description should include, as applicable: artwork title, medium, dimensions, budget (if appropriate), and short summary (if appropriate). Save the file as a PDF and name it using this convention: last name_first name_script.&lt;br/&gt;4. A copy of your artist statement. Save the file as a PDF and name it using this convention: last name_first name_statement&lt;br/&gt;5. A copy of your resume, up to three pages. Save the file as a PDF and name it using this convention: last name_first name_resume&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;TIMELINE&lt;br/&gt;February 14, 2019 – RFQ deadline @ 11:59 p.m., E.S.T.&lt;br/&gt;February 21, 2019 – Jury review and selection&lt;br/&gt;March 2019 – Selected artists notified&lt;br/&gt;Fall 2019 – Project completion/installation&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CONTACT INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;If you have questions about this RFQ, please contact Tamryn McDermott, Campus Arts Associate at 814-865-0775 or by email at tlm6018@psu.edu. You can find more information on our website at campusarts.psu.edu and follow us on Instagram @campusarts_psu.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/dd04fff2-708c-4ad9-b7c5-f10f3595f46c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a4188d07-630e-4d77-8581-7be610c892a6</id><title>2/18 - Free Open Call &amp;#39;RECYCLING IS CULTURE&amp;#39;</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488080+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;KENEKTID Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/18/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.kenektid.us/xearth"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York's creative collaboration project agency, Kenektid Inc. challenges to spark new creative projects to recreate our culture that cares humanity and our only home, the Earth.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As the first project, we started an environmental art campaign 'Recycling Is Culture' in New York City. We support one of NYC's mission 'Zero waste to landfill 2020' and this campaign is about showing art pieces to public with the information of what to recycle in NYC.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We opened the Instagram page 'Recycling is culture' as an idea to contribute our talent to support the mission and also help artists and designers be inspired and showcase their works. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We believe the influence of art can help the community to lead the culture and visually emphasize the importance and the effects of recycling. We also wish this art campaign could give valuable influence to next generation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This call is part of the art campaign and the artwork should be created by specific topic and color code.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is an opportunity for artists to experiment with new ideas in the global issue and utilize 'Recycling Is Culture' as a valuable resource.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The works will be exhibited at our gallery space on March 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our long term goal is to present the contributed artworks on the construction fences on the street as recycling the space. New York itself is already a culture, and we sincerely wish that the 'Recycling Is Culture' campaign can elevate NYC's art &amp; culture and positively influence other cities around the globe.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Topic:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The topic should include one of garbage subject and contains NYC's recycling color code; Blue(Plastic, Metal, Glass, Carton), Green(Paper), Grey scale(Landfill).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Topic and color code is based on DSNY's recycle poster.&lt;br/&gt;Please refer to other artists works on our website.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists and designers can submit their works through email, and we post the submitted works to our Instagram account.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You must follow the instruction on our website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;www.kenektid.us/xearth&lt;br/&gt;www.kenektid.us/instruction&lt;br/&gt;Contact: xgallery@kenektid.us&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a4188d07-630e-4d77-8581-7be610c892a6" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>02ad693e-662e-4ef8-a12c-8240553676dc</id><title>3/1 - Annmarie&amp;#39;s Salon des Refuses: A Last Chance Show &amp;amp; Sale</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488050+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Annmarie Sculpture Garden&lt;br/&gt;📍 Dowell, MD, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://annmariegarden.wufoo.com/forms/artist-application-annmaries-salon-des-refuses/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Last Chance Show &amp; Sale for rejects and unsold art!&lt;br/&gt;Exhibit Dates: March 8 - April 22, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline to submit works: March 6, 2019 &lt;br/&gt;Open to all media; must be original work of art&lt;br/&gt;$15 application fee for up to 4 works&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Modeled after the Parisian Salon of 1862, Annmarie's Salon des Refuses, or 'exhibition of rejects', will include works that have previously been turned down by a gallery or show, or just haven't sold. Let's give these rejects, underappreciated, and misunderstood works another chance!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REVIEW - this is NOT a juried show, but we will lightly review all works as they are submitted. Once you apply, please allow 2-5 business days for a decision. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DELIVERY: we expect most artists to hand deliver their art on March 8 for the Artist Hanging Party. If you are not able to attend the party, please arrange to ship or drop your work off by March 6. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT DATES&lt;br/&gt;--Artist Hanging Party &amp; Potluck: March 8, 2019, 12pm-3pm&lt;br/&gt;--Annmarie After Hours Reception: March 8, 2019, 5-8pm&lt;br/&gt;--Exhibit: March 8 - April 22, 2019&lt;br/&gt;--Artwork Return/Pick-up: April 23 - April 28, 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Questions: &lt;br/&gt;art@annmariegarden.org&lt;br/&gt;410-326-4640&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/02ad693e-662e-4ef8-a12c-8240553676dc" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2c2d36de-cf4d-4fcb-816c-94c220127edf</id><title>1/30 - The Body</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.488017+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.sitebrooklyn.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Body&lt;br/&gt;March 15, 2019 – April 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;This is an open call to artists for an exhibition at Site:Brooklyn Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The human body has inspired artists throughout the ages – it was often used to explore myth and allegory, signify beauty, sexuality, or life itself. The twentieth and twenty-first centuries saw a significant expansion of the importance of the body in art. Bodily representation still acts as a repository for beauty, nature, or religious ideas, but it has also taken on new roles. They bear and sometimes thwart identity, are sites of political and social struggle, and are fragmented or unseen.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Benjamin Sutton is an art critic, journalist, and curator who lives in Park Slope. He is the News Editor at Artsy and his articles on public art, artist documentaries, the tedium of art fairs, and art crime have appeared there and in Hyperallergic, artnet, Brooklyn Magazine, Art+Auction, and elsewhere. He has curated exhibitions at the Lower East Side Printshop, Field Projects, the Spring Break Art Show, and the Gowanus Loft.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: December 15, 2018&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: January 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: February 8, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: March 15 – April 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, March 15, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in drawing, painting, printmaking, photography, wall mounted sculpture, collage, and video.&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $35.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by January 30, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:&lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2GnHq3q&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 60” X 60” X 12” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Assemblage, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt; 4. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “The Body” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2GnHq3q" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2c2d36de-cf4d-4fcb-816c-94c220127edf" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>777196fe-5d59-4c0a-b2b3-395a98525af5</id><title>3/3 - Open Call to Artists</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.487988+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Openings Artist Collective&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/03/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.openingsny.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Openings Collective announces an open call for the group exhibition, "The Lovely Wild." &lt;br/&gt;Looking out into a wilderness, not knowing where you are headed, where we are headed.    Artists, if they are to be artists,  must go into that wilderness and have conversations, conversations where all involved are changed such that the wilderness is no longer fearful but hopeful; not a place of terror, but one of peace.    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Artists are asked to submit a detailed proposal for artwork in any medium which explores their interpretation of this theme, addressed either personally, publicly, politically, aesthetically, conceptually, or spiritually. Artwork will be exhibited within the unique space of the interior of the Church of St. Paul the Apostle on the corner of Columbus Avenue and W. 60th Street in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;Artists are asked to submit the following materials:&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;•     Detailed Visual Proposal for The Lovely Wild, which includes clear and descriptive &lt;br/&gt;      text/drawings/sketches/schematics of a proposed artwork for the exhibition or images of finished &lt;br/&gt;      artwork that you are proposing to show. Artists are encouraged to visit the exhibition space within the &lt;br/&gt;      Church of St. Paul the Apostle in advance of sending their proposal.&lt;br/&gt;•     Proposal Statement of 250 words or less (only in .doc or .docx format) describing the proposed &lt;br/&gt;      artwork and how it addresses the theme. No .pdf please.&lt;br/&gt;•     Contact Information: name, address, email, telephone, website URL (only in .doc or .docx format).&lt;br/&gt;•    10 separate jpeg images of recent work (no greater than 800 pixels or 11 inches at 72 dpi). Each file &lt;br/&gt;      must be labeled with title, medium, dimensions and artist’s name.&lt;br/&gt;•     Current CV (only in .doc or .docx format).&lt;br/&gt;•     Artist Statement of 250 words or less (only in .doc or .docx format).&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Submissions that do not follow requested formats will not be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;This call for entries is open to any visual artist over the age of 18. All submissions must be received via email to mail@openingsny.com There is no fee for submitting a proposal; however, we will ask accepted artists to consider submitting a voluntary $25.00 donation. This donation will go towards the cost of promotion, hanging, publicity, and opening reception. Please note that no one has ever been turned away for inability to afford this donation. Artists will be selected by a jury of current Openings members and invited guest jurors from the field. In addition, selected artists are required to sign an exhibition contract and to comply with the terms therein. A release of liability form is also required. Failure to do so will result in disqualification.  &lt;br/&gt;Public contact:  mail@openingsny.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/777196fe-5d59-4c0a-b2b3-395a98525af5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>413c9d2e-3fd2-44e9-a10d-092432aa634c</id><title>3/15 - The 3rd Art Olympia International Open Art Competition</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.487958+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Art Olympia Executive Committee Office&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $60.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://artolympia.info"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art Olympia is an open art competition held as a biennial event with the goal of discovering talented artists from around the world and supporting their art activities. Approximately 160 artworks (80 from Japan and 80 worldwide) will be selected and undergo a final review in Tokyo by a panel of esteemed judges invited from around the world. In addition, 1,000 artists will be honored.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[Entry Locations]&lt;br/&gt;The primary screening will be held at two locations: New York and Tokyo. There will be 80 works selected from each location, which will proceed to the final review in Tokyo. At the final review, 160 artworks will be evaluated to select the winners. The New York-based entry is for artists residing outside of Japan regardless of nationality.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[Awards]&lt;br/&gt;The first place winner will receive $120,000 and 1,000 artists will be featured on the Art Olympia website as well as art magazines.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[Judging Process]&lt;br/&gt;At the primary screening, a panel of five (5) jurors will evaluate the works as digital images in March 2019. Ten (10) jurors will conduct the final review by evaluating the actual works in Tokyo in June 2019. In order to have a fair competition, all artworks will be judged without disclosing the name of the artists. Art Olympia also adopts a clear point system for their judging. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[Jurors]&lt;br/&gt;The following is the list of jurors for Art Olympia 2019. Don’t miss out on this great opportunity to have these esteemed art experts look at your work!&lt;br/&gt;Primary screening jurors for New York Entries &lt;br/&gt;Brett Littman: Director of The Noguchi Museum/New York &lt;br/&gt;Chu Teh-I, Artist: Founder of the Kuandu Museum of Fine Arts/Taipei&lt;br/&gt;Florence Derieux: Director of Exhibition at Hauser &amp; Wirth New York/New York&lt;br/&gt;Emmanuelle Lequeux: Journalist for Le Monde /Paris&lt;br/&gt;Zheng Lin: Founder and Director of Tang Contemporary Art/Beijing&lt;br/&gt;Final review in Tokyo, above plus next Tokyo Jurors&lt;br/&gt;Hiroshi Senju: Artist &lt;br/&gt;Toyomi Hoshina: Vice President of Tokyo University of the Arts &lt;br/&gt;Akiya Takahashi: Director of the Mitsubishi Ichigokan Museum &lt;br/&gt;Yuko Hasegawa: Curator at Museum of Contemporary Art Tokyo &lt;br/&gt;Akiko Endo: Artist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[Entrysite] &lt;br/&gt;http://www.juriedartservices.com/index.php?content=event_info&amp;event_id=1452&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[Entry Rules and Regulations]&lt;br/&gt;Two-dimensional works, representational or abstract; oil,&lt;br/&gt;acrylic, watercolor, pastel, mineral pigments, print, charcoal, digital/multimedia art, mixed media, photography etc. (calligraphy, video,  sculpture,  and  group/collaboration  works  are  not  accepted) &lt;br/&gt;Original works that have never been previously submitted to other competitions (rule offender will be revoked)&lt;br/&gt;Size and weight&lt;br/&gt;Maximum Size: 117cm x 117cm (46 x 46 inch)&lt;br/&gt;Maximum Depth: 10cm (4 inch) (including the frame)&lt;br/&gt;Maximum weight: 20kg (44.1lbs)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[Entry Period]&lt;br/&gt;Entry Period: September 15, 2018 – March 15, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[Eligibility]&lt;br/&gt;Regardless of nationality, you must be a resident outside of Japan and the age of 18 or older for New York entries.&lt;br/&gt;Categories:&lt;br/&gt;- All-Entrants Category: All entrants&lt;br/&gt;- Student Category: Entrants who are enrolled in a university, graduate school, technical school or similar and less than 35 years old at the time of entry.&lt;br/&gt;*Student artists are simultaneously registered in the All-Entrants&lt;br/&gt;Category when they enter the Student Category.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[Entry Fee and Payment]&lt;br/&gt;General submission: &lt;br/&gt;$60 for 1 image, $100 for 2 images, $140 for 3 images&lt;br/&gt;Student submission:&lt;br/&gt;$40 for 1 image, $70 for 2 images, $100 for 3 images&lt;br/&gt;*Student ID will be required for the Student Category prior to the final review.&lt;br/&gt;*Each artist is limited to THREE images.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/413c9d2e-3fd2-44e9-a10d-092432aa634c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c6abf004-ac1d-453d-9819-a87118dfe728</id><title>2/8 - DRAWN: An Exhibition of Contemporary Drawing</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.487929+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/08/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/drawn"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cincinnati based non-profit arts organization and gallery, Manifest, presents an open call for artwork exploring contemporary drawing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DRAWN seeks to survey and present the broad scope of drawing being made today. This gallery exhibit is completely separate from the annual INDA publication project. Artists are invited to submit works of drawing in any media relevant to the practice (including non-traditional approaches), any style, and any genre (fine art, illustration, design, conceptual, realism, etc.).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submissions can range from the most traditional to the most conceptual or experimental. Past exhibit and book participants are welcome and encouraged to submit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNUAL CASH AWARD: The annual Manifest Grand Jury Prize will result in the awarding of one significant cash prize ($2500) to a single work selected as the 'best of the entire season'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To view the full prospectus and to apply, visit &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/drawn." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c6abf004-ac1d-453d-9819-a87118dfe728" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>592c2572-10c4-416c-9764-14eaed973a69</id><title>1/28 - 14C Art Fair - opportunities for artists, galleries and arts organizations</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.487899+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jersey City Arts Council/14C Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 Jersey City, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/28/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.artfair14c.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;14C Art Fair is a new - and mission-driven - art fair, which is an initiative of the Jersey City Arts Council, a 501c3 non-profit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Recognizing that art fairs can be out of reach for small and medium sized galleries, as well as visual arts organizations, 14C Art Fair offers artists and galleries the opportunity to participate at cost.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Held from March 15-17, 2019 on three floors of the Hyatt Regency Exchange Place on the Jersey City waterfront, with abundant mass transit and parking options, exhibition rooms are available for $249/night.  Galleries, arts organizations and individual artists are all welcome to apply for exhibition rooms.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is also a Juried Show that is restricted to artists who live or work in New Jersey, which will be on display in the Penthouse ballroom of the Hyatt.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More information, and FAQs, on our website - artfair14c.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications deadline is January 28, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applicants for either the exhibition rooms or the Juried show should fill out the forms available at artfair14c.com/apply&lt;br/&gt;Juried Show applicants must have an address in New Jersey and can submit 3 images.&lt;br/&gt;Applicants for an exhibition room (approx 360-400 sq ft hotel room) have no geographic restriction, but must submit representative images of the art they plan to exhibit. &lt;br/&gt;Application deadline is January 28, 2019, 11:59PM ET, and the application fee is $35.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is more information and FAQs on our website - artfair14c.com.  Or write to us at info@artfair14c.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/592c2572-10c4-416c-9764-14eaed973a69" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e8745af9-6bb1-4c33-bffa-2d9541ce6366</id><title>2/10 - PACKAGED: Call for Works Made Using (or About) Packing Materials</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.487869+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/packaged"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cincinnati based non-profit arts organization and gallery, Manifest, presents an open call for artwork about or made using packing materials.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The stuff is all around us, to the point of becoming a global bio-crisis, yet at Manifest we have seen sublime and compelling works of art give new life and meaning to such cast-off materials from time to time. Whether through pure recycling of pre-used materials into new forms, by employing them 'virgin' to create art, or by making more traditional work about them, we invite artists to share works of art focused on, created from, or made about packaging materials of any and all types.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All types of work are welcome, including traditional and non-traditional approaches in any media, and any subject, non-objective, abstract, conceptual, etc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists are encouraged to take a broadly creative view of the theme. The artists we invite to jury our exhibits enjoy surprise, creative solutions, and most of all exceptionally well put together visual art. The bottom line is that work must be by, of, or about packaging materials.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNUAL CASH AWARD: The annual Manifest Grand Jury Prize will result in the awarding of one significant cash prize ($2500) to a single work selected as the 'best of the entire season'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/packaged." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e8745af9-6bb1-4c33-bffa-2d9541ce6366" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>091cbba5-9874-4945-b65b-48711c7a32ef</id><title>2/11 - OyG Projects: Open Call for Two Solo Exhibitions</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.487836+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ortega y Gasset Projects&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.oygprojects.com/open-call-2019"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ortega y Gasset Projects is pleased to announce an Open Call for TWO Solo Exhibitions to open in September of 2019: one in the main gallery space at OyG and one in The Skirt, OyG's dedicated space for site-specific installation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Both opportunities will include an opening reception on Saturday, September 14, 2019, $350 honorarium for each artist/proposal, and one programmed event (an artist talk or a closing event), and will be promoted on OyG social media outlets. OyG Co-Directors will work with the artists and make studio visits leading up to the opening of the exhibitions, if possible. The artists are required to fully participate in the exhibitions' installation and deinstallation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Visual artists of all disciplines (and geographical locations) are encouraged to apply. The artists will be selected by the OyG Co-Directors based on the quality of their work and commitment to their practice. Artists are highly encouraged to specify which space they'd like to exhibit in, the main gallery space or The Skirt. The OyG Co-Directors will make the final decision.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An alternate list of candidates/runners-up will be posted on our website and considered for future programing at the gallery. Past/future exhibition artists that we discovered from our past Open Calls include: Patrice Helmar, Jihyun Hong, Familien Iglesias,  Carl E. Hazlewood, Rose Nestler, Norm Paris, Ben Pederson, Padma Rajendran, Adam Liam Rose, Winnie Sidharta and Kuldeep Singh.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To see images of the space:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.oygprojects.com/spatial-specs&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Application opens: January 14, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: Monday, February 11, 2019, midnight&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notification: May 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition install: August 31, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Opening reception: Saturday, September 14, 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition ends: October 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ortega y Gasset Projects is an artist-run gallery founded in 2013, located within the Old American Can Factory building in the Gowanus section of Brooklyn. OACF is a 24-hour access building accessible by the D, R, N, W, F, G trains. For more information about OyG click here. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;OyG Co-Directors:&lt;br/&gt;Eleanna Anagnos (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Clare Britt (Chicago, IL)&lt;br/&gt;Catherine Haggarty (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Eric Hibit (Queens, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Will Hutnick (Wassaic, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Nickola Pottinger (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Zahar Vaks (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Lauren Whearty (Philadelphia, PA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to apply:&lt;br/&gt;https://ortegaygassetprojects.submittable.com/submit/130768/open-call-2019-two-solo-exhibitions-at-oyg-projects&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMAGES:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;10 images of work including: title, year, media and dimensions &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Size requirements:  Images (up to 5MB each), Video (up to 250MB each), Audio (up to 30MB each)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CV:&lt;br/&gt;2 pages max&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;REFERENCES:&lt;br/&gt;Please provide us with two references who can talk about your work and practice: name, title/organization, relationship, email address. We will only contact these individuals if need be.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PROPOSAL:&lt;br/&gt;Please describe your work and what you envision as your solo exhibition. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some things to consider: Why do you want a solo exhibition at OyG? What does this opportunity mean to you? If you're applying for the Skirt, please consider how your work will respond to/interact with the specific space.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(200 words max).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please email oygsubmissions@gmail.com if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/091cbba5-9874-4945-b65b-48711c7a32ef" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>24d458ab-f686-4590-8580-8db43f5a9fe2</id><title>1/25 - LAST WEEK TO APPLY: Superfine! Art Fair | Los Angeles 2019</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.487802+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Superfine! Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 Los Angeles, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.superfine.world/exhibit-la"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rapidly growing art fair takes its tried and true yet untraditional approach to the west coast for the first time next month after reinvigorating the New York, Miami, and Washington DC art markets. Superfine! LA '19 applications officially close this Friday, January 25th, and there are still a small handful of gallery and solo artist booths up for grabs. Here's what's still available:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GALLERIES:&lt;br/&gt;• SIX booths in our Gallery Pavilion ranging from 16 - 32 linear feet of wall ($3,600 - $7,200)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SOLO ARTISTS:&lt;br/&gt;• THREE Elevate/LA Booths: 12-foot artist booths dedicated to LA-based artists ($2,700)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MULTIMEDIA ARTISTS, COLLECTIVES, GALLERIES, + CURATORS:&lt;br/&gt;• ONE A/V Room: 575 square foot room for audio, visual, VR, AR, olfactory-and-beyond projects ($3,000)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! receives frequent and consistent media coverage in outlets like Washington Post, New York Post, and Artnet, and the fair holds the key to the growing, "maturing", and engaged young collector masses. About 20% of visitors make a significant purchase of at least $500, and 90% of past exhibitors report selling to almost exclusively new clients outside of their existing collector network.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! LA will be hosted from February 14-17 at DTLA's familiar Magic Box convention center. Superfine! is an art fair engineered for galleries who recognize a needed shift in the art market and for artists treating their talents as a serious art business.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GET A BETTER SENSE OF THE FAIR:&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! LA on Artnet: &lt;a href="https://news.artnet.com/partner-content/superfine-la" target="_blank"&gt;https://news.artnet.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! NY '18 Recap Video: &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/_vyyZ8LQjOk" target="_blank"&gt;https://youtu.be&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibitor Testimonials: &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/testimonials/" target="_blank"&gt;https://superfine.world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Review our floor plan and decide which available space you would like (link below).&lt;br/&gt;2. Fill out and submit your application (~10-15 min., link below).&lt;br/&gt;3. Email five high-quality artwork images to exhibit@superfine.world (these are only examples for initial promotion, you may show different/more works for the fair itself).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FLOOR PLAN + EXHIBITOR INFO:&lt;br/&gt;https://superfine.world/exhibit-la&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DIRECT LINK TO APPLICATION:&lt;br/&gt;https://na3.docusign.net/Member/PowerFormSigning.aspx?PowerFormId=04ccfe1f-218a-4fee-8b47-af2ce43ec25a&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/24d458ab-f686-4590-8580-8db43f5a9fe2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a79ac1ba-749e-4284-9bc2-faf5931f2a93</id><title>2/8 - Taking Pictures: 2019</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.487767+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/08/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show with an open theme at Black Box Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="http://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a79ac1ba-749e-4284-9bc2-faf5931f2a93" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6c6e7218-1f0b-49ee-97aa-c956b5ace00a</id><title>3/1 - Call for Artists/Designers</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.487723+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Southern Vermont Arts Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Manchester, VT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.svac.org/wilson/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Southern Vermont Arts Center (SVAC) is excited to announce their upcoming exhibition, Unusual Threads: Stitching Together the Future of Fashion, opening on May 11, 2019. This exhibition will explore the future of high fashion in conjunction with practices of sustainability using reused/recycled and organic materials. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SVAC is accepting applications from designers/students/artisans who are creating high-craft/high-fashion, wearable objects (including: garments, accessories, jewelry and/or footwear), or fiber art within the spectrum of reused/recycled or organic materials. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;u&gt;Applicants can choose from the following options:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;1.	Fashion Show only:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt; a.	 At least 3-5 pieces per designer/student in the fashion show &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;2.	Fashion Show and Exhibition:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;a.     At least 3-5 pieces per designer/student in the fashion show&lt;br/&gt;b.	At least 3-5 pieces per designer/student showcased in the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt;(Note: some of the pieces worn in the fashion show may be used in the exhibition after the fashion show)&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;3.	Exhibition only:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;a.	5-8 pieces exhibited in the exhibition for the duration of the exhibition.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please visit our website &lt;a href="https://www.svac.org/wilson/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.svac.org&lt;/a&gt; to apply!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;u&gt;You will be asked to provide the following:&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Full name and contact info (email, address, phone)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Designer/Artisan statement (250 words max) explaining pieces/concept&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Portfolio of 3-5 digital images for consideration in the exhibition. Entries may vary from 2-d concepts/drawings, prototypes, or ready-to-wear pieces (entries should be available for purchase)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Designer bio/resume. Specify your title (i.e. student/designer), what kind of designs you create and where you work or attend school &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Websites, digital media, or social media accounts&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Please indicate which option you are applying for &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;The deadline for applications is March 1, 2019.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit: &lt;a href="https://www.svac.org/wilson/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.svac.org&lt;/a&gt; to complete the application. &lt;br/&gt;Please contact submissions@svac.org with questions. No phone calls please.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6c6e7218-1f0b-49ee-97aa-c956b5ace00a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>be6342a7-8c01-4433-89bc-57ce68618851</id><title>3/10 - OPEN CALL: Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists</title><updated>2019-01-31T19:48:09.487656+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Friend of The Artist&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="friendoftheartist.com/application"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FOA is a publication dedicated to elevating the work of emerging artists around the world. Our publication releases as a hardcover art book every quarter. It includes the work of artists who work in a variety of mediums, informative articles, and interviews. Accepted artists will have a four page spread of their work, information, and artist statement. Volume 9 will be juried by Alice Bonno, Erika B. Hess, Masha Vlasova, and FOA staff.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Volume 9 will be printed in hardback on premium color paper and are available online through booksellers like Amazon, Barnes and Noble, and are available in catalogs for libraries and bookstore distribution.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details of the Volume 9 Open Call:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Winners Receive&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3 works published in Volume 9, complimentary digital copy of publication, social media post of work, Discounts on publications for family and friends, and free digital access to future publications&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$25 for 5 Images&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;March 8, 2019 (midnight, CST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists of all academic disciples are welcome to apply. This includes painting, sculpture, photography, installation, new media, and performance art. Please do not submit videos since we are unable to publish.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guest Jurors&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Alice Bonnot&lt;br/&gt;Erika B. Hess&lt;br/&gt;Masha Vlasova&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Alice Bonnot is an independent curator and art consultant based in London. She is the co-founding director of Picnic, a contemporary art space occupying a long window in the Aylesham Centre in Peckham, London, and the founding director of the Zone d’Utopie Temporaire (Z.U.T.) residency programme, a nomadic annual residency addressing the notion of Utopia as a vehicle for artistic and critical comment. With this residency she curated exhibitions and events in Paris, London, Athens and Lisbon.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As an independent curator Alice organised a broad range of exhibitions for galleries, institutions and artist-run spaces. Her current exhibition Hyper Mesh(18 Jan – 23 Feb 2019) at Assembly Point, London, is an exhibition that brings together new work from eight international artists; Jonathan Baldock, Pauline Bastard, fleuryfontaine, Holly Hendry, Jessie Makinson, Morgan Wills and Fani Parali. The exhibition explores contemporary notions of identity, and sets out to examine how identity structures could be re-imagined or reconstructed. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Previous exhibitions include: Engine, Picnic, London, 2018,Bored but secured, Wozen, Lisbon, 2018,  Acts of disruption, The Concept Space, London, 2018, A series of pocket Utopias, Yellow Brick and Snehta, Athens, 2017, Right Through You, The Koppel Project Hive, London, 2017, Le corps comme activateur d’art numérique, Le Carreau du Temple, Paris, 2015, Prix Canson finalists, Palais de Tokyo, Paris / co-curated with Mr Laurent Boudier, 2015. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Erika B Hess  is a painter based in Columbus, OH recognized for her use and interest in color. Hess’s work has been exhibited nationally including Prince Street Gallery in NYC, Last Projects in Los Angles, CA, and Boston Center for the Arts in Boston, MA. In 2017, she had two solo exhibitions, “The Line Between the Past and the Present,” at the Musa Collective, Allston MA and “Viewing Light,” at Newton Free Library, Newton, MA. Her work has been featured in various publications including, Poets and Artists, Fresh Paint, Charles River Journal and Post Industrial Complex, a book released by the Museum of Contemporary Art Detroit. Her work was selected by John Seed to be featured in, “Fifty Memorable Artists 2015”. She has served on panels such as Cleveland Institute of Art’s, “Feminism Now: Exposing the Truth”, was a visiting juror for Dayton Visual Art Center’s 2016-2018 biennial, and is a recurring juror for the Walker Art MFA Prize at Boston University. Hess is a co-founder of Musa Collective, an artist collective in Boston and is the creator of I Like Your Work podcast, a podcast dedicated to interviewing artists, curators and collectors. Hess received her MFA from Boston University.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Masha Vlasova is an interdisciplinary artist, filmmaker, and educator. She holds a BFA from the Cooper Union and an MFA from Yale School of Art. She is a recipient the Fulbright Fellowship in Filmmaking, Alice Kimball Fellowship and the JUNCTURE Art and Human Rights Fellowship at Yale Law School. Her works have been exhibited and screened at Smack Mellon, Anthology Archives, and Abrons Arts Center in New York, Vox Populi and Temple University in Philadelphia, Carpenter Centerfor the Visual Artsat Harvard University among others. Her latest curatorial project “Women Filmmakers at the Intersection of Documentary, Video Art, and Avant Garde,” premiered at Indiana University Cinema in Bloomington, IN Fall of 2018. Her forthcoming essay about monument rotation will be published in a collection titled Monument Culture: International Perspectives on the Future of Monuments in a Changing World by the American Association for State and Local History/Rowman &amp; Littlefield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at friendoftheartist.com/application&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Email contact@friendoftheartist.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/be6342a7-8c01-4433-89bc-57ce68618851" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>