<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-06T07:17:10-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>44c9da31-f754-4060-bdc1-b415c45d9660</id><title>6/30 - Hudson Valley MOCA Juried Member Exhibition</title><updated>2019-06-06T07:17:10.064101+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hudson Valley MOCA&lt;br/&gt;📍 Peekskill, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.hudsonvalleymoca.org/juried-member-exhibition"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Hudson Valley MOCA Juried Member Exhibition is an opportunity to showcase a variety of perspectives and practices within the contemporary visual arts. Juried by Legacy Russell, Associate Curator of Exhibitions at The Studio Museum, this exhibition seeks to unite a multitude of voices both local and national to explore our contemporary moment, and the unique work created within it. The exhibition will be on view at Hudson Valley MOCA from August 10 to September 8, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: June 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Notification to artists: July 12, 2019 (via email)&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Saturday, August 10, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates:  August 10 - September 8, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Legacy Russell is a curator, writer, and artist. Born and raised in New York City, she is the Associate Curator of Exhibitions at The Studio Museum in Harlem.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Russell’s academic, curatorial, and creative work focuses on gender, performance, digital selfdom, internet idolatry, and new media ritual. She has lectured internationally on the intersection of art, the Internet, and feminism; a selection of engagements include Academy of Fine Arts, Munich, Rewire Festival 2018, IMPAKT Festival 2017, and The London School of Economics. In 2017, Russell hosted the Serpentine Marathon GUEST, GHOST, HOST: MACHINE! in London. Her first book, Glitch Feminism, is forthcoming from Verso Books. Russell’s written work, interviews, and essays and can be found in BOMB Magazine, The White Review, Rhizome, Guernica, Berfrois, Screen Shot Magazine, and beyond.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Russell holds a dual-major B.A. with Honors from Macalester College in Art History &amp; Studio Art and English &amp; Creative Writing with a focus in Gender Studies, and an MRes with Distinction in Art History from Goldsmiths, University of London with a focus in Visual Culture.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRIZES AND AWARDS:&lt;br/&gt;FIRST PRIZE $500&lt;br/&gt;SECOND PRIZE $250&lt;br/&gt;THIRD PRIZE $100&lt;br/&gt;VISITORS’ CHOICE: Upgraded Membership to Benefactor level&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSIONS:  All entries must be submitted online through CaFE, due June 30, 2019: &lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=6568." target="_blank"&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org&lt;/a&gt; POSTAL ENTRIES WILL NOT BE ACCEPTED. Artists must submit between two and four images per entry, but only one entry per artist will be included in the exhibition as selected by the juror. CaFÉ is an online application and jury management system for calls for entry. Visit www.callforentry.org for more information. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: National artists 18 years or older with current Hudson Valley MOCA membership. Original works accepted in all media, executed during the past two years, and never previously exhibited at Hudson Valley MOCA. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEE: A non-refundable $10 fee will be charged for each artwork submitted. Each entry must be paid in full. Check, Visa, Discover, Mastercard, or American Express will be accepted through the CaFÉ site. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MEMBERSHIP: You must have a current Hudson Valley MOCA Membership to be eligible to submit your work. If you are not a current member, Hudson Valley MOCA reserves the right to remove your work from the jurying process with the loss of entry fees as a result. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For membership information, please contact Francesca Ricapito at francesca.ricapito@hudsonvalleymoca.org or (914) 788-0100, or go to hudsonvallymoca.org and see “Membership” under “Support” on the homepage before accessing CaFÉ.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/44c9da31-f754-4060-bdc1-b415c45d9660" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>