<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-30T16:17:01-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>2124ccb2-0d3a-4abc-9590-73bfd381b01b</id><title>6/26 - 2019 LONDON, UK ARTIST RESIDENCY OPEN CALL (ART-LED GRIEF RESEARCH)</title><updated>2019-05-30T16:17:01.361065+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;CENTRE. SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS: Applied Grief &amp;amp; Bereavement Research&lt;br/&gt;📍  , United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/26/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING:&lt;br/&gt;OPEN CALL&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNUM: &lt;br/&gt;2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PARTICIPATING CITIES:&lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For Berlin, Germany deadlines please see our website for more information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;***NEXT DEADLINE - SHORT-TERM RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING***:&lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom Autumn 2019 Residency Cohort 1 (1 Month Program): 03 JUN 2019 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ADDITIONAL DEADLINES - SHORT-TERM RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING:&lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom Autumn 2019 Residency Cohort 2 (1 Month Program): 26 JUN 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS is now accepting applications for residency programming commencing in 2019. Artists, researchers, and other arts professionals are encouraged to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ORGANIZATION:&lt;br/&gt;Established in 2009, the CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS is a Canadian organization dedicated to the development of applied grief and bereavement research. Documented through the use of practice-led methods within art and comprised of work from an interdisciplinary network of creative and technical practitioners; the CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS  is committed to the advancement of the arts and sciences; providing programming in support of education; public and professional engagement; and the development of field research in partnership with local, national, and international academic bodies, institutions, foundations, and non-profits.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION CRITERIA &amp; ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:&lt;br/&gt;The artist-in-residence candidates are selected annually through an open call application process or in some cases, by invitation. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The residency program encourages experimentation and the development of multi/interdisciplinary studio work grounded in research within the field of grief and bereavement. The work can encompass and explore varying physical and emotional processes (or loss) that people undergo. Previous residents and collaborators have undertaken both theoretical-historical and practice-led projects working with, but not limited to the following subject matter: the aging process and the elderly; cancer, disease, and terminal illness; sex work and sexual assault; abortion and miscarriage; suicide and survivorship; mental illness, mental health, and trauma; spousal and familial loss; and associated grief and bereavement-centered themes etc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The residency aims to provide working artistic professionals with a platform for research and production; one that may lead to expanded possibilities, collaboration, a broader network, and possibly new works. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information and to apply please review the Residency Guide and complete an Application Form by visiting:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To be notified of upcoming opportunities including new and existing programming, open calls, and initiatives, please subscribe to our newsletter here:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/contact/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;——&lt;br/&gt;CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS (Est. 2009) &lt;br/&gt;Applied Grief and Bereavement Research&lt;br/&gt;Interdisciplinary/Multidisciplinary Studio &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Follow us here:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/&lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/substructuredloss/&lt;br/&gt;https://vimeo.com/substructuredloss&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and to apply please review the Residency Guide and complete an Application Form by visiting:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The completed application form and all applicable supplementary attachments must be submitted by email.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;——&lt;br/&gt;CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS (Est. 2009) &lt;br/&gt;Applied Grief and Bereavement Research&lt;br/&gt;Interdisciplinary/Multidisciplinary Studio &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Follow us here:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/&lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/substructuredloss/&lt;br/&gt;https://vimeo.com/substructuredloss&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2124ccb2-0d3a-4abc-9590-73bfd381b01b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2f5feeab-a459-4a22-9b01-5b51396e123c</id><title>6/12 - Call for Proposals:  Art on the Beach at Rye Playland</title><updated>2019-05-30T16:17:01.361005+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtsWestchester&lt;br/&gt;📍 White Plains, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/12/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artswestchester.submittable.com/submit/140311/rye-playland-art-on-the-beach-2019-artwork-commission-rfp"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ATTENTION ARTISTS! CALL FOR PROPOSALS! ART ON THE BEACH, RYE, NY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ArtsWestchester, in collaboration with Westchester County and the Westchester Parks Foundation announces a unique opportunity for artists to create a temporary site-specific installation that will activate a former vendor booth on the boardwalk of Rye Beach at Playland Park. Installations can take any form (mural, sculptural, new media etc) and can be interactive. Projects may include community engagement elements and/or interactive components. Artists should consider that the park is a family destination enjoyed by visitors from within and beyond the County. Artwork installation must be completed by July 2, 2019, and the work will be on view through summer 2019. This is a fast moving project, so apply now! For full site and application details, please visit artsw.org/artonthebeach&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RFP Website:                artsw.org/artonthebeach&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist info session:      Monday, June 3, 2019 @ Rye Playland&lt;br/&gt;                                    5:30PM&lt;br/&gt;                                    1 Playland Parkway, Rye 10580&lt;br/&gt;                                    RSVP required to Lhanley@artswestchester.org. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HONORARIUM:            $5,000 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:                Applicants must be at least 18 years old, and live, work, or maintain a studio address in the lower Hudson Valley region of New York, including NYC (all 5 boroughs), Westchester, Rockland, Putnam, Orange, Dutchess, Ulster, and Sullivan Counties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Electronic submissions only.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For all application-related questions, contact: Logan Hanley, ArtsWestchester lhanley@artswestchester.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2f5feeab-a459-4a22-9b01-5b51396e123c" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>