<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-04T00:15:40-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>9fee97b7-4fd7-48d5-b224-a8a9143b5779</id><title>5/1 - OPEN CALL FOR INTERNATIONAL  JURIED PHOTOGRAPHY EXHIBITION - URBAN DANCE: Visual Rhythm of Cities</title><updated>2019-04-04T00:15:40.524821+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LiC-A&lt;br/&gt;📍 LIC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.licartists.org/urban-dance"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call for Photography &lt;br/&gt;Urban Dance - Visual Rhythm of Cities&lt;br/&gt;​Awards:&lt;br/&gt;Jury Prize “Individual Image”: $500&lt;br/&gt;Jury Prize “Series” : $500&lt;br/&gt;4 Honorable Mentions&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Curated by Orestes Gonzalez and John A. Bennette&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition will focus on a selection of images from international photographers interpreting today's urban experience around the globe.  The curators are looking for work that will show a visual score of cities in the 21st century.&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;Curators' Statements:&lt;br/&gt;"Jagged, abrasive, point, twist, turn, leap, sleek glide, humming, recumbent, silence. I think of cities as living, organic beings with movement, songs and rhythm, set against robust geometry and evolving histories. I can visualize not only the noisy cacophony of people, horns, pumping and blasting engines, but also the quiet, shadowy moments of reflection as light and memories soften.  With Urban Dances, we would like to show a visual score of cities in the 21st century." – John A Bennette&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;“Urban centers around the world now house a majority of the worlds population. These divergent cities, vessels of diminishing cultural identities and an ever evolving landscape, hold increasing similarities with each other. We would like to see images that express the dynamism of today's economic, political and technological forces at work. We seek images showing the energy, solitude, individuality, strength, frailties, excesses and isolation of living in today's urban landscape.  We are not looking for the stereotypical, identifiable views of cities and landmarks, but of new interpretations of the power and rhythm inherent in cities at this moment in time.”&lt;br/&gt;– Orestes Gonzalez&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Jurors: John A Bennette, Jonathan Blaustein, Alexa Dillworth, Orestes Gonzalez, Aline Smithson&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please apply by filling out the application at the link below:&lt;br/&gt;http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_urban_dance&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: May 1&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;On View: June 19 - July 21, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: June 19, 6-9pm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To Submit Individual images:&lt;br/&gt;http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_urban_dance_individual_images&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To Submit a Narrative Series:&lt;br/&gt;http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_urban_dance_narrative_series&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9fee97b7-4fd7-48d5-b224-a8a9143b5779" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>