<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-02T07:15:38-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>772e338b-e75c-410f-9e52-c42fa358ea71</id><title>6/1 - CALL FOR ENTRIES: The Fourth No-Boundaries International (Youth) Art Exhibition</title><updated>2019-04-02T07:15:38.287122+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;No-Boundaries Committee, Columbia Global Centers, and Lamont-Doherty Earth Observatory&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.noboundariesartshow.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No-Boundaries Committee, in partnership with Columbia Global Centers and Lamont-Doherty Earth Observatory, Columbia University, has launched the fourth annual 2019 No-Boundaries International Art Exhibitions to foster global awareness and social responsibility in young citizens around the world. The No-Boundaries theme this year is “A Drop of Water”, which encourages exploration of the relationship between human beings and water through art. All youth participants, from kindergarten to high school across the world, are encouraged to submit their artwork. Submissions are currently being accepted until June 1, 2019. There is no application fee.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The selected artworks will be shown in galleries open to the public in the host cities of Beijing, Paris, Nairobi, New York and Rio de Janeiro. The U.S. exhibitions will begin in August 2019 at the Lamont-Doherty Earth Observatory, Columbia University and the United Nations Headquarters in New York, and then travel to other regional hubs through January 2020. Artists will be invited to the exhibition openings after registration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more details about 2019 No-Boundaries:&lt;br/&gt;https://globalcenters.columbia.edu/content/no-boundaries-2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please follow us on:&lt;br/&gt;Facebook: No-Boundaries International Art Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;Instagram: noboundaries_nyc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Groups:&lt;br/&gt;Age Groups: A. Pre-school, B. Elementary Grades 1-3, C. Elementary School Grades 4-6, D. Middle School, D. High School.&lt;br/&gt;Regional Groups: the U.S., China France, Kenya, Brazil and others.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;Materials: Painting, including gouache, watercolor, oil painting, Chinese painting, wood block painting, etc.&lt;br/&gt;Size: The maximum size for each painting is 100CM x 100CM.&lt;br/&gt;Each attendee is allowed to submit up to three art pieces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;How to Apply:&lt;br/&gt;Visit the official site: www.noboundariesartshow.org and click “Application.”&lt;br/&gt;Fill in all required entry fields and upload the photo of your artwork. Please note that the format for the files should be JPG. The minimum resolution requirement is 72dpi. The size of each file should be between 200KB and 5MB, within 7500×7500 pixel.&lt;br/&gt;After submitting your online application, you will see “You successfully submitted! Thank you for your participation.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Group Application：&lt;br/&gt;If you are an educator from schools or organizations and interested in group application, please contact us at info@noboundariesartshow.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About No-Boundaries:&lt;br/&gt;No-Boundaries is a 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization based in New York City. We aim to promote future generations’ global awareness and social responsibility through art education and hone socially responsible global citizens. Since our establishment in 2016, we have held international art exhibitions in China, the United States, France, Brazil and Kenya through the platform of the Columbia Global Centers and the United Nations for three consecutive years, in which more than 20,000 children from 15 countries participated.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/772e338b-e75c-410f-9e52-c42fa358ea71" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>be35b8d5-81be-4649-b4b7-aa1d807c83ae</id><title>4/24 - PARADICE PALASE SUMMER OPEN CALL SHOW</title><updated>2019-04-02T07:15:38.287081+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;PARADICE PALASE&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/24/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.paradicepalase.com/opencall"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARADICE PALASE is excited to announce our 2nd annual summer open call exhibition! This year’s theme is roots, considering works that engage the term in relationship to culture, geography, identity, and community. This year's guest juror is interdisciplinary artist Tiffany Smith. We are seeking works from emerging and underrepresented artists 18 years+ who live in the United States and currently do not have gallery representation. Please read below for the show prompt, full eligibility, and more details, plus how to apply!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried show with a 1st place award of $300 USD plus a 6-month artist membership with us at PARADICE PALASE. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-------&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee: $15  |  $8 for Palase neighbors (see eligibility for details)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline to Apply: Wednesday April 24th, 2019 at 11:59 pm EST&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: May 31st - June 23rd, 2019*&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application &amp; details: www.paradicepalase.com/opencall&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Prompt: &lt;br/&gt;PARADICE PALASE is seeking artwork that responds to this year’s theme of roots, engaging audiences through topics of personal and geographic history, nature, or the environment. To put down roots is a common American expression that directly relates the long-term growth and stability of plants to the same long-term development of human habitats. With a multitude of insinuations, it’s a concept with that is being increasingly challenged in our current sociopolitical global economy. We chose this theme to bring awareness to these faults and consider ways artists dissect this broad but impressionable word. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Acceptable Artwork:&lt;br/&gt;Painting, photography, prints, works on paper, 3D sculpture, fiber arts, sound, and video. All works on paper (including photography) MUST be in a non-ornamental frame - either white, black, or light wood -  unless explicit reasoning as to otherwise can be presented. Explanation can only relate to the content or aesthetic of the work. Artwork must be no larger than 35” in any direction, no longer than 2 min in length, and weigh no more than 20 lbs.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About PARADICE PALASE:&lt;br/&gt;We are a project space in Brooklyn, NY that confronts the limitations of the art world by creating a self sustaining, community-minded and inclusive space. We are dedicated to furthering the development of artists and building a symbiotic network of patrons and creators. We create accessibility in the arts by offering affordable artwork, monthly programs, and membership benefits to our community. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Guest Juror:&lt;br/&gt;Tiffany Smith is an interdisciplinary artist from the Caribbean diaspora, working in photography, video, installation, and design. Using plant matter, design and home decor elements, pattern, and costuming as cultural signifiers, Smith creates photographic portraits, site responsive installations, user engaged experiences, and assemblages focused on identity, representation, cultural ambiguity, and displacement. Visual references from an array of multi-cultural influences, derived from her upbringing between Miami, Florida, Nassau, Bahamas, and Jamaica inform constructed environments that serve to articulate cultural subjectivities that oscillate between visitor and native roles. Smith’s practice centers on what forms and defines communities of people color, in particular; how they are identified and represented, and how they endure. She is a recipient of the 2018 NYFA Fellowship Award and the Bronx En Foco photography award. She has collaborated with non-profit organizations such as Recess Art and is a faculty member teaching photography at SVA. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;Artists 18 years and older living and working within the United States who do not have gallery representation are welcome to apply. Artworks must be an original work produced by the artist applying and must have been completed within the last 5 years. Eligibility for the Palase neighbors fee is current residence for at least 2 years within the zip codes 11207, 11221, and 11233, with proof of address upon acceptance of your application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juried Awards: Best in Show, 2 Runner Ups&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;--Best in Show Grand Prize of $300 plus a 6 month artist membership with PARADICE PALASE ($60 value)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;--Runner Ups each receive a 1 year artist membership with PARADICE PALASE ($120 value each)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*exhibition dates may change or be extended dependent on location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit our website at www.paradicepalase.com/opencall to apply. The form link is at the bottom of the page. You must have a valid gmail account to apply (we use Google Forms)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please also review the TERMS &amp; CONDITIONS and the EXHIBITION CHECKLIST linked on our webpage for further details and artist expectations before completing your application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thanks and good luck! We look forward to reviewing each of your applications.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/be35b8d5-81be-4649-b4b7-aa1d807c83ae" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9f27f090-2e82-48b3-ac09-cc1f9f98713a</id><title>4/30 - PROTO Gallery Open Call for Spring 2018</title><updated>2019-04-02T07:15:38.287023+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Project Studios and PROTO GOMEZ Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hoboken, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://tumblr.projectstudiosllc.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Project Studios Ceramics Residency is a work-only residency focused on exploring ceramics as a medium in contemporary art. Resident artists will have opportunities to create custom glazes, participate in Raku firings, and work with various techniques in clay. Although the focus of the residency is to produce new work in a mostly self-guided manner, there will the availability of consultation and light instruction regarding safe and effective use of the tools and materials within the ceramics studio as well as opportunities for studio visits with other artists and independent curators and area gallerists who often visit the studios. In addition, the Residency offers creative interaction and exchange with other artists working in the Ceramics Studio who will share their knowledge and experience.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The artist chosen for the residency will be awarded a solo exhibition at PROTO GOMEZ Gallery in New York City in fall or winter of 2019. The exhibition will be featured on the PROTO Gallery Artsy page and all social media for PROTO Gallery and PROTO GOMEZ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applicants must apply using our Submittable form at this link:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://protogallery.submittable.com/submit/136974/ceramics-residency-at-project-studios&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that this residency is work-only. We do not supply housing for artists-in-residence.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9f27f090-2e82-48b3-ac09-cc1f9f98713a" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>