<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-30T10:16:19-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>3cd5fd96-8ba8-4ca7-aa76-c4bd9625b2f7</id><title>Call for Submissions: Artists and Curators</title><updated>2019-04-30T10:16:19.580413+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Catskill Art Society&lt;br/&gt;📍 Livingston Manor , NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://catskillartsociety.squarespace.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAS will accept applications from artists and curators in all mediums, including and not limited to digital, fiber, film/video, illustration, installations, performance, pottery and sculpture. Please note artists who presented their work as part of the 2019 season will not be eligible to re-apply until 2021. CAS Arts Center, 48 Main Street will be closed  January through September for renovation and expansion. The Laundry King, 65 Main Street will host the CAS exhibition program during that time. Winter hours will be in effect January through April, with the space open Friday - Sundays, and Monday’s on holiday weekends. CAS Arts Center programming will resume in October. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All proposals will be reviewed by the CAS Artists Council, a newly formed a group of professional mid-career and established visual, literary and performing artists local to the Catskill area acting as stewards and advocates for the organization’s curatorial pursuits in relation to exhibitions, education, programs, lectures and performances.  Artist Council members include and are not limited to Mac Adams, Ellen Brooks, Francis Cape, Carol Hepper, Mary Lucier, Patterson Sims, Robin Winters and Bing Wright. CAS will notify all applicants of the Artists Council’s decision by July 2019.  All work will be considered for solo and group shows at CAS Arts Center or the Laundry King at the recommendation of the Artist Council.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To apply online, please visit &lt;a href="http://catskillartsociety.squarespace.com/2020-exhibition-season-submission-form." target="_blank"&gt;http://catskillartsociety.squarespace.com&lt;/a&gt; Please direct any questions to Sally Wright, Executive Director at info@catskillartsociety.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3cd5fd96-8ba8-4ca7-aa76-c4bd9625b2f7" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>