<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml</id><title>open-calls-7</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>1daffde0-b00c-4670-a5c2-b434c792c004</id><title>1/20 - Digital Twin</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.884134+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Data Through Design&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/20/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://2020.datathroughdesign.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of New York City’s Open Data Week, Data through Design is now accepting submissions for our exhibition. We invite artists, designers, coders, technologists, engineers, architects, and citizens alike to submit their proposals for the event. All submissions should use at least one of NYC’s open datasets, available through Open Data Portal. (https://opendata.cityofnewyork.us/)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The theme of our event will be Digital Twin, a term used to describe a virtual replica of a real world object or phenomenon. Digital twins — avatars, simulation models and artificial intelligence — constitute virtual worlds which can be used to both interpret and shape our reality. How are individuals, societies, cities and natural systems reflected in and impacted by digital worldbuilding? How can they help us better understand ourselves and our reality? On the other hand, how can implicit or explicit bias distort or mislead such efforts, and what are the consequences when we lose control of these digital worlds?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The mission of Data through Design and Open Data Week, a city-wide endeavor by the NYC Mayor’s Office of Data Analytics, is to encourage a wider knowledge of New York City’s open datasets and how these resources can enable better public understanding of what is happening in NYC’s neighborhoods, schools, streets, and parks. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The deadline to submit a proposal is January 20th. Selected artists will be announced by January 27th, and must have their works ready for installation by February 27th. The exhibit will run from February 28th (opening reception) through March 7th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit your proposals here: &lt;br/&gt;https://forms.gle/7nz8pSw7rWChgRaw9&lt;br/&gt;In addition to filling out the form at the link above, please attach the following (upload through the form):&lt;br/&gt;   - A maximum 2-page sketch detailing your idea, its size dimensions, and contextual information for your proposal &lt;br/&gt;   - Your Digital portfolio (either website or PDF)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; The format of submissions is flexible. It is the artist's responsibility to ensure the communication of the art work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions can be directed to: datathroughdesign@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1daffde0-b00c-4670-a5c2-b434c792c004" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8bcb57bb-6116-429e-bfd8-b38ce200a1bc</id><title>1/31 - Call for Artists.  Mother Cabrini Memorial in NYC</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.884106+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;New York State&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/31/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.governor.ny.gov/cabrinimemorial"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governor Andrew M. Cuomo announced the Mother Cabrini Memorial will be placed in Battery Park City's South Cove in direct view of the Statue of Liberty and Ellis Island. The Mother Cabrini Memorial Commission has begun its search for artists who will design and execute the Memorial honoring the legacy of Mother Cabrini. Mother Cabrini founded dozens of institutions that served the less fortunate, including educational organizations and programs to support her fellow Italian-Americans who immigrated to the United States. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Mother Cabrini Memorial Commission will review and select finalists from the submitted proposals and will recommend proposals to the Governor for his final selection. The budget for design and fabrication of the memorial site and artwork is approximately $750,000. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Experienced artists can find guidelines for proposed designs and may submit proposals via this link: &lt;a href="https://www.governor.ny.gov/cabrinimemorial." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.governor.ny.gov&lt;/a&gt; Proposals must be completed and submitted online by Friday, January 31, 2020 before 11:59 pm EST. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Prospective artists may submit written questions and requests for clarifications by Monday, December 27, 2019 to MotherCabriniMemorial@OGS.ny.gov. Responses will be posted on this website by January 8, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SPECIFIC REQUIREMENTS FOR THE MEMORIAL&lt;br/&gt;-Show a life-sized figure (or slightly larger) of Mother Cabrini with two children&lt;br/&gt;-The height of the figure should be between 5 and 6 feet.&lt;br/&gt;-The statue should include a pedestal base (sealed stone) between 3 and 4 feet high.&lt;br/&gt;-The preferred material for the statue, (for longevity and maintenance) is silicon bronze&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION&lt;br/&gt;Artists must email the below submission documents to MotherCabriniMemorial@OGS.ny.gov.  More detail on requirement can be found on the website.&lt;br/&gt;Contact Information (1 page maximum)&lt;br/&gt;Statement of Qualifications (2 pages maximum)&lt;br/&gt;Statement of Intent (1 page maximum)&lt;br/&gt;Presentation of Proposed Concept (3 pages maximum)&lt;br/&gt;Material Selection and Estimated Budget (1 page maximum)&lt;br/&gt;Maximum file size: 10MB&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Maximum pages: 8&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications for the Mother Cabrini Memorial Competition must be submitted by Friday, January 31, 2020 before 11:59 pm EST. Any application that does not comply with the guidelines, file size restrictions, and maximum number of pages will not be considered.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions on requirements or criteria must be submitted to MotherCabriniMemorial@OGS.ny.gov. by Monday, December 27, 2019 at 11:59 PM.  Answers will be posted on the website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8bcb57bb-6116-429e-bfd8-b38ce200a1bc" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1d757f5b-b874-4c1b-a4e1-5d21ed97a7fb</id><title>12/22 - PRINCE STREET GALLERY, NYC /Call for entries/ annual jurried show March 2020</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.884080+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;PRINCE STREET GALLERY&lt;br/&gt;📍 NYC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/22/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.princestreetgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;12th ANNUAL JURIED EXHIBITION -   Juror: Susan Lichtman&lt;br/&gt;Entry Submission Deadline: March 22&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: July 7-25&lt;br/&gt;Open to artists 18+ living in the USA. Original paintings, drawings, prints, and mixed media only.********No giclees, digital prints, videos or photographs will be accepted.******&lt;br/&gt;SIZE LIMIT: 2-Dimensional art,work, including frame, must not exceed 36 inches in any direction. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the juror:  Susan Lichtman is a figurative painter of domestic spaces. She is the Charles Bloom Professor of Fine Arts at Brandeis University where she teaches painting and drawing. &lt;br/&gt;Please visit her website  for more details&lt;br/&gt;Please visit  www,princestreetgallery.com for full details on  juried show&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prince Street Gallery&lt;br/&gt;530 West 25th Street 4th Floor&lt;br/&gt;New York, NY 10001&lt;br/&gt;Tel. 646.230.0246&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Hours:Tuesday – Saturday 11AM – 6PM&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1d757f5b-b874-4c1b-a4e1-5d21ed97a7fb" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>050ccf5c-817c-4127-bc1c-568949c515b6</id><title>1/15 - I Like Your Work Juried Winter Exhibition</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.884052+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I Like Your Work&lt;br/&gt;📍 Columbus, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/15/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.ilikeyourworkpodcast.com/submitwork"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I Like Your Work is an online platform and podcast dedicated to supporting artists by featuring their work and sharing informative interviews. Emerging and mid-career artists are invited to submit their work for consideration to our February 2020 Online Exhibition juried by the artist &amp; curator Kirstin Lamb. International applicants and all mediums accepted. All submissions will be considered to be featured on social media and podcast interviews.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;One artist will be selected to be interviewed on the I Like Your Work Podcast and one artist will be selected to be interviewed by Kirstin and will be published on the I Like Your Work website. Artists who are not accepted will receive a PDF of observations/tips for applying to juried shows written by I Like Your Work Podcast Host Erika b Hess. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;​Deadline: Jan 15, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLY&lt;br/&gt;In order to apply please follow the instructions. &lt;br/&gt;​Please email the following to ilywjuriedshow@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;-3-5 images&lt;br/&gt;-Image list&lt;br/&gt;-CV&lt;br/&gt;- Website Link&lt;br/&gt;-Insta handle link &lt;br/&gt;​Please make sure your Subject Headline is: WINTER 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please format images as follows:&lt;br/&gt;Lastname_firstname_title_medium_dimensions.jpg&lt;br/&gt;Application fee $15. Please pay through the button below.&lt;br/&gt;Please do not send Google Drive Folders or Zip Files. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: Jan 15, 2020&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition will go live: Feb 15, 2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLY&lt;br/&gt;In order to apply please follow the instructions. &lt;br/&gt;​Please email the following to ilywjuriedshow@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;-3-5 images&lt;br/&gt;-Image list&lt;br/&gt;-CV&lt;br/&gt;- Website Link&lt;br/&gt;-Insta handle link &lt;br/&gt;​Please make sure your Subject Headline is: WINTER 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please format images as follows:&lt;br/&gt;Lastname_firstname_title_medium_dimensions.jpg&lt;br/&gt;Application fee $15. Please pay through the button below.&lt;br/&gt;Please do not send Google Drive Folders or Zip Files. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: Jan 15, 2020&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition will go live: Feb 15, 2020&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/050ccf5c-817c-4127-bc1c-568949c515b6" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cf680daf-ce69-412e-a5d2-86ffdaa4763d</id><title>1/6 - Beam Center Seeks Ambitious Project Proposals for the New York City Beam Project</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.884022+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Beam Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/06/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://beamcenter.org/nycbeamprojectproposal"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for proposals for the 2020 NYC Beam Project, a collaborative public artwork project for display in Brooklyn. As the winning designer you and/or your team will work with the Beam Project Team comprised of Beam Staff and Beam Youth to site and fabricate your big idea.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Beam Projects are spectacular collaborations between visionary big thinkers and the Beam Community of youth and creative and technical experts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What we’re looking for in Beam Project Proposals:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Projects coming from creative individuals and teams, including but not limited to Artists, Designers, Architects, Builders, Engineers, Musicians, Fabricators &amp; Technologists who have a connection with Brooklyn.&lt;br/&gt;• Big ideas that culminate in a unique, ambitious, and spectacular artwork in a public space&lt;br/&gt;• Utilize a range of materials and a range of fabrication processes&lt;br/&gt;• Proposals that communicate a clear vision (sketches, diagrams, and other visuals are always helpful) and represent your/your team’s expertise&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Beam Center Disciplines and Facilities include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Full wood and metal shops, equipped with a range of hand and power tools&lt;br/&gt;- Welding facilities&lt;br/&gt;- Textile, dye and sewing stations&lt;br/&gt;- Ceramic studio&lt;br/&gt;- Molding and casting facilities&lt;br/&gt;- Digital Fabrication (CNC routing, Laser-cutting, 3D printing, Vinyl Cutting)&lt;br/&gt;- Audio and Video editing / production&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;New York City Project Call - &lt;a href="https://beamcenter.org/nycbeamprojectproposal" target="_blank"&gt;https://beamcenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposal deadline is Monday, January 6, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://beamcenter.org/nycbeamprojectproposal" target="_blank"&gt;https://beamcenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cf680daf-ce69-412e-a5d2-86ffdaa4763d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4460ec7b-c8ed-4a49-bc73-9c603de258d1</id><title>2/4 - Gesture and Motion</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883977+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/04/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $37.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gesture and Motion&lt;br/&gt;March 20, 2020– April 18, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We understand gesture and motion in the broadest sense of the word; works that capture movement, energy, activity, and develop an active relationship to the world. While the term gestural was first used to describe the painting style of certain abstract expressionists, Site:Brooklyn is looking for works that take this history not as an endpoint, but as a point of departure, considering the subject in pluralistic and open-ended manner. All mediums are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror:&lt;br/&gt;Margaret Carrigan is a writer and editor at The Art Newspaper. She has written essays and reviews for Artsy, Artnet, The Art Newspaper, Cultured, Elephant, Frieze, Galerie, Garage, Hyperallergic, and the Observer. She graduated fromUrbana-Champaign the University of Illinois and received a master's in Art History School of the Art Institute of Chicago. She divides her time between New York and London.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Gallery:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: December 16, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: February 4, 2020 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: February 13, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: March 20, 2019– April 18, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, March 20, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in all media. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Submissions and Fees:&lt;br/&gt;Only original work may be submitted. The fee is $37.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by February 4, 2020 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Directions For Online Submission: &lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2PQ2W2j&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Presentation:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 72” X 60” X 12” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment. No artwork can be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shipping:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring the artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Liability:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Sales/Commissions:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Contact/Questions:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Entry Agreement:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Gesture and Motion” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2PQ2W2j" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4460ec7b-c8ed-4a49-bc73-9c603de258d1" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6ae9c53e-6490-4d5c-bb88-504c05b7e1e2</id><title>1/8 - Wassaic Project 2020 Summer Exhibition Open Call</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883945+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wassaic Project&lt;br/&gt;📍 Wassaic, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/08/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://wassaicproject.slideroom.com/#/Login"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wassaic Project Open Call for our Summer Exhibition for artists of all mediums — 2D, sculpture, video, new media, performance, site-specific pieces, etc. Every May through October, Wassaic Project hosts the work of over 60 artists in our Summer Exhibition. If selected, your work would be showcased alongside a diverse range of pieces and performances in and around historic Maxon Mills.  It is free and open to the public every weekend from May 23 through September 19, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applications are run through our SlideRoom portal. Notification of acceptance will occur within 60 days of the application due date. Accepted applicants will have 7 days to commit to the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PROJECT PROPOSALS&lt;br/&gt;We accept three types of proposals for our 2020 Summer Programming: ready-to-hang work, site-specific installations, and temporary installations/performances. Your application can include multiple proposals.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For all proposals, include:&lt;br/&gt;A formal description of the work you would like to show&lt;br/&gt;A three-sentence conceptual description of the work you would like to show or your artistic practice more generally.&lt;br/&gt;A note about any special circumstances you anticipate around the installation of your work. We have limited equipment available, so we need to know in advance if you require anything specific.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For ready-to-hang work proposals:&lt;br/&gt;Please outline any special circumstances you anticipate around the installation of your work. We have limited equipment available, so we need to know in advance if you require anything specific.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For site-specific installation proposals:&lt;br/&gt;Please include completed past works, drawings and/or style references, and explain how the piece will look or function.&lt;br/&gt;Artists interested in creating a site-specific installation for the 2020 Summer Exhibition are also eligible for an Exhibitions Fellowship to help realize their work. Up to five fellows will be offered a fee-free residency from May 2 to May 31, 2020, and will be considered full participants in our Summer Residency program.&lt;br/&gt;No separate application is needed for the Exhibitions Fellowship, and acceptance of the fellowship — should it be offered — is entirely optional. Artists interested in making site-specific work for the exhibition should still apply regardless of whether or not they are interested in or able to be in residence in May.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For temporary installations or performances for the Summer Festival Program:&lt;br/&gt;Please explain how the piece will look or function.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6ae9c53e-6490-4d5c-bb88-504c05b7e1e2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6f554caf-04b8-4812-a00e-cc272b2a5137</id><title>2/9 - stARTup Art Fair San Francisco 2020: Call for Artists</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883911+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Startup Art Fair LLC&lt;br/&gt;📍 San Francisco, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/09/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.startupartfair.com/artists-page"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;stARTup Art Fair San Francisco is a contemporary art fair for independent artists.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our three-day fair is April 24-26, 2020 at the fun and retro Hotel del Sol, within walking distance to the nearby SF Art Market gallery fair. Exhibiting artists will have a unique opportunity to expose new work to a myriad of collectors, curators, gallerists, art consultants, and writers who will be coming to the city for a weekend of contemporary art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The core mission of stARTup Art Fair is to provide a marketplace that gives artists the power to present and sell work on their own terms. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline to apply is February 9, 2020. Those selected from the open application process will each take over a hotel room for the course of three days to present a solo show of their work. Applicants will have their work reviewed by an impressive Selection Committee of art world professionals:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Andrew Rafacz, Owner Director, Andrew Rafacz Gallery, Chicago&lt;br/&gt;Michelle Nye, Director, SFMOMA Artists Gallery, San Francisco&lt;br/&gt;René de Guzman, Senior Curator of Art, Oakland Museum of California&lt;br/&gt;Danielle Fox, Owner/Director, Slate Contemporary Gallery, Oakland&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At stARTup, you take control of your career and create your own success.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Install your artwork, make your own sales, speak directly to potential collectors and art world professionals and unlike most contemporary artist fairs, and keep 100% of your sales. Exhibitor fees include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	4 nights at the hotel&lt;br/&gt;•	Complimentary fair passes your guests&lt;br/&gt;•	A personal artist page on the stARTup website&lt;br/&gt;•	Discounted valet parking&lt;br/&gt;•	PR, advertising, and marketing through our newsletter, ad buys, and social media channels&lt;br/&gt;•	Curatorial and professional development support in the weeks before and after the fair&lt;br/&gt;•	Automatic acceptance to our leading online sales partner, Artfinder and newest art discovery platform, Wescover&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information please visit: &lt;a href="https://www.startupartfair.com/artists-page" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.startupartfair.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply with a resume, bio, proposal, and 10 images.&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Contact: ray@startupartfair.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6f554caf-04b8-4812-a00e-cc272b2a5137" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3ac6d26b-cf3d-404d-b98a-e51e10f1a917</id><title>1/20 - Torrence Creek Tributary #2 Greenway Public Art Opportunity</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883881+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arts and Science Council&lt;br/&gt;📍 Charlotte, NC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/20/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Arts &amp; Science Council is accepting qualifications from artists/artist teams for a public art opportunity at Torrence Creek Tributary #2, Huntersville, NC.&lt;br/&gt;The selected artist will work with the ASC, Mecklenburg County Park and Recreation, Dewberry Design-Builders, Inc., and the local community to create an impactful artwork that responds to the parameters of the site and the themes identified by the project team. The programmable, permanent light installation should increase visibility and improve pedestrian security throughout the 300-foot tunnel. The minimum light level requirement is 200 lumens. The design should transform the underpass into a dramatic and lively suburban experience through the use of interactive and animated colors or patterns of varying intensity throughout the tunnel. The artwork should encourage the use of the Torrence Creek Greenway by those who live, work and play and in area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the complete RFQ, please visit: &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.artsandscience.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3ac6d26b-cf3d-404d-b98a-e51e10f1a917" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f35d89e0-dc63-45a1-92e6-4e8c35170202</id><title>1/10 - Black and White: 2020</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883849+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/10/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on black and white photography at Black Box Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f35d89e0-dc63-45a1-92e6-4e8c35170202" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cd15639b-0e8c-40ba-a7d8-c87edfdb2693</id><title>2/3 - Craft in Contemporary Art</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883818+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/03/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $37.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Craft in Contemporary Art&lt;br/&gt;March 20, 2020– April 18, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The marriage of craft and art-making is one of humanity's earliest moments. From the Neolithic period onwards, textiles, metals, glass, stone, and other materials were laboriously and carefully woven into images and figures, marking the intersecting and complex paths of commerce, religious and domestic life, and the arts. The Industrial Revolution begin the mass manufacture of textiles, making them available to ever larger swaths of society. These materials and methods have been increasingly integrated into the fine arts, creating a flourishing and exciting conjunction. What is the place, and future of craft in contemporary art? Site:Brooklyn is looking to answer this question, with works that range across all styles and mediums.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror:&lt;br/&gt;Samantha De Tillio is a curator and writer specializing in modern and contemporary craft. She is Assistant Curator at the Museum of Arts and Design, where her upcoming exhibition Beth Lipman: Collective Elegy (May 14, 2020 to March 28, 2021) is the artist’s first midcareer survey. She is also a Contributing Editor for GLASS: The UrbanGlass Art Quarterly and her ongoing personal research includes the first in-depth study of the life and fiber sculpture of Dorian Zachai (1932-2015). She has worked at the Metropolitan Museum of Art, the Smithsonian National Museum of American History, the Thomas Cole National Historic Site, and the Albany Institute of History and Art in various curatorial and research capacities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Gallery:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: December 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: February 3, 2020 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: February 12, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: March 20, 2019– April 18, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, March 13, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in drawing across all mediums. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Submissions and Fees:&lt;br/&gt;Only original work may be submitted. The fee is $37.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by February 3, 2020 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Directions For Online Submission: &lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/36zTeaK&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Presentation:&lt;br/&gt;1. All artwork must be suitably presented to a professional standard.&lt;br/&gt;2. The artist needs to provide a method for displaying the artwork such as a plinth, stand, wall shelf or bracket plus all hardware for attachment into the wall or ceiling.The gallery ceiling height is 18’. The gallery has some pedestals.&lt;br/&gt;3. Artists provide complete instructions for installation and/or assembly and may be required to assist on the installation of their artwork upon the gallery’s request.&lt;br/&gt;4. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shipping:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring the artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Liability:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Sales/Commissions:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Contact/Questions:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Entry Agreement:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Craft in Contemporary Art” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/36zTeaK" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cd15639b-0e8c-40ba-a7d8-c87edfdb2693" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>bc916ccc-e398-47f2-ac6e-5ec0cc8bc08b</id><title>12/20 - Open Call for Midnight Moment—chance to show moving-image art on 60+ screens in Times Square!</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883792+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.TSq.org/Arts"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts invites you to submit original moving-image artwork to Midnight Moment, the world’s largest, longest-running digital art exhibition synchronized on electronic billboards and newspaper kiosks throughout Times Square nightly from 11:57pm to midnight. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for submissions: January 20, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Learn more about submission guidelines here: TSq.org/MMSubmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open applications for the Midnight Moment program are accepted through the online Slideroom portal. Please review submission guidelines and access the portal here: TSq.org/MMSubmission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have any questions about your proposal, please email arts@tsq.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/bc916ccc-e398-47f2-ac6e-5ec0cc8bc08b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>65728207-4b02-4901-b0bf-7f13904eea0a</id><title>12/22 - Call for Artists at the Oculus at the World Trade Center</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883765+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;MvVO ART&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/22/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="www.mvvoart.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested in having your BIG screen moment? Interested in having your Art viewed by over 10 million people? Interested in showing your Art in New York city without the need to necessarily travel all the way here?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After a successful debut at Sotheby's in 2018, AD ART SHOW is BACK in a BIG WAY. During Frieze Art week (May 2020), AD ART SHOW will be showcasing artists from all over the world on the monumental SCREENS at the Oculus at Westfield World Trade Center, one of the most famous architectural landmarks in New York City. The show is on for the whole month of May! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is easy to apply. All you have to do is to submit 4 images of your Art (submit your photography or a photo of your painting, mixed media...think Instagram- what would you post on Instagram). Our renown Art selection committee will review it and if you are selected then you will be part of the show. (no commercial work please- only your fine Art).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is a selling exhibition (fees apply).&lt;br/&gt;Fortune favors the bold!! check it out.&lt;br/&gt;Go to www.mvvoart.com for details and application and to check if you qualify.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thank you. &lt;br/&gt;MvVO ART team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Access application via www.mvvoart.com. This is a selling exhibition (fees apply)&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/65728207-4b02-4901-b0bf-7f13904eea0a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>009ffba4-d4fe-4ad2-9e52-2e8ed0fe8009</id><title>12/21 - OPEN CALL - Race and Revolution: Home/Land Exhibition</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883735+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Lewis Latimer House Museum&lt;br/&gt;📍 Flushing, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://lewislatimerhouse.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call for Artist Submissions&lt;br/&gt;Race and Revolution: Home/Land&lt;br/&gt;A contemporary art exhibition at the Lewis Latimer House Museum&lt;br/&gt;Opening: February 8, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION DEADLINE: 11:59PM on Saturday, December 21, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Curator: Katie Fuller&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“ . . . he who has the power, and is inhuman enough to trample upon the sacred rights of the weak, cares nothing for race or color . . .” &lt;br/&gt;William Craft, escaped from slavery in Georgia in 1848. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;“These aren’t people. These are animals.” &lt;br/&gt;Donald J. Trump on immigration, 2018&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;    &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Race and Revolution: Home/Land, the fourth art exhibition in a series that confronts historical patterns of systemic racism in the United States, is putting out an open call to emerging artists of all media whose work relates to and engages in conversation with the themes related to the enduring impact of government-sanctioned family separation, bounty hunting, and detention for border crossing. For the open call, we would like to view completed works that address this topic and/or proposals for work related to the topic. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Home/Land will look at the influence of the Fugitive Slave Act of 1850 on Lewis Latimer’s family, focusing on the tactics used to detain, deport, and re-enslave “runaways” with current practices used by Immigration Customs Enforcement to control the influx of immigrants, refugees, and asylum seekers. The exhibition will pair true stories of those who escaped or attempted to escape slavery in the years surrounding the Fugitive Slave Act of 1850 with current experiences of families attempting to migrate to the United States with the hope of finding a home in the land of the free. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Eight to ten artists will be given access to primary source documents from the past to create works that show a connection between then and now. Basing their art pieces on families’ migration journeys and their encounters with ICE brings the pain of the past into the present. Excerpts from historical documents: runaway slave ads, letters, journal entries, will be posted on the wall next to the art piece. Displayed together, the documents and the artworks will ask viewers what, if anything, has changed regarding how this country treats humans labeled as “illegal”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thematic Questions&lt;br/&gt;●What does “home” mean?&lt;br/&gt;●What is the relationship between one’s home and one’s homeland?&lt;br/&gt;●Do you think a home and a homeland is a human right? &lt;br/&gt;●How can we, as informed people, condemn how enslaved people seeking freedom were treated as a result of the Fugitive Slave Act, yet continue to dehumanize people who are seeking better lives for their families?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS:&lt;br/&gt;Projects in all media are welcome (though see “exhibit specifications” section below for specific requirements). We are also open to temporary indoor or outdoor event proposals that engage with this theme, from both artists and community organizations. Artists are especially encouraged to propose community workshops that complement artwork on view in the gallery (as opposed to stand-alone events).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;TO SUBMIT: Please email ONE PDF file with all requested information including images/videos or links to images/videos to info@lewislatimerhouse.org under the title “Home/Land Submission.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Brief description (approx. 1 paragraph or 500 words) of proposed project–please address how it engages the exhibition theme!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;● Up to 10 images/videos of the proposed project and/or related work, or send links to images/videos online. Sketches of proposed new work are ok. Please attach a work sample script explaining the content of the work samples, or link to captions online. NOTE: if you are proposing a public program/performance, please share info on any related programs/events you have previously produced.&lt;br/&gt;● Funding request (if any): The Lewis Latimer House Museum is dedicated to offering at minimum a $150 honorarium for all participating artists. Additional funds may be available, especially to cover materials/transport costs for new and site-specific work.&lt;br/&gt;● Attach or link to artist resume or bio&lt;br/&gt;● Please title the email subject line with “Home/Land Submission”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;** Artists/organizations are highly encouraged to visit the Lewis Latimer House Museum exhibition space (see below) and to contact the curator in advance to discuss ideas or to arrange a studio visit. As an exhibition space, the house is unique. The artwork will be displayed in the first-floor parlor rooms, the room currently used for public programs and workshops, and the Museum garden. There are existing artifacts and relics in some of the artwork display areas, so it is strongly suggested that you visit the space prior to submitting a proposal.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/009ffba4-d4fe-4ad2-9e52-2e8ed0fe8009" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d7a65c8c-9eee-4adf-bdf7-cd33a28c3de3</id><title>2/2 - Call for Women Artists</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883706+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia , PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/02/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://createmagazine.com/callforart"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine is pleased to announce an international open call for women artists. We are passionate about highlighting work by contemporary female (identifying as female) creatives and are dedicating the spring 2020 edition to this group. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUEST CURATOR: LIEZEL STRAUSS | FOUNDER OF ART GIRL RISING AND CO-FOUNDER OF SUBJECT MATTER ART&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;South African-born Liezel Strauss is passionate about addressing the under-representation of women artists across the art world and in 2018 the idea for Art Girl Rising sparked. Her creative endeavours span four continents over a decade and she has spoken widely on the positive value of art around the world. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Liezel is also the co-founder and director of Subject Matter and in 2019 was named one of UN Women's top 100 female innovators worldwide, as part of their She Innovates Global programme. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT CREATE! MAGAZINE&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We connect our artists to a larger audience by featuring work in international print issues, our website and social media platforms.Create! Magazine promotes fresh, unique contemporary art from around the world. Each issue is filled with vibrant art, craft, design, and inspiring stories of the makers behind it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY: All international artists 18 and older who are female or identify as a female are welcome to apply with works in any medium: painting, sculpture, digital, printmaking, fiber, photography, mixed media, installation and more. A university degree is not required to participate in our open call.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION FEE: $35 for 3 individual artwork images&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS: 3+ jpeg images of individual artworks, a text (word or text) document with a bio and artist statement, website or social media link, and your email address. Please see our Submittable form for further details.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTISTS: If your work is selected by our guest juror, you will receive a custom designed two-page spread in both the print and digital versions of the magazine that will include your artist biography, website, and two images. Published artists will be sent a complimentary digital issue and will be listed as a participating artist in your issue on both our website and social media. We also promote artists individually via blog and social media posts that reach over 125,000 total followers worldwide. All featured artists will automatically be considered for any upcoming curatorial projects, not limited to art fairs, exhibitions, and gallery projects organized by our team.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHERE TO FIND: Print copies of Create! Magazine are available in our online shop and at several global retail locations in London, New York, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Chicago, Amsterdam, Stockholm, Ft. Lauderdale, Wilmington (DE), and more. Digital issues can always be purchased on our website.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: February 2, 2020 (Midnight EST)&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d7a65c8c-9eee-4adf-bdf7-cd33a28c3de3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6dd55b68-5cd6-48cc-b238-415ce165e511</id><title>1/20 - Viridian Artists presents: &amp;quot;30 Under 30&amp;quot;</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883679+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Viridian Artists&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/20/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.viridianartists.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Viridian Artists presents:"30 Under 30"&lt;br/&gt;Juried by Kelly Kivland Curator, Dia Art Foundation&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: February 18-March 7h, 2020: Reception, February 20, 2020, 6-8pm&lt;br/&gt;Submission Guidelines: &lt;br/&gt;Any media, no larger than 30″ in any direction is welcome. &lt;br/&gt;Artists must be under 30 years of age.&lt;br/&gt;$30 for 3 images&lt;br/&gt;$5 for each additional image&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: January 20th, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Artists will by notified January 20th, 2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send your entries to :&lt;br/&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=7321&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6dd55b68-5cd6-48cc-b238-415ce165e511" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>efde0ece-f4fb-4527-a545-1131ad3b7f7c</id><title>1/9 - BRIC ArtFP</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883650+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;BRIC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/09/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $5.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.bricartsmedia.org/artist-opportunities/exhibition-open-calls/artfp"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BRIC ArtFP is an open call initiative led by BRIC’s Contemporary Art program, where local artists receive honorariums and production fees for exhibition of their work in the Project Room or Hallway spaces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION TIMELINE:&lt;br/&gt;Application Period: November 9 - January 9, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Finalists will be contacted: March 2020&lt;br/&gt;For projects being exhibited: Fall 2020 - Spring 2021&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTISTS WILL RECEIVE:&lt;br/&gt;An honorarium + production fees&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition space in either the Project Room or Hallway space of BRIC House&lt;br/&gt;Technical and installation support&lt;br/&gt;Artistic mentoring&lt;br/&gt;Marketing and promotional support&lt;br/&gt;Photography of exhibition&lt;br/&gt;Opening reception&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION CRITERIA&lt;br/&gt;We are looking for Brooklyn or New York City-area visual artists who are developing new work that is relevant to diverse Brooklyn audiences. Projects will be chosen through a panel review that will include previous ArtFP artists and BRIC staff. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SPACES:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PROJECT ROOM&lt;br/&gt;Location: The Project Room is a separate small gallery adjacent to the main gallery at BRIC House that focuses on highglighting a body of new work. &lt;br/&gt;Dimensions: 24 x 12 ft.&lt;br/&gt;Duration: 6 weeks&lt;br/&gt;Honorarium and Production Fees: $1000&lt;br/&gt;Installation: 2 days with an art installer.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HALLWAY&lt;br/&gt;Location: A highly trafficked but not completely white-box space, Hallway commissions provide space to create wall and ceiling-based installations. We seek artists for the Hallway who are excited by the opportunity to share their work in a public-facing alternative space. &lt;br/&gt;Dimensions: 55 running ft.&lt;br/&gt;Duration: 8-12 weeks&lt;br/&gt;Honorarium and Production Fees: $1000&lt;br/&gt;Installation: 2 days with an art installer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;br/&gt;To apply for the BRIC ArtFP, please fill out and submit the online Application Form via SlideRoom. Link available on BRIC's website: &lt;a href="https://www.bricartsmedia.org/artist-opportunities/exhibition-open-calls/artfp." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.bricartsmedia.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/efde0ece-f4fb-4527-a545-1131ad3b7f7c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cbd7d6d4-7b3a-4964-8d32-ded33b12138c</id><title>12/20 - Call for Artists - Get featured in Artqol Magazine</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883620+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Artqol&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artqol.com/magazine-call"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get featured in the next publication of Artqol Magazine.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artqol Magazine is a collection of stories behind artists and their works, promoting its contemporary artists and curator members, with focuses on conceptual, expressive, social, political and environmental art practices.  The magazine is digitally distributed directly to international art professionals, including curators, artists, galleries and art institutions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application deadline for the next publication:&lt;br/&gt;December 20th 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The magazine is exclusive for Artqol members.&lt;br/&gt;To Join: www.artqol.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists receive a nice spread including introduction, images and Q&amp;A. &lt;br/&gt;Take a look at the recent publication: artqol.com/art-magazine&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cbd7d6d4-7b3a-4964-8d32-ded33b12138c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2934c740-c986-4344-9772-7b36412fc8ca</id><title>3/1 - AT THE 17th ARCHITECTURE VENICE BIENNALE SUMMER SCHOOL IN CURATORIAL STUDIES VENICE OPEN CALL</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883583+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;School for Curatorial Studies Venice&lt;br/&gt;📍  , Italy&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/01/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $4500.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.corsocuratori.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd June – 1st September 2020&lt;br/&gt;The School for Curatorial Studies is an ambitious and challenging project promoted since 2004 and conceived as a school committed to experimentation and interdisciplinary thinking. The main goals are to spread the knowledge in the field of visual arts and to introduce the students to the professions related to the art world, focusing on contemporary curatorial theory and practice and contemporary museology. The School’s activities are meant for all those interested and passionate in art, graduated students or professionals who want to deepen their knowledge and improve their practical skills. The School’s teaching staff is formed by Italian and international professionals, scholars, historians and art critics of recognized experience. Among them: Matt Williams (curator), Filippo Lotti (Sotheby’s), Chiara Barbieri (Peggy Guggenheim Collection), Francesca Colasante (Pinault Collection), Andrea Goffo (Found. Prada), Nicola Lees (Serpentine London).&lt;br/&gt;The program:&lt;br/&gt;The Summer School in Curatorial Practice will take place during the 17th International Architecture Biennale Venice. With an interdisciplinary approach, the course provides practical training and experience within museums and exhibition settings. Its international faculty includes curators and museum professionals, artists and critics. The course is designed to increase students understanding of the intellectual and technical tasks of the curator figure. English-taught lectures cover both theoretical and practical topics that go from the history of contemporary visual arts and practices of exhibition-making, to Exhibition Management. The students will participate in weekly activities, such as artist studio visits, tours of exhibition spaces, networking events and workshops. The program culminates with the set up of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;The Summer School includes visits of specific art venues all over the city of Venice during the 17th International Architecture Venice Biennale. A series of selected case studies will offer the students an opportunity to observe the development of contemporary art. The School’s goal is to align these specific theoretical lectures with a practical approach. Besides the theoretical lectures, a series of laboratories and workshops aims to introduce the students to the work of critical text writing, press releases and to structure all the different aspects of publishing. The students will be offered the possibility of a gallery training and of setting up together - with one of our tutors, their exhibition in Venice, as a final project of the course.&lt;br/&gt;The first module:&lt;br/&gt;June 3rd – August 5th, 2020&lt;br/&gt;The first module involves 350 contact hours:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. History of Curatorial Practices&lt;br/&gt;2. Exhibition Design&lt;br/&gt;3. Aesthetics and Cultural Theory&lt;br/&gt;4. Contemporary Art History&lt;br/&gt;5. Cultural Events Management and Organization&lt;br/&gt;6. Curating Exhibitions&lt;br/&gt;7. Fine Arts Management.&lt;br/&gt;8. Fundraising and Marketing / Workshop&lt;br/&gt;9. Communication Strategies and Artistic Events Promotion / Workshop&lt;br/&gt;10. Workshop on Critical Writing&lt;br/&gt;11. Artist Studio Visits and Visits of the 17th International Architecture Biennale&lt;br/&gt;Optional: Trip to an European art capital.&lt;br/&gt;August 7th –12th, 2020&lt;br/&gt;We warmly recommend to take part. &lt;br/&gt;Visit of an art city with many opportunities: private galleries, collectios. We will visit artist studios and public galleries and Museums of contemporary art. &lt;br/&gt;The second module:&lt;br/&gt;August 17th – 21st, 2020&lt;br/&gt;The second module is dedicated to individual researching and finalizing the exhibition project. During this period of time the students will have to face practical duties, such as coordinating the artists, managing transportation and insurance policies, promoting and curating the promotional material. &lt;br/&gt;The third module: &lt;br/&gt;August 24th - September 1st, 2020&lt;br/&gt;The last part of the course lies in the production of the event. During this period of time all the work concerning the final event will take place. The students will coordinate the arrival and the display of the works of art and supervise all the different aspects related to the event, such as promotion, organization, last details about the publication, opening. After the presentation to the public, the student will be given the tools to professionally document the event.&lt;br/&gt;Duration and structure&lt;br/&gt;The course has a duration of 450 hours. The participants will develop themes as well as concepts, organization, acquisition, communication and the concrete implementation of their skills together with the course director and international guests (artists, curators, architects, critics, fine arts scientists and publishers of art journals).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application deadline: March, 1st 2020.&lt;br/&gt;The application form must be sent by e-mail before the deadline (March 1st  2020) of the Curatorial Program to:&lt;br/&gt;Xac – School for Curatorial Studies&lt;br/&gt;San Marco, 3073, 30124 Venice&lt;br/&gt;Email: curatorialschool@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;Tel: +39 0412770466&lt;br/&gt;The application form can be downloaded at www.corsocuratori.com, where you can find more information about our curatorial program and your stay in Venice.&lt;br/&gt;The Summer school has a limited number of places available.&lt;br/&gt;Information:&lt;br/&gt;info@corsocuratori.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2934c740-c986-4344-9772-7b36412fc8ca" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>66251374-d227-4de2-9eec-5467144598f9</id><title>12/15 - ACCEPTING CURATORIAL APPLICATIONS | SPRING/BREAK Art Show NYC + Los Angeles 2020</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883528+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SPRING/BREAK Art Show&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $150.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.springbreakartshow.com/2020-application/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SPRING/BREAK Art Show is accepting submissions by curators until December 15, 2019*, midnight (your time), for the upcoming 2020 New York City and Los Angeles exhibitions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*This is our late application deadline. Regular applications were accepted until November 22, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2020 THEME | IN EXCESS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“The more the merrier.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;                          - Traditional&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The term ‘tipping point’ is used frequently in current affairs in regards to a variety of topics. Environmental extinction predominantly first and foremost, but also resumed economic stability, political divisiveness, information overloads, cancel culture mania, all are together thought to be at every manner of places along an axis of toppling the heck over, with varying ideas circulated as to which side of their scales are too overstuffed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art and entertainment feel indistinguishable from one another, piled together as “content”, which is consistently billed as in overwhelming supply from creators both amateur and professional; News peppers everyday moments through our devices’ push notifications and peer updates; tech-aided romantic possibilities appear infinite, as do all the other seductions of a globalized world—people to meet, people to follow, things to buy and eat and do. (Should one be able to afford it…For better or worse, then, the ‘too much’-ness of everything is certainly on the mind. In line with these grumblings of overmuch, SPRING/BREAK Art Show 2020 seeks similar inquiries into the paradoxes and nuances of ‘more’. For both upcoming New York and Los Angeles shows, IN EXCESS is actively searching for exhibitions dealing with virtues and/or limitations of maximalism, materialism, digression, hysterical realism, capitalism, encyclopedii, redundancy, consumerism, the over-foot-noted and the overlabored. Submissions may or may not include touchstones on multimedia, multiracial, or multiverse theories and perspectives; environmentalism, globalization, and future shock; the baroque, the Simulacrum, the epic, human play, the hall of mirrors, or any manner of other meditations on the Anthropocene and its anxieties; and, maybe—where we can find them—joys.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The pleasure of ‘more is more’ may be explored through the joyously overindulged overabundance of ideas, forms, perspectives. Aesthetically, ‘the bigger, brighter, busier, the better’ was once the zeitgeist with the intent to create, not a nauseous geegaw of consumer pleasures, but an impression that rattled complacency—generating, instead, awe, surprise, wonder; a sense of the infinitude of our World. Where is our awe now in all this excess? Where is the new Rocaille? Is it any good? Is it a spectre of Greed or Good? How much is not enough, and when is too little too soon?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;References in the current and former art landscape include, but are not limited to, Peter Saul’s rambunctious hypercolor paintings of interwoven political brutality, Joyce Kozloff’s reframing of “women’s work” in her P &amp; D movement pieces and their extension over into, and reframing by, artist Liz Collins, William Powhida’s art world cartography of complicit capitalism. Marco Brambilla crafts sprawling video pop cultural hells and heavens, packed with re-appropriated movie characters all fighting each other for a place in the pantheon, Mickalene Thomas constructs dizzying pastiche domiciles where tactile textiles, personal experience, and the figure from memory converge, authors like Thomas Pynchon and Zadie Smith jam-pack characters into stories teeming with a dance of detritus both intimate and historical; Stan Brakhage deploys the barrage for the sake of recalibrating our vision, Anselm Kiefer, with his fussy gigantic meditations, employs scale to save our soul. Robert Breer’s lightning speed animations stagger in their short running time pummel, Azikiwe Mohammed toils to find overstocked thrift store tapestries of Black utopias, and for Alison Zuckerman, art history, digital self-documentation, and Photoshop fiddling all find themselves locked, arm-in-arm, in triplicate.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Wilde suggested moderation in art and life was a fatal thing. But how does it support or subvert our consumptive excesses? Like Gittes once said to Mulwray, “how much better can you eat? What can you buy that you can’t already afford?”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;People, go for baroque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION GUIDELINES + CURATORIAL REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There are separate applications for the New York City and Los Angeles shows. Please note that curators may apply to both the New York City and Los Angeles shows and will need to submit separate applications for each show to be considered for either and/or both. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications will be accepted by independent curators, galleries and non-profit organizations during the late application period between November 23 - December 15, 2019. The online application form will be available during those dates until December 15, 2019 at 11:59pm your time. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;No proposals nor applications will be accepted via email.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Please note that "Late Applications" are reviewed in the same manner as "Regular Applications". We do not prioritize applications based on when they were submitted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION FEE&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is a non-refundable late application fee of $150.00 per application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our mission is to create an unique environment for showcasing independent curators by providing free exhibition space to each selected curator, and therefore, require an application fee to cover our administrative fees for processing the applications.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHO MAY APPLY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1) INDEPENDENT CURATORS: Independent Curators may submit an application for the 2020 SPRING/BREAK Art Show, including a curatorial proposal related to the theme of IN EXCESS, sample images of art work, a curatorial statement and additional information necessary to complete the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that an artist may apply as an Independent Curator only if they are applying with a group show or a solo show of another artist's work. An artist may not apply with their own art work in a solo show, but must have a curator who applies on behalf of him/her/they.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is NO FEE for the exhibition space if you are selected as an independent curator.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2) GALLERIES + PROJECT SPACES + NON PROFIT ORGANIZATIONS: Applicants affiliated with a gallery or project space/non-profit organization may submit a curatorial proposal comprised of artists from the gallery's roster and this curatorial proposal will fall into our SPECIAL PROJECT section. If you have an affiliation with a gallery, project space or non-profit organization, please define your affiliation/title and include the full roster of artists in the application below for our reference.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Special Project section was initiated in 2015 as a way to invite established, new and recently closed galleries to participate in the show. We encourage participants in the Special Project section to explore the theme in full and to go beyond what they typically would do in a traditional art fair environment. In 2019, there were 26 Special Projects as part of the program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each Special Project contributes a fee to participate, which helps to cover the production costs of the event.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information on applying at an Independent Curator, Gallery or a Non-Profit Organization, please visit our website for more details:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;http://www.springbreakartshow.com/2020-application/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED CURATORIAL APPLICATIONS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission of an application does not guarantee participation. We will review applications in December and notify selected curators by the beginning of January, if not before. If we have any questions about your proposal, we will contact the primary curator listed on the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each curatorial proposal will be given one (1) room/space for exhibiting artworks. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected curators will receive a consignment agreement to review and complete. All artworks included in the show must be included in and subject to the terms of the consignment agreement. Artworks that are not listed on the consignment agreement will not be permitted on the show premises. If you have any questions about the consignment terms, please contact us for details.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/66251374-d227-4de2-9eec-5467144598f9" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>611e22dc-b446-4a3d-8ef4-22bb23533511</id><title>3/16 - Reflections National Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883501+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arc Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 San Francisco, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/16/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.arc-sf.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Reflections” can mean the throwing back of light, sound or images by a body or surface, an image you see when you look in a mirror, an image given back by a reflecting surface. It can also be interpreted as a careful thought about something or a thought occurring in consideration or meditation.  Artists are free to interpret “reflections” with either or both of these meanings.  Categories: Sculpture, painting, drawing, photo, printmaking, ceramics, assemblage, collage, mixed media, fiber art, artist book. Juror:  Shelley Barry, Slate Contemporary Gallery, Oakland, CA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online application only through &lt;a href="https://www.arc-sf.com/reflections.html" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.arc-sf.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Questions? email ArcgallerySF@gmail.com with any questions. If you would like to talk to us by phone, please include your phone number in your email.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/611e22dc-b446-4a3d-8ef4-22bb23533511" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>bc3b3569-7307-4bef-8d57-5d0bde733c0e</id><title>12/19 - Greenpoint Gallery 2019 HOLIDAY SALON SHOW!</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883472+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our 2019 Holiday Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FRIDAY, December 20th, 2019 at 8pm&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, December 19th at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Come celebrate the start of Winter and invite your friends to see or participate in this great showcase of local talent!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! This is a juried event and runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show and with other runner-up winners! Give the great gift of art to your loved ones while supporting your artistic community!&lt;br/&gt;It’s the best show of the year, so come celebrate the holiday season with us and GET YOUR ART ON! &lt;br/&gt;Submissions are now open.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of local bands and musicians sure to entertain, so mark your calendars.&lt;br/&gt;FRIDAY, December 20th at 8pm&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit JPEG's or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive ready to hang. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, December 19th at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces in the $150-$500 range. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/507857419814499/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit JPEG's or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/bc3b3569-7307-4bef-8d57-5d0bde733c0e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e54ca407-c82d-4864-b2e6-7f9d36212bfb</id><title>1/15 - 31st National Drawing &amp;amp; Print Competitive Exhibition</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883441+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Gormley Gallery - Notre Dame of Maryland University&lt;br/&gt;📍 Baltimore, MD, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Printmaking&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/15/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $36.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://ndm.edu/gormleygallery"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gormley Gallery at Notre Dame of Maryland University invites artists to submit drawings and prints for our annual juried exhibition. This year’s juror is Doreen Bolger, Former Director of the Baltimore Museum of Art. A minimum of $1,500 is available in purchase prize awards.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility and Media: Drawing and prints (not photography) in any medium up to 60" high (framed) are eligible, with no limitations as to color, surface, or materials. All drawings and prints must be original works of art. Each artist may submit up to 3 works online only. No mailed or emailed entries will be accepted. Accepted artworks must arrive at the gallery ready to hang.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee: A nonrefundable entry fee of $36.00 entitles the artist to submit up to three entries.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selection process: Initial jury will be of online submissions received by January 15, 2020. Notification will be by email on January 31, 2020. Accepted drawings and prints received by March 2 will be juried for purchase prize awards at the value set by the artist. Works selected for purchase prize awards will become the property of Notre Dame of Maryland University.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition dates: March 23 through April 24, 2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To apply:&lt;br/&gt;https://artndm.slideroom.com/#/login/program/52095&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More information: &lt;br/&gt;ndm.edu/gormleygallery&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contact: &lt;br/&gt;gormleygallery@ndm.edu&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e54ca407-c82d-4864-b2e6-7f9d36212bfb" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>5ead4d3b-23c6-4d8c-a8bf-f788a3902f03</id><title>2/7 - FIBER 2020</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883412+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Silvermine Arts Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Canaan, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Crafts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/07/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://silvermineart.org/exhibition/fiber-2020/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIBER 2020 – seeks to exhibit the best of contemporary fiber art. Submissions are invited that reflect the breadth of functional or non-functional works that use fiber and/or fiber art techniques in traditional or innovative ways. Works made from natural or high tech materials that reference fiber and that blur the lines between art, architecture and craft are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;CURATOR – Beth C. McLaughlin is Chief Curator of Exhibitions and Collections at Fuller Craft Museum in Brockton, Massachusetts. Ms. McLaughlin has held leadership and curatorial roles in the arts and museum fields for over 25 years at institutions across the U.S., including Fuller Craft Museum, Oakland Museum of California, and DeCordova Sculpture Park and Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eligibility – Open to all artists, 18 years of age and older, residing in the United States. Original artwork in any media will be considered. Eligible artwork must have been completed after January 1, 2018, and fall within the restrictions. Check website for prospectus.&lt;br/&gt;Awards – Best in Show awards an artist a solo exhibition at Silvermine Arts Center with a $1,000 stipend for show related expenses. The Juror has additional awards to give at their discretion.&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee – $45 for up to 5 entries. To be considered for the Best in Show Award, artists are required to enter a minimum of three works.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5ead4d3b-23c6-4d8c-a8bf-f788a3902f03" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7f4116c6-e4b5-4325-a73b-d6efd0beaa8e</id><title>12/30 - SOLO EXHIBITION 2020 at The Untitled Space gallery in Tribeca, NY</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883382+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Untitled Space&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://untitled-space.com/artist-opportunities/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Untitled Space gallery invites artists to apply for a Solo Exhibition to take place at the gallery in Tribeca, New York in 2020.&lt;br/&gt;The Untitled Space is looking for an artist with an exceptional body of work that has not been previously exhibited for this unique opportunity. The exhibit will be curated by gallery director Indira Cesarine who will work directly with the artist to select final artwork for exhibition as well as promote it via print and online media. Artists who submit may also be considered for future opportunities with The Untitled Space gallery such as international art fairs, group shows, and online exclusives.&lt;br/&gt;Artists should have an established exhibition track record, and the focus of the proposal should be on new, unexhibited work. The recipient of the solo exhibition will additionally be represented by The Untitled Space gallery for a minimum of 6 months in support of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE UNTITLED SPACE&lt;br/&gt;The Untitled Space is an art gallery located in Tribeca, New York in a landmark building on Lispenard Street. Founded in 2015 by Indira Cesarine, the gallery features exhibits of emerging and established contemporary artists exploring conceptual framework and boundary pushing ideology through mediums of painting, sculpture, printmaking, photography, video and performance art. The gallery is committing to exploring new ideas vis-à-vis traditional and new mediums and highlights a program of women in art as well as special events aligned with our creative vision.&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT CURATOR INDIRA CESARINE&lt;br/&gt;Indira Cesarine’s curatorial for The Untitled Space includes includes solo shows for artists Sarah Maple, Rebecca Leveille, Alison Jackson, Fahren Feingold, Miss Meatface, and Jeanette Hayes as well as group shows "BODY BEAUTIFUL", “IRL: Investigating Reality”, "EDEN" and "(HOTEL) XX" at SPRING/BREAK Art Show; ”SECRET GARDEN”, “SHE INSPIRES,” and internationally-celebrated group shows “UPRISE/ANGRY WOMEN” and “ONE YEAR OF RESISTANCE” responding to the political climate in America, as well as numerous other critically-acclaimed exhibitions. &lt;br/&gt;Recent press on Indira Cesarine &amp; The Untitled Space includes Vogue (US), Vogue Italia, CNN, Forbes, Newsweek, W Magazine, Harper’s Bazaar, Teen Vogue, New York Magazine, i-D Magazine, Dazed and Confused, and The New York Times among many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online - visit our website for more information: &lt;br/&gt;http://untitled-space.com/artist-opportunities/&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7f4116c6-e4b5-4325-a73b-d6efd0beaa8e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>fea0876c-980c-4d5f-bbc1-81b1e4b8ddce</id><title>12/20 - Japan Day Art Contest 2020</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883352+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Japan Day Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.japandaynyc.org/artcontest2020"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan Day is inviting all visual artists to submit their work to Japan Day Art Contest to select our Japan Day Official Artist 2020. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are accepting submissions that incorporate all of the three themes of New York, Japan, and Central Park. The chosen artwork will become the official image of Japan Day @ Central Park 2020, and will be used for collateral materials including poster, program, flyer, and T-shirts. Several artists will receive honorable mentions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Japan Day Official Artists will receive a round trip ticket for two (2) to Japan, provided by ANA and Digital camera, provided by Nikon Inc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All winners will be announced in late March/early April 2020. The awards will be presented on the day of event in May 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RULES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Art must incorporate all of the following three themes: “New York,” ”Japan,” and “Central Park.”&lt;br/&gt;- Size must be 24" tall x 18" wide.&lt;br/&gt;- Only two-dimensional media is accepted.&lt;br/&gt;- Only one submission per artist will be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;- All entries must be the original work of the entering artist.  &lt;br/&gt;- Artwork which has been submitted to previous contests and/or previously shown or published is not eligible. &lt;br/&gt;- Artwork does not need to include the Japan Day logo or any text related to the event.&lt;br/&gt;- Artwork that violates copyrights, intellectual property rights, and/or any related rights of a third party, is not eligible. (For example, the use of existing anime characters would be a violation of copyrights.)&lt;br/&gt;- Art must not contain explicit sexuality, violence, or any discriminatory elements.&lt;br/&gt;- The final layout and design of the poster, flyer and other publicity materials will be created and approved by Japan Day Inc.  Artist’s approval is not required for publication.&lt;br/&gt;- By submitting their artwork, artists grant Japan Day Inc. the right to use their work for the purpose of marketing, exhibition and other Japan Day-related uses. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please visit the website (http://www.japandaynyc.org/artcontest2020) for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fea0876c-980c-4d5f-bbc1-81b1e4b8ddce" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>136b594c-46f3-417b-9bab-e6bd96744b58</id><title>1/3 - Dog Days of Winter - Member Artist Showcase</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883321+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;AKC Museum of the Dog&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/03/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $60.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://museumofthedog.org/events-and-education/calendar/dog-days-of-winter"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This February, the AKC Museum of the Dog will be hosting a Members Only pop-up exhibition showcasing the artistic talent within our community called Dog Days of Winter. Anyone currently enrolled in a membership program is encouraged to submit their art for consideration—this includes all membership levels and types. If you’re a non-member and wish to submit your work, never fear! Memberships start at $60 and you can join at any time during the entry period—which runs from October 31st to January 3rd—in order to submit your work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition will be juried. Individual Members are allowed one submission. Family/Dual and all higher levels of Membership are allowed up to four submissions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To submit your work to be considered for Dog Days of Weekend members showcase, you must be a member of the Museum. To become a member, visit our website or contact Molly Marcotte at molly.marcotte@museumofthedog.org. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guidelines for Juried Artwork Submission:&lt;br/&gt;-Anyone currently enrolled in a membership program will be encouraged to submit their work - this will include ALL membership levels and types.&lt;br/&gt;-Individual Members are allowed one submission.&lt;br/&gt;-Family/Dual Members and all higher levels of Membership are allowed up to 4 submissions.&lt;br/&gt;-Member Libraries who wish to participate will field submissions for their patrons and submit the top 4.&lt;br/&gt;-Any non-members who wish to submit must become a member in order to submit their art.&lt;br/&gt;-20 submissions will be chosen and featured on our third floor gallery.&lt;br/&gt;-All other submissions that are not selected will be featured on our Community Wall.&lt;br/&gt;-All mediums welcome with a size limitation of 25" x 30".&lt;br/&gt;-All artists will be responsible for getting their own pieces to the Museum no later than January 17, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;-Museum will not be responsible for framing any artworks that will be displayed, nor is the Museum responsible for any damage that may occur to a piece.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/136b594c-46f3-417b-9bab-e6bd96744b58" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3d5ad007-6f0a-402e-80f5-61b0a0bb0060</id><title>12/31 - 8th International Photography Annual [$2000 in Cash Awards]</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883291+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/inpha8"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cincinnati based non-profit arts organization and gallery, Manifest, invites visual artists to submit works that incorporate the lens or photographic process in some significant way, including manipulated and mixed processes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;INPHA is not a gallery exhibition. It does not require shipping works to Manifest. It is an award-winning non-profit hardcover publication with cash awards.&lt;br/&gt;INPHA is open to a very broad range of lens-based and photographic submissions. This is not just for 'photographers' and 'photography' but also for anyone working creatively in a visual art (or design) field with work that incorporates the lens or photographic process in some significant way, including manipulated and mixed processes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;First, Second, and Third Place awards for VISUAL works will be decided by the jury committee. Each award winner will have a brief artist's statement included in the publication. There will be three cash prizes of $1200, $500, and $300 for first, second, and third place winners.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$40 for up to FOUR entries submitted. $5 per each additional entry.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;**The next open call for INPHA 9 will be in 2022**&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To view the full prospectus and entry form visit &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/inpha8." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email info@manifestgallery.org with questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3d5ad007-6f0a-402e-80f5-61b0a0bb0060" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9264811c-a00a-45db-8da4-89b249d7ebbf</id><title>1/14 - Solo Shows 2020-2021 at Locust Grove Estate</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883260+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Barrett Art Center (Dutchess County Art Association)&lt;br/&gt;📍 Poughkeepsie, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/14/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.barrettartcenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Locust Grove Estate, is partnering with Barrett Art Center to announce four Solo Show opportunities in 2020-2021.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each 10-12 week show presents artists with the opportunity to present a solo show of 20-30 artworks in the Transverse Gallery in the Visitor Center at Locust Grove, a National Historic Landmark museum, education center, and nature preserve which attracts over 90,000 visitors annually.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;http://www.lgny.org/&lt;br/&gt;http://www.barrettartcenter.org/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Locust Grove was the nineteenth-century country estate of Samuel Morse, who, in addition to inventing the telegraph and Morse Code, was an artist and the founder of the National Academy of Design. In the twentieth century, the estate was owned by Poughkeepsie’s prominent Young family, noted collectors of Hudson River School paintings and the founders of the museum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Barrett Art Center works with curators from around the globe to bring exemplary contemporary art from international artists to its exhibitions in the Hudson Valley. Our reputation for high-quality exhibitions and programs attracts thousands of art enthusiasts to our 1840s Greek Revival townhouse-turned gallery annually. Arts professionals from Barrett Art Center are part of the curatorial team juroring the shows.&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Information&lt;br/&gt; Solo shows are available for 2-D artwork. Please note the galleries are frequented by visitors of all ages, including school groups. Artists’ discretion is requested. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We encourage artists to develop new works of art for this exhibition opportunity. If selected for a solo show, the images submitted for review do not necessarily have to be among the works exhibited. In an effort to give artists time to prepare, solo shows are being offered now for July 2020 through June 2021. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted artwork must be properly mounted, framed and ready to hang from a track-type hanging system. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork may be either for sale or for exhibition only. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Terms for sale of artwork: artist receives 75%; commission is 25% &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Recommended number of works for display is 20-30 pieces, depending on size. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Locust Grove reserves the right to not exhibit any artwork that does not meet our display criteria. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BAC Members, please email info@barrettartcenter.org or call us at 845-471-2550 for coupon code to receive discount.  To become a member, visit, www.barrettartcenter.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applications can be made directly to: &lt;br/&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=7280&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9264811c-a00a-45db-8da4-89b249d7ebbf" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a9d132f2-6601-4d84-bbfa-be227080b1ac</id><title>1/5 - Straight Through the Wall 2020 -- CALL FOR ARTISTS</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883227+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Straight Through the Wall&lt;br/&gt;📍 BROOKLYN, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/05/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://sttw.nyc/open-call/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeking artists working in Video, Experimental Film, Performance &amp; Animation for STRAIGHT THROUGH THE WALL’s 2020 program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NEXT DEADLINE: DECEMBER 5TH&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are STRAIGHT THROUGH THE WALL, a guerrilla Arts collective that projects video art onto walls throughout NYC. We scour the city for blank building facades, willing canvases waiting above busy avenues or hovering over quiet gardens and empty lots. With every screening, we incorporate art into the cityscape, merging it with New York’s varied architecture, bringing it out of the rigid structures of galleries &amp; exhibitions, and delivering it directly to the masses.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our first two seasons included screenings in the Lower East Side, Bed Stuy, Crown Heights, Chelsea, Dumbo, Two Bridges, Downtown Brooklyn, Brownsville &amp; the East Village. Each screening is 30 minute program that plays on loop &amp; the events are free to all. Emerging &amp; established artists are invited to submit their video proposals following the guidelines below.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EARLY DEADLINE - NOVEMBER 5 - FREE&lt;br/&gt;STANDARD DEADLINE - DECEMBER 5 - $10&lt;br/&gt;LATE DEADLINE - JANUARY 5 - $20&lt;br/&gt;If applying after November 5th, paypal your submission fee to sttw.nyc@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected artists will create videos that play with the idea of portraits. All videos should explore the human experience or human figure. What is it to be human in this time of history, what defines us and unites us? Alternative takes on portraiture are welcome &amp; encouraged. Straight Through the Wall seeks to better understand people both collectively &amp; individually by assembling a diverse video program consisting of different voices &amp; viewpoints.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All proposals must be for portrait videos (vertical dimensions - 1080 x 1920). All videos should be 3 - 5 minutes long. Once selected, you'll be asked to complete your video by April 5, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Email your submission to: sttw.nyc@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE INCLUDE:&lt;br/&gt;-Contact Info&lt;br/&gt;-Description of proposed work (max 500 words)&lt;br/&gt;-Artist statement or bio (max 200 words)&lt;br/&gt;-1 - 3 Video Samples (Links to Youtube or Vimeo)&lt;br/&gt;**Don't forget to Paypal submission fee to sttw.nyc@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a9d132f2-6601-4d84-bbfa-be227080b1ac" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0fc3a2db-6750-4c8f-a963-8fa34e914f29</id><title>12/29 - Upstream Gallery Juried Photography Show 2020</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883194+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Upstream Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hastings on Hudson, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/29/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.upstreamgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upstream Gallery Juried Photography Show 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; “Chaos &amp; Calm: Envisioning Order” &lt;br/&gt;There is no argument that the world around us is changing in a multitude of disturbing ways. Photographers are invited to submit work from their own practice that speaks to randomness and unpredictability or the creation of order from chaos for our annual juried exhibit of photographically based work.  Exhibition will be held at Upstream Gallery, Hastings on Hudson, NY, Jan. 30th to Feb. 23rd, 2020. Reception: Sunday, Feb. 2nd 2-5 pm. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Work: Artists from around the world are invited to submit photographs in any technique. All work must be photographically based.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Specifications: All work must be suitably framed.  The maximum framed size may not exceed 30 x 40 inches. Accepted pieces must be wired for hanging. The gallery reserves the right to reject poorly presented pieces. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Entries, Sunday Dec. 29th, 2019.  All entries must be made via Submittable: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee: Minimum entry of 3 pieces $45; each additional entry $5 up to a maximum of 6 pieces ($60).  The jury may select one, several, all, or none of your submissions. All pieces must be for sale. The gallery will retain a 30% commission on all sales. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT DATES &lt;br/&gt;Friday, January 24th: All shipped work must be received no later than 5 pm.&lt;br/&gt;Monday, January 27th 10 a.m. to 2 pm: Delivery of artwork to gallery by local artists &lt;br/&gt;Thursday, Jan. 30th: Opening of exhibition &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sunday, February 2nd, Opening reception – 2 to 5 pm&lt;br/&gt;Sunday, Feb 23rd, Last day of exhibition &lt;br/&gt;Monday, Feb. 24th Local Artists pick up work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All entries must be made through Submittable:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0fc3a2db-6750-4c8f-a963-8fa34e914f29" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a67ef9a9-2624-4e96-9c29-2548da07ccec</id><title>1/19 - CALL FOR ARTWORK - Suffrage and Struggle: Feminist Art and the 19th Amendment Centennial</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883158+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hamilton Gallery, Salve Regina University, Newport, Rhode Island&lt;br/&gt;📍 Newport, RI, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/19/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://art.salvereginauniversity.com/juried-show/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suffrage and Struggle: Feminist Art and the 19th Amendment Centennial&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: March 5 – April 7, 2020 Deadline: January 19, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Fee: (USD) $30.00&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;“Suffrage and Struggle: Feminist Art and the 19th Amendment Centennial” commemorates the centennial of women’s suffrage in the United States by marking the milestone of the 19th Amendment. This exhibition aims to celebrate women’s empowerment and the changes that have occurred over the last century, while at the same time acknowledging that more work remains to be done to achieve equality in our society. Regional in scope, this exhibition seeks to recognize the outstanding creative accomplishments of visual artists working in the New England and New York area whose work explores the complex place of women in society. We welcome submissions from all people that broadly interpret this theme around any issues of gender and sexuality.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror&lt;br/&gt;Jan Howard is the Chief Curator and Houghton P. Metcalf Jr. Curator of Prints, Drawings and Photographs at the RISD Museum. Prior to coming to RISD in 2000, she spent fourteen years as a curator in the Department of Prints, Drawings and Photographs at The Baltimore Museum of Art. Her exhibitions and publications have primarily focused on modern and contemporary art, including Drawing Ambience: Alvin Boyarsky and the Architectural Association 2014; America in View: Landscape Photography 1865 to Now, 2012; Made in the UK: Contemporary Art from the Richard Brown Baker Collection, 2011; Pat Steir: Drawing Out of Line, 2010; Interior Drama: Aaron Siskind’s Photographs of the 1940s, 2003; Laurie Simmons: The Music of Regret, 1997; Roni Horn: Inner Geography, 1994.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Dorrance H. Hamilton Gallery&lt;br/&gt;The Hamilton Gallery is a vibrant exhibition space on the campus of Salve Regina University in Newport, Rhode Island. This newly renovated Gallery hosts seven to ten exhibitions per academic year and serves as a center for art and visual culture.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility&lt;br/&gt;The Hamilton Gallery is currently accepting submissions in all media. This is an open call to artists living in Rhode Island, Massachusetts, Maine, Vermont, Connecticut, New Hampshire and New York. Artists must 18 years of age or older and all artwork must fit through a standard 36” x 80” door.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee&lt;br/&gt;The application fee for this exhibition is $30.00. Credit card payments must be made through the following weblink: www.salve.edu/ArtAppFee&lt;br/&gt;Checks must be made to the order of “Salve Regina University”. Do not email, fax or leave personal or financial information on voice mail. All inquiries and online submissions can be sent&lt;br/&gt;to ernest.jolicoeur@salve.edu. Please type “Suffrage and Struggle Exhibition” in the subject line. Entry fees will support the opening reception, printed materials and a stipend for the juror.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submissions&lt;br/&gt;The following items must be sent in a single email to ernest.jolicoeur@salve.edu or mailed in a single package to the mailing address listed below. All materials must be clearly labeled with the artist’s name. Materials received without payment of the application fee will not be given consideration. (Example: Jane_Smith_IMAGES or Jane_Smith_CV)&lt;br/&gt;   &lt;br/&gt;Resume&lt;br/&gt;A typewritten CV of no more than two pages that includes your contact information&lt;br/&gt;List of Works: A typewritten illustrated list (thumbnails only) of no more than three pieces including title, dimensions, date, medium and insurance value that includes your contact information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement: A brief typewritten statement about your submission(s) of no more than 200 words that includes your contact information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Images&lt;br/&gt;A single .pdf file or a dedicated weblink including no more than three high quality images (2MB or less) or three video shorts (5 minutes or less). Do not send link to websites or bodies of work. The juror will only review three works from each artist.&lt;br/&gt;    &lt;br/&gt;Mailing Address&lt;br/&gt;Hamilton Gallery: Suffrage and Struggle Dorrance H. Hamilton Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Antone Academic Center&lt;br/&gt;Salve Regina University&lt;br/&gt;100 Ochre Point Avenue Newport, RI 02840&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;All fees must be received and all materials must be postmarked or submitted by January 19, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;Conditions of Acceptance&lt;br/&gt;Artwork must arrive at the Hamilton Gallery ready for exhibition with all appropriate hardware and equipment. All accepted work must remain on display for the full duration of the exhibition, from March 5 through April 7, 2020. Please consider any potentially conflicting commitments before making your selections for submission.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Terms&lt;br/&gt;The Hamilton Gallery reserves the right to not exhibit work that is not ready for installation or differs from the images submitted. Images of all work accepted into this exhibition must be available for publicity purposes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notification of Acceptance&lt;br/&gt;Notifications will be sent by email during the week of January 27-31, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shipping&lt;br/&gt;All shipping and transportation are the responsibility of the artist. Shipped works must arrive in a reusable container that includes all necessary PREPAID postage. Artists may also hand deliver work to and from the gallery on February 25 or 26, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Insurance&lt;br/&gt;The Hamilton Gallery provides insurance for all artwork while on its premises for exhibition purposes. The Gallery does not cover insurance while work is in transit.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a67ef9a9-2624-4e96-9c29-2548da07ccec" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>019ca8c9-3a20-4c50-8a1f-c147d3b6c30b</id><title>12/14 - Chelsea Gallery OPEN CALL</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883118+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Field Projects&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com/open-call/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Field Projects is pleased to announce our Winter Open Call! Emerging and mid-career artists are invited to submit their work for consideration.. All submissions will be considered by our Guest Curators: Christin Graham &amp; Sam Trioli (LAUNCH F18 Gallery, NY). Simultaneously, Field Projects Panel (4-5 curators) will be considering the submissions for future solo exhibitions, group exhibitions, 2 person exhibitions, art fairs, pop-up shows, off-site exhibitions and our studio visit program, where we invite outside curators to accompany us to your studio. (85% of the artists we have shown in the last 8 years have been discovered through the Open Call.) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With your submission you will get several opportunities:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. Winter Exhibition by our Guest Curator: Christin Graham &amp; Sam Trioli (LAUNCH F18 Gallery, NY)&lt;br/&gt;2. Online Exhibition &lt;br/&gt;3. Future Solo and Group Exhibitions at Field Projects.&lt;br/&gt;4. Future Art Fairs with Field Projects.&lt;br/&gt;5. Outside Exhibitions by our FP panel members.&lt;br/&gt;6. Studio Visit pool for NYC Artists.&lt;br/&gt;7. Field Magazine&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Field Projects is an NYC-based project space located in the heart of Chelsea's gallery district. As an artist run space, we are committed to opening the field of exhibition opportunities to other working artists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow our website link above or cut and paste : &lt;a href="http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com/open-call/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit :&lt;br/&gt;up to 5 images of your work&lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement&lt;br/&gt;CV&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline : December 14th, 11:59 PM !!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Winter Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;The theme of the show will come from the work submitted. &lt;br/&gt;Selected artists will be notified by Dec 23rd, 2020&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must arrive at Field Projects by Thursday, January 2nd, 2020. &lt;br/&gt;Winter Exhibition opens Thursday January 9th, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Winter Exhibition closes Saturday February 8th, 2020&lt;br/&gt;All artwork in the exhibition will be for sale, with artists receiving 50% of final sale. &lt;br/&gt;We look forward to seeing your work!!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Field Projects&lt;br/&gt;526 W 26th Street, &lt;br/&gt;#807&lt;br/&gt;New York, NY 10001&lt;br/&gt;info@fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;www.fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/019ca8c9-3a20-4c50-8a1f-c147d3b6c30b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cb33efad-e6e9-467e-927d-f92d79ae09e6</id><title>12/15 - ACCEPTING CURATORIAL APPLICATIONS | SPRING/BREAK Art Show NYC + Los Angeles 2020</title><updated>2019-12-21T04:28:47.883047+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SPRING/BREAK Art Show&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $150.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.springbreakartshow.com/2020-application/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SPRING/BREAK Art Show is accepting submissions by curators until December 15, 2019*, midnight (your time), for the upcoming 2020 New York City and Los Angeles exhibitions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*This is our late application deadline. Regular applications were accepted until November 22, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2020 THEME | IN EXCESS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“The more the merrier.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;                          - Traditional&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The term ‘tipping point’ is used frequently in current affairs in regards to a variety of topics. Environmental extinction predominantly first and foremost, but also resumed economic stability, political divisiveness, information overloads, cancel culture mania, all are together thought to be at every manner of places along an axis of toppling the heck over, with varying ideas circulated as to which side of their scales are too overstuffed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art and entertainment feel indistinguishable from one another, piled together as “content”, which is consistently billed as in overwhelming supply from creators both amateur and professional; News peppers everyday moments through our devices’ push notifications and peer updates; tech-aided romantic possibilities appear infinite, as do all the other seductions of a globalized world—people to meet, people to follow, things to buy and eat and do. (Should one be able to afford it…For better or worse, then, the ‘too much’-ness of everything is certainly on the mind. In line with these grumblings of overmuch, SPRING/BREAK Art Show 2020 seeks similar inquiries into the paradoxes and nuances of ‘more’. For both upcoming New York and Los Angeles shows, IN EXCESS is actively searching for exhibitions dealing with virtues and/or limitations of maximalism, materialism, digression, hysterical realism, capitalism, encyclopedii, redundancy, consumerism, the over-foot-noted and the overlabored. Submissions may or may not include touchstones on multimedia, multiracial, or multiverse theories and perspectives; environmentalism, globalization, and future shock; the baroque, the Simulacrum, the epic, human play, the hall of mirrors, or any manner of other meditations on the Anthropocene and its anxieties; and, maybe—where we can find them—joys.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The pleasure of ‘more is more’ may be explored through the joyously overindulged overabundance of ideas, forms, perspectives. Aesthetically, ‘the bigger, brighter, busier, the better’ was once the zeitgeist with the intent to create, not a nauseous geegaw of consumer pleasures, but an impression that rattled complacency—generating, instead, awe, surprise, wonder; a sense of the infinitude of our World. Where is our awe now in all this excess? Where is the new Rocaille? Is it any good? Is it a spectre of Greed or Good? How much is not enough, and when is too little too soon?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;References in the current and former art landscape include, but are not limited to, Peter Saul’s rambunctious hypercolor paintings of interwoven political brutality, Joyce Kozloff’s reframing of “women’s work” in her P &amp; D movement pieces and their extension over into, and reframing by, artist Liz Collins, William Powhida’s art world cartography of complicit capitalism. Marco Brambilla crafts sprawling video pop cultural hells and heavens, packed with re-appropriated movie characters all fighting each other for a place in the pantheon, Mickalene Thomas constructs dizzying pastiche domiciles where tactile textiles, personal experience, and the figure from memory converge, authors like Thomas Pynchon and Zadie Smith jam-pack characters into stories teeming with a dance of detritus both intimate and historical; Stan Brakhage deploys the barrage for the sake of recalibrating our vision, Anselm Kiefer, with his fussy gigantic meditations, employs scale to save our soul. Robert Breer’s lightning speed animations stagger in their short running time pummel, Azikiwe Mohammed toils to find overstocked thrift store tapestries of Black utopias, and for Alison Zuckerman, art history, digital self-documentation, and Photoshop fiddling all find themselves locked, arm-in-arm, in triplicate.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Wilde suggested moderation in art and life was a fatal thing. But how does it support or subvert our consumptive excesses? Like Gittes once said to Mulwray, “how much better can you eat? What can you buy that you can’t already afford?”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;People, go for baroque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION GUIDELINES + CURATORIAL REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There are separate applications for the New York City and Los Angeles shows. Please note that curators may apply to both the New York City and Los Angeles shows and will need to submit separate applications for each show to be considered for either and/or both. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications will be accepted by independent curators, galleries and non-profit organizations during the late application period between November 23 - December 15, 2019. The online application form will be available during those dates until December 15, 2019 at 11:59pm your time. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;No proposals nor applications will be accepted via email.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Please note that "Late Applications" are reviewed in the same manner as "Regular Applications". We do not prioritize applications based on when they were submitted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION FEE&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is a non-refundable late application fee of $150.00 per application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our mission is to create an unique environment for showcasing independent curators by providing free exhibition space to each selected curator, and therefore, require an application fee to cover our administrative fees for processing the applications.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHO MAY APPLY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1) INDEPENDENT CURATORS: Independent Curators may submit an application for the 2020 SPRING/BREAK Art Show, including a curatorial proposal related to the theme of IN EXCESS, sample images of art work, a curatorial statement and additional information necessary to complete the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that an artist may apply as an Independent Curator only if they are applying with a group show or a solo show of another artist's work. An artist may not apply with their own art work in a solo show, but must have a curator who applies on behalf of him/her/they.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is NO FEE for the exhibition space if you are selected as an independent curator.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2) GALLERIES + PROJECT SPACES + NON PROFIT ORGANIZATIONS: Applicants affiliated with a gallery or project space/non-profit organization may submit a curatorial proposal comprised of artists from the gallery's roster and this curatorial proposal will fall into our SPECIAL PROJECT section. If you have an affiliation with a gallery, project space or non-profit organization, please define your affiliation/title and include the full roster of artists in the application below for our reference.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Special Project section was initiated in 2015 as a way to invite established, new and recently closed galleries to participate in the show. We encourage participants in the Special Project section to explore the theme in full and to go beyond what they typically would do in a traditional art fair environment. In 2019, there were 26 Special Projects as part of the program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each Special Project contributes a fee to participate, which helps to cover the production costs of the event.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information on applying at an Independent Curator, Gallery or a Non-Profit Organization, please visit our website for more details:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;http://www.springbreakartshow.com/2020-application/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED CURATORIAL APPLICATIONS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission of an application does not guarantee participation. We will review applications in December and notify selected curators by the beginning of January, if not before. If we have any questions about your proposal, we will contact the primary curator listed on the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each curatorial proposal will be given one (1) room/space for exhibiting artworks. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected curators will receive a consignment agreement to review and complete. All artworks included in the show must be included in and subject to the terms of the consignment agreement. Artworks that are not listed on the consignment agreement will not be permitted on the show premises. If you have any questions about the consignment terms, please contact us for details.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cb33efad-e6e9-467e-927d-f92d79ae09e6" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>