<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml</id><title>open-calls-7</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>c363cb9e-2373-4b24-a87a-7c79183964ab</id><title>1/31 - Call For ArtTable Fellowship Proposals</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164482+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtTable&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/31/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/ATFellowship2020"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ArtTable is currently soliciting proposals from arts organizations and institutions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For 20 years, the ArtTable Fellowship program has addressed the marked lack of diversity in arts employment. The objective is to provide quality real work experiences and mentorship for women identifying graduate/pre/post-doc students and emerging professionals from backgrounds generally underrepresented in the field to aid their transition from academic to professional careers.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Through one-on-one mentoring relationships with ArtTable members, every year, a selected number of fellows have the opportunity to work with an established leader in the field and gain exposure to a range of professional activities at first class cultural institutions throughout a five to eight week period during the summer. Each fellow will be connected with an ArtTable 'mentor' for the duration of their fellowship and be awarded a $4,000 stipend for the five to eight-week commitment during the summer.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The program was established in 2000 as a conscious effort to enrich and strengthen the visual arts field by supporting an inclusive and diverse professional landscape. The ArtTable Fellowship is one of the longest-standing programs supporting diversity in the visual arts. The mentored fellowships introduce emerging women-identifying professionals to the range of professional career tracks in the visual arts, including but not limited to: curatorial, education, public programming, archival research and collections management. ArtTable has already supported eighty-five fellows around the country.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ArtTable is soliciting proposals from arts organizations and institutions that meet the following criteria:&lt;br/&gt;•	Enable the fellow to work collaboratively as well as independently on a focused and cohesive project that significantly contributes to a public exhibition or program initiatives&lt;br/&gt;•	Offer opportunities to expand their research, writing, communication and project management skills&lt;br/&gt;•	Provide integration into the institution's staff and interface with other departments for maximum experience and exposure to day-to-day activities&lt;br/&gt;•	Encourage working closely with and receiving consistent direct supervision from a designated mentor&lt;br/&gt;•	Have a take-away component, be it research or skills-based with recognition given for contributions made to a major current or forthcoming project or program&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This year, ArtTable will accept proposals from host institutions through January 31, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The ArtTable Fellowship program is made possible thanks to the invaluable support of individuals and foundations. To learn more about contributing to this program please email director@arttable.org&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ArtTable is the foremost professional organization dedicated to advancing the leadership of women in the visual arts. Through our national membership network and community initiatives, we expand opportunities for women from diverse backgrounds and at all stages of their careers, fostering a stronger future for all women in the arts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Learn more about our impact programs:&lt;br/&gt;https://arttable.org/impact/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selection Process and Program Timeline:&lt;br/&gt;The process for selecting both hosts and fellows across the US is highly personalized and competitive. ArtTable staff, along with an ad hoc selection Fellowship Committee composed of current ArtTable members who represent professional, cultural, and geographic diversity review applications.&lt;br/&gt;Prospective fellows are selected through a similar competitive application. ArtTable will begin to accept fellow’s applications on February 12 through March 6, 2020. A final decision will be communicated to applicants on April 6.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, please contact Lucia Roldan, Education and Community Engagement Coordinator at lroldan@arttable.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c363cb9e-2373-4b24-a87a-7c79183964ab" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2f436c2f-4b25-473b-aa48-1cb0defd0e04</id><title>3/10 - 2020 Farm/Art DTour Call for Artists</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164439+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wormfarm Institute&lt;br/&gt;📍 Reedsburg, WI, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/10/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://wormfarminstitute.org/call-for-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OVERVIEW&lt;br/&gt;The Farm/Art DTour is a 50-mile, self-guided drive through the beautiful working lands of Sauk County, Wisconsin, punctuated by Art Works (large-scale temporary art installations), pasture performances, roadside poetry, local food, and more. The DTour is part of Fermentation Fest - A Live Culture Convergence including classes, workshops, and art events celebrating live culture in all its forms. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Wormfarm Institute will commission 6-8 original Art Works to be installed along the DTour route. The work will be on public view from September 25-October 4, 2020. We seek artists (individuals or teams) who are interested in creating site-responsive works that engage with the agricultural landscape, the farmers, landowners, and surrounding rural communities. This is an opportunity to contribute to a unique and exciting project with an established reputation for its innovative approach to creative placemaking.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We seek to curate a diverse group of artists for projects that respond to the land on the edge of Wisconsin’s Driftless Region. Successful past projects have ranged from fixed objects, to interactive environments, to work activated by natural processes. Some have invited hands-on participation, utilized existing agricultural infrastructure, or were installed in/on buildings in the small towns along the route. The viewers (DTourists) are usually traveling by car and guided by a map, so proposals should be large-scale and visually compelling. Artists are responsible for both installation and de-installation (volunteer assistance possible) and will have about two weeks to install and one week to de-install. Unless other arrangements are made, artists retain ownership of the work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This project has been supported by The National Endowment for the Arts, Wisconsin Arts Board, ArtPlace America, The Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, and The Educational Foundation of America. The Wormfarm Institute, the event’s presenter, is an award-winning non-profit organization with the mission to integrate culture and agriculture along the rural/urban continuum. This will be the 8th year of the DTour (now a biennial) and the first year along a new route.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BUDGET&lt;br/&gt;Wormfarm will fund projects at two levels: $5,000 and $2,500. Six to eight proposals will be selected from a combination of funding levels. Please indicate on your application which funding level you are applying for. &lt;br/&gt;An itemized budget is not required for Phase One.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;VISION: “Art Amplifies what landscape quietly asserts” - Max Garland, past Wisconsin Poet Laureate&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This project, which began as a celebration of food, farming and rural life, has revealed itself to be a powerful tool for bringing people together across perceived divides. Rooted in an arts and culture focus, we emphasize the cross-sector collaboration necessary to build a vibrant region that values both its rural and urban parts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In ecology there is a concept called "edge environments” – areas between one sort of landscape and another, where ecosystems overlap. These edges tend to have more diversity (and therefore more hardiness) than either of the adjoining environments alone. These mixed-use zones, both literal and conceptual, characterize the DTour experience and allow us to see new possibilities for our land, our work, and our communities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The DTour is an invitation for people, both rural and urban dwellers, to follow a path and take a closer look at a rural community and landscape where farming plays a central though changing role. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION PROCESS&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be chosen to participate through a two-part selection process. Initial proposals will be reviewed by a jury consisting of the organizers, past DTour artists, and regional and national arts professionals. Up to 15 finalists will be selected and notified by March 30. Finalists will be expected to attend a two-day Orientation in Sauk County, WI in May.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Orientation aims to deepen the participants’ understanding of the event, the landscape, the current state of agriculture as well as provide an opportunity for artists to meet with event organizers, landowners, past DTour artists, and one another. The weekend will include a tour of the DTour route, shared meals, and ample opportunity to share ideas and ask questions. Meals and housing will be provided. It is our hope that this experience has value independent of being selected for this year. Participants will receive a stipend to help cover travel expenses and subsequently develop a full proposal. Afterwards, finalists will have two weeks to develop a full proposal.    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION CRITERIA&lt;br/&gt;- Artistic excellence&lt;br/&gt;- Visual Impact&lt;br/&gt;- Demonstrated ability to realize&lt;br/&gt;- Community Engagement&lt;br/&gt;- Feasibility in the context of the larger event&lt;br/&gt;- Curatorial vision&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;Please respond with: &lt;br/&gt;- One page Letter of Interest including contact information &lt;br/&gt;- Preliminary Project Concept indicating funding level, not to exceed one page &lt;br/&gt;- Concept drawings or visual references &lt;br/&gt;- 8-10 images of applicant’s recent work demonstrating capacity to realize large-scale outdoor project &lt;br/&gt;- Resume or C.V. not to exceed two pages.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Format:&lt;br/&gt;- Letter of Interest, Project Concept, Drawings, Resume/C.V. should be saved as a single PDF or Word doc.&lt;br/&gt;- Images must be JPEG format, “high” or “fine” quality, not to exceed 2 MB per image. &lt;br/&gt;- Image file names should include artist’s last name and be numbered: “Smith-01.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Things to keep in mind when developing your proposal:&lt;br/&gt;- Wisconsin weather can be unpredictable, plan for rain, cold &amp; high winds.&lt;br/&gt;- The landscape can dwarf even the most ambitious projects.&lt;br/&gt;- DTour audience interaction ranges from drive-by to direct engagement with installations. Keep both scenarios in mind as you develop your idea.&lt;br/&gt;- The DTour runs primarily along farm fields, but also includes woods, wetlands, and small towns. Most sites however, will be located in hay fields or pasture.&lt;br/&gt;- The DTour is expected to attract 20,000-30,000 people from near and far. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;TIMELINE  &lt;br/&gt;March 10:  Email Applications due by 5 p.m. CST   &lt;br/&gt;March 30:  Finalists selected, notification sent to applicants&lt;br/&gt;May 2-3:  Finalist Orientation in Sauk County, WI &lt;br/&gt;May 20:  Final Proposals due&lt;br/&gt;June 1:  Artists chosen, notified&lt;br/&gt;June: Contracts with selected artists, final site selection &lt;br/&gt;September 11- 23: Installation of Art Work&lt;br/&gt;Sept 25 – Oct 4: Farm/Art DTour + Fermentation Fest&lt;br/&gt;October 5 – 19: De-installation of work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Email application to info@wormfarminstitute.org by March 10, 5 p.m. CST. Please include "DTour Proposal" in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2f436c2f-4b25-473b-aa48-1cb0defd0e04" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>58e16591-27f6-46c1-8a58-e9904ce2c4a9</id><title>2/20 - INTERNATIONAL CALL FOR ART, ArtMaze Magazine Spring Edition: Issue 17</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164411+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtMaze Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍  , United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/20/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artmazemag.com/call-for-art/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art Maze Magazine is an independent artist-run and ad-free international print and online publication dedicated to showcasing and promoting experimental and progressive contemporary art, which reflects modern society and its environment, provokes conversation and action; fosters innovation and diversity of mediums which make today’s art scene so intriguing and versatile.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: Artists are welcome to submit works in any medium: painting, drawing, sculpture, ceramics, printmaking, photography, textile, installation, mixed media, digital, film (only jpg + link to video) etc. All visual art mediums are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists or any art organisations on behalf of artists from all countries are welcome to submit their works for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each submitted artist, whether selected for a publication or not, will receive a digital copy of the magazine's issue which they applied for.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: February 20th, 2019 (12:00 AM, midnight: end of the day 20th February - Eastern Standard Time)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUEST CURATOR: Matthew F Fisher, artist and independent curator&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO APPLY: www.artmazemag.com/call-for-art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DISTRIBUTION: Physical and digital copies of ArtMaze Mag are distributed worldwide via bookshops, galleries and online. More info: &lt;a href="http://artmazemag.com/shop/" target="_blank"&gt;http://artmazemag.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Matthew F Fisheris a painter living and working in Brooklyn, NY. He has had solo shows with SHRINE, New York, NY (2020), Taymour Grahne, London, UK (2019, 2017), Ochi Projects, Los Angeles, CA (2019), and Johansson Projects, Oakland, CA (2018). He has also had an active side hustle curating group shows such as Crunch, The Breeder, Athens, GK (2017), Nothing Less, SARDINE, Brooklyn, NY (2014), New York, New Work: The Object Direct, Mississippi State University (2008), and The Longest Day, co-curated with Jon Lutz, Brooklyn, NY (2008). He maintains an Instagram account where he actively promotes artists whose work differs greatly from his own; but, like himself, these are artists who use the act of painting or sculpting in combination with the inaccuracies of the handmade as the best way to translate their ideas into reality.&lt;br/&gt;www.matthewffisher.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selected artists will be asked for high resolution images and will be published in the next print and digital issue of ArtMaze Magazine. Each (selected) artist will receive a 1 or 2-page spread in print and digital (PDF) magazine including bio, statement, website, and 1-5 featured artworks. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All submitted artists will receive a complimentary PDF copy of the magazine and all published artists will be promoted on our website/social media. Physical copies of Art Maze Magazine are printed to the highest quality in London, UK.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/58e16591-27f6-46c1-8a58-e9904ce2c4a9" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>403582a0-c2a6-42fd-a8f0-9db9c2a48577</id><title>3/2 - Open Call: Art Underneath the Elevated 2020</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164383+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Rockaway Waterfront Alliance&lt;br/&gt;📍 Queens, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/02/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://riserockaway.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Rockaway Initiative for Sustainability and Equity (RISE) is soliciting proposals for the 2020 Art Underneath the Elevated II initiative, which will commission two to three artists to envision, produce, and exhibit temporary public art installations underneath or adjacent to the elevated A-train in Far Rockaway, Queens.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This exciting initiative will use art and creative placemaking as a catalyst to temporarily transform and animate this fragmented and underutilized roadway into a vibrant and active public space. Through this initiative, RISE hopes to inspire the community to re-imagine the potential of Rockaway Freeway to reconnect the Peninsula and serve as an adaptable civic space.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This call for proposals invites an individual or a group of artists to submit a project proposal for temporary public artworks. Two to three projects will be selected. Potential project mediums include lighting installations, digital projections, street furniture, signage, murals, or sculptures. The RISE Center (58-03 Rockaway Beach Blvd) will serve as the hub of activity, and it’s gallery for public programs and community engagement that build on the chosen projects. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected artists will receive a $3,000 to 6,000 production grant to support all costs associated with their project and a one month community engagement residency that includes access to the resources and facilities at the RISE Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The application deadline is March 2nd, 2020 at 11:59 PM EST. Selected artists will be notified in April. Please visit our website (riserockaway.org) for more detailed program information and application instructions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/403582a0-c2a6-42fd-a8f0-9db9c2a48577" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0927c629-fbe4-4a18-9b87-7188173ef3c8</id><title>3/15 - The Creative Time Emerging Artist Open Call</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164355+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;CREATIVE TIME&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/15/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://creativetime.org/open-call-2020-2021/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Creative Time Emerging Artist Open Call is back! Following the resounding success of the inaugural iteration -- which culminated in Risa Puno’s The Privilege of Escape in summer 2019 -- New York’s leading public art nonprofit is once again inviting emerging artists to submit proposals for a socially engaged public artwork.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The call is open to New York City-based, practicing artists at a pivotal juncture in their career, who have not yet received substantial support from a major cultural institution. Creative Time is most interested in ideas that take unconventional exhibition formats, speak to a pressing social issue, and engender public dialogue or debate. The project should be timely, and hold the potential to spark critical public exchange.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposals will be accepted between January 21 and March 15, and the selected project will be presented in New York City in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;Applications are accepted electronically via Submittable. All complete applications received by March 15 at 11:59PM will be reviewed. Application materials sent by mail, in person, or by phone will not be considered.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;The open call is intended for emerging artists, regardless of age, at a critical career juncture in which the opportunity to experiment and receive resources from a major arts organization would be impactful. Please see the specific parameters of eligibility below:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists must have experience conceiving and executing works or projects, but have not yet received substantial support from a major arts institution&lt;br/&gt;Artist must be over 21, and based in the New York City area &lt;br/&gt;Applicants cannot be currently enrolled in a degree program &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We encourage anyone who considers themselves an emerging artist to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, including application guidelines and FAQs, visit our website or contact opencall@creativetime.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0927c629-fbe4-4a18-9b87-7188173ef3c8" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cd72afce-4a05-4926-9edb-591641fe6310</id><title>2/10 - Open Call for Art: &amp;quot;reflecting on social transformation&amp;quot; curated by Lisa di Donato</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164325+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LiC-A @ The Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/10/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.licartists.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call for Art: Title TBD "reflecting on social transformation" curated by Lisa Di Donato&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An exhibition in response to the centennial anniversary of Women’s Suffrage in the United States that queries &lt;br/&gt;-Who are We- in relation to our complicated histories and present realities as individuals and communities, as women and as citizens. In keeping with the theme of Woman’s History Month, the focus is mainly feminist-centric, but, the call also seeks to include works that highlight adjacent movements and concerns to those of women and feminism, which notably have a history of engaging in self-examination. Artists and creatives, individual or collective, of all genders, nationalities, and mediums- visual arts, video, sound art, text, and poetry are encouraged to apply.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;During this very uncertain time of increasing divisiveness in the country and the world, the remembrance of the Suffragette Movement could serve as a cautionary tale on the struggle and preservation of human rights. The Nineteenth Amendment all too frequently is viewed only &lt;br/&gt;in its decisive moment of victory, a fait accompli, glossing over its problematic and arduous progression towards ratification and the current day disenfranchisement and oppression that continue to threaten many here and abroad.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Rather than striking with defensive declarations of -We Are- that flatten conversation and knowledge, this exhibition looks to the heart of our cultural and political clashes where the question of -Who are We- resides. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists are in a unique position to ask this question through their work; politics in art is not limited merely to statement-making. Art offers us the opportunity to explore how we understand and apprehend our worlds, the manifold methods of communication that may reveal otherwise untold perceptions, and exposure of a creative process the vulnerability of which is an invitation to the shared meanings that are the underpinnings of every society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To apply please copy and paste the below link into your browser or visit us at www.licartists.org for more information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_social_transformation&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the curator:&lt;br/&gt;Lisa di Donato received her BFA from the Rhode Island School of Design. Her artwork has been shown in the US and Europe, and she also has independently curated numerous exhibitions. She received recognition in the 2019 Julia Margaret Cameron Women in Photography Award in the category of Abstraction and is currently in the accompanying exhibition in Barcelona, Spain. In May 2019 she was artist in residence at Fusion Gallery AIR Inaudita in Torino, Italy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cd72afce-4a05-4926-9edb-591641fe6310" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d7f39fca-87ea-4bbd-9093-f8fee936d6ff</id><title>2/15 - Submit to “The Sick” for publication</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164297+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Seventh Child&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/15/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://seventh-child.com/submit"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New art &amp; literary press, Seventh Child, is seeking submissions for its first open call, to result in a print publication dissecting THE SICK. All interpretations of the theme are welcome, including those which are arguably challenging, subversive, unorthodox, or uncomfortably subjective. Art of every stripe is encouraged, with little or no restriction: poetry, photography, illustration, creative nonfiction, three-dimensional work represented two-dimensionally in order to be fit for print, etc. Final selection from submissions will be based on considerations of craft, relevance, and potential for stimulating connections with other pieces set for inclusion. Everyone featured in the final publication will receive a free copy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send 1-5 work samples as email attachments (hi-res jpegs or pdfs) to info@seventh-child.com and include your name as you wish it to be printed, as well as website, social media handles, or other online presence, if applicable. There is no fee to submit.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d7f39fca-87ea-4bbd-9093-f8fee936d6ff" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c7786f71-63c0-4fc3-b3f7-d4627a084be5</id><title>2/7 - OPEN CALL - Night &amp;amp; Day - Group Show - Local Project NYC</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164269+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Local Project&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/07/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://localproject.org/night-day-group-show-open-call/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for works of art that symbolize the day and the night.&lt;br/&gt;As we head into a new decade, we want to show the artist’s vision, state of mind,  and the effects of light and darkness pertaining to the direction we are headed.&lt;br/&gt;As Dorothy M. Richardson said : ”Night is torment. This is why people go to sleep. To avoid clear sight and torment” &lt;br/&gt;Do you see the light ahead ?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are really excited to be partnering with Departure Studios in LIC, to make this a 2 part exhibition simultaneously happening in each space, creating a flow of light and darkness between both locations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Dates :&lt;br/&gt;Open call Deadline: FRIDAY FEB 7&lt;br/&gt;Notification: MONDAY FEB 10&lt;br/&gt;Delivery of selected works: FEB 14-15 Time TBC via email&lt;br/&gt;Opening Thursday FEB 20  6-9pm in conjunction with the LIC Gallery Nights&lt;br/&gt;Show runs through March 14, 2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-Artwork must be original and come from you – the artist. (no digital reproductions).&lt;br/&gt;-Artist must live in NYC or NJ.&lt;br/&gt;-There is no entry fee to submit your work but accepted artists pay a hanging fee of $30, by cash, check or Venmo.&lt;br/&gt;-Hanging fees go directly toward the expenses of the exhibition and the reception.&lt;br/&gt;-Work must be ready to hang ie; frames or wired, no clips or pins&lt;br/&gt;–no size limit and prices bellow $1,000 preferable ( we hold the right to make exceptions)&lt;br/&gt;-Please SUBMIT up to 2 jpeg images of the works you like to show, include title, year, dimension, material, and price to opencall@localproject.org including NIGHT &amp; DAY in the subject.&lt;br/&gt;-Jpegs must not exceed 2mb.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Local Project takes a 30% fee if your work is sold. Sales will be finalized at the end of each exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;-This exhibition will be Juried by LP curators John Baber and Carolina Peñafiel.&lt;br/&gt;-Once notified, you will be guided to drop off dates, payment must be done at drop off.&lt;br/&gt;-Artists are responsible for the drop-off and pick-up of any and all artwork.&lt;br/&gt;-Any artwork left without notice for more than a week after the end of the show at LP, Local Project will not be held responsible.&lt;br/&gt;-Please note Local Project and Departure Studios does NOT provide insurance for the artwork.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c7786f71-63c0-4fc3-b3f7-d4627a084be5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0e31352c-596c-4ab8-b66d-d10028c17238</id><title>2/29 - EMERGING CURATORS - OPEN CALL - LOCAL PROJECT NYC</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164241+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Local Project&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/29/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://localproject.org/emerging-curators-2020/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEADLINE: February 29, 5pm, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;Notifications by March 5, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Emerging Curators is an open call invitation to independent curators who may not have had opportunities to present a project to an audience, or first time curators to submit a Project/Exhibition proposal to be part of Local Project’s 2020 exhibition calendar. This program will provide the curator with a $500 honorarium and a budget of $500 to split between the artists of each show, exhibition space, guidance in marketing and art handling and a printed catalog.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposals will be reviewed by our LP curatorial team, we will then select 6 proposals for the year 2020 to happen in the LP gallery and at site specific locations or other galleries in LIC area between March and June 2020.&lt;br/&gt;The Emerging Curators will represent the vision of a new generation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application is FREE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;Proposals must include :&lt;br/&gt;-Title of the project, number of artist involved (min 2 – max 10) name of the curator/s.&lt;br/&gt;-Proposals must be submitted as a PDF.&lt;br/&gt;-Proposals can be 1-2 weeks exhibitions, 2-3 days popups, or 1 day events.&lt;br/&gt;-For a 2 week exhibitions Programming during the exhibition on view is required (performance, screening, artist talk/walk, workshop),&lt;br/&gt;-Describe your idea in a simple way – up to 1000 words.&lt;br/&gt;-Include up to 5 sample images of the work to be selected.&lt;br/&gt;-Curator and Artists must be residents of New York City.&lt;br/&gt;-All mediums and ideas are accepted.&lt;br/&gt;-Curators can’t  include their own work in the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;– Once selected curator must supply all the content for the catalogue, including high res images, artist bio and a paragraph about the exhibition etc via PDF&lt;br/&gt;-Only one proposal per curator, curatorial collaborations accepted.&lt;br/&gt;-Selected Curators must be present all the times during installation, opening, programs and closing ceremony, and embrace the DIY mentality of LP, by participating, collaborating and sitting at the gallery.&lt;br/&gt;-Submit a PDF to opencall@localproject.org with EMERGING CURATORS on the subject line.&lt;br/&gt;-Do NOT send/attach CV/PRESS or any other information not listed here&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions email opencall@localproject.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0e31352c-596c-4ab8-b66d-d10028c17238" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>428d0e3b-c921-422e-a241-dd920e420284</id><title>1/30 - January 31st Open Call People&amp;#39;s Choice Salon Show! WIN $200 AND A SOLO SHOW!</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164213+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/30/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our January 31st People's Choice Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, January 31st , 2020 from 8pm- 12am.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, January 30th, 2020 at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For this show, we let the people decide, which means everyone who attends votes for the winners! We pass out ballots at the door and guests who attends choose the winners! It is always one of our most well attended nights, boasting record art sales and a large community of fellow artists and art lovers!&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of local bands!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, Jan. 30th at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces already this past year. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com  Instagram: @ GreenpointGallery&lt;br/&gt;Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/greenpointgallery/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To submit, send us JPEG's of your artwork or a link to your website at greenpointgallery@gmail.com!&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/428d0e3b-c921-422e-a241-dd920e420284" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6c10d1ca-ba27-4aee-9e52-c0604514255f</id><title>2/7 - AD ART SHOW 2020- Call for Artists at the Oculus at the World Trade Center-</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164186+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;MvVO ART creator of AD ART SHOW&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/07/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $75.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.mvvoart.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a successful debut at Sotheby's in 2018, and at the Oculus in 2019, AD ART SHOW is BACK at the Oculus in a BIG WAY. Opening during Frieze Art week (May 2020), AD ART SHOW will be showcasing artists from all over the world on the monumental SCREENS at the Oculus at Westfield World Trade Center , one of the most famous architectural landmarks in New York City. The show is on for the whole month of May! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is easy to apply. All you have to do is to submit 4 images of your Art.  Our renown Art selection committee will review it and if you are selected then you will be part of the show. (no commercial work please- only your fine Art). All the Art will also be featured for sale on MvVOART's Artsy gallery, the leading Art market place for collectors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is a selling exhibition (fees apply). Includes VIP invitation to the May 4 opening reception attended by Art professionals, collectors, press and Ad industry. Eligible to win a creative immersion day at NBC Universal and your Art will be reviewed by well know NY Art professionals and important collectors. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Go to www.mvvoart.com for details and application and to check if you qualify.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thank you. &lt;br/&gt;MvVO ART team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Access application via www.mvvoart.com. Also follow Mvvoart on Instagram for constant updates. It is easy to apply. Just submit 4 images of your Art! and answer a few questions. The artists are selected based on their submission not their experience in the Art world. Please see FAQ on Mvvoart and application for all info.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6c10d1ca-ba27-4aee-9e52-c0604514255f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>94a0a3a2-6aba-4df1-a3d8-e2f605391076</id><title>2/7 - Vellum Magazine special project open call</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164155+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Vellum Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/07/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www. Vellumartzine.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the success of Vellum Magazine’s curatorial project “Forest of Illusion” we’re set to start working on our next project “Human Nature”. The project will feature 10-15 artists who can address the human condition in various ways. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The special edition issue due out in spring 2020 will travel to art fairs around the globe including Frieze NY, Scope Miami, Art Basel, Liste, Volta, Artissima, Swab Barcelona, Fiac, and more.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To be considered for the project, please send 3-5 (low res) JPEG images of your work, a short bio/cv and links to your website (email to: vellumartzine@gmail.com) by Feb  7, 2020. Those artists chosen will be contacted, and upon acceptance a $160 participation fee will be due. The fee will help cover all costs associated with the project (printing/shipping to the fairs/administrative). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;www.vellumartzine.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To be considered for the project, please send 3-5 (low res) JPEG images of your work, a short bio/cv and links to your website (email to: vellumartzine@gmail.com) by Feb  7, 2020. Those artists chosen will be contacted, and upon acceptance a $160 participation fee will be due. The fee will help cover all costs associated with the project (printing/shipping to the fairs/administrative). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;www.vellumartzine.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/94a0a3a2-6aba-4df1-a3d8-e2f605391076" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6afe1573-c076-4a04-837b-8a40b5457fe5</id><title>1/22 - Window Gallery Exhibition open call</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164101+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;UrbanGlass&lt;br/&gt;📍 BROOKLYN, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/22/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://urbanglass.org/studio/detail/window-installations-community-activation-project"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;UrbanGlass is accepting proposals, to showcase artwork in the UrbanGlass Window Gallery during 2020-2021. This program will feature a total of 4 exhibitions, from May 2020- January 2021. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The space that is open for showcasing in the duration listed is the western-facing windows-- the triangular window space on the corner of Rockwell and Fulton and the large windows that are parallel to Rockwell Place. The exhibition proposal must prioritize the viewpoint from the street looking into the windows.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ideal proposals will include consideration of the unique opportunity for visibility 24/7 in this public- facing space. UrbanGlass is seeking proposals that clearly showcases plans for how the artist plans to use the windows explicitly. Please be sure to explicitly describe your use of the space and how your work will be viewed from Fulton and Rockwell Street. Your plans should be bold and visible from the street view and consider the nature of this space. The majority of viewers seeing your exhibition will interface with the installation from the street-view, and not by walking into the gallery.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications can include proposals for:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Installations. &lt;br/&gt;An installation of artwork that is representative of work being made in the contemporary glass community. The proposed works can be a combination of glass and mixed media.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Performances.&lt;br/&gt;Performances using handmade glass, scheduled for the opening nights of exhibitions of AVAC and possibly additional times that include high foot-traffic hours for the Rockwell and Fulton corner. If this format is proposed, this must include a plan for artwork that is also installed permanently in the space while the artist is not present. Note: open flame is not allowed in this space.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Window Residencies. &lt;br/&gt;Artists may propose an activation project. This can include being present in the Window Gallery during certain hours to showcase their making process or other interactive opportunities for visitors to UrbanGlass. The artist must include in their proposal an explanation of what artwork will be installed permanently in the space while the artist is not present.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To apply, please submit: a proposal, your resume or CV, exhibition design using the Window Gallery map below, exhibition budget draft, 5 images, and an image list.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details of materials for applications:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposal, one page long in PDF format, that outlines your intent for an exhibition in the Window Gallery. Maximum of 800 words. Please include your preference, for an opening date for an exhibition in 2020: May 2020, July 2020, September 2020, November 2020. Each exhibition is scheduled to run for approximately 2 months. Typically UrbanGlass hosts an opening reception on the opening week of the show. &lt;br/&gt;Resume or CV, one page long, PDF format, which lists your involvement at UrbanGlass (If applicable). Maximum of 500 words. &lt;br/&gt;A draft of the exhibition you have in mind and how it will be laid out in the space. Feel free to use the Window Gallery map below to draw/ design how you plan to utilize this space. UrbanGlass understands if this design shifts slightly from your original plan, but any dramatic shifts from the originally proposed exhibition design must be approved by UrbanGlass staff. &lt;br/&gt;Exhibition budget draft, which includes how you plan to use the honorarium included with this opportunity. &lt;br/&gt;5 images that represent your proposal and showcases the work that you intend to show in the Window Gallery. Images must be in JPG format and be 300 DPI. Maximum size of 6 inches in height and width. Each image should be a maximum of 8M each. Label each image with your last name and the number in the order in which you would like the image to be viewed. Example: Smith_01.jpg.&lt;br/&gt;Image List, in PDF format, which includes: title, size, date, and materials. &lt;br/&gt;Artists who have shown in the Window Gallery previous to 2017, can apply for this opportunity with new work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Please consider printing out your materials as a test-run before submitting them, to make sure that the application easily prints from any computer.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists will receive a stipend of $500 to use for all supplies needed, including hardware, to install artwork in the space. Artists are responsible for both installation and de-installation of Window Gallery exhibitions. This includes wall repair during de-installation, i.e., patching and sanding of any holes or blemishes created by the artist. If you need assistance in installing or de-installing the work, please consider including the expense of an art handler in your exhibition budget draft. Because the gallery staff is so small, they are unable to dedicate time to assist in this part of the process.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists whose exhibitions are selected for this exhibition opportunity are asked to provide the following 3 months prior to the opening of their show in the space: 3-4 images of works in the show, a brief artist bio, exhibition essay (max 800 words), and a final budget draft. 1 month prior to the exhibition opening artists submit a completed loan agreement and title list (with insurance values). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission deadline: Wednesday, January 22, 2020 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;How to apply: Send and email to opportunities@urbanglass.org with the subject line "2020 Window Gallery Application." &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposals are evaluated by a panel of artists and curators. All artists submitting a proposal will be notified of the jury’s decision by March 3rd, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;opportunities@urbanglass.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6afe1573-c076-4a04-837b-8a40b5457fe5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>26bbe9dd-8f9c-46a7-ae13-f94fd7d32884</id><title>2/14 - 33rd Annual McNeese National Works on Paper Exhibition</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164068+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;McNeese State University, Department of Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Lake Charles, LA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Interdisciplinary/Hybrid&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/14/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.mcneeseartonline.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 33rd Annual McNeese National Works on Paper Exhibition will be juried by Eleanor Heartney, art critic and contributing editor to Art in America and Artpress.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$3,000 is available for purchase awards. The awards will become part of the McNeese’s Works on Paper Permanent Collection.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible for entry are works in any medium that is on or of paper. The artwork, including frame, should not exceed 40 inches in any dimension. The prospectus may be copied or downloaded from:      www.mcneeseartonline.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A non-refundable entry fee of $35 is charged each entrant. This fee entitles the artist a maximum of three entries. The deadline for entry is February 14, 2020. Entries are submitted using the CaFÉ™ website www.callforentry.org. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition will be on view from March 26 through May 8, 2020 in the Grand Gallery, Shearman Fine Arts Annex, McNeese State University, Lake Charles, Louisiana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MEDIA SPECIFICATIONS &lt;br/&gt;Work in any medium using paper as a component part is eligible. Artwork, including frame, should not exceed 40” in any dimension.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY &lt;br/&gt;Open to all artists living in the United States. All artwork should be original and completed in the last two years.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION &lt;br/&gt;Accepted artwork must be suitable for formal gallery presentation as well as the rigors of packaged shipping.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRIES &lt;br/&gt;Artists may submit no more than three entries. Entries are submitted using the CaFÉ™ website www.callforentry.org. &lt;br/&gt;You may prep your materials in advance by following these specifications below: &lt;br/&gt;File format - JPEG or JPG &lt;br/&gt;File dimension - minimum 1,200 pixels on the longest side &lt;br/&gt;File size - under 5 MB&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEE &lt;br/&gt;A non-refundable entry fee of $35 is charged each entrant. This fee entitles the artist to a maximum of three entries. Credit card payments are accepted using the CaFÉ™ website. Entries will be marked complete upon receipt of payment. The prospectus may be copied or downloaded from:      www.mcneeseartonline.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DELIVERY OF ACCEPTED WORK&lt;br/&gt;Please ship work to: &lt;br/&gt;33rd Annual McNeese National Works on Paper Exhibition &lt;br/&gt;McNeese State University/Dept. of Visual Arts &lt;br/&gt;4205 Ryan St.&lt;br/&gt;Lake Charles, LA 70609&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Works must be received by March 13. &lt;br/&gt;• C.O.D. deliveries will not be accepted. &lt;br/&gt;• All accepted works must include prepaid return shipping label. &lt;br/&gt;• Late or damaged shipments will be returned collect. &lt;br/&gt;• Works must be shipped in reusable packing cartons.&lt;br/&gt;• NO PACKING POPCORN &lt;br/&gt;• Hand deliveries accepted March 10-13 (9 a.m. to 4 p.m.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RETURN OF ACCEPTED WORKS &lt;br/&gt;Return of artwork begins ...May 14 &lt;br/&gt;Hand delivery pick up ..........May 19 (9 a.m. to 4 p.m.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY &lt;br/&gt;All reasonable care will be given to objects in the custody of the Department of Visual Arts. Works are insured while on exhibition in the Grand Gallery.  The Department of Visual Arts cannot assume responsibility for the damage or deterioration incurred before or after exhibition, or for possible loss in transit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SALES AND REPRODUCTION &lt;br/&gt;While no commission will be charged on purchase prize awards, a 40 percent commission will be charged on all other artists’s sales by the Grand Gallery. The exhibition committee reserves the right to reproduce accepted entries in press releases, catalog and on the website.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CONTACT INFORMATION &lt;br/&gt;McNeese State University Department of Visual Arts &lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Coordinator, Heather Ryan Kelley &lt;br/&gt;Phone: 337-475-5060 (office), 337-475-5927 (fax)&lt;br/&gt;Email: hkelley@mcneese.edu &lt;br/&gt;Mailing address:&lt;br/&gt;33rd Annual McNeese National Works on Paper Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;McNeese State University/Dept. of Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;4205 Ryan St.&lt;br/&gt;Lake Charles, LA 70609&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CATALOG&lt;br/&gt;Each entrant will receive a copy of the exhibition catalog. Additional catalogs may be obtained at the cost of $2.50.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/26bbe9dd-8f9c-46a7-ae13-f94fd7d32884" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2f5cbb6a-d06b-49d0-8779-65201d278b6f</id><title>1/31 - Call for Proposals: Large Window Installations</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.164031+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Chashama&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/31/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.chashama.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your interest in Chashama’s Fordham Plaza 2020 Application&lt;br/&gt;-3 Presentations will be installed January 2020 - June 2020.&lt;br/&gt;-Presentations Start: January, March and May 2020&lt;br/&gt;-Applications will be viewed on a rolling basis.&lt;br/&gt;-Deadline to Apply:  January 31st, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Chashama, in collaboration with the Department of Transportation, is offering presentation space to artists in a highly visible location on Fordham Road. The building provides unobstructed floor to ceiling windows that let in a plethora of natural light, while the surrounding area is a hub for commuters, shoppers, &amp; students alike.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The first group presentation is currently up for public viewing January - February 2020.  We are currently looking for compelling window installations that will be curated into two group presentations between March 1, 2020 and June 30, 2020. Artwork will be exposed to a high volume of pedestrian traffic to admire, enjoy &amp; be inspired by.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE EXHIBITION SPACE&lt;br/&gt;-Located directly in Fordham Plaza&lt;br/&gt;-Exhibition windows are approximately 11'5'' tall&lt;br/&gt;-The Space is closed to the public, so the installations will be outward facing&lt;br/&gt;-There is access to a bathroom &amp; slop sink inside the space&lt;br/&gt;-Near to Fordham University, New York Botanical Garden, Bronx Public Library, Poe Park, as well as plenty of cafes and shopping centers.&lt;br/&gt;-Closest MTA train stop - B/D Fordham Road&lt;br/&gt;-Closest MetroNorth Stop - Fordham Road station on the Harlem, New Haven, and New Canaan Metro-North lines is located directly across the street.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;REQUIRED MATERIALS&lt;br/&gt;-CV&lt;br/&gt;-Artist Bio (500 words or less)&lt;br/&gt;-Artist Statement (1500 words or less)&lt;br/&gt;-5-10 images or video of recent work (.jpg, .png, .tiff)  that relate to the artist statement&lt;br/&gt;-Two (2) professional references - name, contact information, and how you know each other&lt;br/&gt;-Brief Presentation Proposal with a description of how you will display your work&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important things to note:&lt;br/&gt;-Installations will be on display for a 2 month period.&lt;br/&gt;-All pieces should be family friendly.&lt;br/&gt;-3-4 Artists or Collectives will participate per exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;-Ideally, installation should either fill an entire window or make use of the window height.&lt;br/&gt;-Artists must be available to install their work.&lt;br/&gt;-Presentations will be organized by independent curator Laura James.&lt;br/&gt;-Presenting artists will receive a stipend, which is determined based on a variety of factors.&lt;br/&gt;-Artists should be available for a studio visit.&lt;br/&gt;-Exhibitors keep 100% of the price for any work sold in the space. Inquiries and all sales of work are made through the artist.  Inquiries/Sales are not managed by Chashama, Laura James or the NYC DOT.  &lt;br/&gt;-Access to Materials for the Arts (MFTA) is available on a limited basis&lt;br/&gt;-Exhibitors are fully responsible for the installation and deinstallation of their presentation and for setting up any technical equipment or displays. Chashama does not provide art transportation, hanging materials or tools.&lt;br/&gt;-Exhibitors are responsible for leaving the space in the same condition that they received it in, or better; Chashama provides materials for restoration.&lt;br/&gt;-There is a Security Deposit of $100 due at the time of signing presentation agreement. Deposits are refunded in full, if the space is returned in the same condition as it was received.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply here:&lt;br/&gt;https://chashama.submittable.com/submit/153541/space-to-connect-fordham-plaza-2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please do not hesitate to reach out to spacetoconnect@chashama.org if you have any issues or questions regarding this form. We are happy to support you throughout the application process.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2f5cbb6a-d06b-49d0-8779-65201d278b6f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>12252d2e-b5b8-4bad-a896-5a7992531102</id><title>1/22 - Call for Curatorial Proposals featuring the Art of Immigrant Artists</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163990+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Chashama&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/22/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.chashama.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your interest in the Space to Connect: Call for Immigrant Artists Application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Chashama is offering presentation space to curators, collectives and/or artists who will showcase the work of Immigrant artists at 340 E 64th Street (Upper East Side, NYC). We are looking for curators, collectives and/or artists who have an interest in engaging the community through showcasing visual art, but also through hosting workshops, performances, screenings, talks, etc. The space has a large garden level window, on a street that has regular foot traffic.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As is noted, this application is specifically for proposals that feature the art of Immigrant artists.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This application form is specific to the venue.  Please read the following information completely before applying.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notes about this Opportunity:&lt;br/&gt;-Chashama is organizing 4 shows featuring the art of Immigrant Artists from December 2019 through the end of June 2020.&lt;br/&gt;-The first show, Progressive Transition, was part of the 2019 Latin American Art Triennial.&lt;br/&gt;-The dates of the next 3 shows are as follows:&lt;br/&gt;               ▲ February 12th - March 10th&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;               ▲ April 8th - May 5th&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;               ▲ June 2nd - June 30th&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-This application is open to everyone, but the majority of the artists featured in the proposed shows should be immigrants.  In addition, immigrant curators will receive priority.&lt;br/&gt;-Community Engagement/Events are mandatory for each show.  &lt;br/&gt;-There is funding for each show, according to a stipend schedule.&lt;br/&gt;-We encourage applicants to visit the current show to get a sense of the space.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What You Should Know Before Applying:&lt;br/&gt;-Submitting your proposal indicates that your exhibition is ready to be programmed, or will be ready by the preferred dates included in the proposal.&lt;br/&gt;-Once programmed, exhibitors are responsible for scheduling and staffing 20 open hours per week. Please note, workshops, performances, and other events count toward the weekly open hours.&lt;br/&gt;-This venue requires a refundable $275 deposit for the use of the space. The payment of this deposit may not come from any grant and is due at signing.&lt;br/&gt;-Exhibitors will keep 100% of the price for any work sold in the space. Chashama does not take a cut.&lt;br/&gt;-Exhibitors are responsible for programming their exhibit. All work on display must be family-friendly; no nudity, violence/gore, profanity, etc. Chashama reserves the right to deny the showing of any artwork deemed inappropriate.&lt;br/&gt;-Exhibitors are fully responsible for the installation and deinstallation of their presentation and for setting up any technical equipment or displays. Chashama does not provide hanging materials or tools.&lt;br/&gt;-Exhibitors are responsible for leaving the space in the same condition that they received it in, or better; Chashama provides materials for restoration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Materials You Will Need to Apply:&lt;br/&gt;-CV in PDF form&lt;br/&gt;-2 Professional References (someone you have worked with or who knows you as an artist or curator).&lt;br/&gt;-Presentation Proposal (500 words or less)&lt;br/&gt;-Artist or Curator Statement (500 words or less)&lt;br/&gt;-Community Engagement Proposal (1 page)&lt;br/&gt;-10 images of recent work (.jpg, .png, .tiff) that relate to the proposal. If proposal is for an installation, one of the 5 images should be a layout sketch. For video work, include 5 stills and a link to externally-hosted videos.&lt;br/&gt;-Preferred dates for presentation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notes about the Space:&lt;br/&gt;-The space is garden level, and has a large window.&lt;br/&gt;-There is a bathroom and a small amount of storage space onsite.&lt;br/&gt;-Build out of the space is possible with approval from Chashama.&lt;br/&gt;-There is WIFI in the form of a hotspot, which is fixed to a location in the space.&lt;br/&gt;-Unfortunately, the space is not ADA accessible. The space is accessed by approx. 5 steps and there is no ramp. There are some uneven aspects to the gallery floor.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following informational documents may be found online:&lt;br/&gt;               ▲ Floorplan&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;                ▲ Photos of previous shows, workshops&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;                ▲ Agreement for space - (for reference only)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;                ▲ Community engagement requirements&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;                ▲ Stipend Schedule&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please complete application here: &lt;br/&gt;https://chashama.submittable.com/submit/155303/space-to-present-call-for-curatorialproposals-featuring-the-art-of-immigrant-ar&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/12252d2e-b5b8-4bad-a896-5a7992531102" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8308758f-bdc3-4bb8-a00f-6060f9d97daf</id><title>2/28 - Call For Artists: The Other Art Fair Chicago</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163954+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Other Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 Chicago, IL, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/28/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://chicago.theotherartfair.com/applications"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Other Art Fair returns to Chicago this summer for its third edition in a brand new, brilliant location, Skylight at the Board of Trade Chicago, May 27-30 2020  The Other Art Fair provides a unique platform for artists to showcase their work to gallerists, curators, critics and collectors. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Presented by leading online gallery Saatchi Art, the fair is recognized as the definitive place for buyers to discover exciting and emerging talent. In addition to artwork sales, these four days enable artists to launch their work in the contemporary art world, gauge the public’s response to their pieces and meet fellow artists for potential future collaborations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As part of our exciting collaboration with leading online gallery Saatchi Art, exhibitors will be presented as fair artists to an extensive network of curators, collectors, interior designers and international buyers via saatchiart.com/theotherartfair, social media and the Canvas blog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online now: &lt;a href="http://chicago.theotherartfair.com/applications" target="_blank"&gt;http://chicago.theotherartfair.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Deadline for applications: February 28, 2020&lt;br/&gt;There is no application fee. Stand fees start at $1,680 + sales tax.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions? Please contact Sasha Ali, Fair Assistant, sasha@theotherartfair.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8308758f-bdc3-4bb8-a00f-6060f9d97daf" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f3f49394-ab60-4b0d-86d9-5f705f5f0544</id><title>Open Call for Solo Show or Group Show curatorial proposals</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163847+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open&lt;br/&gt;📍 LIC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply to curate or exhibit at The Gallery LIC, a premier 2000 sq. foot art-space in the heart of New York located in The Factory. We are seeking curators and artist-curators for solo and group shows.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Successful applicants will be notified within 4 weeks of submission and will have 1 week to confirm. Exhibition contribution fee for confirmed shows is $500. This fee will cover curatorial support, installation, hospitality, signage and promotion. Exhibitions will run for three weeks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application fee $30&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note that all work must be hand-delivered to the Factory and ready to hang. Therefore, while we encourage artists from outside of the NYC metro-area to apply, please be aware we cannot accept work that is shipped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply with this form.  The form requires images.  If you are not sure which images would be relevant please submit an image from a previous show or exhibition:&lt;br/&gt;Please cut and paste into your browser:&lt;br/&gt;https://form.jotform.com/trimistopheles/-call-for-group-or-solo-show-partic&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f3f49394-ab60-4b0d-86d9-5f705f5f0544" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ef2292ca-0f70-4da0-ac02-a7c1af08a341</id><title>3/1 - Call for submissions: Brooklyn Utopias 2020</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163812+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Old Stone House&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/01/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://theoldstonehouse.org/event/call-for-submissions-brooklyn-utopias-2020/2020-01-15/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An exhibition at the Old Stone House &amp; Washington Park, curated by Katherine Gressel&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: March 1, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: August 20 –October 18, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE EXHIBITION &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;"Utopia:" An ideal place or state, usually imaginary; any visionary system of political, social, environmental, or moral perfection&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- What would characterize a Brooklyn Utopia?&lt;br/&gt;- How has Brooklyn changed in the past decade (for the better or worse)?&lt;br/&gt;- What is the role of artists in creating a more ideal Brooklyn?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Brooklyn Utopias: 2020 will address Brooklyn’s past, present and future by inviting artists to consider differing visions of an ideal Brooklyn, or imagine their own. It corresponds with the 10-year anniversary of the original Brooklyn Utopias? exhibitions series developed by curator Katherine Gressel and presented at Old Stone House (OSH) among other sites in 2009-2010. At a time of reflection on the past decade, OSH invites artists to explore how Brooklyn has continued to change over the past 10 years, and if/how it can serve as a model for urban and American living on a national scale, especially in the months leading up to the 2020 election. Brooklyn Utopias also addresses the possibilities (or limitations) of art in creating a better world. We welcome submissions from artists based in or exploring issues in our surrounding Gowanus/Park Slope/Sunset Park area, as well as a range of diverse Brooklyn neighborhoods. In addition to an August opening reception, we plan to host a closing event during the annual Gowanus Open Studios, October 15, 16 or 17, focused on the future of the arts in this neighborhood. As with all our exhibitions, we also encourage projects that engage with our unique history and space; this exhibition will be featured in our annual Battle Week events calendar celebrating the anniversary of the Revolutionary War Battle of Brooklyn, which took place on OSH grounds.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please visit the open call link on our website for more information on the the Brooklyn Utopias series, as well as our history and exhibition space: &lt;a href="https://theoldstonehouse.org/event/call-for-submissions-brooklyn-utopias-2020/2020-01-15/" target="_blank"&gt;https://theoldstonehouse.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Projects in all media are welcome (though see “exhibit specifications” on our website for specific requirements). As in the past, we are also interested in commissioning public art for the surrounding Washington Park, and artwork created with the participation of local community groups or schools–please contact OSH in advance if you’d like us to help try to match you with a community partner organization.  We are also open to temporary indoor or outdoor event proposals that engage with this theme, from both artists and community organizations. Artists are especially encouraged to propose community workshops that complement artwork on view in the gallery (as opposed to stand-alone events). Due to OSH’s busy event calendar, public programs will be arranged at mutually convenient times, based on OSH’s availability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TO SUBMIT – &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please email the following to Katherine Gressel, curator at  katherinegressel@gmail.com, by 11:59 PST on March 1, 2020 with the email subject line “Brooklyn Utopias Submission” &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. Brief description (approx. 1 paragraph or 500 words) of proposed project–please address how it engages the exhibition theme!  &lt;br/&gt;** If you are a returning artist proposing an update to a previous Brooklyn Utopias project, please address how it will be modified to reflect more recent events. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2. Up to 10 images/videos of the proposed project and/or related work, or send links to images/videos online. Sketches of proposed new work are ok. Please attach a work sample script explaining the content of the work samples, or link to captions online. NOTE: if you are proposing a public program/performance, please share info on any related programs/events you have previously produced. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3. Funding request (if any): OSH is dedicated to offering at minimum a $150 honorarium for all participating artists. Additional funds may be available, especially to cover materials/transport costs for new and site specific work. OSH can also sometimes assist artists in applying for their own grants, or with crowdfunding.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4. Attach or link to artist resume or bio&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;** Artists/organizations are encouraged to contact the curator in advance to discuss ideas or to arrange a studio visit, and to visit the OSH exhibition space **&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ef2292ca-0f70-4da0-ac02-a7c1af08a341" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9b18a1bf-3c4c-428f-ba01-1f091bbd3a6c</id><title>2/7 - Animation Nation - OPEN CALL</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163780+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open&lt;br/&gt;📍 LIC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/07/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open invites artists who have created a character that is near and dear to share these personas in a utopian group show, "Animation Nation," opening Thursday, February 20th. Characters reflect facets of ourselves and grow, develop and die just as we do. Let's join and meet one another's!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We invite artists of all disciplines and mediums to participate in this group show at LIC Arts Open's Gallery ONE at The Factory LIC, 30-30 47th Ave, LIC, 11101, a premier 2000 sq. ft. art space.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We accept all disciplines including painting, performance, sculpture, photography, video, installation and multi-media. Video equipment is not provided. If your project requires technology please state so on your application and the equipment you will provide.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Dates&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline February 7th x Notification February 10th&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art drop-off February 15th at The Factory LIC between 2 PM - 5 PM.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Opening reception February 20th, 5 PM - 8 PM.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art pick up March 14th and 15th between 12 PM - 5 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fees&lt;br/&gt;Please note there is an application fee that offsets the installation costs and helps to pay for the refreshments. If you have previously participated please select option 2 otherwise if new to LIC Arts Open please select option 1.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork&lt;br/&gt;Work must be ready to hang. We do not allow shipping; all work must be hand-delivered on the designated times and dates.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Gallery commission is 25%. Please price accordingly.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Information&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Standard Artwork Drop off&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork must be ready to hang with appropriate fixings. Please know that some walls are the cinderblock/cement and others are drywall. If you are bringing a sculptural or video work, please provide the necessary technology.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have proposed performance or other live work (an installation, etc.) we will contact you directly with further information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Please take/remove your wrappings at drop off unless you are fine with it being disposed of; we do not have storage for wrappings, boxes, bubble wrap, etc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Storage&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;While we are open to NY artists from all boroughs all work must be hand-delivered in person (i.e. either yourself or someone dropping off in your place). If you live in another city but can drop off and pick up the work at the specified dates and times then please feel free to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no storage option; by completing and submitting this application you agree to pick up on the dates listed above (3/14 &amp; 3/15 btwn 2 pm - 5 pm). The inability to do so will release the ownership and work to the disposal of the Factory as they see fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please cut and paste this link and use the form to submit: &lt;a href="https://form.jotform.com/200126806356955" target="_blank"&gt;https://form.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9b18a1bf-3c4c-428f-ba01-1f091bbd3a6c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cc558169-3276-40be-98a1-8fc30bba2462</id><title>2/5 - Starta ARTA</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163748+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Starta Arta&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/05/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.startaarta.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;STARTA ARTA seeks art for inclusion in a pop-up art show. Located in the heart of New York’s bustling business district Flatiron, STARTA ARTA provides space for artists to show and gain exposure and connections with a community from different industries. The call is open to artists who recently graduated from art schools (graduated from 2014 to 2019). The exhibition will be held at STRATA ARTA exhibition space in 220 23 rd Street, Manhattan, NY from March 5 to March 8, 2020. An opening reception will be held on Thursday March 5, 2020 from 6pm to 8pm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists may submit up to five works. All types of work can be submitted including painting, drawing, collage, sculpture, printmaking, photography, video, installation and performance. Artwork must be installation-ready and appropriately framed. All works must be for sale. The entry fee is $ 20 (via PayPal @ StartaArta@gmail.com ). Selected artists will be responsible for delivery and pick-up. Artists will receive a confirmation email upon receipt of submission and if selected for the show. The deadline for submission is 8pm, February 5, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cc558169-3276-40be-98a1-8fc30bba2462" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>830571af-7a14-4b31-b12f-0666344aa62b</id><title>2/11 - Focus: Shadow and Light</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163715+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/11/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on shadow and light in photography at Black Box Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/830571af-7a14-4b31-b12f-0666344aa62b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>10c5680a-1bcd-4eb0-8efd-d0e413fdfb33</id><title>2/4 - Wide Open 11: National Juried Show</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163679+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;BROOKLYN WATERFRONT ARTISTS COALTION&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/04/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://bwac.org/national-juried-art-show-nyc-may-9-june-21-2020/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce our eleventh annual national juried art show, Wide Open 11 opening May 9, 2020.  This year we are privileged and delighted to have returning to BWAC as a juror one of New York’s very knowledgeable curators, Paulina Pobocha, of MoMA.  With her guidance and selections, we look forward to another spectacular show.&lt;br/&gt;Ours is a truly unique and generous space – a beautiful stone Civil War‐era warehouse overlooking New York Harbor from the piers of Red Hook, in  Brooklyn NY. We welcome the opportunity to exhibit unusually large work, and look forward to exhibiting artwork from all around the country, work in all sizes, and subjects, and media. Virtually every medium is accepted including: Oil, Acrylic, Pastel, Watercolor, Photography, Drawing, Print, Mixed Media, Sculpture, Assemblage, Installation*, and Textile..&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Call to Artists for Submissions:&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility: This call for submission is open to all residents of the U.S. and its Territories 18 years of age or older. This is a juried exhibition for artists working in all traditional and non‐traditional 2D and 3D media, *including film/video only when part of an Installation. Works may be submitted in one or multiple media. All artwork must be original in concept, design and execution. Limited edition prints/photographs are accepted. Artwork not meeting the criteria, although juried, may be rejected. Note: Kit work or reproductions of original works in other media (such as giclee prints of oil paintings), unless used as part of a mixed media work, will not be considered.&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: Early Bird: February 4, 2020; Final Application Deadline: March 2, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition Dates: Saturday May 9 – Sunday June 21, 2020; weekends 1‐ 6P.M.&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Saturday May 9, 2020 from 1 ‐ 6 P.M.&lt;br/&gt;Theme:&lt;br/&gt;The broad theme of Wide Open 11 encompasses all the possibilities of knowledge and freedom and love ‐ wide open spaces…arms wide open…eyes wide open ‐ but as with all things, there is the inevitable opposite ‐ wide open to attack…corruption…failure. What kind of fantasy is this? What does it really indicate? This juried show looks to explore the idea of “wide open” in all the hidden niches of our collective psyche.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Applications will be process via www.smarterentry.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Register/Login into the Client account and read all instructions for this show.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/10c5680a-1bcd-4eb0-8efd-d0e413fdfb33" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>33403d35-2d97-4baf-b0f7-33fb5f3c4f22</id><title>3/1 - Call for Artists: 42nd Annual Artexpo New York &amp;amp; [SOLO]</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163644+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Redwood Media Group&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/01/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.artexponewyork.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jumpstart your career in the new decade by applying to show your work at the world's longest-running art far: Artexpo New York! Following a smashing 41st edition in 2019, which saw record-breaking sales and attendance figures, Artexpo New York, [SOLO], and [FOTO SOLO] return to Pier 94 for the 42nd edition April 23–26, 2020.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For 40+ years, Artexpo New York has earned the distinction of being the world’s largest fine art marketplace.  As in past years, we’ll be co-locating with [SOLO], and  [FOTO SOLO] section, featuring collections of fine art photography. Artexpo connects artists, galleries, and publishers with art buyers, art dealers, interior designers, architects, and collectors. It’s an art- and design-packed weekend no industry professional should miss. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Wondering what makes each show unique? Here’s a bit of info about each: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artexpo Pavilion:&lt;br/&gt;The Artexpo Pavilion features well-established galleries, art publishers, artist collectives, and professional artists. Within the main pavilion, the Platinum Pavilion features new collections from key local and international galleries. Our Exhibitor Committee selects which exhibitors will be featured in the Platinum Pavilion.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[SOLO] Pavilion:&lt;br/&gt;Are you an established and emerging independent artist ready to showcase work on an international stage? The [SOLO] Pavilion is a curated exhibition of independent artists.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Rising Artist Gallery:&lt;br/&gt;Not quite ready for your own [SOLO] exhibit? Unable to make it to New York? The Rising Artist Gallery offers shared exhibition space and a professional sales team for emerging artists who are unable to attend or only wish to exhibit a few pieces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[FOTO SOLO] Pavilion:&lt;br/&gt;Are you a fine art photographer looking to broaden your market reach? The [FOTO SOLO] Pavilion features collections of fine art photography from some of the world’s finest photographers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A wide array of media is on display at Artexpo New York, including paintings, photography, sculpture, glassworks, and more. We do not accept jewelry, tapestries, or any sort of arts and craft works.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All applications will be juried by our Exhibitor Committee.  All exhibitors will be required to submit a portfolio or website for review. Upon acceptance from the Exhibitor Committee, a booth location will be assigned (normally within three days).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Register: &lt;a href="https://artexponewyork.com/exhibitor-application/" target="_blank"&gt;https://artexponewyork.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Email info@artexponewyork.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/33403d35-2d97-4baf-b0f7-33fb5f3c4f22" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cc1cc53b-5af2-4d98-8063-36d50050a767</id><title>1/16 - Win 200$ and a Solo Show ! Greenpoint Gallery&amp;#39;s First Open Call Salon Show of 2020!</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163608+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/16/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our First Open Salon Show of the 2020 Season!&lt;br/&gt;Join Us as We Kick off our Brand New Season of awesome exhibits in 2020!&lt;br/&gt;In this New Year be proactive about your art career and make 2020 your year to succeed!&lt;br/&gt;FRIDAY, January 17th, 2020 at 8pm&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, January 16th at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Come celebrate the start of Our Winter/Spring season  and invite your friends to see or participate in this great showcase of local talent!&lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/307209356863044/&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! This is a juried event and runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show and with other runner-up winners! Give the great gift of art to your loved ones while supporting your artistic community!&lt;br/&gt;It’s the best show of the year, so come celebrate the holiday season with us and GET YOUR ART ON! &lt;br/&gt;Submissions are now open.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We have two floors of Gallery Space and a stellar lineup of local bands and musicians sure to entertain, so mark your calendars.&lt;br/&gt;FRIDAY, January 17th at 8pm&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit JPEG's or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive ready to hang. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, January 16th at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces in the $150-$500 range. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/307209356863044/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit JPEG's or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cc1cc53b-5af2-4d98-8063-36d50050a767" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c5b197e9-fdd0-4ae4-88f2-9a365cd7ef31</id><title>2/10 - Take it to the Streets - Past and ongoing movements that support global equal rights</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163551+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LiC-A @ The Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/10/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.licartists.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Description of Exhibition:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An Exhibition inspired by the Centennial celebration for Woman’s suffrage&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;March 31, 1776: In a letter to her husband, Founding Father John Adams, future first lady Abigail Adams makes a plea to him and the Continental Congress “If particular care and attention is not paid to the ladies, we are determined to foment a rebellion, and will not hold ourselves bound by any laws in which we have no voice or representation.” This exhibition celebrates the past and ongoing movements that support global equal rights for all.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This Exhibition is open to artists of all genders and countries that support equal rights and wish to express their activism through any medium including video, film, sculpture, virtual reality, painting, photography, performance art, dance etc. These works should serve as a reflection of the past and a reminder for all the work that is still upon us to create a world with equal rights for all. Rights are not just handed to everyone but rather require an ongoing dialogue.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The encompassing theme is about taking action for equal rights for all. Artists are invited to explore different movements from the past and present:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Examples: First Wave of Feminism (1920s Suffrage centennial), 2nd Wave (1960s/70s - EPA), 3rd Wave (90s - Punk), 4th Wave (#MeToo).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition will be divided into two parts, a dark room for technology related artwork(video mapping, film, light boxes etc) that requires a darker area and a regularly lit gallery for all other artworks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Invited Artists:&lt;br/&gt;Caroline Voagen Nelson&lt;br/&gt;Ruth Sergel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To apply please copy and paste the below link into your browser or visit us at www.licartists.org for more information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_take_it_to_the_streets&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c5b197e9-fdd0-4ae4-88f2-9a365cd7ef31" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>60a69c1f-d08d-478d-8ad6-394127ecac9f</id><title>1/10 - **Call For Artists: The Other Art Fair Brooklyn**  Brooklyn Expo Center, April 30 - May 3, 2020</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163513+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Other Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/10/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://nyc.theotherartfair.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Other Art Fair returns to the Brooklyn Expo Center, April 30 - May 3, 2020!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Other Art Fair provides a unique platform for artists to showcase their work to gallerists, curators, critics and collectors. Presented by leading online gallery Saatchi Art, the fair is recognized as the definitive place for buyers to discover exciting and emerging talent. In addition to artwork sales, these four days enable artists to launch their work in the contemporary art world, gauge the public’s response to their pieces and meet fellow artists for potential future collaborations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Other Art Fair in Brooklyn in November 2019 welcomed over 12,000 visitors and attracted representatives from many esteemed New York galleries and cultural institutions such as Gagosian Gallery, Pace Gallery, Elizabeth Dee Gallery, The Museum of Modern Art, The Metropolitan Museum of Art and Christie’s. This reception was met with numerous sales, commissions and post fair collaborations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply online now: &lt;a href="http://nyc.theotherartfair.com/applications" target="_blank"&gt;http://nyc.theotherartfair.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for applications: January 10&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no application fee. Stand fees start at $1,880 + sales tax.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As part of our exciting collaboration with leading online gallery Saatchi Art, exhibitors will be presented as fair artists to an extensive network of curators, collectors, interior designers and international buyers via saatchiart.com/theotherartfair, social media and the Canvas blog.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions? Please contact Sasha Ali, Fair Assistant, sasha@theotherartfair.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online now: &lt;a href="http://nyc.theotherartfair.com/applications" target="_blank"&gt;http://nyc.theotherartfair.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for applications: January 10&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no application fee. Stand fees start at $1,880 + sales tax.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/60a69c1f-d08d-478d-8ad6-394127ecac9f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>30bc275f-99a0-44d6-8b1f-54a99d2ebe69</id><title>1/14 - Solo Shows 2020-2021 at Locust Grove Estate</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163471+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Barrett Art Center (Dutchess County Art Association)&lt;br/&gt;📍 Poughkeepsie, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/14/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.barrettartcenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Locust Grove Estate, is partnering with Barrett Art Center to announce four Solo Show opportunities in 2020-2021.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each 10-12 week show presents artists with the opportunity to present a solo show of 20-30 artworks in the Transverse Gallery in the Visitor Center at Locust Grove, a National Historic Landmark museum, education center, and nature preserve which attracts over 90,000 visitors annually.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;http://www.lgny.org/&lt;br/&gt;http://www.barrettartcenter.org/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Locust Grove was the nineteenth-century country estate of Samuel Morse, who, in addition to inventing the telegraph and Morse Code, was an artist and the founder of the National Academy of Design. In the twentieth century, the estate was owned by Poughkeepsie’s prominent Young family, noted collectors of Hudson River School paintings and the founders of the museum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Barrett Art Center works with curators from around the globe to bring exemplary contemporary art from international artists to its exhibitions in the Hudson Valley. Our reputation for high-quality exhibitions and programs attracts thousands of art enthusiasts to our 1840s Greek Revival townhouse-turned gallery annually. Arts professionals from Barrett Art Center are part of the curatorial team juroring the shows.&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Information&lt;br/&gt; Solo shows are available for 2-D artwork. Please note the galleries are frequented by visitors of all ages, including school groups. Artists’ discretion is requested. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We encourage artists to develop new works of art for this exhibition opportunity. If selected for a solo show, the images submitted for review do not necessarily have to be among the works exhibited. In an effort to give artists time to prepare, solo shows are being offered now for July 2020 through June 2021. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted artwork must be properly mounted, framed and ready to hang from a track-type hanging system. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork may be either for sale or for exhibition only. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Terms for sale of artwork: artist receives 75%; commission is 25% &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Recommended number of works for display is 20-30 pieces, depending on size. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Locust Grove reserves the right to not exhibit any artwork that does not meet our display criteria. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BAC Members, please email info@barrettartcenter.org or call us at 845-471-2550 for coupon code to receive discount.  To become a member, visit, www.barrettartcenter.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applications can be made directly to: &lt;br/&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=7280&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/30bc275f-99a0-44d6-8b1f-54a99d2ebe69" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b9975c53-321d-4755-b191-ed432ffefc22</id><title>Calling All Female Artists, Musicians, Writers &amp;amp; Witches! Everywhere!</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163342+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;OyeDrum&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OyeDrum is a soon-to-be launched feminist online magazine, project, and community, dedicated to international female voices in the arts and writing, encouraging the experimental. We provide a platform for all types of work and exploration in creative writing, performance and visual art, conceptual art, multimedia, and hybrid work as well by women only.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you a writer or poet? Fabulous! Send us your essay, short-short story, flash fiction, creative nonfiction piece, traditional or non traditional poem, etc. Are you an illustrator or photographer? Super! We need images along with published words. Do you have a soundcloud account with original music you composed in your bedroom? Send it! Is it a spoken word piece? Is it abstract? Is it surreal? Send it!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are most interested in creative pieces with substance that evokes memory, feeling, thought, or straight-up invokes a spirit or deity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are seeking original material, i.e. never been published anywhere, but we are willing to accept work that’s been previously published on your personal platform - like a blog, tumblr, etc. It’s a case-by-case situation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Everyone submitting must include a brief, third person bio - keep it short!  Please include a short cover letter introducing yourself and your work, and attach a photograph or illustration of yourself. Please clarify the genre of your work on the subject line of your email.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You may send multiple submission and simultaneous submissions, but we ask that you please let us know if your work is accepted elsewhere. Submissions are free and accepted on a rolling basis. However, if you would like us to consider including your work in our opening issue, the deadline to submit is January 15th, 2020. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CREATIVE WRITING:&lt;br/&gt;Send us up to two pieces with a word limit is 4,000 words, double spaced. Submit as a Word file- no PDFs, please! Flash fiction word count limit is 1,000. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;POETRY AND PROSE: &lt;br/&gt;You may send up to 10 pages of poetry, prose, or some combination thereof for consideration. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PHOTOGRAPHY AND ART: &lt;br/&gt;OyeDrum welcomes photography and art submissions to accompany the work we're publishing. Send a minimum of 5 images in a single submission—they should work together as a set. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We will post another open call after our launch. Stay tuned! We are super excited to hear back from you ladies! Although we are listed as an organizations in NYC, we are everywhere! Our OyeDrum team members can be found in New York, Texas, Scotland, and the moon. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Send your submissions and questions to submit@oyedrum.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b9975c53-321d-4755-b191-ed432ffefc22" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c4a782f4-8e11-4a8a-a017-38aa5bb9eb59</id><title>1/15 - FASHION Week NY- Call  to ARTISTS/SCULPTORS/PHOTOGRAPHERS-  NEW YORK FASHION WEEK NYFW</title><updated>2020-01-25T00:29:42.163277+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Six Summit Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/15/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.sixsummitgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK FASHION WEEK- &lt;br/&gt;Six Summit Gallery curates ART HEARTS FASHION!&lt;br/&gt;This is the Largest ongoing fine art and fashion platform in NYC, LA and Miami.  SSG currently has installations in Hudson Yards, Dag Hammarskjold Plaza and Port Authority and more. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;172 Norfolk St (lower east side) Angel Orensanz Gothic Cathedral&lt;br/&gt;New York, NY 10002&lt;br/&gt;917-573-0029&lt;br/&gt;www.sixsummitgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fashion Week: Angel Orensanz Center – Contemporary Art and Gothic Revival for “Art Hearts Fashion”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Six Summit Gallery is a leading multi-platform fine art and entertainment concern.  Art Hearts Fashion is a leading large award winning internationally known exquisite haute couture inclusive fashion platform whose designers dress some of the worlds most notable people. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Over 18  Shows- Thousands expected. Accepted artists will receive complimentary tickets for Every show and discount for friends. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;– One of the true extraordinary venues in NYC. Over 30,000 square feet, multiple levels.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art does not have to be directly fashion related but logical visual transition and of course fashion related accepted. &lt;br/&gt;Six Summit Gallery curates New York Fashion Week&lt;br/&gt;with Art Hearts Fashion.&lt;br/&gt;Art Hearts Fashion events are a leading platform for artistically inspired emerging, celebrity and couture designers to showcase their collections in a contemporary fashion week setting. AHF events have been held coast to coast as a national showcase for designers to participate in New York, Miami, Mercedes-Benz Fashion Week China and Los Angeles Fashion Week. Participating designers can be seen on every major Hollywood celebrity including: Beyoncé, Lady Gaga, Katy Perry, Nicki Minaj, Rita Ora, Jennifer Lopez, Shakira, Miley Cyrus, Carrie Underwood, and countless more. The platform is unequivocally intertwined with the causes and organizations it supports.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art Hearts Fashion to Break New Ground during NYFW with over 20 Designers at the Angel Orensanz Foundation&lt;br/&gt;(New York, New York)—Revolutionary bi-coastal fashion platform Art Hearts Fashion hosts New York Fashion Week Feb 6 -9th at the Neo-Gothic NYC landmark, the Angel Orensanz Foundation on the culturally flourishing lower east side. The Angel Orensanz Foundation, a replica of the Sistine Chapel in Rome, has long been the home for artistic and performing arts. The Cathedral will serve as the dramatic setting for NYC’s most highly attended shows this season of Art Hearts Fashion. A favorite among press and celebrities alike, this season Art Hearts Fashion brings an impressive lineup of over 20 acclaimed designers to the catwalk during 4 full days of runway shows and exclusive closing gala.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Global Juried Show by Six Summit Gallery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global Juried Show by Six Summit Gallery&lt;br/&gt;The ART and FASHION shows take place in the same room.  If you are not accepted your fee will be returned minus small processing fee which will not exceed four dollars. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Call to ARTISTS&lt;br/&gt;EMAIL SUBMISSIONS ONLY TO&lt;br/&gt;fashion@sixsummitgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBLE WORK: Paintings, Photos works in all media.This show is open to all artists regardless of place of residence however you must deliver in person and you may be responsible for hanging.  (ceilings are high/see floorplan or google Angel Orensanz Foundation. All work must be wired and ready to hang. SUBMISSIONS: All work will be judged by email entry via fashion@sixsummitgallery.com. You MUST write [YOUR NAME]” IN THE SUBJECT OF EMAIL. YOUR NAME MUST BE THE SAME ON YOUR CREDIT/DEBIT CARD Example: Subject: FASHION SUBMISSION: John Doe. Files must be in .jpg format, 300 dpi, max 900 pixels in any dimension. File name should correspond to the title of the piece. PUT title, medium, artist, price, and size as JPEG FILE EXTENSION NAME.!  No accepted work may be removed prior to the show’s conclusion (unless of course it is sold) ALL work must be for sale. Existing hanging system goes around perimeter  (we have the wires) You may not make holes n walls. Sculptors must bring their own pedestals or free standing is ok. You are required to make your own labels. They must include Title, Medium,Price, and Your Name, www.sixsummitgallery.com – with “Purchase or Inquire Now” “Call or text Leo 917-573-0029” clearly visible on the bottom below www.sixsummitgallery.com. Purchases will take place during the show- Customers can leave with art or we can help arrange delivery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: The Show Committee reserves the right to disallow the exhibition of any work which, in the opinion of the Committee, is considered detrimental to the good public image of the show and its sponsors, which is too fragile to handle, or which is not accurately represented by the photo submitted. Six Summit Gallery, Angel Orensanz, or Art Hearts Fashion its officers or agents are NOT responsible for loss or damage or theft of any. We reserve the right to photograph work or use submitted images for publicity. ENTRY FEES: $50 for up to 2 entries. $75 for up to 5 entries.  Only work submitted with fee will be considered. Easily click on www.sixsummitgallery.com online store and go to ONLINE STORE-EVENTS SUBMISSION  &lt;a href="https://sixsummitgallery.com/products/event-submissions-products" target="_blank"&gt;https://sixsummitgallery.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;and choose $50 or $75.- Please call the Gallery for any special situations.&lt;br/&gt;Artist receives 55% on accepted sold work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This show and venue is the highlight of NYFW. We expect active participating artists for this show. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;QUESTIONS CAN BE EMAILED ONLY TO: Fashion@sixsummitgallery.com Include your Call Back Number!&lt;br/&gt;DO NOT CALL OR EMAIL ANGEL ORENSANZ OR ART HEARTS FASHION&lt;br/&gt;(DATES and TIMES Subject to Change)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Delivery – February 6th,  9AM- 11AM  (you can stay and hang art or drop off only if pre arranged)&lt;br/&gt;Pick up – Feb 9th  after last show (if approved) OR Feb 10th 9-10:30AM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Show dates and times- announced on our website www.sixsummitgallery.com (click on Art Hearts Fashion link)&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c4a782f4-8e11-4a8a-a017-38aa5bb9eb59" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>