<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-20T04:17:29-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>f33365b7-d942-4066-8168-3d34634cfab3</id><title>7/19 - **Call For Artists: The Other Art Fair Brooklyn**  Brooklyn Expo Center, Nov. 7-10, 2019</title><updated>2019-06-20T04:17:29.779852+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Other Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://nyc.theotherartfair.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Other Art Fair returns to the Brooklyn Expo Center to present its final edition of 2019 (Nov. 7-10, 2019). The Other Art Fair provides a unique platform for artists to showcase their work to gallerists, curators, critics and collectors. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Presented by leading online gallery Saatchi Art, the fair is recognized as the definitive place for buyers to discover exciting and emerging talent. In addition to artwork sales, these four days enable artists to launch their work in the contemporary art world, gauge the public’s response to their pieces and meet fellow artists for potential future collaborations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Other Art Fair in Brooklyn in November 2018 welcomed over 12,300 visitors and attracted representatives from many esteemed New York galleries and cultural institutions such as Gagosian Gallery, Pace Gallery, Elizabeth Dee Gallery, The Museum of Modern Art, The Metropolitan Museum of Art and Christie’s. This reception was met with numerous sales, commissions and post fair collaborations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply online now: &lt;a href="http://nyc.theotherartfair.com/applications" target="_blank"&gt;http://nyc.theotherartfair.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for applications: July 19&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no application fee. Stand fees start at $1,880 + sales tax.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As part of our exciting collaboration with leading online gallery Saatchi Art, exhibitors will be presented as fair artists to an extensive network of curators, collectors, interior designers and international buyers via saatchiart.com/theotherartfair, social media and the Canvas blog.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions? Please contact Sasha Ali, Events Assistant, sasha@theotherartfair.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online now: &lt;a href="http://nyc.theotherartfair.com/applications" target="_blank"&gt;http://nyc.theotherartfair.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for applications: July 19&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no application fee. Stand fees start at $1,880 + sales tax.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f33365b7-d942-4066-8168-3d34634cfab3" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>