<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-04T21:16:26-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>bcbc21b1-aa22-4333-bd69-01209feb601b</id><title>6/1 - SOLO, GROUP &amp;amp; CONCEPT SUBMISSIONS (SEASON 16: 2019/2020)</title><updated>2019-05-04T21:16:26.321512+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSION PROCESS FOR SEASON 16 IS NOW OPEN!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Manifest is happy to receive proposals of various types and accepts these on an ongoing basis starting usually in late winter, reviewing them starting in early June in consideration for the upcoming exhibit season. No notifications are made until the final season schedule is decided (usually by the end of July), but updates are sent to all artists at the start of our committee's review process. Anyone can submit a proposal, and selections are open to all traditional and non-traditional genre and media.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On average, one-third of Manifest's exhibits are dedicated to solo exhibits. Solo exhibitors have included local, regional, and national artists from as far away as New York City, San Francisco, Canada, and Hong Kong. Our exhibits are routinely reviewed in local and sometimes national news and art publications (including Sculpture Magazine, Drawing Magazine, and Art Papers among others). And while our focus is on providing a museum-like experience of visual art, patrons and collectors, including museums, watch Manifest and our publications for future acquisitions and exhibitors. We believe this makes the spots in our schedule reserved for solo or proposed exhibits highly valuable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNUAL CASH AWARD: The annual Manifest Grand Jury Prize will result in the awarding of one significant cash prize ($2500) to a single work selected as the 'best of the entire season'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;View the full prospectus and apply online at &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/proposals." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For questions email info@manifestgallery.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/bcbc21b1-aa22-4333-bd69-01209feb601b" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>