<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-19T18:15:19-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>553ce6a1-968b-496b-b0ac-1d186c0b8cc5</id><title>5/6 - OPEN CALL FOR ARTISTS IN THE AD INDUSTRY — CHANCE TO SHOW WORK ON 60+ SCREENS IN TIMES SQ</title><updated>2019-03-19T18:15:19.280472+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="TSq.org/arts"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re an artist working in the advertising industry, Times Square Arts, Advertising Week, and the Out of Home Advertising Association of America (OAAA) invite you to submit original moving image artwork to Midnight Moment, the world’s largest, longest-running digital art exhibition. The selected 3-minute work will be shown on electronic billboards throughout Times Square every night in September 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The submission deadline is May 6, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;For more information, visit TSq.org/AdArt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit TSq.org/AdArt for information on submission guidelines and technical specifications. Applications for the Midnight Moment program are accepted through the online Slideroom portal linked to at the bottom of the page.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/553ce6a1-968b-496b-b0ac-1d186c0b8cc5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>46957a44-c27e-4d78-954c-29ee09a85125</id><title>4/1 - Call for Entries: 118th Annual Juried Art Exhibition</title><updated>2019-03-19T18:15:19.280436+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;New Haven Paint and Clay Club&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Haven, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.newhavenpaintandclayclub.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 118th Annual Exhibition of the New Haven Paint and Clay Club will be juried by Dr. Elizabeth Hodermarsky, the Sutphin Family Associate Curator of Prints and Drawings at Yale University Art Gallery. She will award prizes in excess of $4000 with additional funds available for purchases to the NHP&amp;CC Permanent Collection. The exhibition will be on view at the Susan B. Hilles Gallery at the Creative Arts Workshop from May 11- June 1.&lt;br/&gt;Selected work must be hand delivered to the Creative Arts Workshop, 80 Audubon St. New Haven, CT.&lt;br/&gt;Eligible media include drawing, painting, mixed media (no larger than 40" in width) and sculpture (no heavier than 75 lbs). Giclees, photography, digital work and video are not eligible for entry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit www.newhavenpaintandclayclub.org to access the prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/46957a44-c27e-4d78-954c-29ee09a85125" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4f44fd14-6768-4c7c-af56-3eed0804be09</id><title>4/20 - OPEN CALL/Video - 13 Fruitcakes (La MaMa, Stonewall 50)</title><updated>2019-03-19T18:15:19.280382+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;13 Fruitcakes&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://tinyurl.com/13FruitcakesOpenCall"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEN CALL FOR VIDEO WORKS &lt;br/&gt;We are looking for video works for 13 Fruitcakes: Musical Vignettes, a performance that celebrates the 50th anniversary of the Stonewall Riot. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION DEADLINE: April 20, 2019, 11:59PM (EST)&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION ANNOUNCEMENT: May 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;PERFORMANCE DATES: June 13-16, 2019  &lt;br/&gt;VENUE: La MaMa Experimental Theatre, New York City &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION FORM: &lt;a href="https://tinyurl.com/13FruitcakesOpenCall" target="_blank"&gt;https://tinyurl.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT ‘13 FRUITCAKES: MUSICAL VIGNETTES’   &lt;br/&gt;'13 Fruitcakes: Musical Vignettes' premieres June 2019 at La MaMa Theatre, where more than 5,000 theatrical productions and 150,000 artists from around the world have been supported since its opening in 1961. This production celebrates the 50th anniversary of the Stonewall Riot where, for the first time in U.S. history, the American LGBTQ community raised a united voice to defend their basic human rights. The show is also dedicated to those who were able to influence humanity through their great achievements in the arts, politics, philosophy, and science, despite the persecution that they had to endure as homosexuals.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Poems by queer poets such as Oscar Wilde, Virginia Woolf, and Arthur Rimbaud are set as art songs by Gihieh Lee, a celebrated Korean composer. Korean-American director Byungkoo Ahn transforms the song cycle into a series of musical vignettes about 13 LGBTQ figures who changed the world through their work. Although the characters and the poets lived in different time periods and cultures, many of them had to disguise their true identities in order to survive society’s discrimination. However, despite the judgement of society, they were able to express their true selves through their works of art and literature. Their bravery paved the way for their descendants who came out to the streets of Greenwich Village in 1969 during the Stonewall Riot. '13 Fruitcakes: Musical Vignettes' captures and revitalizes those moments of truth in the queer foreparents’ lives through the power of art songs and queer literature of the 19th and 20th centuries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;** NO FEE to apply. &lt;br/&gt;** We are open to all Gender Identities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WE ARE INVITING YOU TO SUBMIT VIDEO WORKS THAT CAN CREATIVELY ADDRESS THE LIFE OF THE FOLLOWING LGBTQ FIGURES. &lt;br/&gt;Harmodius and Aristogeiton&lt;br/&gt;Dong Xian (董賢)&lt;br/&gt;King Hyegong (혜공왕) &lt;br/&gt;Leonardo da Vinci &lt;br/&gt;Hans Christian Andersen&lt;br/&gt;Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky&lt;br/&gt;Gertrude Stein&lt;br/&gt;Virginia Woolf&lt;br/&gt;Alan Turing &lt;br/&gt;Frida Kahlo and Josephine Baker&lt;br/&gt;Eleanor Roosevelt &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT CRITERIA ABOUT THE VIDEO SUBMISSION (MUST READ)&lt;br/&gt;1. A video should be about one particular individual from the list of historic figures (with the exception of Harmodius and Aristogeiton, and Frida Kahlo and Josephine Baker; they should be addressed together).  &lt;br/&gt;2. Each video should visually interpret provided quotation about the individual from  "13 Fruitcakes - Reference.pdf" available at the submission site that discusses a certain aspect of the person’s life. Additional research about the individual is welcome. &lt;br/&gt;3. No music *  /  No watermark  **&lt;br/&gt;4. Each video should be about 2 MINUTES in length.&lt;br/&gt;5. You may submit up to two different videos. &lt;br/&gt;6. As for the final selection, only one video will be chosen for each historic figure. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://tinyurl.com/13FruitcakesOpenCall" target="_blank"&gt;https://tinyurl.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4f44fd14-6768-4c7c-af56-3eed0804be09" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>