<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-02T13:14:52-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>e22ce79f-6cb3-4c87-89c3-0afb60b937cf</id><title>3/14 - Love Triangle: For the Love of Geometry</title><updated>2019-03-02T13:14:52.243528+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;1milliondiamonds&lt;br/&gt;📍 Morganville, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/14/18 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/1milliondiamonds/?hl=en"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEEP SPACE GALLERY &amp; 1 MILLION DIAMONDS PRESENT&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LOVE TRIANGLE: For the Love of Geometry&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A  Summertime Juried Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On view June 27th - July 20th&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepting applications now through March 14, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1milliondiamonds and Deep Space Gallery are both turning 3 this year!  In celebration, we are joining forces to produce our first collaborative, juried exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What we are looking for:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Geometric abstraction&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Do you think in shapes?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Does your work fit into the aesthetic world of 1MILLIONDIAMONDS?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Originals only&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any size up to 36 x 36”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any medium (digital, sculpture, paintings, works on paper, photography)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Up to 5 works, with high resolution images of each&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork Information List including title, medium, dimensions (H x W x D), year produced, retail price&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist bio and CV, links to online presence (IG, website, etc.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Information for Artists:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$25 submission fee to submit 3 works*&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;       *only one piece of artwork from each artist selected will be exhibited in             the gallery show, so send us your strongest work!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$5 each to submit additional pieces for consideration (up to 2 additional)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All works must be ready to hang&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All works must be available for purchase&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All sales will be split 50/50 (Love Triangle/Artist)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Must submit by March 14, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juried selections will be made by April 25th and notifications will be sent out in the week that follows.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juried exhibition will take place at Deep Space Gallery in Jersey City, NJ, and will be on view from June 27th through July 20th.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Transportation of artwork to and from the gallery will be the sole responsibility of the artist.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please fill in the highlighted fields below, click the gray “Submit” button, and then click the yellow “Click to Complete Submission” button to finalize. (If it doesn't open on one click, click it again.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please submit your Artist CV/Bio/Artist Statement and Artwork  information list as one document in .pdf form&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist Benefits:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Inclusion in featured summertime gallery show at DS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Featured on 1milliondiamonds &amp; DS online platforms*&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;       *Note that all submissions will be considered for features online&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Inclusion in print magazine/catalog of the show&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Inclusion in gallery programming including artist panels, workshops, and networking events&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Love Triangle Jurors&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Debra Lynn Manville, curator and founder of 1milliondiamonds&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Keith VanPelt, owner and cofounder of Deep Space Gallery&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Works selected for in-gallery exhibition and/or online features will be chosen from those works submitted in your initial application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions, please email: deepdiamondlovetriangle@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e22ce79f-6cb3-4c87-89c3-0afb60b937cf" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>5972d098-85b9-48c3-afa1-b5c9f34c2642</id><title>5/1 - Helpful Discomfot</title><updated>2019-03-02T13:14:52.243468+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hidden Currencies&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $5.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://hiddencurrencies.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hidden Currencies presents hécatombe, an extension of the collective through print. We are seeking open calls for our 1st edition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For hécatombe’s first edition we are examining the implications of discomfort and it’s potential to inspire growth, regression, fear, and hope. Discomfort can reflect a projected incongruence of identity, fueled by the pressures of society and self. This discomfort can be at the epicenter of our dissonance from society: we now face the question if it is the individual or the society which should be made to feel uncomfortable. If so, what is the utility of discomfort for each party? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In approaching this topic and examining your work please consider:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;How discomfort helps you?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;How do people benefit from each other's discomfort?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Who do you want to see uncomfortable? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Where do you want to be uncomfortable?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;_____________________________________________________________________________________&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Hidden Currencies is an interdisciplinary collective consisting of artists, musicians, dancers, sculptors and scientists. It was founded in early in May of 2017. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The reason for the inception of the Hidden Currencies is three fold:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is an interdisciplinary creative community to prompt artists to explore new dimensions of their art through critiques, demonstrations, and workshops. Artists of different mediums give valuable feedback that will stem from their various backgrounds. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;In the midst of a climate that commoditizes art and music, it is important to create a network of individuals who can hold each other accountable to their ethical standards of making art. This community will facilitate growth outside of what could be attained independently. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To work with local communities to establish a connecting point for the next generation to engage with art in a variety of mediums.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;_____________________________________________________________________________________&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Those who are selected to participate in our first magazine will be invited to the release party in New York City. Location and date to be announced in line with release of the publication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are accepting submissions from any medium which explore this theme to be printed in our first edition, including but not limited to: writing, painting, sculpture, photography, installations, games, data sets, experiments, multimedia, etc. This is limited to media which can be printed within our pages. For video and music submissions we have the capability to include a QR Code. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An email sent to info@hiddencurrencies.com with:&lt;br/&gt;Up to 5 images with the longest edge being 1000p (jpg.) &lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement (300 words)&lt;br/&gt;Link to your website or portfolio&lt;br/&gt;$5 entry fee to be paid over paypal to info@hiddencurrencies.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5972d098-85b9-48c3-afa1-b5c9f34c2642" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>