<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-09T13:15:03-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>961a55b5-df8f-4107-a5a2-4c0b2287ff4b</id><title>4/26 - 2019 Visiting Curator Exhibition - Sophia Marisa Lucas (Queens Museum)</title><updated>2019-03-09T13:15:03.346641+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;CFEVA&lt;br/&gt;📍 PHILADELPHIA, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/26/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Center for Emerging Visual Artists invites you to submit images of your artwork for review by our guest curator, Sophia Marisa Lucas, Assistant Curator, Queens Museum (Queens, NY). Of the applicants, 10 to 25 artists will be asked to present a digital portfolio of approximately ten images. One to three of those artists will be selected for an exhibition in CFEVA’s Felicity R. “Bebe” Benoliel Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Visiting Curator Program allows CFEVA to showcase the abundance of talented artists from our region to a curator who is not yet familiar with our artist community. CFEVA is proud to create more exposure for the artists we serve and provide beneficial new leads for noteworthy curators. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sophia Marisa Lucas is Assistant Curator at the Queens Museum, where she recently organized Queens International 2018: Volumes, the eighth iteration of the museum's biannual exhibition of Queens-based artists. At the Queens Museum, she has also co-organized QM-Jerome Foundation Fellowship exhibitions by Sable Elyse Smith (2017) and Julia Weist (2017) with Hitomi Iwasaki and worked with Larissa Harris on Maintenance Art (2016), a museum-wide retrospective of Mierle Laderman Ukeles. Previously, she contributed to exhibitions and programming at The Museum of Modern Art, New York; Museum of Art and Design, New York; The Artist’s Institute, New York; and Slought Foundation, Philadelphia. During her M.A. studies at CUNY Hunter College, she was a member of the ACE Curatorial Collective (2011–2013) and contributed to or co-organized several exhibitions for the university’s galleries, including Gego/Gerd: a dialogue (2014), and Objects of Devotion and Desire: Medieval Relic to Contemporary Art (2012). Her work appears in Anthony Huberman's Today we should be thinking about (2015), published by The Artist’s Institute and Koenig Books.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The Queens Museum is dedicated to presenting the highest quality visual arts and educational programming for people in the New York metropolitan area, and particularly for the residents of Queens, a uniquely diverse, ethnic, cultural, and international community. The Museum fulfills its mission by designing and providing art exhibitions, public programs and educational experiences that promote the appreciation and enjoyment of art, support the creative efforts of artists, and enhance the quality of life through interpreting, collecting, and exhibiting art, architecture, and design. In November 2013, the Queens Museum completed an expansion that doubled its size to 105,000 square feet. The expansion provides an additional 50,000 square feet of space, including a suite of new galleries, artist studios, flexible public and special event spaces, education classrooms, a café, back-of-house facilities and visitor amenities. This light-filled new space, designed by Grimshaw Architects, exemplifies the Museum’s commitment to openness, inclusion, and community partnership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DETAILS AND REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be asked to provide a resume, artist statement, image list and 5 images. The total application fee is $25 (this includes the fee to use Slideroom). Artists must reside within 100 miles of Philadelphia and must not currently be a student.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To apply please visit &lt;a href="https://cfeva.slideroom.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://cfeva.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information please contact Genevieve Coutroubis at (215) 546-7775 x11 or genevieve@cfeva.org .&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/961a55b5-df8f-4107-a5a2-4c0b2287ff4b" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>