<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-11T07:17:17-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>92756e33-5273-4495-b8e9-69c80167203a</id><title>7/1 - Wythe Hotel Cinema Series Open Call</title><updated>2019-06-11T07:17:17.626708+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wythe Hotel&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.WytheHotel.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wythe Hotel is accepting applications from artists, writers, filmmakers, curators and performers for use of its Cinema in the 2019-2020 calendar year. Applications are due by July 1, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Residencies are one evening and offer use of the Cinema as well as coordination and AV technical support, promotion of the event on our website and social media channels, plus an $150 stipend. This opportunity is for anyone interested in developing an evening of material to be showcased in the space.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists at any stage of their career are encouraged to apply through our online application. Must be based in New York. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For questions regarding the program, please contact us at artists@wythehotel.com. Finalists will be invited for an in person interview, and all applicants will be informed of the committee's decision by the end of July, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artistic excellence is the primary criteria for acceptance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit using our online application form: &lt;a href="https://wythehotel.com/apply/" target="_blank"&gt;https://wythehotel.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email Artists@WytheHotel.com with any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/92756e33-5273-4495-b8e9-69c80167203a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8734bebd-0908-4735-82fc-4d56bee9285f</id><title>6/30 - Artfare Submissions Program</title><updated>2019-06-11T07:17:17.626673+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Artfare, Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artfare.com/for-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artfare is a new platform that allows artists and patrons to connect through our iPhone app (artfare.com/app).  Patrons can follow artists, request studio visits, and purchase work posted by our curated group of professional artists. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artfare allows artists to present their work to a broad audience and connect with patrons both digitally and in person through studio visits, exhibitions and events. Using our app, artists can also discover and communicate with other artists and curators, and work together to independently organize exhibitions and events.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artfare artists are based in NYC and actively make and show their work. Our group is carefully curated and  selective. In addition to quality and maturity in the work, we seek artists with professional track records and career ambition. We aim to create a well rounded program that represents all voices and mediums. Please browse the app and artfare.com to get a sense of our mission and artist list. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our tools and services allow artists to:&lt;br/&gt;1. Easily share links to your available works and facilitate sales from your studio, both on and offline&lt;br/&gt;2. Build a following of potential patrons and curators in a professional context&lt;br/&gt;3. Receive tax documents at year end and let Artfare collect, file, and pay sales tax on your behalf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you would like to submit your work for consideration please do so by June 30 via this link:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://artfare.slideroom.com/#/login/program/48475&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8734bebd-0908-4735-82fc-4d56bee9285f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>eaecb5cb-5d38-4761-bad8-870281e43ffa</id><title>6/26 - Blackbird Gallery Looking for Artists</title><updated>2019-06-11T07:17:17.626610+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Blackbird Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York , NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/26/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.blackbird.gallery"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New gallery space is looking for artists for tandem exhibitions. Artists must have a complete body of work to showcase. All mediums excepted. Looking to pair artists for Tandem exhibitions happening through this summer and for future shows happening through the summer of 2020.&lt;br/&gt;Blackbird Gallery is a new contemporary art gallery promoting local emerging artists as well as artists at varying stages in their careers. It will focus on exhibiting artists who create works that span a variety of media and subject matter that are shaping the future of contemporary art. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please submit directly through the NYFA site. Should you have any questions please email info@blackbird.gallery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To be considered please submit up to five images and links to social media and/or website. &lt;br/&gt;Deadline to apply is June 26th &lt;br/&gt;Exhibition calendar:&lt;br/&gt;June 26th - Final Entry Deadline&lt;br/&gt;July 2nd/3rd - All artist notifications sent&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/eaecb5cb-5d38-4761-bad8-870281e43ffa" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>