<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-17T17:17:26-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>cc60089a-3ac6-4742-8849-709161156932</id><title>7/15 - BURN THIS - OPEN CALL all disciplines</title><updated>2019-06-17T17:17:26.324904+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burn This - inspired by the title of an incredible Lanford Wilson play that features Pale, a truly volcanic character. We are looking for all kind of work [including performances] that utilizes or represents heat. Work created using welding, heat transfer, flame, acid, lasers or just representations or images of the aftermath of flames, fusion, and heat.   Therefore all ceramics or work that is 'fired' is eligible.  Laser etching would also be eligible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Work can be submitted, for example, that uses charcoal, flame, chemical processes or any kind of process that involves reactive elements. Photography, painting or video of smoke, heat, vapor, gasses, Deserts or the effects of heat, the effects of the Sun are all welcome.  A video of the Yule log?  Maybe. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE NOTE THAT WE CANNOT ACCEPT WORK THAT HAS TO BE SHIPPED. ALL WORK MUST BE DELIVERED AND PICKED UP AT THE GALLERY.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION FEES - If you have previously shown with us the fee is $15, if not, $30. There is also a link for our Artist Directory if you wish to have a entry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit using the form link here: &lt;a href="https://form.jotform.com/trimistopheles/burn-this-2019-open-call" target="_blank"&gt;https://form.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cc60089a-3ac6-4742-8849-709161156932" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>