<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-24T23:18:16-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>75023a24-8708-45e5-96b0-a541967297a0</id><title>9/12 - Reused and Recycled</title><updated>2019-07-24T23:18:16.423747+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/12/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;November 1– November 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What is the relationship between recycling and art? We constantly seek out ways to deal with what we produce, consume, and discard. The aesthetic potential of trash is well established in artistic practice. It has had its place in avant-garde since the early twentieth century, when Marcel Duchamp introduced the idea of the readymade: discarded, modified works, remanufactured and displayed as an art. Site:Brooklyn is seeking artists whose practice continues to investigate the relationship between discarded materials and art. We are looking for works across all mediums&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Jean Shin is nationally recognized for her monumental installations that transform everyday objects into elegant expressions of identity and community. Her work has been widely exhibited in over 150 major museums and cultural institutions, including solo exhibitions at The Museum of Modern Art in New York, Fabric Workshop and Museum in Philadelphia, Smithsonian American Art Museum in Washington DC.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: July 23, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: September 12, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: September 21, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: November 1– November 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, November 1, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in all materials and processes. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $35.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by September 12, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:&lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2JNMMVe&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. All artwork must be suitably presented to a professional standard.&lt;br/&gt;2. The artist needs to provide a method for displaying the work such as a plinth, stand, wall shelf or bracket plus all hardware for attachment into the wall or ceiling.The gallery ceiling height is 18’.&lt;br/&gt;3. Artists provide complete instructions for installation and/or assembly and may be required to assist on the installation of their artwork upon the gallery’s request.&lt;br/&gt;4. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates- Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the accepted artwork as listed on notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;5. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Reused and Recycled” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:&lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2JNMMVe&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/75023a24-8708-45e5-96b0-a541967297a0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>5c92e7f4-24eb-442e-96ac-e75e0e4af746</id><title>8/21 - OPEN CALL: Annual Patterns show at La Bodega Gallery in Brooklyn</title><updated>2019-07-24T23:18:16.423688+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;La Bodega Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.labodega-gallery.com/opportunities-1#/rererepatterns"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;La Bodega Gallery is currently accepting submissions for the third annual patterned themed exhibition!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;"RE: RE: RE: patterns" will feature artists who have aesthetically or conceptually incorporated patterns and/or repetition into their art practices. This exhibit focuses on stylistic varieties of repeating art elements that drive toward movement, harmony and unity. For this open call we are inviting both emerging and established artists who work with patterns in a multitude ways, work can utilize any medium and/or technique to create works that explore a myriad of subject matter. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RE:RE: patterns will be exhibited from September 6th thru 29th. The opening reception will take place on September 6th from 7-10pm. All attendees of the opening will be asked to wear patterns, the more the better!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION DEADLINE: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;8/21 11:59:59 pm   Exhibition dates: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;September 6th – September 29th, 2019 Location: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;La Bodega Gallery, 695 5th Ave Brooklyn, NY   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contact: submission.gallerylabodega@gmail.com &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility  This exhibition is open to any artist, anywhere. ALL SUBMISSIONS MUST BE RECEIVED BY 8/21 11:59:59 pm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to apply:&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;1. Submissions must be via email at submission.gallerylabodega@gmail.com. We require you to upload 1 - 3 images, your CV, and artist statement. Submission does not guarantee acceptance into the exhibition, all entrants will be notified on August 25th, 2019&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 2. Cost of submission is $15 for up to 3 entries and $5 per every entry thereafter (maximum 5). It is a non-refundable fee and no changes of images can be made after you submit. Your submissions do not guarantee inclusion into a show.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 3. Your JPEGs data files must be labeled: First name Last &lt;br/&gt; name_Title of the piece_Medium_Height x Width in inches.jpg making sure that underscores go between your name and the name of the piece: (Jane Doe_Self-Portrait_Oil_32x40in.JPG). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Things to include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-Art work images (Correctly Labeled)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-Image list with a short description of each image (please also include dimensions &amp; medium)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-Artist Statement&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-CV&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-Submission Fee ($15 via paypal submission.gallerylabodega@gmail.com or via Venmo @LaBodega-Gallery)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Rules:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Types of art accepted&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 4. All two-dimensional work including photography, paintings, drawings, digital, mixed media, fabric art, chalk, ink, pastels, wax, graphite and printmaking. Essentially, if we can hang it on a wall, we will consider your art for acceptance. We will also accept free standing sculptures and small sculptures that can fit on a pedestal. Video work is accepted, La Bodega Gallery will provide the monitor and the media player. The maximum size for each piece submitted needs to be less than 40 inches on the longest side.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Shipping + presentation&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 5. If your submission is accepted, you will be notified with information for drop off or shipping your artwork(s) to the gallery. Please take care to ship your artwork carefully with padding and in ther event that it does not sell we will return it to you in the same box with the same padding. Artist is responsible for shipping cost both to/from the gallery (in the event the. work does not sell). The return postage can be a label or a bill of lading from either UPS, Fedex or UPS included with your artwork.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 6. All artwork must be received at least 4 days before the art reception.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 7. All works must be prepared and ready to hang. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Gallery commission&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 8. La Bodega Gallery retains the right to represent an artist in a sale of the artwork that was accepted and exhibited for the duration of the exhibition. All artworks will be offered for sale. The gallery takes a 50% commission on all sales.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 9. Accepted entries are represented by La Bodega Gallery for the duration of the exhibition, and artworks will be promoted on our website and other social media.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Gallery installation rules&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 10. La Bodega Gallery reserves the right to refuse to hang an artwork or exhibit it if it is radically different from the image that was submitted.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Copyright&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 11. Artist maintains copyright.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5c92e7f4-24eb-442e-96ac-e75e0e4af746" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>