<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-20T17:15:20-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>a99ca442-9f33-4374-946d-47f67145383b</id><title>4/20 - Bowery 28th Annual Juried Competition</title><updated>2019-03-20T17:15:20.476117+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Bowery Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.bowerygallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;July 30-August 17,2019&lt;br/&gt;Reception Thursday, August 1, 5-8 PM&lt;br/&gt;Ro Lohin is our juror. She is a New York City based painter and curator. Was the director and owner of Lohin Geduld Gallery in NYC 2003-2013 and has shown extensively in New York area.&lt;br/&gt;Eligible two dimensional work includes painting, drawing, printmaking and mixed media not to exceed 36" in any dimension.  Images must by JPGs. Minimum 500px width/height. Maximum size 3MB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See complete submission guidelines and online entry form on website at www.bowerygallery.org.&lt;br/&gt;Email: info@bowerygallery.org&lt;br/&gt;Phone: 646-230-6655&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a99ca442-9f33-4374-946d-47f67145383b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>105ae5cc-bbdc-42c1-9ae2-10ab9294396a</id><title>5/2 - Red</title><updated>2019-03-20T17:15:20.476081+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/02/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.sitebrooklyn.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red&lt;br/&gt;June 14– July 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Red is a color that calls up associations of love, luck, passion, and violence but also the mementos of childhood, such as balloons and toys. It is found in Paleolithic painting, China’s imperial and popular imagery, the Dutch Renaissance, it is also present in the contemporary graphic texts of Barbara Kruger and the abstract etchings of Anish Kapoor. This is the second installment of Site:Brooklyn’s ongoing investigation into color: its meaning, its roles, and place in contemporary practice. We are seeking works in all genres and mediums.&lt;br/&gt;This is the second installment of Site:Brooklyn’s ongoing investigation into color: its meaning, its roles, and place in contemporary practice. What does red mean to you?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Sara Reisman is the artistic director of The Shelley &amp; Donald Rubin Foundation, curator of the Donald Rubin Private Collection, and professor of curatorial practice at SVA. Previously, she was associate dean at The Cooper Union and a guest curator and curatorial consultant at the Queens Museum, International Studio &amp; Curatorial Program, and Socrates Sculpture Park. In addition, she received curatorial fellowships from the New Museum of Contemporary Art, Omi International Art Center, and the Institute of Contemporary Art, University of Pennsylvania.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: March 18, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: May 2, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: May 11, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: June 14– July 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, June 14, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in drawing, painting, printmaking, wall mounted sculpture, collage, and video.&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $35.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by May 2, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION: &lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2W4IR9M&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 60” X 60” X 12” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;5. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Red” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2W4IR9M" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/105ae5cc-bbdc-42c1-9ae2-10ab9294396a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0b586dfc-9703-4251-bc21-d62761ee4030</id><title>4/19 - Dear Earth,</title><updated>2019-03-20T17:15:20.476044+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Woman Made Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Chicago, IL, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.womanmade.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chicago's Woman Made Gallery, Openlands, and Brushwood Center at Ryerson Woods partner to illuminate women’s voices of action and hope for the planet. Together, we invite artists to submit artwork that highly reflects personal concerns and connections to the natural environment where they live.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dear Earth was inspired by Sibylle Szaggars Redford whose performance, The Way of The Rain, was created as a “love letter to Mother Earth.” Szaggars Redford and her husband, Robert Redford, were Brushwood Center’s 2018 environmental leadership award recipients.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All applicants should submit a brief artist statement. The first sentence of the statement should begin, “Dear Earth…[add your message of action, hope, or inspiration]”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Works in all media are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror:  &lt;br/&gt;Catherine Game is the Executive Director of Brushwood Center at Ryerson Woods. &lt;br/&gt;Catherine ensures that the legacy of Brushwood Center thrives through strong partnerships and inspiring programs that connect art, nature, and wellness. Prior to joining Brushwood Center, Catherine served as Director of Communications and Engagement for Chicago Wilderness where she oversaw the organization’s communications, member engagement, and efforts to cultivate a diverse conservation constituency. Catherine has held previous positions in communications, program evaluation, and education with conservation groups. She holds a Master’s degree in Natural Resources and Environment from the University of Michigan, Bachelor’s degree in Biology and Art from Albion College, and is the recipient of the Doris Duke Conservation Fellowship and a Morris K. Udall Scholar. Catherine is an artist, using homemade, natural paints to bring visibility to urban nature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Works in all media are welcome. The application fee for our juried exhibitions is $30 for up to three images of work, plus one detail image if necessary. &lt;br/&gt;Any questions, please call us :  (312) 738-0400&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To submit your work:  &lt;br/&gt;https://womanmadegallery.submittable.com/submit/135676/dear-earth&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0b586dfc-9703-4251-bc21-d62761ee4030" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>553ce6a1-968b-496b-b0ac-1d186c0b8cc5</id><title>5/6 - OPEN CALL FOR ARTISTS IN THE AD INDUSTRY — CHANCE TO SHOW WORK ON 60+ SCREENS IN TIMES SQ</title><updated>2019-03-20T17:15:20.475988+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="TSq.org/arts"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re an artist working in the advertising industry, Times Square Arts, Advertising Week, and the Out of Home Advertising Association of America (OAAA) invite you to submit original moving image artwork to Midnight Moment, the world’s largest, longest-running digital art exhibition. The selected 3-minute work will be shown on electronic billboards throughout Times Square every night in September 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The submission deadline is May 6, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;For more information, visit TSq.org/AdArt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit TSq.org/AdArt for information on submission guidelines and technical specifications. Applications for the Midnight Moment program are accepted through the online Slideroom portal linked to at the bottom of the page.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/553ce6a1-968b-496b-b0ac-1d186c0b8cc5" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>