<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-08T21:16:32-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>c3e4884f-7344-444d-83dd-f1c68fb322c0</id><title>West Chelsea Open Studios Tour - Over 50 stops on the Tour</title><updated>2019-05-08T21:16:32.139831+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Leo House NYC/Six Summit Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="www.sixsummitgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE LEGENDARY NEW YORK CITY-  WEST CHELSEA OPEN STUDIOS GRAND TOUR IN CHELSEA AT &lt;br/&gt;THE LEO HOUSE - 332 W 23RD ST, NYC (between 8th and 9th Ave)-  The Gateway to the Arts&lt;br/&gt;Spring Celebration- participation in West Chelsea Open Studios tour at the coolest NYC hotel/guesthouse you may have never heard of, on legendary 23rd ST west of the Chelsea Hotel and at the beginning of historic Chelsea Art District. We will have two opening receptions  June 1st and 2nd  from 12:30 - 5:30PM at 332 W 23rd St at The Leo House, which was established in 1889 by Pope Leo XIII whose miter and 8 other antiquities were  featured at The Met show "Heavenly Bodies: Fashion and the Catholic Imagination" with Vogue, Cardinal Gianfranco Ravasi, Donatella Versace, and Anna Wintour. We will be accepting both religious (non ironic) and non religious art. Prizes - Most artist will have the choice to keep hanging work for sale for up to 8 weeks.  We will be donating portions of our proceeds of sales to The Leo House. Artists receive 50% of sales.  If you wish to donate all or portions of your submissions please specify upon submitting.......we are also taking 100% donated art items to be featured on our website as part of our GALA in November.   See below for submission instructions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EMAIL LEOHOUSE@SIXSUMMITGALLERY with any questions.  Please do not call The Leo House or West Chelsea Open Studios &lt;br/&gt;........................................................................................................................................................................................&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK Submit entries to leohouse@sixsummitgallery.com SUBMISSIONS:All work will be judged by email entry via leohouse@sixsummitgallery.com. You MUST write [YOUR NAME]” IN THE SUBJECT OF EMAIL. YOUR NAME MUST BE THE SAME ON YOUR CREDIT/DEBIT CARD Example: Subject: FASHION SUBMISSION: John Doe. Files must be in .jpg format, 300 dpi, max 900 pixels in any dimension. File name should correspond to the title of the piece. PUT title, medium, artist, price, and size as JPEG FILE EXTENSION NAME.!  No accepted work may be removed prior to the show’s conclusion. ALL work must be for sale. Sculptors must bring their own pedestals or free standing is OK (We also have room for sculpture in the outdoor garden- please specify if your work can be outside) You are required to make your own labels. They must include Title, Medium,Price, and Your Name, www.sixsummitgallery.com – with call or text Leo 917-573-0029 clearly visible on the bottom below www.sixsummitgallery.com. Purchases will take place during the show on our website and ongoing for prize winners.- Customers can leave with art. The Show Committee reserves the right to disallow the exhibition of any work or artist, which, in the opinion of the Committee, is considered detrimental to the good public image of the show and its sponsors, art which is too fragile to handle, or which is not accurately represented by the photo submitted. Six Summit Gallery, We reserve the right to photograph work or use submitted images to help yours and our publicity. ENTRY FEES: Easily click on www.sixsummitgallery.com online store and go to ONLINE STORE-EVENTS SUBMISSION section and choose up to 3 submissions for $35 or  5 submissions for $50 Please call 917-573-0029 with any special situations. Art must be wired and ready to hang and not exceed 48" by 48" or 25 pounds unless its sculpture QUESTIONS CAN BE EMAILED ONLY TO: leohouse@sixsummitgallery.com Include your Call Back Number! DO NOT CALL OR EMAIL THE LEO HOUSE DEADLINE to Submit- May 21st.  Delivery: We will announce Removal: Most artists will have choice to stay on at venue for up to 8 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c3e4884f-7344-444d-83dd-f1c68fb322c0" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>