<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-26T17:14:46-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>a9771ba3-58b5-4b56-bbd0-da872caf4d96</id><title>3/26 - MAGNITUDE SEVEN: International Call for Small Works</title><updated>2019-02-26T17:14:46.513832+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/26/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cincinnati based non-profit arts organization and gallery, Manifest, presents an open call for small work, 7” or smaller.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Every year Manifest produces an exhibit of little works of art from around the world. Each iteration of the exhibit brings in hundreds of powerful yet diminutive works for our jury to consider. Inevitably this results in a gallery full of diverse, compelling, and exquisite little gems. Manifest’s patrons eagerly await the Magnitude SEVEN event each year. This annual project is one of the most varied exhibits in our season. So we are always excited to offer this call to artists to submit works no larger than seven inches in any dimension (any proportion).   Standard presentation devices like pedestals, mats, and frames that are not considered part of the work of art are not limited by the 7" criteria.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Unless specified otherwise by the exhibit or project parameters Manifest has no requirements on timeframe when submitted works must have been made.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNUAL CASH AWARD: The annual Manifest Grand Jury Prize will result in the awarding of one significant cash prize ($2500) to a single work selected as the 'best of the entire season'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To view the full prospectus or to submit work visit &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/seven." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For questions please email &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/seven." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a9771ba3-58b5-4b56-bbd0-da872caf4d96" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>