<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-07T13:48:19-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>a41e6157-26d2-4ab9-91be-b2b1cef238ea</id><title>3/1 - Arcadia Earth 2019 - Calling All Sustainable Artists</title><updated>2019-02-07T13:48:19.084507+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arcadia Earth&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.arcadia.earth"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ABOUT ARCADIA:&lt;br/&gt;Arcadia is a platform to raise awareness on sustainability through immersive art experiences, a solution driven marketplace and educational talks. Our mission is to gather like minded partners, brands, and organizations to create content and innovative sustainable solutions to connect with the new generation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THE OPPORTUNITY:&lt;br/&gt;We are looking for artists interested in creating immersive environment Installations to promote sustainability. The artwork will be displayed during a collective event. The event will be promoted with strong marketing strategy where all installations and their creators will be highlighted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THE INCENTIVES:&lt;br/&gt;- 3 grant levels: $2500, $5000, $7500. Apply to see what you qualify for.&lt;br/&gt;- Promotion and Marketing&lt;br/&gt;- Marketing Exposure - Social Media exposure &lt;br/&gt;- Arcadia web presence &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists will need to create immersive sustainable experiences by: &lt;br/&gt;1. Areas to Activate : activate an area of 15’ x 10’ more or less &lt;br/&gt;2. Materials used: upcycled / recycled / sustainable &lt;br/&gt;3. Messaging: sustainability and global warming&lt;br/&gt;4. Immersive/ Experiential: Teleport guests into an experiential and engaging environment using mixed media&lt;br/&gt;5. innovative: Use of new technologies such as Projection Mapping, VR, and AR&lt;br/&gt;6. Interactive: art experiences where guests can participate in creating or being part of the artwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSIONS&lt;br/&gt;Depending on the category artists will need to submit the following to Arcadia to review at ap@arcadia.earth :&lt;br/&gt;1.     IMMERSIVE / EXPERIENTIAL:&lt;br/&gt;	a. Example of the immersive installation (renderings, layout, photos etc.)&lt;br/&gt;	b. Materials being used&lt;br/&gt;	c.  A paragraph explaining the concept and message behind the piece&lt;br/&gt;2.     INNOVATIVE:&lt;br/&gt;	a. A link or video explaining the technology being used&lt;br/&gt;	b.  Materials being used (if applicable)&lt;br/&gt;	c.  A paragraph explaining the concept and message behind the piece&lt;br/&gt;3.     INTERACTIVE:&lt;br/&gt;	a.  A paragraph explaining the concept and message behind the piece&lt;br/&gt;	b.  A rendering/ reference of installation&lt;br/&gt;	c.  Materials being used&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a41e6157-26d2-4ab9-91be-b2b1cef238ea" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>30649a9c-30dc-490c-a495-2a8ca1788c18</id><title>3/11 - Sculptors Guild | Curator Call for Proposals</title><updated>2019-02-07T13:48:19.084469+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sculptors Guild, Inc&lt;br/&gt;📍 NY, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sculptorsguild.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sculptors Guild&lt;br/&gt;Curator Call for Proposals&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Sculptors Guild is accepting curatorial proposals from emerging and established curators for consideration for Sculptors Guild member exhibition opportunities. We are looking for multiple curators for a number of upcoming opportunities in both indoor and outdoor, large-scale exhibition spaces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Sculptors Guild, an artist-run nonprofit 501c3 organization based in New York City, has had a vital presence for decades in New York City. Its mission is to promote, encourage, and serve as an advocate for sculpture and to make contemporary sculpture a relevant part of the cultural experience. It maintains a professional membership of acclaimed sculptors and is dedicated to the promotion of sculpture and sculptors through exhibitions and educational outreach programs. The Sculptors Guild has enjoyed a resurgence of interest by emerging sculptors of various divergent aesthetics. We are an alternative cultural institution, have a self-directed board, and are supported by our network of active artist participants.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A honorarium will be provided in exchange for curation, an essay and press release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PLEASE SUBMIT the following via  email with the Subject Line: Curatorial Proposal to SculptorsGuild@gmail.com:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1) A one page proposal maximum&lt;br/&gt;2) Resume&lt;br/&gt;3) 3-5 images or links to past projects&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Monday, March 11, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To view SG activities and member artwork please visit our website: &lt;a href="https://www.sculptorsguild.org" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.sculptorsguild.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;View DIGITAL CATALOGS of past exhibitions to get an overview of guild members at the following links:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2018 Catalog: politics of space&lt;br/&gt;http://www.blurb.com/bookstore/invited/7900789/0baae92e384e727bba47868a01973ce7d7766e5d&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2017 Catalog:    Currently 80&lt;br/&gt;https://www.sculptorsguild.org/s/CURRENTLY-80-CATALOG.pdf&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2016 Catalog:    American Twist&lt;br/&gt;https://www.sculptorsguild.org/s/2016-American-Twist-Catalog.pdf&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2015 Catalog:    Laws of Attraction&lt;br/&gt;https://www.sculptorsguild.org/s/2015-SG-LOA-CATALOG.pdf&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2014 Catalog:    Transformation&lt;br/&gt;https://www.sculptorsguild.org/s/SG_CATALOG_V18-ONLINE-nmwx.pdf&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/30649a9c-30dc-490c-a495-2a8ca1788c18" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7d83b0cc-d994-4918-8932-06554b023bea</id><title>&amp;quot;...dream again&amp;quot;  Open Call</title><updated>2019-02-07T13:48:19.084351+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Secret Theatre in association with LIC Artists Inc&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.secrettheatre.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call for an LIC Arts Open collaboration with The Secret Theatre&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Hosted by LiC-A at the Plaxall Gallery and curated by Norma Homberg&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: The Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition on View: March 7th, 2019 to March 31st, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Reception: Saturday, March 9th, 7-10PM&lt;br/&gt;Mediums: Paintings, collage, and wall sculptures only. Please, no installation work.&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee: $15.00 for LiC-A members, $30.00 for non-members&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline : Friday, February 22, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition concept: &lt;br/&gt;When submitting to this exhibition running alongside the Secret Theatre’s production of William Shakespeare’s The Tempest, think darker shades of blues and purples. Think medium and larger scale work - small works will get lost in this exhibition. Your work will be part of an incredibly strong Fine Art Exhibition and sets the backdrop for a full length, immersive production of The Tempest while the play is in session in the evenings at the gallery. We are going for monochrome paintings, storm and magical realism. Please avoid overly 'busy' or “whimsy” artwork.&lt;br/&gt;The curator is also looking for artwork which would be specifically for Caliban’s cave. The cave has precious treasures stored in little nooks which Gallery visitors can open and explore.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This form is for artists to submit images of their work for consideration. The final selection of work will be determined by the curator.  To show your full range, we suggest submitting the maximum of five works. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission fee (non-refundable) is $30 for non-members, $15 for members.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS: Please include images of your work to be submitted using the instructions below:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s contact information (Note: address, email, phone will not be published)&lt;br/&gt;Up to 5 images, JPEGs only, under 1 MB each; 72dpi is adequate, image width not to exceed 1024 pixels on the longest side. Label each file as follows: LastName_FirstName_TitleOfWork.jpg. Example: Smith_Jane_Tranquility.jpg.&lt;br/&gt;Description of Work. Descriptions must include: Uploaded Title, date, medium, dimensions (H x W x D) price. For example: “Tranquility”, 2018, Oil on Linen, 20 x 16 inches, $700.00.&lt;br/&gt;Note: Artist's name, website, description of work and price will appear on exhibition wall labels exactly as entered in this form. Please proof your entries before submitting the form. No other personal information will be printed. Accepted artwork may be featured on our website.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DELIVERY DATES: all selected artwork must be delivered to the Plaxall Gallery: Saturday, March 2nd from 12-5PM, Sunday, March 3rd from 12-8PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION DEADLINE: Friday, February 22nd 11:59 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOTIFICATION OF ACCEPTANCE: February 26th&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PICK UP DATE: Sunday, March 31st 7th 5-8PM and Monday, April 1st 10AM-1: 30 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;OPENING RECEPTION: Saturday, March 9th, 7-10PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ADDRESS: Plaxall Gallery, 5-25 46th Avenue, Long Island City, Queens - between Vernon and 5th Street. The entrance to the gallery space is on the parking lot (west) side of the building at the second loading bay.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please e-mail info@licartists.org with any questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PLEASE APPLY HERE:  &lt;a href="http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_dream_again" target="_blank"&gt;http://licartists.formstack.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please do not reply to the email address listed here.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7d83b0cc-d994-4918-8932-06554b023bea" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d95ce4d5-ab1e-4bdf-b5fd-85db11907468</id><title>3/29 - Real Art Awards</title><updated>2019-02-07T13:48:19.084295+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Real Art Ways&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hartford, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/29/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.realartways.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emerging artists living and working in New England, New York or New Jersey who are no more than three years removed from a full-time educational program, or artists with less than five years of exhibition experience are eligible to apply to this call. Artists working in all media are welcome. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NO ENTRY FEE.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Six artists will receive: &lt;br/&gt;- $2,500 prize&lt;br/&gt;- Solo exhibit at Real Art Ways in 2019 or 2020&lt;br/&gt;- Exhibition publication with commissioned essay and documentation &lt;br/&gt;- Curatorial assistance&lt;br/&gt;- Opportunity for an artist talk&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JURORS: &lt;br/&gt;Terry Jenoure, Artist / Curator, Director, Augusta Savage Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Olu Oguibe, Artist / Critic&lt;br/&gt;Will K. Wilkins, Executive Director of Real Art Ways&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This project is supported in part by an award from the National Endowment for the Arts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and submission guidelines, including image and video requirements, download the submissions guide at realartways.org.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions?&lt;br/&gt;Please address questions to: Neil Daigle-Orians, Visual Arts Coordinator, norians@realartways.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d95ce4d5-ab1e-4bdf-b5fd-85db11907468" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>