<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-08-01T02:18:26-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>b0053afc-c769-4e47-bbd4-9e1ef587dbd0</id><title>9/9 - It Could Be You: Portraiture in a Constructed World | Juried Portraiture Show | Call for Entries</title><updated>2019-08-01T02:18:26.218441+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Equity Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.nyartistsequity.org/call-for-entries"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equity Gallery is currently accepting submissions of artwork for our upcoming group exhibition, "It Could Be You: Portraiture in a Constructed World." The exhibition is looking to feature art which explores both the purpose and limits of portraiture, identity, and the self in the contemporary digital age. We are interested in works of all mediums and disciplines. Our panel of jurors consists of fellow practitioners and allied professionals such as Beverly McNeil, proprietor of Portraits. Inc, and portrait artists Patricia Watwood and Hyeseung Marriage-Song.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Entries are to be submitted in digital format (preferably in a PDF format, but Word Docs are also accepted) to info@nyartistsequity.org. Submissions must include a maximum of 3 artworks, complete with accompanying images and information about the artworks, noting size, mediums, and date of production.  Art works may be paintings, photographs, drawings, mixed media works, prints, sculpture, digital media, and more. The works’ size must to not exceed 48” in any dimension (including frame).  Please also include a short bio and a CV within your submission.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2. Entrants must successfully fill out and submit an entry form in the field on the Call for Entries' webpage, www.nyartistsequity.org/call-for-entries&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3. Applicants must pay a submission fee of either $35 for general applicants or $20 for current NYAE members. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4. The deadline for entries is Sept 9th at Midnight.  Artists chosen for the exhibition will be notified by Oct. 7th. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;5. Artists are responsible for arranging the shipping of works to and from the gallery.  To be included in the exhibition, works must arrive at the gallery by or before Nov. 8th.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;6. Entries will juried by a panel comprising fellow practitioners and allied professionals, including Beverly McNeil, proprietor of Portraits. Inc, and portraiture artists Patricia Watwood and Hyeseung Marriage-Song.  The jury will also award a first, second, and third prize to exhibiting artists. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have any questions about the Call for Entries, please contact us at info@nyartistsequity.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b0053afc-c769-4e47-bbd4-9e1ef587dbd0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4095015e-1a0e-48c3-a744-ce12a72718f7</id><title>8/30 - Charlotte Mecklenburg Police Department Independence Division Station Public Art Opportunity</title><updated>2019-08-01T02:18:26.218403+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arts &amp;amp; Science Council&lt;br/&gt;📍 Charlotte , NC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Arts &amp; Science Council is accepting qualifications from artists for a public art opportunity at the upcoming Independence Division Police Station, Charlotte, North Carolina. The selected artist will work with the ASC, staff from the City of Charlotte’s General Services Department, Moseley Architects, CMPD representatives, and local communities to create impactful artwork that responds to the parameters of the site, the aesthetics of the architecture, and the themes identified by the project team. &lt;br/&gt;The artwork should highlight the relationship between the Charlotte Mecklenburg Police Department and the community they serve. The selected artist will be expected to engage with both police department staff and area residents to develop the concept for their work. &lt;br/&gt;The following site has been approved for the CMPD Independence public art opportunity: &lt;br/&gt;1.	Free-Standing Sculpture(s) (Exterior –Along Independence Blvd): Opportunity to create freestanding artwork(s) to be placed along the pedestrian areas of the property. This location will be highly visible to pedestrian and vehicular traffic.&lt;br/&gt;For the complete RFQ, please visit: &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.artsandscience.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the complete RFQ, please visit: &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.artsandscience.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To submit qualifications, please visit: &lt;a href="https://asc.slideroom.com/#/permalink/program/50272" target="_blank"&gt;https://asc.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4095015e-1a0e-48c3-a744-ce12a72718f7" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>86f21e84-fc28-485b-91c0-4172ec83c370</id><title>8/29 - When Darkness Falls: Night Explorations</title><updated>2019-08-01T02:18:26.218344+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Annmarie Sculpture Garden&lt;br/&gt;📍 Solomons, MD, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/29/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://annmariegarden.wufoo.com/forms/when-darkness-falls-night-explorations/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL FOR ENTRIES - a national juried exhibition. All media welcome; small to large-scale works; indoor and outdoor works accepted; cash awards. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHEN DARKNESS FALLS: Night Explorations&lt;br/&gt;October 11, 2019 - January 26, 2020, Kay Daugherty Gallery&lt;br/&gt;ANNMARIE SCULPTURE GARDEN &amp; ARTS CENTER&lt;br/&gt;In Association with the Smithsonian Institution&lt;br/&gt;13470 Dowell Road, Solomons, Maryland, 20676 USA&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE to apply: August 29, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With the setting of the sun, the transition from day to night stirs within us a sense of mystery. What secrets does the night hold? What dreams and possibilities can be uncovered? The jury seeks works that reflect on why we are drawn to the darkness and the unknown, including works that communicate the drama of the night and examine sources of light within the dark. Desirable works will explore the symbolism and superstition of the dark and reveal the mystery cloaked in the wonder of the night.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror: to be announced &lt;br/&gt;(juror is typically drawn from the Smithsonian Institution)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL FOR ENTRIES - a national juried exhibition. All media welcome; small to large-scale works; indoor and outdoor works accepted; cash awards. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHEN DARKNESS FALLS: Night Explorations&lt;br/&gt;October 11, 2019 - January 26, 2020, Kay Daugherty Gallery&lt;br/&gt;ANNMARIE SCULPTURE GARDEN &amp; ARTS CENTER&lt;br/&gt;In Association with the Smithsonian Institution&lt;br/&gt;13470 Dowell Road, Solomons, Maryland, 20676 USA&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE to apply: August 29, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With the setting of the sun, the transition from day to night stirs within us a sense of mystery. What secrets does the night hold? What dreams and possibilities can be uncovered? The jury seeks works that reflect on why we are drawn to the darkness and the unknown, including works that communicate the drama of the night and examine sources of light within the dark. Desirable works will explore the symbolism and superstition of the dark and reveal the mystery cloaked in the wonder of the night.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror: to be announced &lt;br/&gt;(juror is typically drawn from the Smithsonian Institution)&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/86f21e84-fc28-485b-91c0-4172ec83c370" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>