<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-07T23:17:12-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>194b6296-2858-463a-9d74-09fb4078acc3</id><title>6/25 - open call @ East Village, NYC</title><updated>2019-06-07T23:17:12.662027+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;MAGA NY &amp;amp; La Mama La Galleria&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.whenblackswallowsred.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a part of our annual emerging artist promotion project, MAGA NY is seeking submission for its open call program “when black swallows red” co-hosted with La Mama La Galleria, in East Village, NYC. Artists working in all media are welcomed to submit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The theme comes from one of Mark Rothko’s remarks about his artistic concerns: “…(if) there is only one thing I fear in life, my friend: one day, the black will swallow the red.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;While people often believe there are metaphorical meanings behind it, the arcane statement is open for interpretation, as we welcome artists to explore the concepts of processing, oxidizing, coloring, decaying, migration, and transformation to decode, respond, reflect or re-contextualize this statement.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On view: July 5th - July 10th (open reception: July 5th, 5:30 PM)&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: June 25th&lt;br/&gt;Venue: La Mama La Galleria, 47 Great Jones St, New York, NY 10003&lt;br/&gt;please visit &lt;a href="http://www.whenblackswallowsred.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.whenblackswallowsred.com&lt;/a&gt; for the details&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The selection will be made on a rolling-base so we encourage you to submit early!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MAGA (Metropolitan Art Gallery Association) is a 501(c)(3) not-for-profit organization. We aim to facilitate the cultural and intellectual exchanges in contemporary art in the NYC metropolitan area through curatorial events, publications, and public exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;please visit &lt;a href="http://www.whenblackswallowsred.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.whenblackswallowsred.com&lt;/a&gt; for the details&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;for more details on our organization, follow our Instagram @magamaga_nyu&lt;br/&gt;or check our website: &lt;a href="http://www.magany.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.magany.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/194b6296-2858-463a-9d74-09fb4078acc3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9f25e412-691f-4821-b8a6-073499b875c3</id><title>7/1 - ART FROM THE BOROS VII OPEN CALL FOR ARTISTS</title><updated>2019-06-07T23:17:12.661967+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Denise Bibro Fine Art&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York , NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.denisebibrofineart.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/05/Prospectus-Boro-VII-2019.pdf"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s that time of the year again- Denise Bibro Fine Art announces "Art From The Boros VII"&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;From numerous submissions and studio visits, diverse artists were selected to participate in this annual group show highlighting talent found within New York City’s five boroughs for the past 6 years.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art From the Boros VII exemplifies the eclectic artistic community of New York City, showing a varied range of genres of art and mediums. The mission of the exhibition is to seek and find the pulse of talent in the city that is often overlooked and underexposed. The primary purpose of the exhibition is to bring untapped and underexposed talent in all of the 5 boroughs of New York to the public’s attention. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After visiting all the finalists’ studios, a selection of the most talented of the group will be featured in a group exhibition at Denise Bibro Fine Art. Two artists will be chosen to have a special exhibition of their work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Instructions / Public Contact Information&lt;br/&gt;Click Link for submission proposal | Regional Deadline: July 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;MEDIA: All mediums.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION DEADLINE: Monday, July 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;1. No primary gallery representation&lt;br/&gt;2. Live and work in any of the 5 boroughs&lt;br/&gt;3. $45 entry fee&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY INSTRUCTIONS&lt;br/&gt;– Please pay via paypal info@denisebibrofineart.com. Include your first and last name&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;– Or make a check payable to Denise Bibro Fine Art and send to 529 West 20 Street, 4W, New York, NY 10011&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;– Please email information to info@denisebibrofineart.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email subject line: ART FROM THE BOROS VII, FIRST NAME, LAST NAME&lt;br/&gt;* Fill out application form (LINK BELOW)&lt;br/&gt;* A maximum of 10 hi-res images including: title, date, size, medium, and price&lt;br/&gt;* State whether you paid via paypal or sending a check&lt;br/&gt;* CV (if applicable)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION PROCESS: &lt;br/&gt;Jurying will be on going through the submission period. From the applications a selected group will be chosen and studio visits will take place throughout the entry process. From the studio visits, a second and final group will be chosen. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Link for submission proposal:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.denisebibrofineart.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/05/Prospectus-Boro-VII-2019.pdf&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9f25e412-691f-4821-b8a6-073499b875c3" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>