<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-15T05:17:23-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>e7538f1a-2a8b-438c-928e-fde837887575</id><title>8/21 - 2019 Annual Regional Juried Show: In the Moment</title><updated>2019-06-15T05:17:23.063976+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Spencertown Academy Arts Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Spencertown, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.spencertownacademy.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submissions should display how an artist, inspired by  process and vision, captures the ephemeral into an enduring work of art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE VENUE&lt;br/&gt;Housed in a historic landmark 1847 Greek revival schoolhouse, Spencertown Academy Arts Center presents a variety of arts and cultural programming to an audience of local residents, second homeowners, and tourists from the Hudson Valley and Berkshire regions. Programs include: exhibitions of fine arts and craft; musical performances; spoken word, poetry and drama; workshops and classes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Academy, including the gallery, is a not-for-profit institution supported by membership, public and private donations and grant funding. A volunteer committee comprised of professional artists and curators administers the Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Gallery comprises two exhibition spaces: the larger space is approximately 38’ X 15’ and the smaller is 16’ X 15’. Both rooms have abundant natural light as well as track lighting and 9.5’ ceilings.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR&lt;br/&gt;Our juror is Katherine Carter, an artist representative who places art in museums and galleries. As a consultant, she teaches artists to professionalize their methods of presentation and helps them assess where they are on their career track and how to get their work shown. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MEDIA&lt;br/&gt;Any media except photography or fine crafts.  No reproductions or giclée will be considered.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AWARDS&lt;br/&gt;The guest juror will curate the show and bestow First, Second and 2 Honorable Mention Places before the Opening.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;Submissions will be accepted from residents of Columbia County, NY and the following surrounding counties: Rensselaer, Albany, Schenectady, Ulster, Dutchess and Greene in NY, Litchfield and Fairfield in CT, and Berkshire in MA.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DATES AT A GLANCE&lt;br/&gt;Wednesday, August 21, Midnight EDT: Deadline for online submission of entries&lt;br/&gt;Friday, September 6: Notice of Acceptance emailed&lt;br/&gt;Thursday, September 26: Hand delivery to Spencertown Academy 5:00-7:00pm&lt;br/&gt;Saturday, October 5: Exhibition opens to the public 1:00pm to 5:00pm&lt;br/&gt;Saturday, October 5: Opening reception 4:00pm to 6:00pm&lt;br/&gt;Sunday, October 27: Show closes 5:00pm&lt;br/&gt;Sunday, October 27: Pick up artwork 5:00-6:00pm&lt;br/&gt;Monday, October 28: Pick up artwork 10:00- 11:00am&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOW TO ENTER&lt;br/&gt;All submissions must be made online through Showsubmit.com.&lt;br/&gt;Complete guidelines, entry forms and instructions for submission are detailed there.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Up to 4 images may be submitted. Maximum size of entry, including edges of frame must not exceed 36 inches in any direction. Artwork must not have been previously exhibited at the Academy. Work created in the last three years is preferred. 3-D art must be light enough for one person to handle and be able to be hung on the wall, displayed on the floor, an Academy pedestal, or on a shelf provided by the artist.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEE&lt;br/&gt;Members $35. Non-Members $45. This fee covers submission of up to 4 pieces. Become a member today: &lt;a href="https://spencertownacademy.org/support/membership/" target="_blank"&gt;https://spencertownacademy.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ACCEPTANCE&lt;br/&gt;Notification of acceptance will be made on Wednesday, September 5 by email. No substitutions of accepted work will be allowed. All work must remain in the gallery for the duration of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SALES&lt;br/&gt;The Gallery will take a 35% commission on any work sold.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DISPLAY INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;ALL hanging 2D work must be wired for hanging with professional-grade wire and screw eyes. Ensure corners of frames, whether metal or wood, are tightly joined. Examine work for stray debris that may have slipped in during framing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For the entry system, questions should be directed to Joe Baker. &lt;br/&gt;Email: jbaker@showsubmit.com &lt;br/&gt;Phone: (413) 528-5134&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For all other questions, contact Show Chair, Leslie Gabosh at art@spencertownacademy.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e7538f1a-2a8b-438c-928e-fde837887575" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>