<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-14T22:15:49-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>25f539f4-dce6-4555-ac2d-d70b180426bf</id><title>3/25 - Open Call for Artists - &amp;quot;Green: The Impossible Color&amp;quot;</title><updated>2019-02-14T22:15:49.716094+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Painting Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.thepaintingcenter.org/juried-exhibitions"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Green: The Impossible Color&lt;br/&gt;Curated by Rachael Wren&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Of all the colors in the rainbow, green is perhaps the most mutable and multifaceted. As a color, it can lean towards yellow, blue, gray, or brown, while still remaining unquestionably itself. Green evokes associations of landscape and nature – everything from the palest new spring buds to the dark evergreens of deep winter. Yet it can also remind us of cities and the manmade – green glass skyscrapers, copper rooftops, the Statue of Liberty, and printed money. Emotionally, green has long signified envy, a pit of snakes coiled in the body. But add white and the color turns minty, suggesting more pleasant and peaceful states of mind.  What does green mean to you? How does this elusive color make its way into your work, either as the star player or in a supporting role? The Painting Center is interested in work in all media (under 48” in any direction) featuring green in any of its manifestations for this juried exhibition. This exhibition is open to all media.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: April 23 - May 18, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: March 25, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Notification Date: March 31, 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply via Slide Room: &lt;br/&gt;https://thepaintingcenter.slideroom.com/#/login/program/47070&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shazzi Thomas&lt;br/&gt;Director of The Painting Center&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/25f539f4-dce6-4555-ac2d-d70b180426bf" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ec862492-be2d-4410-8c3e-ed23b675145c</id><title>5/15 - 84th Annual National Juried Art Exhibition</title><updated>2019-02-14T22:15:49.716064+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Cooperstown Art Association&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cooperstown, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://fs30.formsite.com/CooperstownArt/r3rna8zfuk/index.html"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;84th ANNUAL NATIONAL JURIED ART EXHIBITION,  7/12/19 - 8/16/19.  Cooperstown Art Association, Cooperstown NY.   JUROR:  Christopher Murray.  All media.  Possible $3,000  in prizes.  Catalog.  Online Entry Deadline:  5/15/19.  Prospectus:  available at www.cooperstownart.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online Entry Deadline:  5/15/19.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Prospectus Available Online:&lt;br/&gt;https://fs30.formsite.com/CooperstownArt/r3rna8zfuk/index.html&lt;br/&gt;and at www.cooperstownart.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ec862492-be2d-4410-8c3e-ed23b675145c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ca3b77fa-9bac-401a-b840-ca088cc29b0c</id><title>3/14 - INTERNATIONAL CALL FOR ART, ArtMaze Magazine Spring Edition: Issue 12</title><updated>2019-02-14T22:15:49.716031+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtMaze Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍  , United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artmazemagazine.submittable.com/submit/133107/international-call-for-art-artmaze-mag-spring-edition-12"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art Maze Magazine is an independent artist-run and ad-free international print and online publication dedicated to showcasing and promoting experimental and progressive contemporary art, which reflects modern society and its environment, provokes conversation and action; fosters innovation and diversity of mediums which make today’s art scene so intriguing and versatile.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: Artists are welcome to submit works in any medium: painting, drawing, sculpture, ceramics, printmaking, photography, textile, installation, mixed media, digital, film (only jpg + link to video) etc. All visual art mediums are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists or any art organisations on behalf of artists from all countries are welcome to submit their works for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each submitted artist, wether selected for a publication or not, will receive a digital copy of the magazine's issue which he/she applied for.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: March 14th, 2019 (12:00 AM, midnight: end of the day 14th March - Eastern Standard Time)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUEST CURATOR: Tristian Koenig, Melbourne-based Gallerist&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO APPLY: www.artmazemag.com/call-for-art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DISTRIBUTION: Physical and digital copies of ArtMaze Mag are distributed worldwide via bookshops, galleries and online. More info: &lt;a href="http://artmazemag.com/shop/" target="_blank"&gt;http://artmazemag.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selected artists will be asked for high resolution images and will be published in the next print and digital issue of ArtMaze Magazine. Each (selected) artist will receive a 1 or 2-page spread in print and digital (PDF) magazine including bio, statement, website, and 1-5 featured artworks. All submitted artists will receive a complimentary PDF copy of the magazine and all published artists will be promoted on our website/social media. &lt;br/&gt;Physical copies of Art Maze Magazine are printed to the highest quality in London, UK.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ca3b77fa-9bac-401a-b840-ca088cc29b0c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e39fed63-d69d-4ad1-8fc1-d167295ee629</id><title>6/15 - Rust Belt Biennial - open for photographic submissions</title><updated>2019-02-14T22:15:49.715992+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Rust Belt Biennial&lt;br/&gt;📍 Wilkes-Barre, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.rustbeltbiennial.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to introduce the first RUST BELT BIENNIAL, a celebration of photography with work realized throughout the Rust Belt Region in all its manifestations. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This land, its people, the pride and the struggles, the patina of the past and above all, the histories and memories ingrained in the soil across the region. It is time to make new memories and new histories, while revisiting and reevaluating old ones; It is time to start a new dialogue about the state of photography and it’s social, cultural and political effects in our society; it is time to give back to the photographic community but also the region; it is time for you to join us! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For our an inaugural Biennial we are grateful to have Andrew L. Moore as competition juror.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are honored to collaborate with the Sordoni Gallery at Wilkes University, in Wilkes-Barre, Penn., where the Biennial will be held from August 27th to October 5h of 2019. Additional information regarding the dates of the main exhibition with lectures and presentations will be published in the Spring.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our juried competition is hosted in an agreement between LensCulture and Rust Belt Biennial.  Using the SUBMIT HERE button &lt;br/&gt;(https://www.lensculture.com/competitions/Rust-Belt-Biennial/events) &lt;br/&gt;on our website will redirect you to LensCulture so that you can sign up for an account and submit your entry through the online entry portal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use this link to skip our website and go directly to the submission form on LensCulture:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.lensculture.com/competitions/Rust-Belt-Biennial/events&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What are we looking for?&lt;br/&gt;We are looking for photographic bodies of works that explore the social and cultural realities that represent or make a commentary of this very important region within the American landscape. &lt;br/&gt;Additionally, we are looking for both in progress or fully realized photographic work in printed form.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Who is eligible?&lt;br/&gt;All are welcome to submit work that was created within the Rust Belt Region (New York, Missouri, Pennsylvania, Ohio, Indiana, Michigan, West Virginia, Illinois, Iowa, Wisconsin)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist information:&lt;br/&gt;Legal Name&lt;br/&gt;Artist Name if different&lt;br/&gt;Address&lt;br/&gt;Email Address&lt;br/&gt;Telephone&lt;br/&gt;Statement (up to 500 words)&lt;br/&gt;Bio (up to 300 words)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Image information and file requirements:&lt;br/&gt;Title format for each image: Title, caption(optional), location&lt;br/&gt;Date&lt;br/&gt;Medium (Print Type)&lt;br/&gt;File naming: First and last name, image title&lt;br/&gt;Example: John_Smith-Image_Title.jpg&lt;br/&gt;File format: JPG&lt;br/&gt;File dimensions: 2500 pixels on the longest side&lt;br/&gt;Color space: sRGB&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission fee:&lt;br/&gt;$35 for up to 25 images&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e39fed63-d69d-4ad1-8fc1-d167295ee629" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b5894a3b-52c1-4735-b2ab-9ae7eaf56fdc</id><title>5/1 - Flow</title><updated>2019-02-14T22:15:49.715936+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Philadelphia Sculptors&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.philaflow.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philadelphia Sculptors seeks artists to create temporary outdoor floating sculptural installations for our Fall, 2019 exhibition "Flow," a collaboration with the Independence Seaport Museum. The exhibition will be sited in the boat basin adjacent to the Museum, located at Penn’s Landing on the Delaware River in Philadelphia and will run from October 11 – November 30, 2019. The intent of the exhibition is to unite art with the river, and with the Museum’s mission and programming.  Five juried artists, along with five invited artists previously selected, will interpret the river and how it affects, and is affected by, human and natural history; human and natural migrations; climate change and the environment; economic development; and political currents. The geographic focus of the show is on the Americas and we are seeking artists from Mexico, South and Central America, and Canada, along with artists from the US and its territories. The jurors will be Nato Thompson, and Teresa Jaynes. The exhibition is also co-sponsored by the Dina Wind Art Foundation. Accepted artists will receive a $2,000 honorarium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and how to apply, go to www.philaflow.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b5894a3b-52c1-4735-b2ab-9ae7eaf56fdc" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>