<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-12T09:17:59-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>6f2fe80e-0428-4ad0-8bae-9b1bd2e50b3e</id><title>7/31 - NXTHVN 2020 Studio &amp;amp; Curatorial Fellowships Open Call</title><updated>2019-07-12T09:17:59.268717+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;NXTHVN&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Haven, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.nxthvn.com/2020-program-overview"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each year, NXTHVN welcomes seven emerging artists, two curators, and five high school apprentices to participate in its highly-competitive Fellowship and Apprenticeship programs. With a focus on mentorship, professional development, and hands-on training, the cohort works collaboratively to cultivate their practices within the context of New Haven’s creative community. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The NXTHVN team, with Deborah Berke Partners, has designed a unique shared environment—within a state-of-the-art facility—where artists, curators and the local community converge to make art, exchange ideas, and extend their networks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NXTHVN’s comprehensive, year-long Fellowships provide dedicated work space, a generous stipend, a rigorous professional development curriculum, and ongoing mentorship opportunities for early-career artists and curators. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some examples of our workshops and seminars include: Strategic Planning, Money Management, Contracts (Art and Law), Online Portfolio Development, Visiting Curator Discussions and Critiques, Professional Artist Talks, and Gallery and Collection Tours.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NXTHVN’s unique pedagogy focuses on both the theoretical and practical components of establishing and nurturing a sustainable art practice. Our curriculum features bi-monthly workshops and seminars led by esteemed industry leaders and visiting lecturers.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In addition to active participation in cohort-building activities, each fellow mentors a local high school student through our Apprenticeship Program to ensure the next generation of talent is given a chance to excel in the arts. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;* For more info on the Studio Fellowship or to apply, click here. &lt;br/&gt;** For more info on the Curatorial Fellowship or to apply, click here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION DEADLINE: NXTHVN welcomes submissions on a rolling basis each year from mid-May until midnight (EST), the eve of July 31st.  All applications to the NXTHVN Fellowship must be submitted via Submittable by the deadline.&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: Applicants must be 21 by the beginning of the Fellowship year. Artists and curators may not be enrolled in an academic program during the Fellowship year.  Applicants are not required to hold an art degree or to have received formal training.  Applicants may be based in the US or internationally. However, NXTHVN  is unable to cover travel and/or visa fees for internationally-based applicants at this time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION FEE: We require a non-refundable application fee per application, submitted through the online application form. Once you have completed and submitted your application, you will receive a confirmation email that will direct you to a link to pay the application fee. This fee must be paid at the time of submission as you will lose access to the payment page once the application is closed.  If you are financially unable to pay the application fee, please contact us at hello@NXTHVN.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOTIFICATION:  Applicants will be notified of the results via email by mid-August.  Please ensure the email address provided on the application form is active.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION REQUIREMENTS:  Applicants must submit their application through Submittable, our online application form. Please review the application requirements listed below before beginning your application. All information submitted on the application form must be in English.&lt;br/&gt;Applicants to the Studio Fellowship Program are required to submit:&lt;br/&gt;- A clear indication of which program (Studio or Curatorial) you are applying for&lt;br/&gt;- A one-page Letter of Intent&lt;br/&gt;- An updated resume or CV&lt;br/&gt;- A 300-word artist statement*&lt;br/&gt;- 8-10 jpegs of recent work. Artists working with film/video/sound may submit up to 3, 4 minute clips of recent work, or a combination of 6 jpegs and one, 2 minute a/v clip.&lt;br/&gt;- A $35 non-refundable application fee**&lt;br/&gt;*A 1- 2-minute maximum video of the artist’s statement is acceptable, in lieu of a written statement.&lt;br/&gt;** If financial assistance is required, please contact hello@nxthvn.com for more information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applicants to the Curatorial Fellowship Program are required to submit: &lt;br/&gt;- A one-page Letter of Intent&lt;br/&gt;- An updated resume or CV&lt;br/&gt;- A 300-500 word exhibition idea, including budget*&lt;br/&gt;- A $35 non-refundable application fee**&lt;br/&gt;*Exhibition proposals should take into consideration NXTHVN’s stated mission, vision and values; the demographics of our local community; and suggestions for innovative ways to engage our community in exhibition content. The proposed budget should include line items for: shipping, fabrication/printing, installation, framing and equipment rental (if applicable).&lt;br/&gt;** If financial assistance is required, please contact hello@nxthvn.com for more information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION PROCEDURE:​  A panel consisting of six prominent curators, museum professionals, collectors and artists from NXTHVN’s network will make the admissions selections based on an applicant’s ability to clearly express innovative ideas in the application, rather than on the applicant’s prior exhibition experience or resume. Incomplete applications will not be considered.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NON-DISCRIMINATION&lt;br/&gt;NXTHVN encourages and welcomes applicants of all backgrounds to apply for the Fellowships. We do not discriminate based on age, race, sex, sexual orientation, disability, religion, marital status, or nation of origin in our admission policies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6f2fe80e-0428-4ad0-8bae-9b1bd2e50b3e" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>