<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-26T14:15:28-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>db30ca1f-c9a7-4ce9-9cf2-ed995d6fa4ec</id><title>4/12 - CALL FOR ENTRY: SQHAP EMERGING ARTISTS EXHIBIT 2019</title><updated>2019-03-26T14:15:28.680053+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Stone Quarry Hill Art Park&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cazenovia, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/12/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://sqhap.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stone Quarry Hill Art Park proudly announces a call for entries for its upcoming Spring exhibition   Discovery: Emerging Artists of 2019.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition will provide a platform for emerging artists to showcase their work in a professional gallery setting at the Art Park’s indoor John and Virginia Winner Memorial Gallery space. Collegiate, developing and mid-career artists are encouraged to complete the application form online at stonequarryhillartpark.org by Friday April 12th, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition begins with an opening reception in the John and Virginia Winner Memorial Gallery on Saturday, June 1st  from 5:00 pm – 7:00 pm; the exhibition will run through June 30, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All applications must be submitted through the online application on sqhap.org.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following must be submitted:&lt;br/&gt;Cover page with name, address, phone, email address, website, and artist bio.&lt;br/&gt;Artist statement which specifically speaks about the work the artist intends to submit for this exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;3-5 Images per entry.  Please submit a list of images (include the title, size, medium and price)&lt;br/&gt;Images must be .jpeg only.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Files should be saved with the following conventions: year of entry_artist last name_artist first name_Entry Title_medium_monthday of entry (Example: 2016_Smith_Michael_Untitled_oil on canvas_feb1).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The cost to apply is $25 per entry (1-3 pieces) with $5 per additional entry.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please contact Sarah Tietje-Mietz (sarah@stonequarryhillartpark.org) for assistance with all additional questions and requests for information.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/db30ca1f-c9a7-4ce9-9cf2-ed995d6fa4ec" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>5ddb1067-e2a2-4f2d-940f-ca142dd07229</id><title>4/26 - WORKS ON PAPER 2019 @ The Long Beach Island Foundation of the Arts, NJ</title><updated>2019-03-26T14:15:28.679994+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Long Beach Island Foundation of the Arts &amp;amp; Sciences, NJ&lt;br/&gt;📍 Loveladies, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/26/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://lbifoundation.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call to Enter &lt;br/&gt;"Works on Paper" 2019 is the 21st Annual National Juried Competition and Exhibition at the Long Beach Island Foundation of the Arts &amp; Sciences, Long Beach Island, NJ. Works on Paper can include but is not limited to Drawing, Painting on Paper, Prints, Photography, Digital Works on Paper, and Paper constructions that can be wall hung.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DR LOUIS MARCHESANO, Curator of Drawings, Prints &amp; Photography at the Philadelphia Museum of Art, is the JUROR.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The application is on-line at: &lt;br/&gt;https://www.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=6110&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CALENDAR&lt;br/&gt;Important DATES: Deadline to enter April 26, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;May 3:  Accepted entries posted on LBIF website by this date; artists will also be notiﬁed by email&lt;br/&gt;May 20:   Work must be received by this date at LBIF&lt;br/&gt;May 24 - June 23: Exhibition dates&lt;br/&gt;June 16   5–7 PM, Reception&lt;br/&gt;June 27, 2019 Unsold Work returned to artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AWARDS: $500 ﬁrst prize, $250 second prize, $100 third prize and three honorable mentions.&lt;br/&gt;Three cash Prizes and three Honorable Mentions will be awarded by the Juror at the opening reception. Artists do not need to attend the reception to be awarded the prizes. The competition and exhibition is open to emerging as well as established artists working in the continental US.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please feel free to share this exhibition opportunity. Open to all artists in the continental USA. The Foundation, our members and patrons, and our extensive audience of more than 7,000 during the summer season look forward to seeing this outstanding exhibition. Sales are encouraged.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror&lt;br/&gt;The Juror for 2019 is Dr Louis Marchesano, the Philadelphia Museum’s new Audrey and William H. Helfand Senior Curator of Prints, Drawings, and Photographs.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dr. Marchesano has served as Curator of Prints and Drawings at the Getty Research Institute (GRI) in Los Angeles since 2002. After completing a BA with honors in the Visual Arts from the University of Western Ontario in 1987, Marchesano received an MA (1990) and PhD (2001) in the History of Art from Cornell University. Dr. Marchesano has written and lectured on topics ranging from antiquarianism in the Renaissance and Baroque and French prints from the period of the Revolution to the end of the Bourbon Restoration to the graphic work of the German artist Käthe Kollwitz. Much of his scholarship has focused on the history of printmaking in France from the seventeenth through the nineteenth centuries, and for these contributions the French government this year bestowed upon him the honor of Chevalier de l’Ordre des Arts et des Lettres (Knight of the Order of Arts and Letters).&lt;br/&gt;       &lt;br/&gt;QUESTIONS? Please email us:  exhibitions@lbifoundation.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SPECIFICATIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Artists 18 years and older, residing in the continental USA, are eligible. &lt;br/&gt;Works on Paper can include, but are not limited to: drawing, painting on paper, hand-pulled prints, photography, digitally created artwork displayed as prints, photographic prints, and paper construction that are wall hung. Entries must have been created within the last two years and not been previously shown at LBIF.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Two dimensional works should not exceed 60 inches in width and 60 inches in height, and not exceed 10 lbs.  Work may not project in the third dimension beyond 18 inches. Larger size work is encouraged and allowed but the artist must provide return prepaid postage or pre-paid return shipping label for work and packaging that is over 10 lbs and/or larger than 60 inches by 60 inches. Please do not submit work that has a retail value over $10,000.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Submitted work must be available for the duration of the exhibition. ALL WORKS MUST BE FOR SALE. The Long Beach Island Foundation of the Arts &amp; Sciences will retain a 40% commission of the purchase price on all works sold during the exhibition. If any artwork is commissioned from this exhibition, the LBIF will retain 40% of the commissioned price.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Work submitted must be suitably framed, firmly wired, prepared for hanging, and professionally presented. No sawtooth hangers; no sandwich frames. We suggest all paper to be displayed framed and protected under acrylic (Plexiglas). 3-D work will be considered, but should be wall mounted, or able to be displayed on a 10” deep wall mounted shelf. Please do not submit three dimensional works in the round that require pedestals.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Long Beach Island Foundation of the Arts &amp; Sciences reserves the right to exclude from the exhibition any works that do not arrive in sturdy condition, or are deemed too fragile to be successfully exhibited. Work that has not been suitably prepared will be hung at LBIF's discretion.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please only submit work that will be available at the time of the exhibition and will remain for its entirety. No accepted entry may be withdrawn prior to the close of the exhibition. No pricing changes will be allowed after acceptance. Work that is copied or done under the guidance of an instructor is not eligible. Entries must not have been previously exhibited at LBIF. If the work does not fully reﬂect what is represented in the submitted images, Long Beach Island Foundation of the Arts &amp; Sciences reserves the right to exclude it from the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Please refer to the prospectus for full details regarding eligibility, deadlines, awards and details posted on the LBIF website at:  &lt;br/&gt;http://lbifoundation.org/events/works-on-paper-2019-national-juried-competition/&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5ddb1067-e2a2-4f2d-940f-ca142dd07229" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>