<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-28T05:14:48-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>da42ad36-2a58-4741-825d-08fb9aba767c</id><title>4/21 - JURIED EXHIBITION, BLUE MOUNTAIN GALLERY, NYC, JURORS: ERIC AHO &amp;amp; RACHEL PORTESI- DEADLINE: 04/21/19</title><updated>2019-02-28T05:14:48.391417+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Blue Mountain Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.bluemountaingallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BLUE MOUNTAIN GALLERY JURIED EXHIBITION SUMMER 2019- July 30- Aug 26&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JURORS:  ERIC AHO, painter&lt;br/&gt;RACHEL PORTESI, photographer&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY DEADLINE: April 21, 2019 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BLUE MOUNTAIN GALLERY, located in the heart of New York City’s Chelsea District, invites emerging, mid-career and established artists to submit work for its 8th Juried Exhibition. For this show the jurors are prominent painter Eric Aho and acclaimed photographer Rachel Portesi, husband and wife, and photography has been added to the media accepted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ERIC AHO is a prominent American painter known for his gestural, abstract paintings that evoke natural forms. He is represented by DC Moore Gallery in NYC. Born in Melrose, Massachusetts in 1966, he grew up in rural New Hampshire. After studying at the Central School of Art and Design in London, Aho received his BFA from the Massachusetts College of Art in Boston. Aho completed his graduate work at the Lahti Art Institute in Finland supported by a Fulbright Fellowship in 1991–92 and an American-Scandinavian Foundation grant in 1993. His works have been exhibited and collected widely in the United States and abroad and are included in the permanent collections of the Currier Museum of Art, Manchester, NH; Denver Art Museum, CO; Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco; Hood Museum of Art, Hanover, NH; The Metropolitan Museum of Art; Museum of Fine Arts, Boston; The Neuberger Museum of Art; and the New Britain Museum of American Art, among others.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RACHEL PORTESI received a BA in Sociology and Photography from Marlboro College, VT. Her work as a black and white documentary photographer was complemented by the acquisition of her first Polaroid Land camera in 1991. Ten years later, with a move to New York City and no access to a darkroom, Portesi’s practice shifted exclusively to the immediacy of the Polaroid.  Working this way resulted in a body of work produced over more than two decades ending a few years ago when an older, even more finicky, and time-consuming way of making “instant pictures” caught Portesi’s attention—the wet plate collodion tintype.  Her current projects in tintype are self reflective “Hair Portraits.” Her photographs have been exhibited at various venues in New England and in New York. She works and lives with her family in Saxtons River, Vermont.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY Open to artists 18+years of age, living in the USA. Two-dimensional Media: original oils, acrylics, pastels, watercolors, prints, drawings, photography and mixed media. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FEES The fee is $40 for 1-3 works. $5 for each additional work up to 6 works total. Entry fees are paid through the entry form’s PayPal link, which accepts credit cards. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Additional submission requirements are available at&lt;br/&gt;www.bluemountaingallery.org/summer-juried-show-2019/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online submission only&lt;br/&gt;PROSPECTUS: &lt;a href="https://bluemountaingallery.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/bmg-summer-juried-2019.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;https://bluemountaingallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;INQUIRIES CONTACT: bluemountaingallery@verizon.net - 646.486.4730&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/da42ad36-2a58-4741-825d-08fb9aba767c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c0b433d4-fc84-4e34-85ae-0d519b77cc00</id><title>4/19 - Diversity in Our Lives</title><updated>2019-02-28T05:14:48.391360+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Art League of Long Island&lt;br/&gt;📍 Dix Hills, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.artleagueli.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call for Artists from the NY Tri-State Area&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Diversity in Our Lives&lt;br/&gt;Exhibiting in the Art League of Long Island's Jeanie Tengelsen Gallery &lt;br/&gt;May 25 - June 23, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Reception: June 9, 1:00-3:00&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Thomas Germano&lt;br/&gt;Professor of Art and Art History, Farmingdale State College&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The concept of diversity encompasses acceptance and respect. It means understanding that each individual is unique, and recognizing our individual differences. These can be along the dimensions of race, ethnicity, gender, sexual orientation, socio-economic status, age, physical abilities, religious beliefs, political beliefs, or other ideologies. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Art League of Long Island hopes, through this exhibition, to encourage understanding of each other and move beyond simple tolerance to embracing and celebrating the rich dimensions of diversity contained within each individual.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Period: Opens February 16, Closes April 19 @ 4:00pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Open to artists residing in the Tri-State area.&lt;br/&gt;• Entry is limited to 5 works not previously exhibited in another juried ALLI show, one of which may be selected&lt;br/&gt;by the juror for admission.&lt;br/&gt;• Two- and three-dimensional work in any medium may be submitted, including photography and fine craft. Sorry, no videos.&lt;br/&gt;• Work MUST be original. Replicas or reproductions of pre-existing work are not admissible. We reserve the&lt;br/&gt;right to reject on delivery work of questionable facture.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Submit entries online at &lt;a href="https://client.smarterentry.com/alli" target="_blank"&gt;https://client.smarterentry.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Prospectus is posted online at www.artleagueli.org under call for artists&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit entries online only at:  &lt;a href="https://client.smarterentry.com/alli" target="_blank"&gt;https://client.smarterentry.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c0b433d4-fc84-4e34-85ae-0d519b77cc00" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>