<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-22T16:18:13-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>0382ff04-8cc9-4b9b-8994-43f42e0dbc0a</id><title>8/6 - OPEN CALL FOR ARTISTS NEAR AND FAR: OUR 2019 MAIL ART BIENNIAL</title><updated>2019-07-22T16:18:13.629368+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ground Floor Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://groundfloorbk.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to officially announce the return of our summer show, “Priority Mail: Our 2019 Mail Art Biennial,” our sweeping survey of small, original artworks mailed to us by contemporary artists from across the globe, “Priority Mail” is a grand and inclusive gesture for our intimate gallery space in Park Slope, Brooklyn: ALL submissions mailed to the gallery will be accepted and shown in the exhibition! Submissions from down to the block to across the country and the globe are encouraged. NO FEE. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you’ve followed the gallery and have wanted to show with us – now is your chance! We look forward to showing artists from near and far while supporting a cause that is near and dear to us as well! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In the spirit of inclusion and accessibility, all artworks will be priced at $125. The gallery and artist will receive 50% commission and 10% of gallery profits will be donated to the Committee to Protect Journalists in their tireless efforts to defend freedom of the press worldwide. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Thursday, August 8th, 6-9pm &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE NOTE: Due to the scope of the exhibition, we cannot return unsold work. You can arrange to have it picked up or it will be donated to a local charity or school in our network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists, please carefully review the guidelines below.  Work that does not adhere to the guidelines will not be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUIDELINES: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Mail your artwork to the gallery by August 6th, 2019. If it arrives later due to late notice or postal issues, we will still hang it when it arrives!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- NO phone calls.  Please direct message us on Twitter, Instagram or Facebook with any and all questions to @groundfloorbk and we’ll respond promptly.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- All work must be sized 5” x 7” (up to 6” x 9” if framed). The work does not have to be framed but, in our experience, framed and mounted work sells best. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Work in all media will be accepted (photography and prints MUST be limited-edition works). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Only ONE submission will be accepted per artist&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- You MUST have your name, email, phone number, artwork title, materials, year and location (e.g. Brooklyn, Madrid, London, Sydney, etc.)  included on the back of your artwork.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Email up to 4 hi res photos (under 5 MB each) of your complete artwork with caption (name, title, materials, year and 2 sentences about the work) to info@groundfloorbk.com with the subject: Priority Mail.  Please name each jpeg with your name, for example: RayJohnson1.jpeg, RayJohnson2.jpeg. We will use these images for documentation and promotion.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DO NOT drop off submissions.  That defeats the whole purpose. All work should be mailed to:&lt;br/&gt;   &lt;br/&gt; Ground Floor Gallery&lt;br/&gt; 343 5th Street&lt;br/&gt; Brooklyn, New York 11215&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0382ff04-8cc9-4b9b-8994-43f42e0dbc0a" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>