<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-06T22:14:59-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>483f4950-e780-491a-8a45-90511448e8e8</id><title>4/1 - Call for Proposals: Summer/Fall Exhibition at Opalka Gallery in Albany, NY</title><updated>2019-03-06T22:14:59.120547+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Opalka Gallery, Sage College of Albany&lt;br/&gt;📍 Albany, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://Opalka.sage.edu"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roads. Pipes. Wires. Bureaucracies. These words describe infrastructure, the physical and metaphysical systems that surround us all.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In-faux-structure, an ambitious indoor/outdoor exhibition scheduled for August – October 2019, will investigate gender and identity as it relates to infrastructure. Who makes decisions related to infrastructure? Who is responsible for the labor? Who designs it?  Everyone uses and pays for infrastructure but is everyone represented in its planning, building, and oversight?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition opportunity is open to artists and non-artists to explore their definition of infrastructure, how it can be improved, who it serves, who it doesn’t serve, and who is left out altogether. We are looking for playful takes on the systems that surround us. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The name In-"faux"-structure refers to false or erroneous meaning related to infrastructure, the ephemeral nature of building materials, and other ambiguities related to physical and social systems and their creation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION GOAL&lt;br/&gt;In-faux-structure will create an awareness of inequities related to infrastructure, its planning, its building, and its public face. The project will encourage dialogue between artists and collaborators and spark dialogues through exhibition-related events and community engagement.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CALL FOR WORK&lt;br/&gt;In-faux-structure is open to those working in all media - for both new and existing work. Proposals for site-specific and related projects — including projects outside the gallery and expanding into the community — are encouraged. We welcome artists who wish to collaborate and will help you find the right person(s) with whom to collaborate. Collaborators  may include other artists, people working in the trades, engineers, architects, poets, social activists, etc. We can provide a layout of the space (indoor and outdoor) for artists to consider. Individual and collaborative proposals may respond to social, emotional, or physical issues related to infrastructure. We welcome humor, irony, and creative interpretations of the topic. Proposals may respond to the following or related ideas:&lt;br/&gt;- The planning of infrastructure&lt;br/&gt;- The naming of infrastructure&lt;br/&gt;- Connection (physical, social, etc.)&lt;br/&gt;- The relationship of power to gender, racial, or other identities&lt;br/&gt;- “Fixing” problems related to structures&lt;br/&gt;- The maintenance of infrastructure&lt;br/&gt;- Erosion of infrastructure&lt;br/&gt;- Reimagining existing structures or networks&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOTE: We have a shared Google doc for people would like to find collaborators. Email request for access to infauxstructure@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;br/&gt;SUBMIT application document to: infauxstructure@gmail.com by APRIL 1, 2019, 11:59PM.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Late applications will not be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PROJECT EVALUATION&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition organizers will select projects based on the following criteria:&lt;br/&gt;- Artistic excellence&lt;br/&gt;- Interpretation of exhibition them.&lt;br/&gt;- Lead individual/artist with a proven record of ability to fulfill projects with high standards of quality&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PROJECT SELECTION&lt;br/&gt;There will be two rounds of participant selection. Semi-finalists will be given a small stipend for further project development. Finalists will be awarded fees based on proposed budget, available funds, and other considerations. Artist fees will most likely range from $300-$1500. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Round 1&lt;br/&gt;Applications Due April 1st. Semi-finalists announced by April 12th.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Round 2&lt;br/&gt;Applications Due May 3rd. Finalists announced by May 17th.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;INSTALLATION&lt;br/&gt;Installation will begin in July 2019 for an exhibition opening August 9th, running through mid-October.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contact infauxstructure@gmail.com if you have questions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;* This project is made possible through generous funding from the New York State Council on the Arts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: infauxstructure@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications require the following materials. Incomplete applications will not be considered. Documents should be compiled into one PDF document; please include the last name of the main applicant in the name of the attached file.&lt;br/&gt;- Name(s) of artist/participant&lt;br/&gt;- Statement of Purpose or Artist Statement&lt;br/&gt;- Resume or CV&lt;br/&gt;- Project Description: No more than one page description of your proposed project. *Note if the artwork is intended for indoor or outdoor installation.&lt;br/&gt;- Project budget&lt;br/&gt;- Names and contact information of three (3) references able to speak to your participation in a collaborative setting. *References will only be contacted if your project advances to the semi-finalist round.&lt;br/&gt;- Up to 6 work samples/images. You may include video samples (2 minutes max, total). *Work should demonstrate the proposed concept.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMIT application document to: infauxstructure@gmail.com by APRIL 1, 2019, 11:59PM.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/483f4950-e780-491a-8a45-90511448e8e8" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>66ad27f9-149d-490e-803d-861a612b0e67</id><title>4/1 - OPEN CALL FOR VISUAL ARTISTS</title><updated>2019-03-06T22:14:59.120486+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;NOGO Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.NOGOArts.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOGO Arts announces an open call to visual and installation artists. &lt;br/&gt;WERQ: We’ve Been Doing This Our Whole Lives &lt;br/&gt;June 7, 2019 – June 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Cluster Gallery at Playground Brooklyn &lt;br/&gt;NOGO Arts seeks submissions from visual artists for a group show that fit into the larger theme of queer work and labor. WERQ is intended to celebrate bodies that labor, that do the work society can take for granted or simply chooses to ignore in order to queer office spaces. While we welcome submissions from all points of view, NOGO Arts encourages artists from under represented communities to submit work.  &lt;br/&gt;With WERQ, NOGO Arts seeks to queer a common workspace while recognizing the momentous 50th anniversary of the Stonewall Riots. While Stonewall is a historical marker, it was not the first time queer people rose up to do the work of social justice, hence: We’ve Been Doing This Our Whole Lives. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOGO Arts has its offices at the Playground Brooklyn, an independent coworking space in Gowanus. The Playground also is the home of Brooklyn Art Cluster’s new gallery space. Selected artists will have their work shown in the gallery which also serves as a common space for the Playground. Themes/topics could include (but are not limited to):&lt;br/&gt;•	Equal pay&lt;br/&gt;•	Equity and Inclusivity &lt;br/&gt;•	Inclusivity&lt;br/&gt;•	LGBTQ protection in the work place&lt;br/&gt;•	Queer Labor&lt;br/&gt;•	In/Visibility of work &lt;br/&gt;•	Play as work&lt;br/&gt;•	Work as subject&lt;br/&gt;•	Labor of art making&lt;br/&gt;•	Capitalism&lt;br/&gt;We are interested in curating an exhibit that crosses media and disciplines. &lt;br/&gt;The exhibit will include live performance twice during its run: at the opening night Friday June 7th and again on Wednesday June 19th.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOGO Arts is a nonprofit organization dedicated to promoting and presenting work in the LGBTQ Arts and Humanities. NOGO Arts does not charge a submission fee. Artists will be expected to meet technical requirements as stated by the gallery, ensure delivery and pickup of artwork by agreed upon date, and attend the opening party or performance event (if they live locally). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOGO Arts, Inc. is a 501(c)(3) charitable organization under the IRS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested artists should go to www.NOGOArts.org/werqsubmission to submit work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contact Todd Coulter at todd@nogoarts.org with any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/66ad27f9-149d-490e-803d-861a612b0e67" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>