<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-28T20:14:49-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>29d3f83e-8282-4e2e-92a2-f106c75e0099</id><title>3/30 - Call for Entry: The Art of Wildflowers</title><updated>2019-02-28T20:14:49.414599+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Rancho Santa Ana Botanic Garden&lt;br/&gt;📍 Claremont, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.rsabg.org/events-programs/call-for-entry-the-art-of-wildflowers"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rancho Santa Ana Botanic Garden, the largest botanical garden dedicated to the promotion and conservation of California native plants, is currently seeking submissions for the inaugural The Art of Wildflowers Exhibition. This group exhibition will feature artworks depicting or inspired by California’s incredibly diverse, beautiful blooms. The Art of Wildflowers will be displayed in conjunction with the Garden’s California Wildflower Show. A tradition that has spanned nearly seventy years, the California Wildflower Show displays hundreds of field-collected wildflowers from multiple regions in Southern California. This year, the endless colors, shapes and fragrances of these intensely beautiful flowers will be paired with the artistic renderings and visions of artists that celebrate these blooms in their work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Garden invites artists to submit their work for inclusion in The Art of Wildflowers group exhibition. The exhibition will run concurrently with The California Wildflower Show, April 13 - April 21 at Rancho Santa Ana Botanic Garden in Claremont, California. Works must be two-dimensional, ready to hang or install and either feature or be inspired by native California flowers. Two-dimensional works can be in any media, including drawing, painting, photography, sculptural reliefs, tile, glass or other materials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Deadline: March 31, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Artwork Delivery Deadline: April 6, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Artwork Pickup Deadline: May 22, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Event Dates: April 13 - April 21, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Location: Rancho Santa Ana Botanic Garden, 1500 N College Ave, Claremont CA 91711&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sales/Commissions: RSABG will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales which go to support the Garden and its programming. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed. Artworks will be offered for sale during the duration of the show. Payment to the artist will be via check made out to the name that the Artist provides and sent to the address the Artist provides. The check will be sent within 30 days of the end of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shipping: The Artist is responsible for delivering his/her work to RSABG, either by dropping work off or arranging for shipping. The Artist is also responsible for picking up or arranging the return shipment of his/her work if it does not sell during the exhibition. Work must be delivered by April 6. If work is not sold during the exhibition, the Artist will be notified on Monday, April 22. At this point, the Artist will have 30 days to arrange for the pick up or return shipment of his/her work. After May 22, RSABG will assume the Artist has decided to forfeit his/her artwork and donate it to the Garden. The Artist is responsible for all costs associated with shipping his/her artwork to and from the Garden.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Liability:  RSABG is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking. Every precaution will be taken in handling the entries, but RSABG assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if she/he wishes, needs to provide his/her own insurance. The Garden does not provide insurance.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibiting:  RSABG will be responsible for the curation, installation and labeling of all artwork in the show. RSABG will showcase the Artist’s artwork at the Garden between April 13 and April 21. Sold artwork will hang through the duration of the show. If a work is sold, RSABG will make shipping arrangements with the buyer and pass on associated costs to the buyer. RSABG will be responsible for the deinstallation of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To submit an application, please email David Bryant, Director of Visitor Experience, at dbryant@rsabg.org. In the email please include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your name&lt;br/&gt;Link to website (if you have one)&lt;br/&gt;Title(s) of artwork(s) - each Artist may submit up to three artworks&lt;br/&gt;Image(s) of each artwork(s) with clear filenames that refer to the artwork title(s) provided&lt;br/&gt;Description of artwork(s) that includes media, dimensions, hanging instructions and 1-2 descriptive sentences pertaining to the subject matter&lt;br/&gt;An artist statement that describes your artistic process and focus&lt;br/&gt;Optional: Bibleography and/or Resume&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/29d3f83e-8282-4e2e-92a2-f106c75e0099" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>da42ad36-2a58-4741-825d-08fb9aba767c</id><title>4/21 - JURIED EXHIBITION, BLUE MOUNTAIN GALLERY, NYC, JURORS: ERIC AHO &amp;amp; RACHEL PORTESI- DEADLINE: 04/21/19</title><updated>2019-02-28T20:14:49.414536+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Blue Mountain Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.bluemountaingallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BLUE MOUNTAIN GALLERY JURIED EXHIBITION SUMMER 2019- July 30- Aug 26&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JURORS:  ERIC AHO, painter&lt;br/&gt;RACHEL PORTESI, photographer&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY DEADLINE: April 21, 2019 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BLUE MOUNTAIN GALLERY, located in the heart of New York City’s Chelsea District, invites emerging, mid-career and established artists to submit work for its 8th Juried Exhibition. For this show the jurors are prominent painter Eric Aho and acclaimed photographer Rachel Portesi, husband and wife, and photography has been added to the media accepted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ERIC AHO is a prominent American painter known for his gestural, abstract paintings that evoke natural forms. He is represented by DC Moore Gallery in NYC. Born in Melrose, Massachusetts in 1966, he grew up in rural New Hampshire. After studying at the Central School of Art and Design in London, Aho received his BFA from the Massachusetts College of Art in Boston. Aho completed his graduate work at the Lahti Art Institute in Finland supported by a Fulbright Fellowship in 1991–92 and an American-Scandinavian Foundation grant in 1993. His works have been exhibited and collected widely in the United States and abroad and are included in the permanent collections of the Currier Museum of Art, Manchester, NH; Denver Art Museum, CO; Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco; Hood Museum of Art, Hanover, NH; The Metropolitan Museum of Art; Museum of Fine Arts, Boston; The Neuberger Museum of Art; and the New Britain Museum of American Art, among others.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RACHEL PORTESI received a BA in Sociology and Photography from Marlboro College, VT. Her work as a black and white documentary photographer was complemented by the acquisition of her first Polaroid Land camera in 1991. Ten years later, with a move to New York City and no access to a darkroom, Portesi’s practice shifted exclusively to the immediacy of the Polaroid.  Working this way resulted in a body of work produced over more than two decades ending a few years ago when an older, even more finicky, and time-consuming way of making “instant pictures” caught Portesi’s attention—the wet plate collodion tintype.  Her current projects in tintype are self reflective “Hair Portraits.” Her photographs have been exhibited at various venues in New England and in New York. She works and lives with her family in Saxtons River, Vermont.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY Open to artists 18+years of age, living in the USA. Two-dimensional Media: original oils, acrylics, pastels, watercolors, prints, drawings, photography and mixed media. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FEES The fee is $40 for 1-3 works. $5 for each additional work up to 6 works total. Entry fees are paid through the entry form’s PayPal link, which accepts credit cards. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Additional submission requirements are available at&lt;br/&gt;www.bluemountaingallery.org/summer-juried-show-2019/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online submission only&lt;br/&gt;PROSPECTUS: &lt;a href="https://bluemountaingallery.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/bmg-summer-juried-2019.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;https://bluemountaingallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;INQUIRIES CONTACT: bluemountaingallery@verizon.net - 646.486.4730&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/da42ad36-2a58-4741-825d-08fb9aba767c" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>