<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-08T05:15:01-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>10faceb1-b009-44fc-8c14-53da3bea28d5</id><title>4/8 - 2019 OPEN CALL: BERLIN / LONDON ARTIST RESIDENCY PROGRAM</title><updated>2019-03-08T05:15:01.204162+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;CENTRE. SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS: Applied Grief &amp;amp; Bereavement Research/Multidiscip. Studio&lt;br/&gt;📍  , Germany&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/08/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING:&lt;br/&gt;OPEN CALL&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNUM: &lt;br/&gt;2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PARTICIPATING CITIES:&lt;br/&gt;Berlin, Germany&lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHORT-TERM RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING: UPCOMING DEADLINES&lt;br/&gt;Berlin, Germany Summer 2019 Residency Cohort 1 (1 Month Program): 08 APR 2019&lt;br/&gt;Berlin, Germany Summer 2019 Residency Cohort 2 (1 Month Program): 06 MAY 2019 &lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom Autumn 2019 Residency Cohort 1 (1 Month Program): 03 JUN 2019 &lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom Autumn 2019 Residency Cohort 2 (1 Month Program): 26 JUN 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LONG-TERM RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING: ADDITIONAL DEADLINES:&lt;br/&gt;Long-Term Study Residency (12 Month Program) Deadline: Ongoing&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS is now accepting applications for residency programming commencing in 2019. Artists, researchers, and other arts professionals are encouraged to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ORGANIZATION:&lt;br/&gt;Established in 2009, the CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS is a Canadian organization dedicated to the development of applied grief and bereavement research. Documented through the use of practice-led methods within art and comprised of work from an interdisciplinary network of creative and technical practitioners; the CENTRE is committed to the advancement of the arts and sciences; providing programming in support of education; public and professional engagement; and the development of field research in partnership with local, national, and international academic bodies, institutions, foundations, and non-profits.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION CRITERIA &amp; ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:&lt;br/&gt;The artist-in-residence candidates are selected annually through an open call application process or in some cases, by invitation. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The residency program encourages experimentation and the development of multi/interdisciplinary studio work grounded in research within the field of grief and bereavement. The work can encompass and explore varying physical and emotional processes (or loss) that people undergo. Previous residents and collaborators have undertaken both theoretical-historical and practice-led projects working with, but not limited to the following subject matter: the aging process and the elderly; cancer, disease, and terminal illness; sex work and sexual assault; abortion and miscarriage; suicide and survivorship; mental illness and trauma; spousal and familial loss; and associated grief and bereavement-centered themes etc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The residency aims to provide working artistic professionals with a platform for research and production; one that may lead to expanded possibilities, collaboration, a broader network, and possibly new works. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information and to apply please review the Residency Guide and submit and Application Form here:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To be notified of upcoming opportunities including new and existing programming, open calls, and initiatives, please subscribe to our newsletter here:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/contact/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;——&lt;br/&gt;CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS (Est. 2009) &lt;br/&gt;Applied Grief and Bereavement Research&lt;br/&gt;Interdisciplinary/Multidisciplinary Studio &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Follow us here:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/substructuredloss/&lt;br/&gt;https://vimeo.com/substructuredloss&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The application form and all applicable supplementary attachments must be submitted by email.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information and to apply please review the Residency Guide and submit and Application Form here:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/10faceb1-b009-44fc-8c14-53da3bea28d5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1cefe68f-c7ff-411e-a04f-b93372a96830</id><title>5/17 - Spring + Summer 2020 Artists-in-Residence Open Call</title><updated>2019-03-08T05:15:01.204086+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Bemis Center for Contemporary Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Omaha, NE, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.bemiscenter.org/apply"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RESIDENCY SESSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;January 22–April 17, 2020&lt;br/&gt;May 20–August 14, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Total Artists Selected: 20 (10 artists per residency session)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: May 17, 2019 by 11:59 PM CST&lt;br/&gt;Notifications to all applicants will be made via email on August 15, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For nearly four decades, Bemis Center’s core mission has been to provide artists from around the world dedicated time, space, and resources to conduct research and to create new work across conceptual, material, performative, and social practices. The independently driven atmosphere and communal environment encourages creative growth, experimentation, confrontation of challenges, and cultivation of new ideas.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Bemis offers artists-in-residence unmatched technical guidance, access to interns, and an established network of resources. Participants have the opportunity to create networks, collaborate, and share their work with fellow artists-in-residence, organizational partners, and the public. Bemis Center is also currently building an alumni program that will further extend ongoing artist support.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;STUDIOS AND FACILITIES&lt;br/&gt;Located in downtown Omaha’s historic Old Market, Bemis Center's campus accommodates a broad range of artistic activity. Selected artists-in-residence enjoy generous sized, private live/work studios complete with a kitchen and bathroom and have 24-hour access to expansive installation and production spaces within Bemis Center’s 110,000 square foot main facility and the Okada Sculpture &amp; Ceramics Facility, a 9,000 square foot large-scale sculpture fabrication space and workshop. A Bemis residency also includes complimentary laundry facilities, utilities, wifi, and access to an on-site research library.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;STIPENDS&lt;br/&gt;U.S.-based artists-in-residence receive a $1,000 USD monthly stipend and an additional $750 USD travel stipend. Due to the limitations of B2 visas (touring/visiting), international artists-in-residence are eligible to receive reimbursement of qualified expenses, such as airfare, ground transportation, and meals. Bemis Center is not responsible for organizing artist’s travel to Omaha to attend the residency. Additional stipends for studio supplies or materials are not available.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;Bemis residency opportunities are open to national and international artists 21+ years of age showing a strong professional working history. A variety of disciplines are accepted including, but not limited to, visual arts, media/new genre, performance, architecture, film/video, literature, interdisciplinary arts, music composition, and choreography.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Bemis residency alumni are allowed to re-apply after a five-year hiatus from the program. Alumni seeking residency must submit a complete application including recent work samples and current resume. Preference may be given to applicants who have not previously attended.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists enrolled in an academic program during the time of the residency opportunity are not eligible to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Small collaborative groups are eligible to apply. Please note, if selected, Bemis Center is only able to accommodate two members of a collaborative group to attend the residency and live on-site.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Bemis welcomes internationally based artists to apply. Working knowledge of English is helpful for international artists as an interpreter will not be provided.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Bemis Center for Contemporary Arts is committed to a policy of nondiscrimination and equal opportunity for all persons regardless of race, sex, color, religion, creed, national origin or ancestry, age, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, gender expression, and disability. For special needs or questions about accessibility, please contact the Residency Program Manager.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;OPPORTUNITIES AND EXPECTATIONS&lt;br/&gt;Artists are invited to participate in at least one opportunity for public presentation, such as our public Open House / Open Studios. This is a process-based residency; there is no expectation or promise of an exhibition in our first-floor galleries. Selected artists must attend a minimum of eight consecutive weeks to receive the award. Artists are not able to defer or reschedule if unable to attend the residency.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FEES&lt;br/&gt;A $40 USD non-refundable application fee is due at the time of submitting an application through SlideRoom paid via credit card or by PayPal. Submission of completed applications is only accepted online through bemis.slideroom.com. Artists interested in applying to both January–April and May–August 2020 open call opportunities will be required to submit a separate application and application fee for each designated session. Fees related to visa processes or passport acquisition are the responsibility of the awarded artist.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION REVIEW PROCESS&lt;br/&gt;SlideRoom will confirm receipt of your submitted application. Residency applications are reviewed by a rotating panel comprised of artists and arts professionals, such as curators, academics, and/or critics. The application review process consists of an online review followed by an on-site panel meeting. The review process takes 12–14 weeks from the application deadline. Notifications to all applicants will be sent via email after the selection panel has made its final decision. If an artist is selected for more than one session, the artist will select one session to attend.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply online at bemis.slideroom.com.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: May 17, 2019 by 11:59 PM CST&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notifications to all applicants will be made via email on August 15, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;REQUIRED APPLICATION MATERIALS&lt;br/&gt;-Your website&lt;br/&gt;-Current phone number&lt;br/&gt;-Current email&lt;br/&gt;-Current ZIP code&lt;br/&gt;-Artistic Discipline&lt;br/&gt;-Are you a collaborative?&lt;br/&gt;-Date of Birth&lt;br/&gt;-A brief statement about your creative and intellectual interests and description of how you anticipate using the time and space, e.g. working on current projects, conducting research, reading, writing, etc., if you are selected for a residency. (500 words max)&lt;br/&gt;-Specific resources necessary to your practice you may require while in residency, based on your interests and residency goals previously mentioned. (100 words max)&lt;br/&gt;-Current Resume. If you are a collaborative group, include a combined resume listing all collaborative members and reflecting previous work history and projects completed as a collaborative. Please list all collaborative members at the top of the resume. PDF format preferred.&lt;br/&gt;-Two references including name, email, phone number, and relationship to each reference. References will be contacted by Bemis Center during the review panel process. Letters of recommendation are not required.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PORTFOLIO&lt;br/&gt;-Up to ten media samples of work completed within the past five years including: images (up to 5MB each), video (up to 250MB each), audio (up to 30MB each), PDFs (up to 10MB each), and/or models (Sketchfab).&lt;br/&gt;-Images should be no larger than 5MB each, .jpegs or .pdfs are preferred.&lt;br/&gt;-Each time-based work sample should be up to five minutes in length or less.&lt;br/&gt;-Text-based media samples should be submitted in .pdf format; 1,500 words max or approximately one page in length, (i.e., one page is the equivalent of one media sample). Works-in-progress may be included. All samples must be submitted in English.&lt;br/&gt;-Do not include external links to media samples or websites. Do not include multiple page .pdfs as one media sample. Do not include trailer video samples.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;OPEN CALL SURVEY&lt;br/&gt;Please answer the following questions for research and statistical purposes.&lt;br/&gt;-How did you hear about this Bemis Center Residency Program opportunity?&lt;br/&gt;-What aspect of this residency opportunity inspired you to apply?&lt;br/&gt;-Would you use your time at Bemis to continue an existing project or create a new project[s]?&lt;br/&gt;-Residencies you are scheduled to attend next year&lt;br/&gt;-Previous artist residencies attended&lt;br/&gt;-Age&lt;br/&gt;-Race&lt;br/&gt;-Gender&lt;br/&gt;-Country of origin&lt;br/&gt;-Highest level of education&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: May 17, 2019 by 11:59 PM CST&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply online at bemis.slideroom.com.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notifications to all applicants will be made via email on August 15, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, contact Holly Kranker, Residency Program Manager, at 402.341.7130 x 12 or hollyk@bemiscenter.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1cefe68f-c7ff-411e-a04f-b93372a96830" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>