<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-28T03:15:30-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>9e534409-d6d4-4c97-936c-fb4fc880f2d8</id><title>4/28 - Space &amp;amp; Time Artist Residency at Guttenberg Arts: Fall 2019 &amp;amp; Winter 2020 Programs</title><updated>2019-03-28T03:15:30.976388+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Guttenberg Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Guttenberg, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/28/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.guttenbergarts.org/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Space and Time Artist Residency at Guttenberg Arts provides artists with a $1,200.00 USD stipend to cover material, travel, and housing in conjunction with 24/7 shared access to a 4,500 sq. ft. professionally equipped workspace for the visual arts including printmaking and ceramics facilities for three months in Guttenberg, New Jersey (just across the Hudson River). Artists will also be given a group show at the end of the residency, as well as studio visits from accomplished professionals from the art world. Each artist is required to give a free public artist lecture and/or workshop towards the close of their three month residency and spend a minimum of 15 hours a week in studio. We highly recommend a site visit to our building if you are unsure of your commute or have questions regarding our facilities. Artists are selected by a blind jury of arts professionals on the merits of their work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guttenberg Arts is dedicated to promoting the visual arts by providing practicing artists with the space and time to develop their work while engaging with the public.  Guttenberg Arts aims to increase opportunities for supported artists by expanding their community through artistic collaborations and promotion to curators and collectors in the tri-state area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit www.guttenbergarts.submittable.com/submit to apply before our April 28th deadline. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;1) Statement of Intent / Project Proposal (500 Words)&lt;br/&gt;2) Artist Statement (500 Words)&lt;br/&gt;3) Artist CV&lt;br/&gt;4) 10 Images (Up to 5Mb Each)&lt;br/&gt;5)  List Of Work Stating Title, Material,Dimensions, Date&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Program Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Fall 2019 Residency is from Sept. 6th Through Dec. 6th&lt;br/&gt;Winter 2020 Residency is from Jan. 6th Through April 6th&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contact info for questions:&lt;br/&gt;matt@guttenbergarts.org  / 201.868.8585&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9e534409-d6d4-4c97-936c-fb4fc880f2d8" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9907fa45-1436-426b-b832-78015b3e2689</id><title>4/11 - Seeking Under-Represented Artists - Deadline April 11</title><updated>2019-03-28T03:15:30.976333+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;440 Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://440gallery.formstack.com/forms/artsy_application"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brooklyn, NY based 440 Gallery was formed in January of 2005 as an artist-run space and we are now looking to add three (3) new under-represented artists to our Artsy Gallery page for one year from May 1, 2019 - May 1 2020. This call is open to artists working in all media, nationally and internationally not currently represented by a gallery. Artsy.net is an internationally based platform dedicated to sales of art online. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Non-Refundable Entry Fee: $35&lt;br/&gt;Entry Deadline: April 11, midnight EST&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;Currently be a practicing artist, making new work&lt;br/&gt;Not currently represented by a gallery&lt;br/&gt;Must have a website&lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement&lt;br/&gt;CV&lt;br/&gt;Upload a minimum of 10 images to start profile&lt;br/&gt;440 Gallery will take 30% commission on all sales&lt;br/&gt;Artist is required to pack and ship artwork (buyer pays for shipping and handling, artist will be reimbursed for expenses)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s Benefits:&lt;br/&gt;Up to 75 images uploaded to the Artsy platform&lt;br/&gt;Dedicated sales director updating profile and handling sales&lt;br/&gt;Artsy is the top read artist magazine, 2.5 – 3 million unique visitors per month&lt;br/&gt;Great way to reach and build relationships with collectors &lt;br/&gt;Artsy works with the Art Genome Project, an algorithm search engine that recommends works to collectors based on their preferences&lt;br/&gt;Artsy proactively markets to collectors based on their likes&lt;br/&gt;Every Sunday, Artsy sends emails to their collectors, they will alert them to new work that is uploaded&lt;br/&gt;All artists on site are represented by gallery partners on Artsy, they do not allow artists to sign up individually&lt;br/&gt;Promotion in the 440 newsletter (more than 5,000 subscribers)&lt;br/&gt;Participation in one online exclusive group show&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application can be found here: &lt;a href="https://440gallery.formstack.com/forms/artsy_application" target="_blank"&gt;https://440gallery.formstack.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All media will be considered for representation, open to national and international artists.  A minimum of five (5) artworks must be uploaded for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For questions, please contact:&lt;br/&gt;Amy Williams&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Director&lt;br/&gt;info@440gallery.com&lt;br/&gt;718.499.3844&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9907fa45-1436-426b-b832-78015b3e2689" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>