<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-12T01:48:25-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>131c6025-dce0-42ff-94a0-b5ea434848ca</id><title>3/8 - Vision: Shadow and Light</title><updated>2019-02-12T01:48:25.543384+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/08/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on shadow and light in photography.&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="http://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/131c6025-dce0-42ff-94a0-b5ea434848ca" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>accb40bf-c624-43c8-8512-a606271360b6</id><title>3/11 - OPEN CALL Maake Magazine ISSUE 9 curated by Hein Koh</title><updated>2019-02-12T01:48:25.543321+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Maake Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.maakemagazine.com/submitissue9/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce our OPEN CALL for Issue 9 of Maake Magazine, curated by Hein Koh.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists making work in all media are encouraged to apply. There are no restrictions. Applicants can be based anywhere in the world. Applications will be accepted via Submittable at: &lt;a href="https://maakemagazine.submittable.com/submit" target="_blank"&gt;https://maakemagazine.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: March 11th, 2019 at 11:59 PM EST&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Curator:&lt;br/&gt;Hein Koh is an artist who lives and works in Brooklyn, NY. She graduated from Dartmouth College with a dual B.A. in Studio Art and Psychology, and received her M.F.A. in Painting from Yale University. She is a recipient of a Mid-Atlantic Arts Foundation Grant, and an Artists in the Marketplace residency at the Bronx Museum of the Arts. Her work has been reviewed in Artforum, Art F City, Time Out New York, Hyperallergic, and The Brooklyn Rail. She has also received additional press in The New York Times, The Wall Street Journal, The Atlantic, The Huffington Post, and The Washington Post, among other publications. Hein has also taught and/or lectured at the California College of the Arts, Tyler School of Art, Dartmouth College, Maryland Institute College of Art, and the School of Visual Arts, among other institutions. She currently has an installation at Rockefeller Center, in collaboration with the Art Production Fund, comprised of sculptures and digital murals. Hein is also currently working on a public art commission for the Bronx Children’s Museum, which is slated to open in February of 2020. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Maake:&lt;br/&gt;Maake Magazine is an independent, artist-run organization that was created to support contemporary artists and other artist-run projects. It is our mission to provide exhibition opportunities as well as both online and print publishing opportunities for emerging and mid-career artists. Through collaborations with artists, curators, artist-run groups, galleries and more, we facilitate projects that support dialogue and community and increase the visibility of the arts while defying geographic boundaries. For more information about our current projects and to read interviews with all of our featured artists, artist-run organizations, and more, visit www.maakemagazine.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Published Artists receive the following:&lt;br/&gt;•Work featured in printed Issue (two full pages) &lt;br/&gt;•One complimentary copy of Maake Magazine printed issue (US Only)&lt;br/&gt;•Feature posted on Maake's social media outlets, website and blog&lt;br/&gt;•Artist Interview and accompanying gallery of work posted on our website&lt;br/&gt;•Future consideration for upcoming exhibitions and projects&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility &amp; Terms:&lt;br/&gt;•Artists may submit up to 6 works.&lt;br/&gt;•Artists working in all media are welcome to apply.&lt;br/&gt;•Artists working anywhere in the world are welcome to apply.&lt;br/&gt;•Artists must be 18 years old or older to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee: $20&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;•6 images of work&lt;br/&gt;•CV&lt;br/&gt;•Short statement&lt;br/&gt;•Short bio&lt;br/&gt;•Social Media info&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, please visit: &lt;a href="http://www.maakemagazine.com/submitissue9/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.maakemagazine.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected artists will be asked for high resolution images suitable for the printed magazine. Artists selected by the curator will receive a 2-page spread including a brief statement, website, and 1–4 images in print, and up to 8 images online.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/accb40bf-c624-43c8-8512-a606271360b6" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>