<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-08T19:15:47-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>9ed968de-d801-4861-87b9-0b89ab50d73d</id><title>5/13 - Wave Hill Sunroom Project Space Open Call</title><updated>2019-04-08T19:15:47.133429+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wave Hill&lt;br/&gt;📍 Bronx, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/13/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.wavehill.org/arts/submission-guidelines/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wave Hill announces a Call to Artists for its 2020 Sunroom Project Space Program. The Sunroom Project Space is a venue for New York-area emerging artists to develop a site-specific project as a solo exhibition at Wave Hill. For 2020, we are starting a new initiative—a commission for an outdoor Sunroom Project that will take place every other year. The three exhibition spaces for 2020 are the windowed Sunroom, windowed Sun Porch (both in Glyndor Gallery) and an outdoor area that is visible from the gallery. Applicants must indicate indoor or outdoor location.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists are encouraged to respond to and engage with these unique spaces. We are also seeking artist projects that are participatory or interactive and engage Wave Hill’s surrounding communities of Riverdale, the Bronx, and New York City.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Four artists will be selected for solo shows that will be on view indoors for six weeks each from April through November 2020. For the indoor exhibition, work in all media will be considered. Selected artists will receive an honorarium of $1,800 and have 6 to 12 months to develop their ideas and create new work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A fifth artist will be selected for the outdoor area for summer 2020. For this outdoor installation, we ask that the work is constructed to withstand the elements and visitor interaction. The selected artist will receive an honorarium of $4000.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility: Open to emerging artists with a record of solid achievement and potential, for whom this opportunity might contribute to professional advancement, and who are not represented by a commercial gallery, not a student, and have not previously shown at Wave Hill. Because we encourage artists to spend time at Wave Hill developing their ideas, artists should live within a 50-mile radius of the Bronx.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An information session will be held at Wave Hill on Saturday, April 13 at 3 pm. Attendance is not mandatory to apply, but strongly encouraged. RSVP for the info session by e-mailing sunroomproject@wavehill.org.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists can submit applications using our online applications portal, SlideRoom, and must submit the following:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1.	Application with an artist statement, preliminary concept and indication of indoor or outdoor location&lt;br/&gt;2.	Résumé &lt;br/&gt;3.	Up to 10 work samples with optional concept drawing&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The deadline is May 13, 2019. For more information and to submit an application, please go to &lt;a href="https://www.wavehill.org/arts/submission-guidelines/." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.wavehill.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications will be reviewed by a jury that includes Wave Hill’s Curator of Visual Arts, an invited curator, and a previous Sunroom artist. The jury will develop a short list of artists for the curator to meet with for an interview. The curatorial staff will balance approaches and schedules to make a final selection. Decisions will be made by August 2019, and all artists will be contacted at that time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Interested artists are strongly encouraged to visit Wave Hill before applying.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Contact sunroomproject@wavehill.org or 718-549-3200, x397.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9ed968de-d801-4861-87b9-0b89ab50d73d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b2ea629b-a3e3-47f1-ab47-b39f595a25c2</id><title>4/19 - Dusklit: Interactive Art Festival- 2019 Call for Art</title><updated>2019-04-08T19:15:47.133370+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dusklit: Interactive Art Festival&lt;br/&gt;📍 Sugar Loaf, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.dusklit.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dusklit is the East Coast's one night interactive art festival. With twilight as a backdrop, Dusklit features over 25 immersive installations, performances, and site-specific environments. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Now in its fourth year, Dusklit 2019 will take place Saturday, July 20, 5-9PM.  Past Dusklit projects include all media, from site-specific dance and sound art to life-size kinetic sculpture, VR, interactive plays, sensory deprivation chambers, and many other offerings. See www.dusklit.com for past festivals. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dusklit is presented outdoors on the historic Seligmann Homestead in Sugar Loaf, New York. Once home to the Surrealist Kurt Seligmann, and frequented by Marcel Duchamp, Kay Sage, and Max Ernst, the property carries a history of art and magic. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dusklit is organized by artists Cody Rounds and Olivia Baldwin.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CALL FOR ART&lt;br/&gt;Artists of all disciplines are invited to propose immersive or otherwise interactive projects for Dusklit 2019. Projects may take the  form of a roving performance/installation, or a stationary environment/installation/performance. Visitor participation must be essential to the work. Projects in which visitors act exclusively as audience will not be considered. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dusklit 2019 will take place outdoors on Saturday, July 20, 5-9pm, before, during, and after sunset. Artists should consider how the changing light of dusk will affect their project, and visitors' engagement with it.  All projects occur throughout the duration of the event (with artist breaks). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Due to the close proximity of installations, music and sound must be contained within ten feet of artists' plots.  PA systems are prohibited.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For full details, visit dusklit.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application deadline: Friday, April 19, 11:59PM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit dusklit.com to apply&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b2ea629b-a3e3-47f1-ab47-b39f595a25c2" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>