<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-31T16:17:02-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>3c436ab4-aa25-41f6-9f08-e4f290fd86d1</id><title>7/7 - OPEN CALL: Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists</title><updated>2019-05-31T16:17:02.822141+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Friend of The Artist&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/07/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.friendoftheartist.com/apply/vol10"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FOA is a quarterly book dedicated to elevating the work of emerging artists around the world. Our publication releases in a hardcover art book every quarter and includes the work of artists who work in a variety of mediums, informative articles, and interviews. Accepted artists will have a four-page spread of their work, information, and artist statement. Volume 10 will be juried by Diana Cerezino, Michael Dewberry, and Tim Ralston and will be available in our store and online retailers including Amazon and Barnes and Noble.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted Artists Receive&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3 works published in Volume 10, complimentary digital copy of the publication, social media post of work, discounts on books for family and friends, and free digital access to future publications&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$30 for 5 Images&lt;br/&gt;or&lt;br/&gt;$50 for 5 Images + Book&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;July 7, 2019 (midnight, CST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists of all academic disciples are welcome to apply. This includes painting, sculpture, photography, installation, and performance art. Works must be submitted in a printable format.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guest Jurors&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Diana Cerezino&lt;br/&gt;Michael Dewberry&lt;br/&gt;Tim Ralston&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Diana Cerezino &amp; Tim Ralston&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Diana Cerezino and Tim Ralston are founding directors of PADA, an artist-led, non-profit arts organisation based in Barreiro on Lisbon’s South Bay. Set within a derelict industrial Park, PADA is a studio provider, international residency and gallery promoting interaction between national and international artists. Both practicing artists, Tim and Diana set up PADA with the aim of creating a unique resource for artists, to provide excellent studios and fabrication facilities alongside the opportunity to exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Having both graduated with BA Hons they have worked in the London art scene for the last 15 years and gained a wealth of experience that they bring to this new project in Lisbon. In this time they have worked for artists such as Damien Hirst, Raqib Shaw and Julian Opie, galleries Alison Jacques and Hauser and Wirth as well as institutions including The Tate, ICA and BFI. The knowledge from assisting and working with these established and well known artists, galleries and institutions informs PADA as a residency that encourages and supports artists development. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As PADA they have curated exhibitions in London and Lisbon, the latest exhibition at AMAC in Lisbon, included 40 artists over 4 galleries. 'Out of Office' curated by Alice Bonnot opens on the 11th May at PADA gallery and Recreational Grounds V opens on 17th May in the project space Tim still co curates in London.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Michael H. Dewberry&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A native of Dallas, TX, Michael H. Dewberry is an emerging curator who has coordinated and collaborated on international traveling exhibitions in Mexico, Dallas, and New York City. He has held positions at the Crow Museum of Asian Art, Brooklyn Museum, Wadsworth Atheneum, Academia Nazionale di San Luca, Museo Internacional del Barroco, and the Bard Graduate Center Gallery. His mission is to curate exhibitions and programming that bridges cultures and creates communities united around art and action. Prior to attending graduate school to focus on decorative arts he studied product design at the Scuola Politecnico di Design in Milan, Italy. Michael earned his master’s degree in Decorative Arts, Design History, and Material Culture from the Bard Graduate Center in New York City and a holds a Bachelor of Arts with honors in Art History from Trinity College in Hartford, Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at friendoftheartist.com/apply/vol10&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Email contact@friendoftheartist.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3c436ab4-aa25-41f6-9f08-e4f290fd86d1" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0224217a-5558-49db-b3e2-6cfc9fc8eb45</id><title>6/30 - Open Call for Midnight Moment—chance to show moving-image art on 60+ screens in Times Square!</title><updated>2019-05-31T16:17:02.822113+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.TSq.org/Arts"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts invites you to submit original moving-image artwork to Midnight Moment, the world’s largest, longest-running digital art exhibition synchronized on electronic billboards and newspaper kiosks throughout Times Square nightly from 11:57pm to midnight. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for submissions: June 30, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;Learn more about submission guidelines here: TSq.org/MMSubmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open applications for the Midnight Moment program are accepted through the online Slideroom portal. Please review submission guidelines and access the portal here: TSq.org/MMSubmission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have any questions about your proposal, please email Public Art Manager Hillary Dvorkin at hdvorkin@tsq.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0224217a-5558-49db-b3e2-6cfc9fc8eb45" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>958d04d4-ae52-4e24-b25e-741c7ad51f12</id><title>7/15 - Call for proposals/open reading period</title><updated>2019-05-31T16:17:02.822082+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Catalpa&lt;br/&gt;📍 Los Angeles, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://catalpa3000.net/proposals"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This reading period/call for proposals is open to all genres, mediums, and disciplines. If we think the work/project/proposal is a good fit we will contact you to discuss next steps. Our “publications” can take the shape of books, video, audio, objects, exhibitions, performances, etc. We welcome work in progress, interdisciplinary, and collaborative projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application instructions are available here: &lt;a href="https://catalpa3000.net/proposals" target="_blank"&gt;https://catalpa3000.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/958d04d4-ae52-4e24-b25e-741c7ad51f12" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>011793b9-11eb-4b40-8c37-bf5182cd9a27</id><title>6/30 - Open Call: ARTWorks Inc</title><updated>2019-05-31T16:17:02.822044+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jamaica Arts Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Jamaica, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.jcal.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamaica Center for Arts &amp; Learning, Inc. (JCAL) invites Queens County artists to apply to participate in our newly initiated professional development program, Artists Residency &amp; Training Seminar Series (ARTWorks, Inc.) Program.  It teaches visual artists to regard their work as a small business, identify their entrepreneurial and professional goals and create a long-term plan for accomplishing them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTWorks, Inc. is a two tier program:  Resident Fellows Tier: 2 Resident Fellows receive monetary support of $10,000 each, a full time studio at Jamaica Art Center, access to the ARTWorks, Inc. Seminar Series which will culminate in a curated solo exhibit with inclusion in the ARTWorks, Inc catalogue; Seminar Fellows Tier: Twelve Seminar Fellows are invited to access the 10 month Seminar Series, some scheduled studio time, an exhibit stipend and be included in a group show in JAC’s Miller gallery and inclusion in the ARTWork, Inc catalogue and receive a $500 stipend. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTWorks, Inc. is a fellowship that serves New York City’s (favorable to Queens’ artists) emerging and underrepresented artists. It offers training in cultural entrepreneurial skills through hands on practicum, educational seminars and mentorships with established working artists and cultural leaders. The program culminates in a group exhibit that has an ARTWorks, Inc. catalogue for the works created and/or curated during the ARTWorks, Inc. fellowship period. The goal is for the fellows to walk away with knowledge for a successful self fulfilled arts career in a range of communities from self defined and emergent to an existing, well defined and competitive global marketplace. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The ARTWork, Inc. artists have access to JCAL’s administrative offices and equipment, including a fax machine, copy machine and computers.  In addition to the studio provided, the artist may also use JCAL’s workshop studio facilities, including a ceramics studio equipped with kilns and a computer design studio.  Theses studios are generally available for use during operating hours Monday through Friday and whenever they are not occupied by JCAL workshops that regularly take place on Saturdays.    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTWorks, Inc. Seminar Series - From October 2019 to August 2020, the seminar schedule includes monthly Off-site Saturdays and/or 3rd Wednesday lectures. Each of the artists will be exposed to mentoring artists and institutional leaders through studio &amp; institutional visits, with peer-to-peer, group and one-on-one guidance and feedback. In addition, JCAL’s Director of Programs &amp; Artist Services will be available as a resource to discuss issues and provide advice to these artists. At the end of the series, in honor of the group’s accomplishments, there will be both solo exhibits of the designated two Resident Fellows and the group exhibition for up to 10 ARTWorks, Inc. artists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;apply through submitable platform, &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2Xf6xt1" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;please visit www.jcal.org for instruction&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/011793b9-11eb-4b40-8c37-bf5182cd9a27" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7011c4f3-8411-472c-a36a-18298a48252e</id><title>6/30 - Open Call: Artist Co-Op 2019</title><updated>2019-05-31T16:17:02.821987+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jamaica Center for Arts and Learning&lt;br/&gt;📍 Jamaica, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.jcal.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Platform for Queens Based Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Once a membership based program, JCAL's Artist Co-Op has been reborn as the center's annual exhibition featuring emerging and mid-career artists from the borough of Queens and NYC. The goal of the exhibition seeks to reflect the diversity of artistic expression in Queens. Submissions will be reviewed by a distinguished panel of peer artists, curators, and JCAL administrators. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;​Since its founding, JCAL has supported the creation and presentation of local, emerging, or established artists. JCAL serves visual and performing artists by providing free/low cost work and exhibition space. It has exhibited renowned artists such as Romare Bearden, Isamu Noguchi, and Elizabeth Catlett, and provided residencies to Lorenzo Pace, Lorna Simpson, and Wangechi Mutu, during the early stages of their careers.&lt;br/&gt;Accepted Media: painting, drawing, sculpture, mixed media, installation, and video/multi-media &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Video/multi-media: If works are accepted, the artist must provide all equipment for display. JCAL is not liable for damage or theft. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Performance &amp; Social Practice: Artists working in Performance and Social Practice are welcome, but physical artworks as a result of the process or documentation of the process can only be submitted and displayed, please include a description of the process in your Artists Statement.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork Size Limit: Flexible in size constraints, but keep in mind the nature of a group exhibition. Gallery Height total 18', Height to track lighting 7'. Gallery Dimensions: 48 'x 22 'x 18'/10'/8' x 22'    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: June 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Announcement of Artists Accepted: August 2019&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: To Be Decided 2020&lt;br/&gt;Location: JCAL's Miller Gallery  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Requirements for the Application: &lt;br/&gt;-Artist Statement (300 words or less)&lt;br/&gt;-CV&lt;br/&gt;-Image  List: Title, Medium, Size, Date (Titles of Images must correspond with  the list, all JPEG's must be labeled ie."01_ArtistLastName"  "02_ArtistLastName" etc.)&lt;br/&gt;-3 JPEGS &lt;br/&gt;-Additional Notes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;apply through submittable platform at &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2JORCmr" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;visit www.jcal.org for application instruction&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7011c4f3-8411-472c-a36a-18298a48252e" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>