<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-18T12:18:07-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>b81039d1-abae-4b42-9843-f7656b110bab</id><title>9/15 - Join treat gallery at PULSE (Miami Beach) + satellite art show (NYC)</title><updated>2019-07-18T12:18:07.506853+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;treat gallery new york&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.treatgallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;treat gallery is excited to participate at PULSE Art Fair in Miami Beach this December 2019 during Art Basel week. treat gallery will also return as an exhibitor to satellite art show for their inaugural New York City premiere in October of 2019. With both exhibitions, we will be raising funds for the New York chapter of the Human Rights Campaign, and the onePULSE foundation in Orlando, FL. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The #1 goal of treat gallery is to help others. Our exhibitions and partnerships raise funds for charities and non-profit organizations. While the parameters of this application may seem unconventional, please refer to the colorful image on our application as a guide to what we're looking for. The end goal is a colorful, clean rainbow-esque grid from floor to ceiling. Early deadline is September 15th. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The content is open, the type of art is open (photography, prints, illustrations, etc) but the art must feature one color in 75% or more of the piece, and it must be a square. No squares? Consider cropping an image for this fundraising event. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT: Please keep in mind that upon acceptance, we will take your image and make it available in an edition of 5, so if you submit a drawing or an original piece, we will be selling a reproduction of this. We recommend photography, printmaking and digital illustration for this project, but we welcome all submissions. Surprise us! Black and White work is welcome, as long as there is a dominant shade in the work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*by paying an application fee for this opportunity, you will be exempt from paying any application fees throughout 2020. If you've applied or participated in our #treatamericaproject or satellite art show Austin, reach out to us directly for your waiver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You must apply via this form.&lt;br/&gt;https://form.jotform.com/treatgallery/octobersatellite&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All questions: info@treatgallery.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Voted best Art Fair by the Miami New Times, SATELLITE ART SHOW presents interactive projects by young dealers, artist-run spaces and non-profits. By fostering a range of programming, SATELLITE is able to offer patrons and collectors with a unique experience where art is at the forefront of creative expression, activism, and curiosity. Our exhibitors are encouraged to provide our visitors both an opportunity to collect new works of art as well as to present exhibitions that are engaging, experiential and interactive. SATELLITE is expanding perceptions on art and community and providing an inclusive environment for guests to feel comfortable in exploration and discovery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;about PULSE art fair&lt;br/&gt;In celebration of their 15th anniversary, PULSE Art Fair is dedicating this edition to creating an atmosphere that will have you lingering for hours and leaving with artwork to add to your collection. In the overwhelming environment that is Miami Art Week, we are your calm in the palms. Experience the energy of stimulating art and balance it with cocktails in hammocks and engaging conversations with friends over a meal in our restaurant. PULSE isn’t just an art fair, anymore.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b81039d1-abae-4b42-9843-f7656b110bab" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>