<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-12T14:15:07-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>7d3ca9d1-97ef-4526-a415-955af11c0ecb</id><title>5/10 - PAPERWORKS 2019 National Fine Arts Competition</title><updated>2019-03-12T14:15:07.953330+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;b.j. spoke gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Huntington, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.bjspokegallery.org/paperworks-2019/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUROR: Hillary Reder, Curatorial Assistant, Department of Prints &amp; Drawings, Museum of Modern Art, NY.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AWARD: Exhibition of up to six selected works, August 2019 at the b.j.spoke gallery. Promotion of winning artists on b.j. spoke gallery website and social media.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: Open to Artists living in the United States who use paper as their primary medium, as a substrate, or as the subject of a video.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MEDIA: Works made of, on or about paper: cut paper, folded paper, woven paper, glued paper, drawings, paintings, pastels, prints, photographs, paper sculpture, 3D, bound books, collage, mixed media, video, and installation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For prospectus and how to submit your work, go to &lt;a href="http://www.bjspokegallery.org/paperworks-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bjspokegallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7d3ca9d1-97ef-4526-a415-955af11c0ecb" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>30be0b57-24ea-4058-978b-1a3ad20baaf2</id><title>4/11 - Portraiture: Through the Lens</title><updated>2019-03-12T14:15:07.953302+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on portraiture in photography at Black Box Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/30be0b57-24ea-4058-978b-1a3ad20baaf2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>54da0a9c-faf3-4b4f-8b39-5d36b12a39c4</id><title>4/6 - 2019-2020 Exhibition Call for Proposals</title><updated>2019-03-12T14:15:07.953271+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;621 Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Tallahassee, FL, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.621gallery.org/apply/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 621 Gallery Exhibition Committee is currently taking application proposals for this coming year for September 2019 – June 2020. The deadline to submit is April 6th, 2019. We are eager to reach out beyond Tallahassee to creatives in our surrounding region in the hopes of adding breadth to our upcoming exhibition season.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our goal is to showcase voices from our local scene and beyond, and we know that there is tremendous talent and diversity just within our regional area.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We would like to urge emerging and established artists and curators to apply with their exhibition proposal with no limitations on medium specificity, from traditional to experimental. 621 Gallery’s main space is 77’ x 30’ with a 12’ x 12’ freestanding wall dividing the space into two rooms with the opportunity to take on half or the entire main gallery.  The adjoining Nan Boynton Memorial Gallery provides a smaller exhibition space. This gallery can be utilized for one-person shows or smaller group exhibitions. We also have an Annex space that can be used for more experimental and installation types of work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send applications to: 621gallerysubmit@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION DEADLINE: APRIL 6th, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION PROPOSALS SHOULD INCLUDE:&lt;br/&gt;One page cover letter of exhibition proposal&lt;br/&gt;One page artist statement&lt;br/&gt;15-20 images of the artist’s work or examples of curated exhibitions&lt;br/&gt;The space you are most interested in showcasing in&lt;br/&gt;Resume/CV&lt;br/&gt;$35 application Fee for Non-members ($25 for members) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMAGE REQUIREMENTS: &lt;br/&gt;Artists and/or curator’s should include 15-20 images of current work. The image files should be no less than 72dpi and 1200px at the longest dimension. Images can be submitted in a powerpoint or zip file or can be mailed to the gallery on USB. *621 prefers online submissions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Mailing Address: &lt;br/&gt;621 Gallery &lt;br/&gt;621 Industrial Drive&lt;br/&gt;Tallahassee, FL 32310&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/54da0a9c-faf3-4b4f-8b39-5d36b12a39c4" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>99d76892-6df0-43e2-882a-433d63af230f</id><title>3/31 - Create! Magazine: International Print Issue and Gallery Exhibition</title><updated>2019-03-12T14:15:07.953238+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia , PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.createmagazine.com/callforart"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CREATE! MAGAZINE IS PLEASED TO ANNOUNCE AN OPEN CALL FOR THE MAY/JUNE PRINT ISSUE CURATED BY PARADIGM GALLERY + STUDIO.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTISTS WILL BE PUBLISHED IN OUR INTERNATIONAL PRINT ISSUE. IN ADDITION, PUBLISHED ARTISTS MAY BE INVITED TO PARTICIPATE IN A GROUP EXHIBITION IN 2020 IN PHILADELPHIA. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JURY PANEL&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PARADIGM GALLERY + STUDIO®&lt;br/&gt;JASON CHEN AND SARA MCCORRISTON&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Paradigm Gallery + Studio® exhibits contemporary artwork from around the world with a focus on Philadelphia-based artists. Established February 2010, the gallery began as a project between co-founders and curators, Jason Chen and Sara McCorriston, as a space in which to create artwork, to exhibit the work of their peers, and to invite the members of the community to create and collect in a welcoming gallery setting. To this day the gallery still aims to welcome all collectors, from first time to lifelong, and continues to support accessible work that welcomes a wide audience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY: All international artists 18 and older, of all genders, ethnicities and from all backgrounds are welcome to apply. We accept works in any medium: painting, sculpture, digital, printmaking, fiber, photography, mixed media, installation and more. A university degree is not required to participate in our open call.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS: 3+ jpeg images, a text document with a bio and artist statement, website or social media link, email address. Please see form for further details.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTISTS: Artists selected by the guest juror will receive a 2-page spread including a brief bio, website, and 2 images in print and digital formats. Published artists will receive a complimentary digital issue and will be listed with images, details and information on our website/social media for life. All featured artists will automatically be considered for any upcoming curatorial projects and exhibitions organized by our team. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHERE TO FIND: Copies will be available in our online shop and at several global retail locations in London, New York, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Amsterdam, Stockholm, Philadelphia, Ft. Lauderdale, Wilmington (DE), and more. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: March 31, 2019&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/99d76892-6df0-43e2-882a-433d63af230f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b7ef31ed-690a-41ef-809f-d4c81806ca4b</id><title>4/15 - CALL FOR ENTRIES - THE CHERRY VALLEY SUMMER SCULPTURE TRAIL</title><updated>2019-03-12T14:15:07.953200+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Cherry Valley Artworks&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cherry Valley, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.cvartworks.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cherry Valley Summer Sculpture Trail is a juried exhibit in the beautiful and historic village of Cherry Valley, NY. Sculptures will be placed along the Main Street from June 29th through October 8th, 2019. Established and emerging artists are invited to apply. Existing, new or site specific works may be submitted for consideration. There are a limited number of opportunities for indoor pieces to be placed in store fronts. Chosen artists will be eligible for the Grand prize of $1,000 and the first prize of $500. Stipends may be available to help with moving expenses and a crane truck is available on site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please go to our website: www.cvartworks.org for full guidelines and applications.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b7ef31ed-690a-41ef-809f-d4c81806ca4b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1d08a229-1967-4233-8445-81c3f740b663</id><title>4/5 - 2019 Adirondacks National Exhibition of American Watercolors</title><updated>2019-03-12T14:15:07.953142+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;View Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Old Forge, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Painting&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/05/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.viewarts.org/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;View, a multi-media arts center in Old Forge, is seeking artists working in all forms of watermedia for the 2019 Adirondacks National Exhibition of American Watercolors. This exhibition is considered one of the top ten watermedia exhibitions in the nation, drawing artists and audiences from all over. Each year, artists compete to receive over $12,000 in prizes and awards.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition is open to artists working in watercolors. All works must be of original design and execution, comprised of 90% watermedia.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Collage and works previously exhibited at View are not eligible for submission. There is a non-refundable entry fee of $30 for View members and $40 for guests, which enables an artist to submit up to two works. Each artist may submit a total of five works at a cost of an additional $10 per work. The submission fees help to support View’s gallery programs. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be made online through www.onlinejuriedshows.com. A full prospectus is available on that website.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline to apply is April 5, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;View is located at 3273 State Route 28 in Old Forge, New York. To learn more about View programming, visit ViewArts.org or call (315) 369-6411.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.onlinejuriedshows.com/Default.aspx?OJSID=34067" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.onlinejuriedshows.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;John Gardner&lt;br/&gt;Director of Visual Arts and Exhibitions&lt;br/&gt;View&lt;br/&gt;PO box 1144&lt;br/&gt;3273 State Route 28&lt;br/&gt;Old Forge, NY 13420&lt;br/&gt;jgardner@viewarts.org&lt;br/&gt;www.viewarts.org&lt;br/&gt;315 369 6411 ext 206&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1d08a229-1967-4233-8445-81c3f740b663" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>