<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-03T05:15:39-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>6e045123-2537-400d-86cc-ce85f6dd913e</id><title>4/11 - Greenpoint Gallery Spring Fling Grand Salon Show</title><updated>2019-04-03T05:15:39.466778+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our Spring Fling Grand Salon Show!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FRIDAY, April 12th 2018 at 8pm&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: April 11th at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Spring is finally here! Come celebrate at the Greenpoint Gallery!&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner up winners receive a slot in a group show and with other runner up winners! Submissions are now open.&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and stellar lineup of local bands and musicians sure to entertain, so mark your calendars.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FRIDAY, April 12th from 8pm- 12am. &lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit JPEG's or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive ready to hang. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, April 11th at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces in the $150-$500 range. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON!&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit JPEG's or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6e045123-2537-400d-86cc-ce85f6dd913e" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>