<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-07T20:15:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>dd88bdbe-4034-437c-9156-ff6899c033d1</id><title>4/1 - Sculpture In The Garden at Edward Hopper House Museum and Study Center</title><updated>2019-03-07T20:15:00.581920+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Edward Hopper House Museum and Study Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Nyack, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.edwardhopperhouse.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL FOR ARTISTS:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MESSAGE IN A …&lt;br/&gt;As a boy at the age of 16, Edward Hopper was inspired by a message in a bottle that he found on the shores of the Hudson River. He kept it as a treasured object and it is displayed to this day on the second floor of The Edward Hopper House Museum and Study Center in Nyack, NY, his boyhood home. Hopper was fascinated by the wide variety of boats on the Hudson River and this considerable interest is evidenced in the many paintings and drawings he created that depict boats, the Hudson River and landscapes of the Hudson Valley.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are calling on Artists to submit existing sculptures or new proposals for art works to be displayed in the newly reopened and renovated Outdoor Sculpture Garden. The theme of this outdoor exhibition&lt;br/&gt;is being coordinated in conjunction with an exhibition in the main gallery of Hopper House by Alastair Noble in which he will create a dynamic installation of paper origami boats containing poetic messages.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are looking for work that relates to the themes of hidden messages, boats, the Hudson River or any other interpretation that is a compelling artistic statement and relates to the theme. All materials as well as installations are acceptable, but work must be suitable for display outdoors for a period of 4 months. &lt;br/&gt;Artists are responsible for delivery/ shipping of art work to Hopper House, 82 North Broadway, Nyack, NY. &lt;br/&gt;A small stipend may be available for accepted artists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;•	Contact Information: Artist name, Address, Phone Number, Website&lt;br/&gt;•	Current CV&lt;br/&gt;•	JPEG Images of Existing work  (300 DPI at least 1MB in Size), &lt;br/&gt;Files labelled: Artist Last Name_Artist First Name_Title_#&lt;br/&gt;•	JPEG Images of artist rendering for new work proposals as well as some examples of previous work that illustrates quality of artist work or relationship to new work&lt;br/&gt;Files labelled: Artist Last Name_Artist First Name_Title_#&lt;br/&gt;•	A corresponding image  list with Title, Materials, Dimensions and year completed (if applicable)&lt;br/&gt;•	For existing work a brief description explaining the relevance to theme of exhibition&lt;br/&gt;•	For new work, a brief description of the new work and relevance to theme&lt;br/&gt;•	Submissions can be made use the following link:  &lt;a href="http://www.edwardhopperhouse.org/exhibiting-at-edward-hopper-house.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.edwardhopperhouse.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	For questions please contact Eric David Laxman:  eric@ericdavidlaxman.com &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: April 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Notification of Acceptance: April 15, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Installation of work:  May 27-31, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: June 13, 2019&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/dd88bdbe-4034-437c-9156-ff6899c033d1" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>