<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-02T18:17:46-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>7aa676ed-63fc-4d25-ad11-caa784b00ff0</id><title>7/15 - OPEN CALL! Stigma Unbound; Sex workers&amp;#39; art collective</title><updated>2019-07-02T18:17:46.657849+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Stigma Unbound&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.stigmaunbound.org/opencall"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stigma Unbound is looking for visual artists for our upcoming Brooklyn exhibition! Accepting all mediums! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Stigma Unbound, created in Dec 2017, is a sex workers' art collective based in Brooklyn, New York. Our mission is to provide platform, resources, and a safe communal space for the artistic expression of sex workers. At our events, sex workers lead discussions about issues important to the community and educate the public. Our collective includes artists who are people of color, queer, trans, and gender non-conforming, kink, and allies. We include “sex workers and allies” as a strategy to build a wider community, provide protection by allies, and to give artist deniability of status. Our greater mission is to help strengthen the sex worker community in New York City and educated the public about sex work. &lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;FOSTA/SESTA stands for Fight Online Sex Trafficking Act and Stop Enabling Sex Trafficking Act. Signed by President Trump on April 11, 2018, the bills are intended to hold online platforms accountable for the content of their creators and eliminate online sex trafficking. However, the bills became a suppressor to consenting and nonconsenting sex workers and police all social media users at large. This bill makes it difficult for sex workers to conduct business, take part in community activities, and share mutual aid, in online spaces. In this environment, Stigma Unbound felt that creating a safe space for the creative expression of sex workers was crucial.  &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Stigma Unbound has curated shows in various underground dungeons in Brooklyn, Anthology Film Archive, and Museum of Sex.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Note: Being exhibited at our events will NOT divulge your sex worker status. We accept artists in a wide variety of communities as an attempt to provide protection by allies and allow intersectional individuals deniability of status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To Apply &lt;br/&gt;fill out a forum at www.stigmaunbound.org/opencall and send to stigmaunboung@gmail.com with subject title OPEN CALL&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7aa676ed-63fc-4d25-ad11-caa784b00ff0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0beb4eee-54ea-40dc-a150-665b917499e9</id><title>10/1 - Open Call for Proposals: Syracuse Area</title><updated>2019-07-02T18:17:46.657814+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Darling Green&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://darlinggreen.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An international and well recognized corporate art collection is seeking proposals for site- specific works for its Syracuse, NY campus. The works will be displayed in and throughout the office space and will expand upon this multi-national corporation’s tradition of collecting and displaying art as a benefit to both its employees and the community.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This project is limited to New York-based artists living and working within 150 miles of Syracuse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This call is an exploratory search to assess the interest of New York artists in working within an office environment, as well as their interest in engaging with both employees and the surrounding communities through site- specific works of art. We hope this will create a specific sense of place and identity within and around the office space and encourage dialogue between the artist, employees and the community.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please send us an email for more information. &lt;br/&gt;info@darlinggreen.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0beb4eee-54ea-40dc-a150-665b917499e9" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6e6055c3-8ef1-42c2-a815-c29b305a6a56</id><title>7/15 - 1708&amp;#39;s InLight 2019 Call for Entries</title><updated>2019-07-02T18:17:46.657758+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;1708 Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Richmond, VA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.1708gallery.org/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1708 Gallery invites national and international artists working in all media and disciplines to submit entries for the 12th annual InLight Richmond. InLight is a public exhibition of contemporary light-based artworks— multimedia and interactive projects, video, projection, sculpture, installation, and performance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;InLight 2019 will take place at Chimborazo Park in the Church Hill neighborhood of Richmond on Friday and Saturday, November 15 and 16. Artists are invited to propose projects that critically engage with the social and geographic history of this site. Two key moments in the park's history include being the location of the largest Confederate military hospital during the Civil War and following Emancipation, hosting a Freedmen’s community for formerly enslaved African-Americans. 1708 seeks artists and projects that respond to, elaborate on, and propose new ways of understanding these complex histories.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE TO APPLY: Midnight (EST), Monday, July 15, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Potential sites for installations and performances include pathways, sidewalks, green spaces, trees, and more. There are no interior sites available. Artists may propose a specific site for both pre-existing and site-responsive works. Please indicate if your work is site-specific on your entry form. 1708 Gallery reserves the right to make final site assignments.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more details about InLight 2019 and to apply, visit www.1708gallery.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applications are accepted via our online form at &lt;a href="https://fs2.formsite.com/1708gallery/7vprjoxmvh/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;https://fs2.formsite.com&lt;/a&gt; or by visiting our website. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For questions, please contact Erin Willett at info@1708gallery.org or 804-643-1708&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6e6055c3-8ef1-42c2-a815-c29b305a6a56" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>