<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-17T04:18:05-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>02c6895e-44c6-4a58-a1fd-5ac5865d502d</id><title>8/10 - Call for Exhibition Proposals</title><updated>2019-07-17T04:18:05.650639+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;String Room Gallery, Wells College&lt;br/&gt;📍 Aurora, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.wells.edu/string-room-gallery"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The String Room Gallery of Wells College is currently accepting exhibition proposals to be considered for upcoming seasons, with opportunities beginning in November, 2019. Successful proposals may be partially funded in accordance with exhibition needs and available funds.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The String Room Gallery serves as the primary exhibition venue for Wells College, a small, private liberal arts institution in the Fingerlakes region of New York. With 1600 sq feet of space, track and natural lighting, and charismatic architectural details, the SRG is a versatile yet highly unique space that accommodates a range of practices. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Successful proposals will articulate clear and sophisticated conceptual grounding. As this exhibition space serves an academic institution, exhibitions will be evaluated, in part, on their relevance to, and potential for, enrichment of the school’s curriculum and pedagogical goals. The Wells experience prepares students to appreciate complexity and difference, to embrace new ways of knowing, to be creative, and to respond ethically to the interdependent worlds to which they belong.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;**Priority will be given to those proposals received by August 1, 2019; proposals will be accepted until August 10, 2019.**&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOLO &amp; COLLABORATIVE EXHIBITIONS: &lt;br/&gt;Email the following to  stringroomgallery@wells.edu, subject line: Solo/Collaborative Proposal: &lt;br/&gt;	&lt;br/&gt;- Link to online portfolio or website, containing at least 10 works related to proposal. In the case of video submissions, links to full versions are required &lt;br/&gt;- PDF containing all documents and information listed below, with Artist name(s) in file title:&lt;br/&gt;         - Current CV &lt;br/&gt;         - Artist Statement  (250 words max)&lt;br/&gt;         - One-page exhibition proposal, including indication of current availability &lt;br/&gt;                     between Nov. 2019 - Mar.  2021.&lt;br/&gt;         - Indication of needs for any special equipment or facilities.  				&lt;br/&gt;         - Works list (if not made clear by proposal or website)	&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CURATORIAL PROPOSALS: &lt;br/&gt;Email the following to: stringroomgallery@wells.edu, subject line: Curatorial Proposal:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- PDF containing all documents and information listed below, with Curator’s name(s) in file title.	&lt;br/&gt;Curator’s Current CV&lt;br/&gt;          - 1-2 page Exhibition Proposal; including indication of current availability &lt;br/&gt;                     between Nov. 2019 - Mar.  2021. &lt;br/&gt;          - Images or web links illustrating sample artists to be included in exhibition &lt;br/&gt;          - Indication of needs for any special equipment or facilities. &lt;br/&gt;          - Copies of or Links to any relevant writing samples.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Incomplete applications will not be reviewed. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;**Priority will be given to those proposals received by August 1, 2019; proposals will be accepted until August 10, 2019.**&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/02c6895e-44c6-4a58-a1fd-5ac5865d502d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3ada7971-d0e7-41c0-8071-855083158668</id><title>8/26 - &amp;quot;And The Earth Shall Set You Free&amp;quot; Open Call</title><updated>2019-07-17T04:18:05.650584+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/26/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And The Earth Shall Set You Free"- A ceramics show curated by Peter Goldwater &amp; Eric Lawrence&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An exhibition of sculpture centered on ceramic as material and muse.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The most basic material qualities of ceramic, that it progresses from unlimited malleability to permanence, makes it an astonishing material for sculpture.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The starting point is always the same – a more or less shapeless, more or less wet, blob of mud. From this unpromising beginning, the hands build up, tear down, start over, repeat again. And again. This process of making is an intimate act, a way of working toward discovery, where meaning beyond original inspiration is found. Nothing is permanent until the work is committed to the kiln.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The wide range of artist’s voices here, the varied methods and styles, throws up a challenge. How do you negotiate a path through all the competing voices, complicated juxtapositions and visual fault lines? It takes time. Each work is clear, it only needs attention to be heard.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submissions due: Monday, August 26th, 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit using the form link here: &lt;a href="https://form.jotform.com/trimistopheles/and-the-earth-shall-set-you-free-op" target="_blank"&gt;https://form.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3ada7971-d0e7-41c0-8071-855083158668" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>