<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-16T19:16:42-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>960058bd-6b4a-4e9f-94a2-bd5f5f40d837</id><title>8/1 - Open Call 2019</title><updated>2019-05-16T19:16:42.785306+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;BOCCARA ART Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://Boccara-art.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOCCARA ART Brooklyn is thrilled to announce its 2019 Open Call, with selected artists exhibiting their work at BOCCARA ART Brooklyn from August 17, 2019, until September 20, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With its museum-like space spanning nearly 3,000 sq ft, BOCCARA ART Brooklyn highlights an important collection of historically influential artists while simultaneously dedicating its focus on emerging artists as well. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BOCCARA ART participates in a variety of art fairs each year, including ART NY, AIPAD, and ART MIAMI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applicants must be living and working in the tri-state area.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications must be submitted at &lt;a href="https://form.jotform.com/Boccara__Art__Brooklyn/application" target="_blank"&gt;https://form.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt; by 11:59 pm on August 1, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Decisions will be released on Thursday, August 8, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted artists will be responsible for dropping off and picking up the work from the gallery. All work must be prepared and ready for installation. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions should be directed to brooklyn@boccara-art.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/960058bd-6b4a-4e9f-94a2-bd5f5f40d837" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>39e61d55-7e7c-4b86-b4c5-0a00ddce4d2e</id><title>6/15 - OPEN CALL - Calling ALL NYC Affiliated Sculptors, Installation &amp;amp; Performance Artists</title><updated>2019-05-16T19:16:42.785269+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sculptors Guild &amp;amp; The Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 LIC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_crashing_the_party"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sculptors Guild &amp; LiC-A team up to create the exhibition "Crashing the Party" curated by Barbara O’Brien. &lt;br/&gt;"Crashing the Party" invites a wide range of interpretations of and responses to the idea and ideals of gender equity, from breaking the “glass ceiling” to political, social, physical, and conceptual ideas. This exhibition will offer an opportunity for sculptors who are questioning and expanding their use of materials, forms, concepts and experiences.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Sculptors Guild in partnership with LiC-A is interested in supporting a creative platform to expand and broaden opportunities for all sculptors. “What’s now?” and “What’s next?”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Details: Artists can submit up to three artworks with three views per submission.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted Mediums: Sculpture, installation, performance, interactive, and works beyond the pedestal strongly encouraged. The 12,000 square foot gallery has 20’ high ceilings and welcomes large works and installations. Submissions of outdoor sculpture to be sited on land or water are also acceptable, as the Plaxall Gallery is situated on the waterfront of the Anable Basin. Visit the gallery during open hours to see the location. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*This exhibition is open to all New York City affiliated artists living, working or connected with a NYC organization.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information on our organization and gallery: www. LICArtists.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;or Visit www.sculptorsguild.org  The mission of the Sculptors Guild is to promote, encourage, and serve as an advocate for sculpture and to make contemporary sculpture a relevant part of the cultural experience.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Barbara O’Brien, an independent curator and critic based in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, was Executive Director of the Kemper Museum of Contemporary Art in Kansas City, Missouri from 2012 – 2017, after serving as chief curator and director of exhibitions since 2009. O’Brien is an elected member of AICA­-USA, International Association of Art Critics.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;O’Brien is currently a consulting curator for the Housatonic Museum of Art in Bridgeport, CT. Her nearly three decades of curatorial practice and criticism have focused on the art and artists of our time. Prior to accepting the post at the Kemper Museum, O’Brien was an assistant professor at Simmons College in Boston, Massachusetts, where she was director of the Trustman Art Gallery and head of the arts administration program. She was editor-­in­-chief of Art New England magazine from 2003 – 06.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;O’Brien earned an MFA from Rhode Island School of Design (RISD) and in 2006 was awarded the RISD national alumni award for professional achievement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit through the link below::&lt;br/&gt;http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_crashing_the_party&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/39e61d55-7e7c-4b86-b4c5-0a00ddce4d2e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>91fafc5b-e3da-4962-ab3c-c9c6cb24a215</id><title>6/15 - Open Call for a juried exhibition open to all artists working in Queens NY!</title><updated>2019-05-16T19:16:42.785218+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LiC-A @ THe Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 LIC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_creative_mosaic"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creative Mosaic curated by NYC based curator Osman Can Yerebakan&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Description of Exhibition: &lt;br/&gt;LIC-A’s  aim is to increase awareness and appreciation of the richly diverse art produced throughout Queens. Included will be a continuous  digital presentation with images of participating artists in their studios and workshops, describing  how the growth of art studios and the presence of artists in every area of Queens has enriched all aspects of community life wherever they occur.  Meet-the-Artists event will be scheduled to enable conversation and connection between  the artists and  community residents  and businesses.    We also plan to create a video documentary on the various arts groups we connect with in the Borough.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, go to LIC-A’s website, www.licartists.org.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Osman Can Yerebakan is a curator and art writer based in New York. His writing has appeared on T: The New York Times Style Magazine, The Paris Review, Vulture and The Cut (both New York Magazine), The Brooklyn Rail, BOMB, Village Voice, Harper’s Bazaar Arabia, Wallpaper*, L’Officiel, Flaunt, Galerie Magazine, Cultured, and elsewhere.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Osman previously organized exhibitions at The Clemente Center (Residual Impression; A Room of One's Own), La MaMa Galleria (Party Out Of Bounds: Nightlife As Activism Since 1980), Radiator Gallery (Works: Reflections on Failure), Equity Gallery (Like Smoke), AC Institute (My Nights Are More Beautiful Than Your Days), Center for Book Arts (En Masse: Books Orchestrated), Local Project (Hopscotch), UrbanGlass (Glass Ceiling: Art of Resilience and Fragility), Leslie Lohman Museum Project Space (Alternate Routes), the Queens Museum (Executive (Dis)Order: Art, Displacement &amp; the Ban), and Residency Unlimited (Contingencies).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit through the link below:&lt;br/&gt;http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_creative_mosaic&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/91fafc5b-e3da-4962-ab3c-c9c6cb24a215" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>