<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-13T07:18:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>aa137da0-ffd9-4d49-a787-6aea8987bf95</id><title>8/9 - WHAT: Cars and Dogs</title><updated>2019-07-13T07:18:00.374362+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on cars and dogs at Black Box Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/aa137da0-ffd9-4d49-a787-6aea8987bf95" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>84107623-c195-4291-ad9f-244c7f91305e</id><title>6/30 - Artfare Submissions Program</title><updated>2019-07-13T07:18:00.374329+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Artfare, Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artfare.com/for-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artfare is a platform that allows artists and patrons to connect through our iPhone app (artfare.com/app).  Patrons can follow artists, request studio visits, and purchase work posted by our curated group of professional artists. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artfare allows artists to present their work to a broad audience and connect with patrons both digitally and in person through studio visits, exhibitions and events. Using our app, artists can also discover and communicate with other artists and curators, and work together to independently organize exhibitions and events.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artfare artists are based in NYC and actively make and show their work. Our group is carefully curated and  selective. In addition to quality and maturity in the work, we seek artists with professional track records and career ambition. We aim to create a well rounded program that represents all voices and mediums. Please browse the app and artfare.com to get a sense of our mission and artist list. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our tools and services allow artists to:&lt;br/&gt;1. Easily share links to your available works and facilitate sales from your studio, both on and offline&lt;br/&gt;2. Build a following of potential patrons and curators in a professional context&lt;br/&gt;3. Receive tax documents at year end and let Artfare collect, file, and pay sales tax on your behalf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you would like to submit your work for consideration please do so by June 30 via this link:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://artfare.slideroom.com/#/login/program/48475&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/84107623-c195-4291-ad9f-244c7f91305e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>dbb6df0c-7247-4121-b3ff-c1dc4ebb1d5c</id><title>8/16 - Exhibition Opportunity -- Performance by Proxy</title><updated>2019-07-13T07:18:00.374293+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;RF Curatorial&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hamtramck, MI, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/16/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Performance by Proxy is a series of performances wherein a proxy substitutes for the performer. The type of activity, movement, task, performance, etc. is open, but the artist’s absence must be an integral element to the piece; however, the artist may attend as an audience member or participate in another way, such as from a different location to where the performance is viewed. The series will take place in Hamtramck, Michigan in September 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A proxy can be:&lt;br/&gt;	Other performer(s)&lt;br/&gt;	Machine(s)&lt;br/&gt;	Interface(s)&lt;br/&gt;	Mediator(s) (conversation or action through someone else, concurrently)&lt;br/&gt;	Object(s)&lt;br/&gt;	Virtual proxy&lt;br/&gt;	&lt;br/&gt;In your proposal, please consider the following questions:&lt;br/&gt;How does the audience engage the work? What does the work ask of the audience?&lt;br/&gt;What is the connection between artist and proxy? Proxy and audience?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please email your proposal and any questions to rfcuratorial@gmail.com. In your proposal, include any significant details or specifications required for the performance.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/dbb6df0c-7247-4121-b3ff-c1dc4ebb1d5c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>27893958-a06d-41f1-a6c9-38458beeb7c0</id><title>8/1 - Open Call 2019</title><updated>2019-07-13T07:18:00.374236+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;BOCCARA ART Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/baopencall2019"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOCCARA ART Brooklyn is thrilled to announce its 2019 Open Call, with selected artists exhibiting their work at BOCCARA ART Brooklyn from August 17, 2019, until September 20, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With its museum-like space spanning nearly 3,000 sq ft, BOCCARA ART Brooklyn highlights an important collection of historically influential artists while simultaneously dedicating its focus on emerging artists as well. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BOCCARA ART participates in a variety of art fairs each year, including ART NY, AIPAD, and ART MIAMI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applicants must be living and working in the tri-state area.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications must be submitted at &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/baopencall2019" target="_blank"&gt;http://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;by 11:59 pm on August 1, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Decisions will be released on Thursday, August 8, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted artists will be responsible for dropping off and picking up the work from the gallery. All work must be prepared and ready for installation. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions should be directed to brooklyn@boccara-art.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/27893958-a06d-41f1-a6c9-38458beeb7c0" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>