<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-21T17:17:31-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>f70ed911-6aa5-4ce4-bf17-bad740915e2a</id><title>6/30 - Hudson Valley MOCA 1st Annual Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-06-21T17:17:31.606237+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hudson Valley MOCA&lt;br/&gt;📍 Peekskill, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.hudsonvalleymoca.org/juried-member-exhibition"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hudson Valley MOCA's 1st Annual Juried Exhibition is an opportunity to showcase a variety of perspectives and practices within the contemporary visual arts. Juried by Legacy Russell, Associate Curator of Exhibitions at The Studio Museum in Harlem, this exhibition will unite a multitude of voices, both local and national, to explore our contemporary moment and the unique work created within it. The exhibition will be on view at Hudson Valley MOCA from August 10 to September 8, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: June 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Notification to artists: July 12, 2019 (via email)&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Saturday, August 10, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates:  August 10 - September 8, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Legacy Russell is a curator, writer, and artist. Born and raised in New York City, she is the Associate Curator of Exhibitions at The Studio Museum in Harlem.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Russell’s academic, curatorial, and creative work focuses on gender, performance, digital selfdom, internet idolatry, and new media ritual. She has lectured internationally on the intersection of art, the Internet, and feminism; a selection of engagements include Academy of Fine Arts, Munich, Rewire Festival 2018, IMPAKT Festival 2017, and The London School of Economics. In 2017, Russell hosted the Serpentine Marathon GUEST, GHOST, HOST: MACHINE! in London. Her first book, Glitch Feminism, is forthcoming from Verso Books. Russell’s written work, interviews, and essays and can be found in BOMB Magazine, The White Review, Rhizome, Guernica, Berfrois, Screen Shot Magazine, and beyond.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Russell holds a dual-major B.A. with Honors from Macalester College in Art History &amp; Studio Art and English &amp; Creative Writing with a focus in Gender Studies, and an MRes with Distinction in Art History from Goldsmiths, University of London with a focus in Visual Culture.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRIZES AND AWARDS:&lt;br/&gt;FIRST PRIZE $500&lt;br/&gt;SECOND PRIZE $250&lt;br/&gt;THIRD PRIZE $100&lt;br/&gt;VISITORS’ CHOICE: Upgraded Membership to Benefactor level&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY: National artists 18 years or older with current Hudson Valley MOCA membership. Original works accepted in all media, executed during the past two years, and never previously exhibited at Hudson Valley MOCA. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEE: A non-refundable $10 fee will be charged for each submitted image of an artwork. Each entry must be paid in full. Check, Visa, Mastercard, or American Express will be accepted through the CaFÉ site.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS:  Online CAFE entry due June 30, 2019. POSTAL ENTRIES WILL NOT BE ACCEPTED. Artists may submit up to four images of artwork. CaFÉ is an online application and jury management system for calls for entry. Visit www.callforentry.org for more information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MEMBERSHIP:  Hudson Valley MOCA's Annual Juried Exhibition is open to our members. If you are not a current member, we invite you to join us by visiting  &lt;a href="https://www.hudsonvalleymoca.org/membership." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.hudsonvalleymoca.org&lt;/a&gt; For additional information please email francesca.ricapito@hudsonvalleymoca.org or call us at (914) 788-0100.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f70ed911-6aa5-4ce4-bf17-bad740915e2a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c340a998-0422-4bdc-aac7-1bd80780e17b</id><title>7/19 - Drawn From Life</title><updated>2019-06-21T17:17:31.606178+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Upstream Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hastings on Hudson, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.upstreamgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call for Artists  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Drawn From Life”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Life drawing is like playing scales for many artists, yet there is always something extraordinary about portraying a living person.  Upstream Gallery invites artists who work in any medium except photography to submit pieces that involve the human figure. This will be the gallery’s first ever exhibition based solely on portraying the figure.  The exhibition will open at the Gallery in Hastings on Hudson on Thursday, August 8th and run through Sunday September 1st.  Opening Reception will be Sunday, August 11th 2-5pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Work:  Artists from across the U.S. are invited to submit 2-D or 3-D work that is based on the figure or live portraits in any medium except photography.  (We hold a separate show dedicated to photographic work.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Specifications:  Maximum framed size may not exceed 30 x 40 inches.  Freestanding sculpture must be accompanied by its own display support.    Accepted wall pieces must be able to be hung and properly wired or mounted for hanging.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror: &lt;br/&gt;TBWard will jury this show. Ward was born in Barnsley, England and trained in painting and printmaking in the UK before relocating to NYC where he worked with Sol LeWitt on a major installation in lower Manhattan in 2000.  He has also worked at the Whitney Museum doing installations and in the Museum’s archives.  Ward has completed commissions in London, Dublin, Stockholm, Moscow and Chicago.  He has exhibited in New York City, Philadelphia, Saratoga Springs NY and the Art Vaults in Shrewsbury, &lt;br/&gt;UK.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee:  Minimum entry of 3 pieces $45, each additional entry $5 up to a maximum of 6 pieces ($60).  The juror may select one, several or none of your submissions.  All pieces must be for sale.  The gallery will retain a 30% commission on all sales.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Entry Deadline:  Friday, July 19th 2019.  All entries must be made via Submittable.&lt;br/&gt;Receipt of Work: all shipped work must be received no later than Friday, August 2nd.&lt;br/&gt;Local Delivery: If you are local, work must be received at the Gallery on Monday, August 5th from 10am to 2 pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Show opens Thursday, August 8th.&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s Reception: Sunday, August 11th 2-5 pm&lt;br/&gt;Last Day of show: Sunday September 1st. &lt;br/&gt;Local Artists pick up work Sunday after 5 pm or Monday Sept. 2nd.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Upstream Gallery, 8 Main Street, Hastings on Hudson, NY 10706&lt;br/&gt;www.upstreamgallery.com                    914-674-8548&lt;br/&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit/142593/drawn-from-life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit/142593/drawn-from-life" target="_blank"&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c340a998-0422-4bdc-aac7-1bd80780e17b" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>