<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-25T15:15:27-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>af0bc0ae-a9de-4f36-8417-99ced80ebc65</id><title>4/9 - 2019 National Juried Competition - DEADLINE EXTENDED</title><updated>2019-03-25T15:15:27.501585+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;First Street Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.firststreetgallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEADLINE EXTENDED TO APRIL 9!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Open to U.S. resident artists at least 18 years old. Exception: Artists currently represented by First Street Gallery. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible works include ORIGINAL oils, acrylics, watercolors, pastels, drawings, prints, mixed media, photography, and sculpture in any medium. No video, film, installation, giclees or similar reproductions. The width of work, including the frame, may not exceed 44 inches. No height limit. Maximum depth: 10 inches. Maximum weight: 30 lbs. All 2D work must be suitably framed (or sides cleanly finished or painted), wired and ready for hanging. D-rings should be used for heavy works. Works on paper must be framed under plexiglass or glass. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Standing sculpture ONLY: maximum weight is 50 lbs. Maximum width or depth of sculpture is 30 inches. No height limit. Sculptors must provide floor stand with a maximum footprint of 30" x 30." (The gallery has a small number of stands which may be available for small sculpture. If your work is chosen, please contact the gallery if you wish to use one of ours.) Wall hung sculpture: maximum weight 30 lbs., maximum width 30 inches, maximum depth 10 inches. No height limit. Must have securely attached wire or other fixture(s) to hang. Cannot be hung from ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For prospectus and application form, please visit: www.firststreetgallery.org/njeprospectus19&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Inquiries: njeinquiries@firststreetgallery.org / 646-336-8053&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/af0bc0ae-a9de-4f36-8417-99ced80ebc65" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>