<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-25T08:16:11-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>4085f16d-5ca0-4db0-a7c1-de5a402bf0f6</id><title>5/6 - 2019 OPEN CALL: BERLIN/LONDON ARTIST RESIDENCY PROGRAM</title><updated>2019-04-25T08:16:11.842397+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;CENTRE. SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS: Applied Grief &amp;amp; Bereavement Research/Multidiscip. Studio&lt;br/&gt;📍  , Germany&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING:&lt;br/&gt;OPEN CALL&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNUM: &lt;br/&gt;2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PARTICIPATING CITIES:&lt;br/&gt;Berlin, Germany&lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;***UPCOMING DEADLINE - SHORT-TERM RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING***:&lt;br/&gt;Berlin, Germany Summer 2019 Residency Cohort 2 (1 Month Program): 06 MAY 2019 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ADDITIONAL DEADLINES - SHORT-TERM RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING:&lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom Autumn 2019 Residency Cohort 1 (1 Month Program): 03 JUN 2019 &lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom Autumn 2019 Residency Cohort 2 (1 Month Program): 26 JUN 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ADDITIONAL DEADLINES - LONG-TERM RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING: &lt;br/&gt;Long-Term Study Residency (12 Month Program) Deadline: Ongoing&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS is now accepting applications for residency programming commencing in 2019. Artists, researchers, and other arts professionals are encouraged to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ORGANIZATION:&lt;br/&gt;Established in 2009, the CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS is a Canadian organization dedicated to the development of applied grief and bereavement research. Documented through the use of practice-led methods within art and comprised of work from an interdisciplinary network of creative and technical practitioners; the CENTRE is committed to the advancement of the arts and sciences; providing programming in support of education; public and professional engagement; and the development of field research in partnership with local, national, and international academic bodies, institutions, foundations, and non-profits.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION CRITERIA &amp; ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:&lt;br/&gt;The artist-in-residence candidates are selected annually through an open call application process or in some cases, by invitation. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The residency program encourages experimentation and the development of multi/interdisciplinary studio work grounded in research within the field of grief and bereavement. The work can encompass and explore varying physical and emotional processes (or loss) that people undergo. Previous residents and collaborators have undertaken both theoretical-historical and practice-led projects working with, but not limited to the following subject matter: the aging process and the elderly; cancer, disease, and terminal illness; sex work and sexual assault; abortion and miscarriage; suicide and survivorship; mental illness and trauma; spousal and familial loss; and associated grief and bereavement-centered themes etc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The residency aims to provide working artistic professionals with a platform for research and production; one that may lead to expanded possibilities, collaboration, a broader network, and possibly new works. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information and to apply please review the Residency Guide and complete an Application Form by visiting:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To be notified of upcoming opportunities including new and existing programming, open calls, and initiatives, please subscribe to our newsletter here:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/contact/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;——&lt;br/&gt;CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS (Est. 2009) &lt;br/&gt;Applied Grief and Bereavement Research&lt;br/&gt;Interdisciplinary/Multidisciplinary Studio &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Follow us here:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/substructuredloss/&lt;br/&gt;https://vimeo.com/substructuredloss&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and to apply please review the Residency Guide and complete an Application Form by visiting:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The application form and all applicable supplementary attachments must be submitted by email.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4085f16d-5ca0-4db0-a7c1-de5a402bf0f6" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>627298da-9d90-458e-989e-6c794f9e121a</id><title>5/4 - 65th Annual Exhibition of the National Society of Painters in Casein &amp;amp; Acrylic</title><updated>2019-04-25T08:16:11.842335+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;National Society of Painters in Casein &amp;amp; Acrylic&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York , NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Painting&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/04/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.nationalsocietyofpaintersincaseinandacrylic.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exhibition features awards totaling over $17,000. The National Society of Painters in Casein and Acrylic was founded to give artists opportunity to exhibit works regardless of style, “school” or subject matter. It is the foremost National Showcase for the two Aquamedia—Casein and Acrylic. Awards and exhibition held at The Salmagundi Club in New York, NY.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Download the prospectus here: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalsocietyofpaintersincaseinandacrylic.com/prospectus/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.nationalsocietyofpaintersincaseinandacrylic.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/627298da-9d90-458e-989e-6c794f9e121a" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>