<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-04T18:17:08-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>fbd6e705-6624-41a8-acc0-5b622a192945</id><title>7/31 - Create! Magazine MFA Edition Call for Art</title><updated>2019-06-04T18:17:08.003632+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.createmagazine.com/callforart"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine is pleased to announce an open call for its first annual MFA Edition. We are now accepting applications from current candidates and recent graduates from 2017 - 2019.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Create! Magazine is an independent contemporary arts magazine focused on highlighting the work of talented emerging and mid-career creatives from across the globe. We are pleased to announce our next call for artists for a custom designed two-page spread in our publication (both print &amp; digital) that will feature your artist biography, website, and two images of your artwork. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Have your work seen by our 125,000+ readers and followers around the world, including leading galleries, art fairs, collectors, curators, writers, art consultants, and more. Don’t miss this opportunity to put your work out there and connect with a new audience!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY: MFA graduates from the past two years and current candidates from both the US and abroad, of all genders, ethnicities, and from all backgrounds are welcome to apply. We accept works in any medium: painting, sculpture, digital art, printmaking, fiber/textile art, photography, mixed media, installation, etc. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS: 3+ jpeg images of different artworks, a text document with a bio and artist statement, website or social media link, and your email address. If your work is three-dimensional, you may include additional images of installation views or detailed shots at no extra cost. Please see our Submittable form for further details. Please note that for best results, artists should include works from the same series per each submission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTISTS: If your work is selected, you will receive a custom designed two-page spread in both the print and digital versions of the magazine that will include your artist biography, website, and two images. Published artists will be sent a complimentary digital issue and will be listed as a participating artist in your issue on both our website and social media. We also promote artists individually via blog and social media posts that reach over 125,000 total followers worldwide. All featured artists will automatically be considered for any upcoming curatorial projects, not limited to art fairs, exhibitions, and gallery projects organized by our team. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;WHERE TO FIND US: Print copies of Create! Magazine are available in our online shop and at several global retail locations in London, New York, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Amsterdam, Stockholm, Chicago, Philadelphia, Ft. Lauderdale, Wilmington (DE), and more. Digital issues can always be purchased on our website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fbd6e705-6624-41a8-acc0-5b622a192945" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6964e1f3-96a0-412c-841d-10a2a9a0955c</id><title>WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW! Open Call Fro artists Friday June 14th 2019</title><updated>2019-06-04T18:17:08.003490+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our &lt;br/&gt;June 14th  People's Choice Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday,June 14th, 2019 from 8pm- 12am.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, May 30th, 2019 at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For this show, we let the people decide, which means everyone who attends votes for the winners! We pass out ballots at the door and guests who attends choose the winners! It is always one of our most well attended nights, boasting record art sales and a large community of fellow artists and art lovers!&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of local bands!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, June 13th at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces already this past year. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com @ Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Facebook:  www.facebook.com/events/302426043994914/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6964e1f3-96a0-412c-841d-10a2a9a0955c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>dee29b16-d2c6-4627-920e-9d2acfe021b6</id><title>7/31 - Juried Exhibition &amp;quot;SHOW YOUR WORLD&amp;quot;</title><updated>2019-06-04T18:17:08.003448+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;RE:ARTISTE International Art Organization&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $39.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.reartiste.com/show-your-world-2019-juried-exhibition"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All entries are accepted. The digital installation is part of our art show: artwork of all participants is projected at the gallery during the entire show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Twenty Winners will display original work at the “Show Your World” exhibition in New York City in November 2019 at Gallery MC.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is more than just a plain exhibition. To promote our artists we host various art &amp; social events to attract a broader audience and your potential buyers. For artists, we organize networking meetups, workshops, consultations. This festival-like art show attracts thousands of visitors - YOUR ART WILL BE SEEN. Show your art and make new connections. Meet new art enthusiasts and sell your art.&lt;br/&gt;Be exhibited in New York City - New York is considered a center of contemporary art life. The world famous art neighborhoods - Chelsea and Soho, Lower East Side and Bushwick, Dumbo and Williamsburg - are located in New York City. The city hosts more than 1500 galleries and hundreds of art shows each year. New York is the place where you can view internationally renowned artworks along with witnessing how modern art emerges. Get the chance to show your world and art to thousands of visitors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;"The artist's job is to be a witness to his time in history." - Robert Rauschenberg&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art is a non-verbal language understood by people speaking different mother tongues. It conveys both historical and social facts, lifestyle, inspiration, and feelings. We’ve been creating a dialogue among artists from various cities and countries.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our Fifth (!) Annual Art Competition and Juried Exhibition “SHOW YOUR WORLD” is open to artists of various media around the globe. Artists of all career levels are welcome. Painters, photographers, mixed media artists from more than 40 countries took part in the previous four editions of “Show Your World”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EVALUATION: The Jury Panel represented by gallery board members, curators, exhibiting artists, art business professionals is evaluating our 5th International Juried Exhibition “Show Your World”. Find out more about the Jurors here.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;INSPIRATION: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Being traditional or rebellious, figurative or conceptual artist, SHOW YOUR WORLD, views, ideas:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Show YOUR World – happy or sad, active or laid back, open or intimate&lt;br/&gt;Show what only artists can depict – feelings, emotions, or relationships&lt;br/&gt;Show wildlife, nature, or urban landscapes&lt;br/&gt;Show what’s close to your heart or what destroys your comfort&lt;br/&gt;Show your inspiration – whether it’s a person, a place, a book, or another work of art&lt;br/&gt;Show your childhood or your future&lt;br/&gt;Show the world you love, hate, or dream about&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS: Entries must be in JPEG format, no larger than 1400 x 1800 pixels, and under 2MB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following disciplines are accepted:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Painting&lt;br/&gt;Drawing/Illustration&lt;br/&gt;Photography&lt;br/&gt;Mixed Media and 3-D Art including Ceramics and Textile&lt;br/&gt;Digital Art/ Video Art&lt;br/&gt;Installation&lt;br/&gt;Performance&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE include your show statement – it will help the jurors and curators understand your work better.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: JULY 31, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION: As soon as your entry is submitted you receive a popup web page confirming your submission. The finalists will be announced on the RE:ARTISTE website by October 1, 2019 and will be personally notified via email. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;COPYRIGHT: The submitting artists own the copyright to their competition entries as their author(s). By submitting an entry to the art competition the artist gives RE:ARTISTE permission for the entry to be used on the RE:ARTISTE website and its social media channels. The artist gives RE:ARTISTE the right to use his/her name and city of residence for the sole purpose of identifying the artist as the author of the entry. The entry fee is not refundable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Entries must be in JPEG format, no larger than 1400 x 1800 pixels, and under 2MB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following disciplines are accepted:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Painting&lt;br/&gt;Drawing/Illustration&lt;br/&gt;Photography&lt;br/&gt;Mixed Media and 3-D Art including Ceramics and Textile&lt;br/&gt;Digital Art/ Video Art&lt;br/&gt;Installation&lt;br/&gt;Performance&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE include your show statement – it will help the jurors and curators understand your work better.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info please email at info@reartiste.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/dee29b16-d2c6-4627-920e-9d2acfe021b6" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>223aec2f-09fc-42e5-a795-0eccb3cfbd74</id><title>7/12 - Call for Proposals:  Take A Seat Exhibition</title><updated>2019-06-04T18:17:08.003389+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtsWestchester&lt;br/&gt;📍 White Plains, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/12/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artswestchester.submittable.com/submit/133709/call-to-artists-and-designers-submit-your-chairs-to-take-a-seat-exhibition-at"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"TAKE A SEAT": An exhibition that explores the form, function, creativity, and tradition of seating.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ArtsWestchester invites artists and artist collectives to submit originally designed and handcrafted chairs, alternative forms of seating, or artwork that represents or incorporates chairs for its exhibition, “TAKE A SEAT”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected work will be on view in ArtsWestchester’s “TAKE A SEAT” exhibition, which will open with a reception on September 28, 2019, and be on view to the public through October 19, 2019.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BACKGROUND: "TAKE A SEAT" explores the forms, functions, traditions, and creative frameworks of seating. For the exhibition, ArtsWestchester will consider work in all media including, but not limited to: sculptural, conceptual, functional (and dysfunctional) seating, 2-dimensional artworks, and installations using chairs/seating. &lt;br/&gt;As with all exhibitions at ArtsWestchester's Gallery, "Take a Seat" will be free to the public. The exhibition will address an audience of all ages and backgrounds.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Applicants must be at least 18 years old, and must live, maintain a studio or be enrolled in an undergraduate or graduate program in New York State.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR SUBMISSIONS:  July 12, 2019 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be notified of their submission status on or around July 31, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION PERIOD:&lt;br/&gt;“TAKE A SEAT” will open with a reception on Saturday, September 28, and be on view through October 19, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;ArtsWestchester Gallery hours are Tuesday - Friday, 12-5PM, and Saturday, 12-6PM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION REQUIREMENTS:&lt;br/&gt;All Submissions must be submitted digitally via Submittable. E-mailed or mailed submissions will not be considered. Artists must submit a separate statement for each piece. &lt;br/&gt;Complete applications must include:&lt;br/&gt;Artist Bio and/or CV (word document)&lt;br/&gt;High Resolution Images of each work (artists may submit up to 5 unique works, with no more      than 3 images per work.) (jpeg, tiff, pdf)&lt;br/&gt;Submission checklist (word document). Checklist should include the following information: title, date, materials, dimensions,  sale price, insurance pricem and installation/display details. &lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement for each submitted work (word document) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Note:  ArtsWestchester reserves the right to use any High Resolution Images of selected works for promotional purposes of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Further Questions: Contact Amy Kurlander, Curator: Akurlander@ArtsWestchester.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/223aec2f-09fc-42e5-a795-0eccb3cfbd74" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>