<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-11T13:16:35-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>54fddffa-987a-42cd-9e9b-02f1ee8ee82b</id><title>6/10 - &amp;quot;America Is ...&amp;quot; Artists Explore, Ask and Answer: What is America today? National Juried Show</title><updated>2019-05-11T13:16:35.695082+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Touchstone Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Washington, DC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.touchstonegallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL FOR ENTRIES&lt;br/&gt;Founded in 1976, Touchstone Gallery, located in a modern street-level space in downtown Washington, DC is seeking entries for "America Is ..." a National Juried Show scheduled for August 2 - 29, 2019. Artists are asked to submit artwork that will Explore, Ask and Answer: What is America today?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jurors:&lt;br/&gt;- Rachel Adams, Chief Curator and Director of Programs, Bemis Center for Contemporary Arts (Omaha, NE)&lt;br/&gt;- Taylor Bythewood-Porter, Assistant History Curator, California African American Museum (CAAM)&lt;br/&gt;- Jen Mergel, Independent Curator; Vice President, Programs, Association of Art Museum Curators (AAMC); Founding Director, Curatorial Network Accelerator of Boston&lt;br/&gt;- Jennifer M. Williams, Public Programs Manager, New Orleans Museum of Art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AWARDS Four artworks will receive Juror's Best in Show Prize of $250&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEES $50 for up to 3 entries/files; artists may submit up to 3 additional entries/files at a cost of $10 per additional entry. Submit one file per piece entered. Entries are accepted via Submittable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Open to all artists living and/or working in the United States, 18-years-old and older.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All original visual media that is the artist's own concept, design and work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit www.touchstonegallery.com to apply.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE TO APPLY:  Monday, June 10, 2019, 11:59 PM ET.&lt;br/&gt;Please email your questions to info@touchstonegallery.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/54fddffa-987a-42cd-9e9b-02f1ee8ee82b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>fa1f10ba-78ed-41be-9578-3dbdbffb0dfb</id><title>6/7 - City of Charlotte - Charlotte Water Zone Four Field Opperations Facility</title><updated>2019-05-11T13:16:35.695023+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arts &amp;amp; Science Council&lt;br/&gt;📍 Charlotte, NC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/07/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Arts &amp; Science Council is accepting qualifications from artists for a public art opportunity at the upcoming Charlotte Water Zone Four Field Operation facility. The selected artist will work with the ASC, Charlotte Water staff, C Design, and local communities to create artwork that is complementary to the architectural design of the facility and reflect the service of Charlotte Water and the history and character of West Charlotte. The selected artist or artist team will be expected to engage with both Charlotte Water staff and area residents to develop the concept for their work. The selected artist will have the opportunity to create engaging, freestanding artwork/s that are complementary to the sites. Two site locations have been identified as possible opportunities for artwork placement: the front entrance along Tyvola Road and the plaza space directly adjacent to the facility. The selected artist/s may choose to site artwork at either or both sites. The artwork should be visually impactful, so scale, materials, and project budget will need to be closely considered. The Tyvola Road entrance site will be highly visible to vehicular traffic. Artwork sited at this location should serve as a landmark representing Charlotte Water and the communities of West Charlotte. For security purposes, access to the Zone Four Field Operations facility is limited. Charlotte Water staff will primarily enjoy artwork sited at the facility plaza with local residents encountering the artwork during visits to the facility’s community space.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the complete RFQ, please visit: &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.artsandscience.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fa1f10ba-78ed-41be-9578-3dbdbffb0dfb" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>