<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-17T21:17:26-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>b30f64b8-7d71-4d44-9af0-9b4f320f49ee</id><title>9/1 - SATELLITE ART SHOW | NYC | APPLICATIONS OPEN</title><updated>2019-06-17T21:17:26.658837+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SATELLITE ART SHOW&lt;br/&gt;📍 brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.satellite-show.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SATELLITE ART SHOW is currently accepting applications for our New York City Art Fair! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Recently called "Miami's Best Art Fair", SATELLITE ART SHOW is the art experience of the future.  We will be debuting our renowned platform in New York this October at the Pfizer building in Brooklyn.  We are looking for interactive, progressive and experiential art projects that span fine art, tech, performance, installation and audio. Applications are available to galleries, curators, art organizations, artist collectives, artists and music organizations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SATELLITE is free to apply to! Simply go to www.satellite-show.com and submit all of the required materials. SATELLITE is reviewing applications on a rolling basis and will accept applications with merit. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? info@satellite-show.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b30f64b8-7d71-4d44-9af0-9b4f320f49ee" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cc60089a-3ac6-4742-8849-709161156932</id><title>7/15 - BURN THIS - OPEN CALL all disciplines</title><updated>2019-06-17T21:17:26.658770+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burn This - inspired by the title of an incredible Lanford Wilson play that features Pale, a truly volcanic character. We are looking for all kind of work [including performances] that utilizes or represents heat. Work created using welding, heat transfer, flame, acid, lasers or just representations or images of the aftermath of flames, fusion, and heat.   Therefore all ceramics or work that is 'fired' is eligible.  Laser etching would also be eligible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Work can be submitted, for example, that uses charcoal, flame, chemical processes or any kind of process that involves reactive elements. Photography, painting or video of smoke, heat, vapor, gasses, Deserts or the effects of heat, the effects of the Sun are all welcome.  A video of the Yule log?  Maybe. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE NOTE THAT WE CANNOT ACCEPT WORK THAT HAS TO BE SHIPPED. ALL WORK MUST BE DELIVERED AND PICKED UP AT THE GALLERY.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION FEES - If you have previously shown with us the fee is $15, if not, $30. There is also a link for our Artist Directory if you wish to have a entry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit using the form link here: &lt;a href="https://form.jotform.com/trimistopheles/burn-this-2019-open-call" target="_blank"&gt;https://form.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cc60089a-3ac6-4742-8849-709161156932" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>