<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-26T11:16:13-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>3da44dd4-ed1a-4582-bef1-de122001e3e5</id><title>5/9 - May People&amp;#39;s Choice Open Call Salon Show- WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!</title><updated>2019-04-26T11:16:13.539060+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our May 10th People's Choice Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, May 10th, 2019 from 8pm- 12am.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, May 9th, 2019 at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For this show, we let the people decide, which means everyone who attends votes for the winners! We pass out ballots at the door and guests who attends choose the winners! It is always one of our most well attended nights, boasting record art sales and a large community of fellow artists and art lovers!&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of local bands!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, May 9th  at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces in the $150-$500 range. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3da44dd4-ed1a-4582-bef1-de122001e3e5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6fb718ad-74ce-489d-b638-d24fed342137</id><title>5/10 - Call for Brooklyn Based Artists</title><updated>2019-04-26T11:16:13.539032+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arco Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Painting&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.arcogallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Description&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Arco Gallery is inviting all Brooklyn based artists to submit their work to be considered for purchase of existing artworks or for commissions of new works, to become part of a permanent collection in a residential building in Brooklyn.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are looking for paintings only, either on canvas or on panel. Three-dimensional works will be considered as long as they are meant to be hung on a wall. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After reviewing all submissions, Arco Gallery will email the artists who will be taken into consideration to schedule a studio visit to view the artwork in person.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The deadline for submission is May 10th, 2019. The artists selected for the studio visit will receive an email to schedule the visit by May 12th 2019. Artists that do not respond by May 15th 2019 will be removed from the selection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Instructions / Public Contact Information&lt;br/&gt;RULES &lt;br/&gt;–No conceptual art will be taken into consideration.&lt;br/&gt;- The medium must be paint or mixed media. The support must be sturdy, preferably on canvas or panel.&lt;br/&gt;- Artworks must be permanent and sturdy. Mediums that are too delicate or fragile will not be considered.&lt;br/&gt;- Applicants must submit 6-8 images of their work by email at info@arcogallery.com&lt;br/&gt;- Images must be of artworks no smaller than 30” x 40”&lt;br/&gt;- Each image must be clearly labeled with Title, dimensions, medium and price&lt;br/&gt;- Each file can’t be smaller than 1MB or larger than 2MB. JPG format only.&lt;br/&gt;- Include website address if you have one&lt;br/&gt;- The applicants must be Brooklyn based. (Please include studio address)&lt;br/&gt;- Applicants must be available for a studio visit between May 15th 2019 and May 20th 2019.&lt;br/&gt;- Note that Arco Gallery is interested in dealing only directly with artists. No third parties involved (another gallery or artist’s rep).&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6fb718ad-74ce-489d-b638-d24fed342137" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2f8834d4-3ffc-410a-a143-1289fd400e77</id><title>5/1 - OPEN CALL FOR ALL DISCIPLINES</title><updated>2019-04-26T11:16:13.539000+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC ARTS OPEN&lt;br/&gt;📍 LIC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LEASE NOTE THE FOLLOWING INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Most all media accepted; however, if sculpture, installation, video or work that requires pedestals, power, projectors, screens/technology, please use the description box below to explain specific needs.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WE CANNOT GUARANTEE TO HAVE THE NECESSARY EQUIPMENT AVAILABLE.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION ADDRESSES:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Raw Gallery at The Factory: 30-30 47th AVE. LIC, NY 11101&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Month long exhibition&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;43-01 21st St, LIC 11101&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Only open on May 18th &amp; 19th&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submissions due: May 1st, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We reserve the right to select any number of pieces&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork Drop off: Information to follow&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Standard Artwork Drop off:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork must be ready to hang with appropriate fixings etc. some walls are the cinderblock/cement, some drywall or if sculptural or video please provide the necessary pedestals or technology. If you have proposed performance or other live work (an installation, etc.) we will contact you directly with further information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Factory Opening Reception: Weds 15th, from 5 - 8 pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;43-01 Reception: Friday, May 17th, from 6 - 9 pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Please take/remove your wrappings at drop off; we do not have storage for wrappings, boxes, or bubble wrap.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are really interested in showing the work of artists from outside of LIC &amp; Queens. We regretfully cannot accept work from other US locations other than NYC and all artwork must be hand delivered. NO SHIPPING. WE ALSO HAVE NO STORAGE AND YOU AGREE TO PICKUP ON THE DATES AS IN APPLICATION&lt;br/&gt;All artists pay an application fee but if you have previously exhibited with us please select the 2nd payment option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply via this form only  &lt;a href="https://form.jotform.com/91135779015964" target="_blank"&gt;https://form.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2f8834d4-3ffc-410a-a143-1289fd400e77" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>bcc094a7-1ffb-4483-8364-a9fa6fe59ad2</id><title>5/11 - call for submissions</title><updated>2019-04-26T11:16:13.538961+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Playtime/Picaflor&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.iloveplaytime.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking for artists to create an installation for a prestigious international kids fashion show in NYC in AUGUST 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Three fine artists will be selected and given a space 14x14ft to create an installation around a "theme" of fashion this season (please see the themes below). YOUR WORK MUST RELATE TO ONE OF THE THREE THEMES. We are looking for fine artists in any medium - sculpture, fabric arts, painting, illustration, etc. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please contact us ASAP with the following...&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Your website which should have a CV AND images of your work&lt;br/&gt;- A brief explanation of how you feel your work relates to one of the themes&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We will then contact you to submit a formal proposal in the coming weeks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Artist will be given $700 as a fee that can cover the creation of the piece (which you can keep after the show) or used as a fee to use an existing piece&lt;br/&gt;- The show will be in NYC in early August&lt;br/&gt;- Past artists have included:&lt;br/&gt;- Please see these links for examples of past shows:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;http://bit.ly/2xKZLBm&lt;br/&gt;http://bit.ly/2hyGd9P&lt;br/&gt;http://bit.ly/2gbWku1&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;List of artists that have exhibited their work at Playtime New York:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Tinou Le Joly Sénoville (France), Tamar Mogendorff (USA), Jasmine Murrell (USA), Florine Demosthene (USA), Sophie Cuvelier (France), Cyril Le Van (France), Jennifer Bongibault (France), Joshua Ben Longo (USA), Collin Velkoff (USA), Matthew Speedy (USA), Ritsuko Hirai (Japan/USA), Danielle Ash (USA), Julie Gauthron (France), Julien Gardair (France/USA), Rose Wong (USA), Julie Tremblay (Canada/USA), Eric Hagan (USA), Melissa Godoy Nieto (Mexico/USA), Dana Haim (USA), Naomi Feuerstein (USA), Klara Varosy (Netherlands/USA), Hanna Xenakis (USA), Kathryne Hall (USA), Elodie Blanchard (France/USA), Zoe Adlersberg (USA), Polina Soloveichik (Russia), Tanya Minhas (Pakistan/USA), Tara Linzalone (USA), Alexandra Hammond (USA), Cecilia Elguero (Argentina/USA), Yura Osborn (Japan/USA), Wendy Letven (USA), Saki Sato (USA), Jason Villegas (USA), Lisa Laubreaux (France), Sarah Philouze (France/USA), Brittany Solem (USA), Fanny Allie (France/USA), …&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SPRING-SUMMER 2020 TRENDS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;#1 PATHFINDERS &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At the dawn of an unprecedented societal, environmental, and human transformation, it can be difficult to find one's bearings. Children, who are more in touch with their senses, are attuned to what nature has to teach them.  Let's follow them: they are harbingers. Yoga, meditation, rites of passage... They use all that is available to them in seeking the right rhythm, in cultivating the kind of benevolence that gives meaning to one’s presence in the world.  This takes the form of a daily commitment, of maieutic engagement. In the wake of Timoci Naulusala or Greta Thunberg and other budding activists, they are brimming with good ideas to change our modes of life: they plant trees, cultivate vegetable gardens in cities, recycle garbage, make objects from recycled materials, organize pottery classes to reconnect with the earth and with others. In doing so, they also undergo a metamorphosis and set out to meet their true selves.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Key words: Sustainability and circular economy activism, common sense, poetic workwear&lt;br/&gt;Key pieces: Simple, practical garments with refined details, overalls, cotton seersucker smocks, knit rompers&lt;br/&gt;Fabrics: bamboo viscose, natural materials, washed linens, open stitch mesh, handmade knitwear&lt;br/&gt;Prints: wildflowers, dry vegetation, fruits from the orchard, positive symbols, talismans&lt;br/&gt;Colors: Warm, earthy and vegetable, half-shades, lighted by a buttercup yellow&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;#2 FANTASIA &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Why not reach out for that hand and join the dance!&lt;br/&gt;You find yourself in a teeming phantasmagoria peopled with strange, half animal, half human creatures... A poetic and joyful fantasy where all wear masks, where optical illusions reign. In a setting somewhere between inextricable jungle and imaginary architectures, one camouflages or presents oneself with panache. Behind every door, a surprise! All possibles are open: one can don any costume, live in different skins, and reinvent oneself to the whim of nested identities. Therein resides the whole magic of childhood... But is it a dream or simply the carnival of life that marches in front of your astonished eyes?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Key words: fantasy, graphic and playful cuts, optical illusions, hidden details, color blocks, gathers, ruches, giant flounces&lt;br/&gt;Key pieces: tulle overdresses, tops and dresses with oversized sleeves, smocked shorts&lt;br/&gt;Fabrics: fluid jerseys, supple satins, tulle, textured knits&lt;br/&gt;Prints: extraordinary worlds, fairytales and legends, terrestrial and aquatic animals, strange plants, surreal collages, free forms, neo camo&lt;br/&gt;Colors: extraordinary multicolor plumages and bursts of exotic flowers, a kaki beauty treatment and deep jungle off-black&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESS START&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accustomed to instant communication and to open source information, the new urban generation seems to live accelerated lives. These 3.0 kids oscillate between reality and virtuality, between the physical and digital realms, mixing them with humor and great agility. Without judgment or self-consciousness they make an instinctive synthesis of them, guided by whatever gives them emotions. Movement: it is their watchword. In this unprecedented adventure, they unpack both future and heritage with the same appetite and appropriate both with spontaneity. An urban and forward-looking theme, tinted with retro-tech nostalgia&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Key words: digital world, new technologies, artificial intelligence, virtual and augmented realities, urban board sports, street-sport-vintage mix &amp; match &lt;br/&gt;Key pieces: jackets or tracksuit bottoms mixed with urban or couture pieces, vintage print T-shirts, cycling shorts, semi-transparent windbreakers, fishnet shorts and skirts, emblazoned sweaters, casual swimsuits, visors, collectors’ sneakers &lt;br/&gt;Fabrics: washed denims, jerseys, duffels, technical fabrics, metallic, lycras, featherweight nylons, PVC, waterproof surfaces&lt;br/&gt;Prints: retro-tech videogames, sports jerseys inspiration, repeat logos, graffiti with edgy messages, 50s &amp; 60s cartoons, tie &amp; dye total look &lt;br/&gt;Colors : cement gray and neutral colors that look machine-processed, lifted by a 70s orange and neons that propel the brand into the future!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please contact us with the following...&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Your website which should have a CV AND images of your work&lt;br/&gt;- A brief explanation of how you feel your work relates to one of the themes&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We will then contact you to submit a formal proposal in the coming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/bcc094a7-1ffb-4483-8364-a9fa6fe59ad2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>43f492b3-03fc-4671-92b9-9491a7226d29</id><title>5/23 - INTERNATIONAL CALL FOR ART, ArtMaze Magazine Summer Edition: Issue 13</title><updated>2019-04-26T11:16:13.538906+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Art Maze Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍  , United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/23/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artmazemag.com/call-for-art/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art Maze Magazine is an independent artist-run and ad-free international print and online publication dedicated to showcasing and promoting experimental and progressive contemporary art, which reflects modern society and its environment, provokes conversation and action; fosters innovation and diversity of mediums which make today’s art scene so intriguing and versatile.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: Artists are welcome to submit works in any medium: painting, drawing, sculpture, ceramics, printmaking, photography, textile, installation, mixed media, digital, film (only jpg + link to video) etc. All visual art mediums are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;Artists or any art organisations on behalf of artists from all countries are welcome to submit their works for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;Each submitted artist, wether selected for a publication or not, will receive a digital copy of the magazine's issue which he/she applied for.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: May 23rd, 2019 (12:00 AM, midnight: end of the day 23rd May - Eastern Standard Time)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUEST CURATOR: Chris Sharp, writer and independent curator based in Mexico City, co-founder of Lulu.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO APPLY: www.artmazemag.com/call-for-art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DISTRIBUTION: Physical and digital copies of ArtMaze Mag are distributed worldwide via bookshops, galleries and online. More info: &lt;a href="http://artmazemag.com/shop/" target="_blank"&gt;http://artmazemag.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selected artists will be asked for high resolution images and will be published in the next print and digital issue of ArtMaze Magazine. Each (selected) artist will receive a 1 or 2-page spread in print and digital (PDF) magazine including bio, statement, website, and 1-5 featured artworks. All submitted artists will receive a complimentary PDF copy of the magazine and all published artists will be promoted on our website/social media. Physical copies of Art Maze Magazine are printed to the highest quality in London, UK.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/43f492b3-03fc-4671-92b9-9491a7226d29" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>