<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-29T13:16:59-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>2c6e0deb-2d89-4932-90c0-ff8f78a93f19</id><title>7/19 - 69th AONE - A National Exhibit</title><updated>2019-05-29T13:16:59.626424+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SIlvermine Arts Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Canaan, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://silvermineart.org/exhibition/69th-aone/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;69th AONE&lt;br/&gt;AONE is a national competition/exhibition highlighting the diversity of work that is currently being made by established and emerging artists. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CURATOR&lt;br/&gt;Bill Carroll, Director of the Studio Program, The Elizabeth Foundation for the Arts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AWARDS  &lt;br/&gt;Best in Show, awards an artist a solo exhibition at Silvermine Arts Center with a $1,000 stipend for show related expenses. The Juror has additional awards to give at their discretion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applications through Slideroom  &lt;a href="https://silvermineart.slideroom.com/#/Login" target="_blank"&gt;https://silvermineart.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2c6e0deb-2d89-4932-90c0-ff8f78a93f19" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>323bc39d-26a5-402b-9069-69ea97891245</id><title>6/30 - CALL FOR ARTISTS: ANIMA MUNDI FESTIVAL 2019 – CONSCIOUSNESS</title><updated>2019-05-29T13:16:59.626379+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ITSLIQUID Group&lt;br/&gt;📍  , Italy&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $300.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.itsliquid.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL FOR ARTISTS: ANIMA MUNDI FESTIVAL 2019 – CONSCIOUSNESS&lt;br/&gt;ITSLIQUID International Art Festival&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: June 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ITSLIQUID Group, in collaboration with Venice Events and Ca’ Zanardi, is pleased to announce the open call for the exhibition CONSCIOUSNESS, second appointment of ANIMA MUNDI 2019 – ITSLIQUID International Art Festival.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANIMA MUNDI FESTIVAL, curated by Arch. Luca Curci, will be presented in Venice at THE ROOM Contemporary Art Space, at Palazzo Ca’ Zanardi and in other prestigious venues between May and November 2019, during the same period of the 58th Venice Biennale, curated by Ralph Rugoff and organized by La Biennale di Venezia 2019, chaired by Paolo Baratta. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANIMA MUNDI consists of 3 main events: RITUALS (May 09 / July 05 2019), CONSCIOUSNESS and VISIONS. We are now selecting artists for the following two upcoming events:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;– CONSCIOUSNESS from July 25 to September 20, 2019 at THE ROOM Contemporary Art Space and from July 26 to September 20, 2019 at Palazzo Ca’ Zanardi&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for applications is June 30, 2019 (11.59 PM of your local time)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;– VISIONS from October 03 to November 24, 2019 at THE ROOM Contemporary Art Space and from October 04 to November 24, 2019 at Palazzo Ca’ Zanardi &lt;br/&gt;Deadline for applications is September 07, 2019 (11.59 PM of your local time)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To take part in the selection, send your works’ submissions with a CV/biography, some still images (for video-art), links of videos/films/performances and pictures of artworks by e-mail to lucacurci@lucacurci.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The participation includes the following services&lt;br/&gt;– exhibition space dedicated to the artist’s works&lt;br/&gt;– assisting with customs formalities, international shipping and local transport&lt;br/&gt;– assisting in finding accommodation for artist&lt;br/&gt;– the design and the printing of invitation cards, posters&lt;br/&gt;– the global and local press office, publicity, press, banners, totem, etc.&lt;br/&gt;– the realization of the exhibition website and dedicated press releases&lt;br/&gt;– mounting and dismounting of the exhibition&lt;br/&gt;– exhibitions opening event with drinks and food&lt;br/&gt;– a one day dedicated presentation, talk or workshop focusing on the artist’s career&lt;br/&gt;– a dedicated interview published on ITSLIQUID website and spread on our social networks &lt;br/&gt;– providing services and drinks for small meetings at the exhibition places for invited guests                       &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The festival focuses on the concept of ANIMA MUNDI, that according to several historical cultures, religions and philosophical systems, is an intrinsic connection between all living entities on the planet, which relates to the world in a similar way as the human soul is connected to the human body.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Plato expressed his thought about the ANIMA MUNDI in the Timaeus, “this world is indeed a living being endowed with a soul and intelligence… a single visible living entity containing all other living entities, which by their nature are all related”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANIMA MUNDI is the invisible energy behind all the natural and the artificial elements that allows the planet to live. Thanks to the hidden connections of ANIMA MUNDI, all the ecosystems of the Earth, before and after the appearance of the mankind, found their equilibrium, their ways to live and to develop themselves, to transform and to evolve. All the beings of the planet, plants, minerals, animals are permeated by a secret force that has always stimulated the human thought and research.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The festival aims to discover these multiple forms of hidden connections between the soul and the body, the mankind and the natural elements, the natural spaces and the cities. We invite artists to show their reflections about the various ways in which the ANIMA MUNDI expresses the relationships among all the existing entities and the natural and cultural systems, and to represent by their artistic works the processes of the evolution of the world in which we all live. Artists, designers and architects are invited to talk about ANIMA MUNDI through photo reportage of cities, hidden places, photographic documentaries, personal experiences, presenting their works of photography, painting, sculpture/installation, design and architecture, video-art and live performance.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ITSLIQUID Group will begin a charity initiative aimed to support some of the most important no-profit organizations that are internationally involved in the environmental protection, such as United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change, Sea Shepherd Conservation Society, One Tree Planted, The Ocean Cleanup and Plastic Oceans. Indeed, they will have some interesting talks during CONSCIOUSNESS and VISIONS, the following ANIMA MUNDI’s appointments. This choice comes from the essence of ANIMA MUNDI in which everything is related to the living entities of the planet. Click here for more information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists, photographers, video makers, architects and performers are invited to submit their works. To take part in the selection, send your works’ submissions with a CV/biography, some still images (for video-art), links of videos/films/performances and pictures via e-mail to lucacurci@lucacurci.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The number of works you can submit is unlimited. The participation in the festival requires an entry fee only for selected artworks. Participation is open to: artists, architects and designers, associate groups and studios.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists interested in taking part in our shows, are free to be sponsored and supported by institutions, organizations, governments and their representers; the logos of their sponsors will be included in all the communication (digital and print) of the events. Artists are free to take part in one or more events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To take part in the selection, send your works’ submissions with a CV/biography, some still images (for video-art), links of videos/films/performances and pictures of artworks by e-mail to lucacurci@lucacurci.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The participation includes the following services&lt;br/&gt;– exhibition space dedicated to the artist’s works&lt;br/&gt;– assisting with customs formalities, international shipping and local transport&lt;br/&gt;– assisting in finding accommodation for artist&lt;br/&gt;– the design and the printing of invitation cards, posters&lt;br/&gt;– the global and local press office, publicity, press, banners, totem, etc.&lt;br/&gt;– the realization of the exhibition website and dedicated press releases&lt;br/&gt;– mounting and dismounting of the exhibition&lt;br/&gt;– exhibitions opening event with drinks and food&lt;br/&gt;– a one day dedicated presentation, talk or workshop focusing on the artist’s career&lt;br/&gt;– a dedicated interview published on ITSLIQUID website and spread on our social networks &lt;br/&gt;– providing services and drinks for small meetings at the exhibition places for invited guests&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists, photographers, video makers, architects and performers are invited to submit their works. To take part in the selection, send your works’ submissions with a CV/biography, some still images (for video-art), links of videos/films/performances and pictures via e-mail to lucacurci@lucacurci.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The number of works you can submit is unlimited. The participation in the festival requires an entry fee only for selected artworks. Participation is open to: artists, architects and designers, associate groups and studios.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists interested in taking part in our shows, are free to be sponsored and supported by institutions, organizations, governments and their representers; the logos of their sponsors will be included in all the communication (digital and print) of the events. Artists are free to take part in one or more events.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/323bc39d-26a5-402b-9069-69ea97891245" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ac4e4ddd-47db-46b8-9c9e-55ebf6d6d388</id><title>6/30 - Submit for 3 paid exhibitions in NYC Class A office rotation</title><updated>2019-05-29T13:16:59.626321+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Easeum&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.easeum.co/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Easeum's mission is to make art newly available in every communal space, empowering creativity and generating economic growth in the communities we serve. Easeum clients are commercial real estate managers seeking curated exhibitions in their space(s) featuring inspiring art from individual artists, galleries, grant-giving-foundations, and private collectors. Proceeds from pieces selected for these engagements are shared with art providers, after costs of operations and installation. This is an opportunity to have your collection displayed (and possibly sold) while collecting cash for your participation. All work will be insured.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Easeum is seeking proposals from curators, galleries, and/or artists for exhibitions at three Manhattan Class A Office lobbies/common areas.  This engagement includes 3 separate building lobbies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each is approximately 6,000 sq ft with at least four walls being over 30' long. Proposals from solo shows all the way to larger group exhibitions will be considered. Each show should have a unique theme apparent to building tenants.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibitions will run for 3+ months in each building before moving to the next. Thus this engagement will range from 9-12 months starting late summer to early fall 2019. Reception events will be held at each location at the beginning of the 3 month period. They will ideally feature appearances from the relevant exhibitors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. high resolution photos&lt;br/&gt;2. piece dimensions&lt;br/&gt;3. wholesale price&lt;br/&gt;4. retail price&lt;br/&gt;5. location for any necessary pickup&lt;br/&gt;6. other installation specifics helpful for logistics cost estimating (weight for sculpture, electricity/tech requirements for installations, etc)&lt;br/&gt;7. artist name(s)&lt;br/&gt;8. your contact information including organization, title, email, and phone&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please also tell us if any of the materials are toxic or hazardous. There are no restrictions on the subject matter but Easeum clients will have final approval rights for each piece.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ac4e4ddd-47db-46b8-9c9e-55ebf6d6d388" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>