<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-05T19:15:43-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>b38403ab-12e7-4c86-8920-e7e82ac11ab1</id><title>6/30 - Open Call for Midnight Moment—Chance to show moving-image art on 60+ screens in Times Square!</title><updated>2019-04-05T19:15:43.119089+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="TSq.org/Arts"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts invites you to submit original moving-image artwork to Midnight Moment, the world’s largest, longest-running digital art exhibition synchronized on electronic billboards and Newspaper Kiosks throughout Times Square nightly from 11:57pm to midnight. &lt;br/&gt;Deadline for submissions: June 30, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;Learn more about submission guidelines here: TSq.org/MMSubmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open applications for the Midnight Moment program are accepted through the online Slideroom portal. Please review submission guidelines and access the portal here: TSq.org/MMSubmission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have any questions about your proposal, please email Public Art Manager Hillary Dvorkin at hdvorkin@tsq.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b38403ab-12e7-4c86-8920-e7e82ac11ab1" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d954d03b-29c4-426d-ba20-5e54e73d83d5</id><title>5/3 - MASTER PIECES: 13th Annual International MFA/MA Exhibition</title><updated>2019-04-05T19:15:43.119051+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/03/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/masterpieces"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open to current graduate students and MFA/MA degree recipients since January 2018.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Every year Manifest offers an opportunity just for graduate students to exhibit at our gallery in Cincinnati. This 13th installment of the Master Pieces project will continue to reveal the intensity and professionalism of students working towards their terminal academic degree in the field of art or design. Often the most exceptional work comes out of these artists’ immersion in their culture of study and intellectual pursuit. Manifest’s goal, therefore, is to select works that set the standard of quality that the artist is expected to maintain throughout his or her professional career and justify the degree of Master. The full-color hardcover Manifest Exhibition Annual publication, a 'yearbook' for the season, will serve as a visual documentation of these artists’ own benchmarks for years to come.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Up to THREE of Manifest's exhibit spaces will be devoted to the Master Pieces 13 exhibition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To view the full prospects or enter work visit &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/masterpieces." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email questions to info@manifestgallery.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d954d03b-29c4-426d-ba20-5e54e73d83d5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>12b531ac-ec5c-4ba1-9ddc-cbcd67810f86</id><title>5/15 - ArtWorks Call to Artists!</title><updated>2019-04-05T19:15:43.118992+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtWorks, The Naomi Cohain Foundation&lt;br/&gt;📍 Englewood, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.artworksfoundation.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello from ArtWorks,&lt;br/&gt;I am writing to you to see if you would be willing to donate a 10 x 10 inch unframed work on paper for our upcoming Square Fair event on June 6th at the White Space Gallery, 555 W. 25th St., NYC.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ArtWorks, is a not-for-profit organization that brings artists and art supplies to children in our 50 hospitals in New York and New Jersey.  We have been providing creative opportunities to children with chronic and life-limiting illness and their families for 17 years.  When you get a chance, please take a look at our website listed below to learn more about ArtWorks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This will be our first art fair event and we think that it will be a wonderful time for all.  If you are able to contribute a piece, we would be most grateful.  Please also feel free to forward the attached Call to Artists information to your artists friends.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have any questions or would like additional information about ArtWorks or the event, please feel free to contact me at any time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thank you very much for your consideration.&lt;br/&gt;Fran&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please email fran@artworksfoundation.org and she will send you the Submission Form and instructions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/12b531ac-ec5c-4ba1-9ddc-cbcd67810f86" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>