<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-13T18:48:28-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>baf7223d-18ff-4d2c-8ae1-bf0e8a9290f7</id><title>3/22 - Open Call for Solo Exhibitions and Curatorial Projects</title><updated>2019-02-13T18:48:28.060525+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;CUE Art Foundation&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/22/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://cueartfoundation.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CUE’s Open Calls provide artists and emerging curators the opportunity and necessary resources to realize an exhibition at CUE’s storefront gallery in East Chelsea, New York.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each year, a panel of established artists and curators select two solo exhibitions and one curatorial project to be realized at CUE. Finalists are paired with a member of the selection panel, who works with them as a mentor throughout the process of planning and mounting the exhibition. CUE provides institutional guidance, generous honoraria, a shipping budget, and an accompanying exhibition catalogue with a critical essay by a participant in CUE's Art Critic Mentoring Program. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications are accepted once annually in the spring. The deadline for the current Open Call is March 22, 2019.    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SOLO EXHIBITION INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;CUE's Solo Exhibition Open Call is for artists who:&lt;br/&gt;-Have not had a solo show in a commercial NYC gallery within the last five years&lt;br/&gt;-Do not have current, consistent commercial gallery representation in the United States&lt;br/&gt;-Are not currently enrolled in a degree program&lt;br/&gt;-Have a demonstrated, consistent studio practice outside an academic setting for three or more years&lt;br/&gt;-Must currently live and work in the United States&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;-The exhibition program is open to artists working in all disciplines.&lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to artists who present ideas or topics that are not well-represented in the commercial sector.&lt;br/&gt;-CUE strongly encourages applications that contribute to our ongoing commitment to diversity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What Finalists receive:&lt;br/&gt;-Five-week solo exhibition at CUE Art Foundation in 2020&lt;br/&gt;-Curatorial support/mentoring from an established artist or curator on the selection panel&lt;br/&gt;-Opportunities to develop related public programming &lt;br/&gt;-32-page full color catalogue with essay produced through the Art Critic Mentoring Program and a statement by the curator&lt;br/&gt;-$5,000 unrestricted honorarium&lt;br/&gt;-An art shipping and art handling budget&lt;br/&gt;-Opening reception&lt;br/&gt;-Press materials and PR support &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CURATORIAL PROJECT INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;-Proposals must be conceptually rigorous and focus on artists, projects, and themes that are innovative, challenging, and engaging.&lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to proposals that demonstrate a creative approach to curatorial research methods and the exhibition plan, as well as those that present ideas or topics that are not well-represented in the commercial sector.&lt;br/&gt;-The proposal must include four or more artists, half of whom must qualify as under-recognized (no gallery representation and no solo exhibitions in a major venue within the past five years).&lt;br/&gt;-Curators may not include their own work in the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;-The curator and all proposed artists must live and work in the United States.    &lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to those in the beginning stages of their curatorial careers.&lt;br/&gt;-CUE strongly encourages applications that contribute to our ongoing commitment to diversity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What the opportunity includes:&lt;br/&gt;-Five-week exhibition at CUE Art Foundation in 2020&lt;br/&gt;-Curatorial support/mentoring from an established artist or curator on the selection panel&lt;br/&gt;-Opportunities to develop related public programming &lt;br/&gt;-Full color catalogue with essay produced through the Art Critic Mentoring Program&lt;br/&gt;-$2,500 unrestricted honorarium&lt;br/&gt;-$2,500 to divide amongst the participating artists and program speakers&lt;br/&gt;-$2,000 production budget&lt;br/&gt;-An art shipping and art handling budget&lt;br/&gt;-Opening reception&lt;br/&gt;-Press materials and PR support&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at &lt;a href="http://cueartfoundation.org/open-call" target="_blank"&gt;http://cueartfoundation.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, please visit our website or email Lilly Hern-Fondation, Programs Associate: lilly@cueartfoundation.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/baf7223d-18ff-4d2c-8ae1-bf0e8a9290f7" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6002bcf2-7474-40d6-a62f-77a71dcd3655</id><title>3/16 - Crystal Park Open Call for outdoor artwork</title><updated>2019-02-13T18:48:28.060487+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Crystal Park&lt;br/&gt;📍 Holmes, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/16/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.crystalpark.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artwork on the rocks along the trail - A creative look for the rock trail&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The rock trail starts from the Crystal Park gate and is about 0.6 mile with rocks placed along the two sides of the trail. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Artists are invited to propose artwork to be placed on/with the rocks as long as the artwork doesn’t obstruct the trail nor cause any safety concern. &lt;br/&gt;•	Please consider the nature outdoor setting. Materials that can withstand the weather and be integrated with the environment are preferred. &lt;br/&gt;•	Selected artist will have access to woodshop and metal shop to fabricate the work if needed. (Fabrication facility location: Flushing, Queens, NY)&lt;br/&gt;•	Crystal Park will provide assistance for the artist to install the work. &lt;br/&gt;•	Artist fee: $5,000&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Please submit the following documents:&lt;br/&gt;o	Drawings or/and rendering images/videos of the proposed artwork&lt;br/&gt;o	Project statement&lt;br/&gt;o	Detailed description of the artwork&lt;br/&gt;o	Artist bio and resume&lt;br/&gt;o	Artwork sample images (Maximum 20 images in jpeg, each under 5MB)&lt;br/&gt;o	Estimated budget&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Email the submission to &lt;br/&gt;info@crystalpark.org by March 16th 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Images and videos of the rock trail:&lt;br/&gt;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1ZaCmYh3Lk7Aw7k4hfK3ntRn8BtpC6MA-&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information about Crystal Park:&lt;br/&gt;www.crystalpark.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please address any question to: &lt;br/&gt;info@crystalpark.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;info@crystalpark.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6002bcf2-7474-40d6-a62f-77a71dcd3655" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f465d717-f518-4c8d-8b02-6eb2966416e3</id><title>3/10 - OPEN CALL: Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists</title><updated>2019-02-13T18:48:28.060423+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Friend of The Artist&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.friendoftheartist.com/application/?utm_source=NYFA&amp;amp;utm_medium=NYFA&amp;amp;utm_campaign=9"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FOA is a publication dedicated to elevating the work of emerging artists around the world. Our publication releases as a hardcover art book every quarter. It includes the work of artists who work in a variety of mediums, informative articles, and interviews. Accepted artists will have a four page spread of their work, information, and artist statement. Volume 9 will be juried by Alice Bonno, Erika B. Hess, Masha Vlasova, and FOA staff.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Volume 9 will be printed in hardback on premium color paper and are available online through booksellers like Amazon, Barnes and Noble, and are available in catalogs for libraries and bookstore distribution.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details of the Volume 9 Open Call:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Winners Receive&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3 works published in Volume 9, complimentary digital copy of publication, social media post of work, Discounts on publications for family and friends, and free digital access to future publications&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$25 for 5 Images&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;March 8, 2019 (midnight, CST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists of all academic disciples are welcome to apply. This includes painting, sculpture, photography, installation, new media, and performance art. Please do not submit videos since we are unable to publish.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guest Jurors&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Alice Bonnot&lt;br/&gt;Erika B. Hess&lt;br/&gt;Masha Vlasova&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Alice Bonnot is an independent curator and art consultant based in London. She is the co-founding director of Picnic, a contemporary art space occupying a long window in the Aylesham Centre in Peckham, London, and the founding director of the Zone d’Utopie Temporaire (Z.U.T.) residency programme, a nomadic annual residency addressing the notion of Utopia as a vehicle for artistic and critical comment. With this residency she curated exhibitions and events in Paris, London, Athens and Lisbon.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As an independent curator Alice organised a broad range of exhibitions for galleries, institutions and artist-run spaces. Her current exhibition Hyper Mesh(18 Jan – 23 Feb 2019) at Assembly Point, London, is an exhibition that brings together new work from eight international artists; Jonathan Baldock, Pauline Bastard, fleuryfontaine, Holly Hendry, Jessie Makinson, Morgan Wills and Fani Parali. The exhibition explores contemporary notions of identity, and sets out to examine how identity structures could be re-imagined or reconstructed. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Previous exhibitions include: Engine, Picnic, London, 2018,Bored but secured, Wozen, Lisbon, 2018,  Acts of disruption, The Concept Space, London, 2018, A series of pocket Utopias, Yellow Brick and Snehta, Athens, 2017, Right Through You, The Koppel Project Hive, London, 2017, Le corps comme activateur d’art numérique, Le Carreau du Temple, Paris, 2015, Prix Canson finalists, Palais de Tokyo, Paris / co-curated with Mr Laurent Boudier, 2015. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Erika B Hess  is a painter based in Columbus, OH recognized for her use and interest in color. Hess’s work has been exhibited nationally including Prince Street Gallery in NYC, Last Projects in Los Angles, CA, and Boston Center for the Arts in Boston, MA. In 2017, she had two solo exhibitions, “The Line Between the Past and the Present,” at the Musa Collective, Allston MA and “Viewing Light,” at Newton Free Library, Newton, MA. Her work has been featured in various publications including, Poets and Artists, Fresh Paint, Charles River Journal and Post Industrial Complex, a book released by the Museum of Contemporary Art Detroit. Her work was selected by John Seed to be featured in, “Fifty Memorable Artists 2015”. She has served on panels such as Cleveland Institute of Art’s, “Feminism Now: Exposing the Truth”, was a visiting juror for Dayton Visual Art Center’s 2016-2018 biennial, and is a recurring juror for the Walker Art MFA Prize at Boston University. Hess is a co-founder of Musa Collective, an artist collective in Boston and is the creator of I Like Your Work podcast, a podcast dedicated to interviewing artists, curators and collectors. Hess received her MFA from Boston University.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Masha Vlasova is an interdisciplinary artist, filmmaker, and educator. She holds a BFA from the Cooper Union and an MFA from Yale School of Art. She is a recipient the Fulbright Fellowship in Filmmaking, Alice Kimball Fellowship and the JUNCTURE Art and Human Rights Fellowship at Yale Law School. Her works have been exhibited and screened at Smack Mellon, Anthology Archives, and Abrons Arts Center in New York, Vox Populi and Temple University in Philadelphia, Carpenter Centerfor the Visual Artsat Harvard University among others. Her latest curatorial project “Women Filmmakers at the Intersection of Documentary, Video Art, and Avant Garde,” premiered at Indiana University Cinema in Bloomington, IN Fall of 2018. Her forthcoming essay about monument rotation will be published in a collection titled Monument Culture: International Perspectives on the Future of Monuments in a Changing World by the American Association for State and Local History/Rowman &amp; Littlefield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at friendoftheartist.com/application&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Email contact@friendoftheartist.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f465d717-f518-4c8d-8b02-6eb2966416e3" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>