<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-20T16:14:36-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>bdcb0a67-aa83-4afb-be31-f28cc8687a35</id><title>3/17 - Far and Wide National Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-02-20T16:14:36.729614+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Woodstock Artists Association &amp;amp; Museum&lt;br/&gt;📍 Woodstock, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.woodstockart.org/art-submission-calendar/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open to all artists living and working in the United States.&lt;br/&gt;Online applications only.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Kimberly Camp, former President and CEO of the Barnes Foundation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists are invited to submit up to 5 works that are innovative in form and content or that have been created within the parameters of traditional genres but nevertheless break new ground. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: May 11 - June 9&lt;br/&gt;Artists Reception: Saturday, May 18, 4-6pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Awards&lt;br/&gt;- The Arthur Harris Best in Show Award ($500)&lt;br/&gt;- Nicholas Buhalis Award for Artistic Excellence in Abstract/Figurative or Figurative Work ($500)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Media &amp; Size Limitations:&lt;br/&gt;Works in the following media will be considered:&lt;br/&gt;Painting&lt;br/&gt;Drawing&lt;br/&gt;Original Prints (Traditional and digital. No reproductions of works existing in other media.)&lt;br/&gt;Photography&lt;br/&gt;Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2-D works should not exceed 36 inches on the longest dimension (38 inches including frame). &lt;br/&gt;3-D work must be no greater than 36 x 36 x 36 inches&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/bdcb0a67-aa83-4afb-be31-f28cc8687a35" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>643ee409-ca18-4ce5-a9ce-9abd539801a0</id><title>4/10 - Open Call to raise money for women immigrants and refugees</title><updated>2019-02-20T16:14:36.729584+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;FeLT NYC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.feltnyc.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you an artist and want to help immigrant women and refugees? Do you believe that education can empower individuals and communities? Do you want some exposure of your work at the same time? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are FeLT NYC: a community organization dedicated to supporting women immigrants and refugees through FREE English language courses and a variety of practical workshops. It is all run by volunteers and donations. Please visit www.feltnyc.org for more information and pictures. You can also look us up on Twitter, Instagram and Facebook&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FeLT NYC is calling for artists to DONATE artwork for a silent auction for its fundraiser on April 25th, 2019 at The Parish of Calvary – St. George’s near Gramercy Park. This would enable us to collect funds to keep programs running for immigrant and refugee women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to help immigrant and refugee women, please follow the submission instructions below:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The theme of the fundraiser is We Are America: Today's immigrants and refugees.  Please take this theme in any direction you would like. We accept any work that relate to this theme or FeLT's core mission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please submit the following to director@feltnyc.org :&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- 1-3 images.  (only .JPGs, please!). &lt;br/&gt;- Please include title, medium, dimensions, and price. &lt;br/&gt;- Artist statement and bio&lt;br/&gt;- Link to your website&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE is April 10th.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We will contact artists that get chosen on April 16th and will give further information about drop off and other logistics. If your work gets selected, please make sure it is ready to hang. We have staff to do the hanging, but if you want to be involved in the process, we you are free to hang your own pieces! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are looking forward to your submission!&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/643ee409-ca18-4ce5-a9ce-9abd539801a0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>46d7036f-237d-4d6d-b2ac-fde83682c697</id><title>3/10 - 4th Annual Drawing Marathon: Entrants Sought</title><updated>2019-02-20T16:14:36.729548+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Binghamton University&lt;br/&gt;📍 Binghamton, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Drawing&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ABOUT: Co-sponsored by the Department of Art and Design, United Health Services, the Binghamton University Fleishman Career Center and the Vice Provost’s Office for Undergraduate Education. The Drawing Marathon offers Binghamton University students, alumni and community artists (18 and over) a unique opportunity to compete for 24 hours to produce a finished figure drawing in the museum. It is a chance to discover one’s artistic second wind, when powerful creative energy is released at the very time physical energy diminishes. This second wind reinvigorates both mind and body, and can result in a rewarding, even spectacular artistic creation. &lt;br/&gt;WHEN: Friday, April 5, 10:00 am–Saturday, April 6, 10:00 am (24 hours with regular breaks).&lt;br/&gt;EVENT DETAILS: A clothed, live model, basic charcoal drawing materials, paper (72” x 48”), and easel will be provided. Light refreshments will be provided. Participating artists are responsible for all other expenses incurred, e.g., transportation, special foods. Artists are urged to consider the mental and physical aspects of this endeavor and must feel that they can safely participate. Dressing in layers of comfortable clothing is recommended.  The event is held in a public setting so that visitors may observe artists at work throughout the  24-hour marathon period. Participants are expected to spend most of the 24 hours in the museum drawing and taking frequent scheduled breaks. &lt;br/&gt;AWARDS:  Two cash prizes will be awarded on the morning of Saturday, April 6: the jury prize of $1000 and the people’s prize of $500. The people’s prize will be awarded on the basis of qualitative comments received by visitors to the marathon as well as statements posted on the Binghamton University Art Museum Facebook age. In addition to these prizes the Binghamton University Fine Art Society (BUFAS) will give a basket of art supplies to one artist demonstrating the most creative or  innovative approach to drawing.&lt;br/&gt;TIMELINE:  The competition will commence Friday, April 5 at 10:00 am. At the end of every hour there will be 15-minute break for the model and participants. Every four hours there will be a 30-minute break. An award ceremony will follow shortly after the competition concludes on Saturday, April 6 at 10:00 am. The drawings will remain on view in the museum through Tuesday, April 9. Participants must retrieve their finished drawings by Saturday, April 13.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION: Artists should send one pdf file with up to 10 samples of their best figure drawings, along with the following contact information: name, address, phone number and email. Please provide answers to the following questions: &lt;br/&gt;~ Are you comfortable with media (video and&lt;br/&gt;photography) documenting you and your artwork&lt;br/&gt;if selected?&lt;br/&gt;~ Do you have interesting a story, a personal&lt;br/&gt;challenge you’ve overcome, or anything special&lt;br/&gt;we should be aware of?&lt;br/&gt;Send your application to: drawing@binghamton.edu. There is no fee. The jury will select the strongest 10-12 competitors among the applicants. Only 10-12 artists will be selected and invited to compete. The competition is open to all students, alumni and community artists (aged 18 and over). The deadline for submitting an application is March 10. No applications will be accepted after this date.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/46d7036f-237d-4d6d-b2ac-fde83682c697" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>583d1e55-7ba2-4849-8550-dfcdff09e4d4</id><title>2/21 - Call for Art! Puffin Cultural Forum, &amp;quot;Measured Hate&amp;quot;</title><updated>2019-02-20T16:14:36.729517+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Puffin Cultural Forum&lt;br/&gt;📍 Teaneck, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://PuffinCulturalForum.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Puffin Cultural Forum seeks submissions for artwork for our upcoming exhibition "Measured Hate." Submissions must be received as soon as possible due to time limitations. The exhibition addresses the increasing reports of hate crimes and incidents in the US since 2016. FBI hate crime reports were up 17% in 2017, marking a rise for the third year in a row. FBI's statistics are an undercounted representation of hate crime trends and 2018 stats are due November of this year. In midst of the discordant political atmosphere, these statistics confirm what many of us have already felt and known: speech and acts of bias are rising around us. Puffin Cultural Forum’s  exhibition, "Measured Hate" seeks to take a focused look at the national and local climate behind the rise of hate and bias incidents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission of artwork of all media will be accepted including 2 dimensional pieces, sculptures not exceeding 5 feet in any direction, video, etc. Most accepted works will be 2 dimensional pieces which can be displayed on our gallery walls not exceed 5 feet in height. All submission have to be emailed to alee@puffinfoundation.org. Please provide your name, email address, phone number, address, title, medium, dimensions, value of artwork. Optional submission of artist’ statement or comment will be accepted.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/583d1e55-7ba2-4849-8550-dfcdff09e4d4" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f7f9e5ea-7db8-4301-b2d1-26ce96e54e43</id><title>2/28 - OyG Projects: Open Call for Two Solo Exhibitions</title><updated>2019-02-20T16:14:36.729482+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ortega y Gasset Projects&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/28/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.oygprojects.com/open-call-2019"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ortega y Gasset Projects is pleased to announce an Open Call for TWO Solo Exhibitions to open in September of 2019: one in the main gallery space at OyG and one in The Skirt, OyG's dedicated space for site-specific installation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Both opportunities will include an opening reception on Saturday, September 14, 2019, $350 honorarium for each artist/proposal, and one programmed event (an artist talk or a closing event), and will be promoted on OyG social media outlets. OyG Co-Directors will work with the artists and make studio visits leading up to the opening of the exhibitions, if possible. The artists are required to fully participate in the exhibitions' installation and deinstallation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Visual artists of all disciplines (and geographical locations) are encouraged to apply. The artists will be selected by the OyG Co-Directors based on the quality of their work and commitment to their practice. Artists are highly encouraged to specify which space they'd like to exhibit in, the main gallery space or The Skirt. The OyG Co-Directors will make the final decision.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An alternate list of candidates/runners-up will be posted on our website and considered for future programing at the gallery. Past/future exhibition artists that we discovered from our past Open Calls include: Patrice Helmar, Jihyun Hong, Familien Iglesias,  Carl E. Hazlewood, Rose Nestler, Norm Paris, Ben Pederson, Padma Rajendran, Adam Liam Rose, Winnie Sidharta and Kuldeep Singh.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To see images of the space:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.oygprojects.com/spatial-specs&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Application opens: January 14, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: Monday, February 28, 2019, midnight&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notification: May 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition install: August 31, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Opening reception: Saturday, September 14, 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition ends: October 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ortega y Gasset Projects is an artist-run gallery founded in 2013, located within the Old American Can Factory building in the Gowanus section of Brooklyn. OACF is a 24-hour access building accessible by the D, R, N, W, F, G trains. For more information about OyG click here. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;OyG Co-Directors:&lt;br/&gt;Eleanna Anagnos (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Clare Britt (Chicago, IL)&lt;br/&gt;Catherine Haggarty (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Eric Hibit (Queens, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Will Hutnick (Wassaic, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Nickola Pottinger (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Zahar Vaks (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Lauren Whearty (Philadelphia, PA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to apply:&lt;br/&gt;https://ortegaygassetprojects.submittable.com/submit/130768/open-call-2019-two-solo-exhibitions-at-oyg-projects&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMAGES:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;10 images of work including: title, year, media and dimensions &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Size requirements:  Images (up to 5MB each), Video (up to 250MB each), Audio (up to 30MB each)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CV:&lt;br/&gt;2 pages max&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;REFERENCES:&lt;br/&gt;Please provide us with two references who can talk about your work and practice: name, title/organization, relationship, email address. We will only contact these individuals if need be.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PROPOSAL:&lt;br/&gt;Please describe your work and what you envision as your solo exhibition. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some things to consider: Why do you want a solo exhibition at OyG? What does this opportunity mean to you? If you're applying for the Skirt, please consider how your work will respond to/interact with the specific space.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(200 words max).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please email oygsubmissions@gmail.com if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f7f9e5ea-7db8-4301-b2d1-26ce96e54e43" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3bf628bc-a595-4e08-9415-54aa91b7aca9</id><title>4/11 - Call for Artists - Seeking Under-Represented Artists</title><updated>2019-02-20T16:14:36.729445+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;440 Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://440gallery.formstack.com/forms/artsy_application"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brooklyn, NY based 440 Gallery was formed in January of 2005 as an artist-run space and we are now looking to add three (3) new under-represented artists to our Artsy Gallery page for one year from May 1, 2019 - May 1 2020. This call is open to artists working in all media, nationally and internationally not currently represented by a gallery. Artsy.net is an internationally based platform dedicated to sales of art online. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Non-Refundable Entry Fee: $35&lt;br/&gt;Entry Deadline: April 11, midnight EST&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;Currently be a practicing artist, making new work&lt;br/&gt;Not currently represented by a gallery&lt;br/&gt;Must have a website&lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement&lt;br/&gt;CV&lt;br/&gt;Upload a minimum of 10 images to start profile&lt;br/&gt;440 Gallery will take 30% commission on all sales&lt;br/&gt;Artist is required to pack and ship artwork (buyer pays for shipping and handling, artist will be reimbursed for expenses)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s Benefits:&lt;br/&gt;Up to 75 images uploaded to the Artsy platform&lt;br/&gt;Dedicated sales director updating profile and handling sales&lt;br/&gt;Artsy is the top read artist magazine, 2.5 – 3 million unique visitors per month&lt;br/&gt;Great way to reach and build relationships with collectors &lt;br/&gt;Artsy works with the Art Genome Project, an algorithm search engine that recommends works to collectors based on their preferences&lt;br/&gt;Artsy proactively markets to collectors based on their likes&lt;br/&gt;Every Sunday, Artsy sends emails to their collectors, they will alert them to new work that is uploaded&lt;br/&gt;All artists on site are represented by gallery partners on Artsy, they do not allow artists to sign up individually&lt;br/&gt;Promotion in the 440 newsletter (more than 5,000 subscribers)&lt;br/&gt;Participation in one online exclusive group show&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application can be found here: &lt;a href="https://440gallery.formstack.com/forms/artsy_application" target="_blank"&gt;https://440gallery.formstack.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All media will be considered for representation, open to national and international artists.  A minimum of five (5) artworks must be uploaded for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For questions, please contact:&lt;br/&gt;Amy Williams&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Director&lt;br/&gt;info@440gallery.com&lt;br/&gt;718.499.3844&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3bf628bc-a595-4e08-9415-54aa91b7aca9" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6009c62e-690b-4892-89a4-723e6cf44939</id><title>3/4 - ARTIST CALLS:   NYC AND  LOS ANGELES -  CHELSEA and LA FASHION WEEK</title><updated>2019-02-20T16:14:36.729379+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Six Summit Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Ivoryton, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/04/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.sixsummitgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES- Exploding Downtown Los Angeles- DTLA  Fashion Week - Six Summit Gallery curates&lt;br/&gt;Art Hearts Fashion at&lt;br/&gt;The Majestic Downtown:  650 South Spring St. Los Angeles CA , 90014&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NEW YORK - Scroll down call for info: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The largest fine art and fashion platform in LA. Multiple inclusive elegant and dynamic shows with attendance in the thousands.  A diverse crowd combining art and fashion draws an international crowd of  artists, designers, and celebrities.   A beautiful combination of emerging and established talent connected to great causes.  The Majestic Downtown is an iconic filming location and event venue that is recognized as being a historical masterpiece in DTLA since 1924. With a combined 25,000+ square feet and stunning historically preserved ambiance, The Majestic has 40 foot high Italian ceilings, arched windows, sculpted marble columns and original marble floors lend a rich historical beauty. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted Artists receive complimentary admission to All shows All days for themselves and a guest. We are encouraging artists who will attend the shows and participate.  See below for more details. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Open Call to, Installers, Interactive, Decorative, Artists, Sculptors, &lt;br/&gt;Photographers, Painters-SIX SUMMIT GALLERY WITH ART HEARTS FASHION! at the newly renovated splendid Majestic.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This venue is large. We are encouraging sculptures, decorative, installation, interactive as well as very Large art.  We can absorb a lot of pieces.  No size limit if it can fit on your easel or free stand.  You may not scratch the floors. Seating for fashion shows  is not guaranteed Nor necessary to enjoy and participate in the production. Call or text (917)-573-0029 with direct questions or email Fashion@sixsummitgallery.com.  Do not call The Majestic  or Art Hearts Fashion. &lt;br/&gt;Art does not have to be directly fashion related. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art Hearts Fashion to Break New Ground with over 20 Designers in DTLA—Revolutionary bi-coastal fashion platform Art Hearts Fashion partners with multi-platform fine art concern: Six Summit Gallery. A favorite among press and celebrities alike, this season Art Hearts Fashion brings an impressive lineup of over 20 acclaimed designers to the catwalk during 4 full days of runway shows.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EMAIL SUBMISSIONS ONLY TO&lt;br/&gt;fashion@sixsummitgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You are required to bring easels for your setup.  Wooden is preferred or you must put pads under to prevent scratching.  Your work will not be permitted if this is not accomplished.  This is an exquisite platform with many friends and artists whom you may know.  We reserve the right to disallow you from the show at any time.   Thank You&lt;br/&gt;Shows dates and times will be listed here:&lt;br/&gt;http://artheartsfashion.com&lt;br/&gt;...........................................................................................................................................................................................&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NEW YORK CITY-  HIGHLINE OPEN STUDIOS GRAND TOUR IN CHELSEA AT &lt;br/&gt;THE LEO HOUSE - 332 W 23RD ST, NYC (between 8th and 9th Ave)&lt;br/&gt;Spring Celebration- participation in Highline Open Studios tour at the coolest NYC hotel/guesthouse you may have never heard of, on legendary 23rd ST west of the Chelsea Hotel and at the beginning of historic Chelsea Art District. We will have two opening receptions March 9th and 10th from 12:30 - 5:30PM at 332 W 23rd St at The Leo House, which was established in 1889 by Pope Leo XIII whose miter and 8 other antiquities were recently  featured at The Met show "Heavenly Bodies: Fashion and the Catholic Imagination" with Vogue, Cardinal Gianfranco Ravasi, Donatella Versace, and Anna Wintour. We will be accepting both religious (non ironic) and non religious art. Prizes will be for your art will be to keep it hanging for  a minimum 4 week temporary residence at The Leo House. We will be donating portions of our proceeds of sales to The Leo House. Artists receive 50% of sales.  If you wish to donate all or portions of your submissions please specify upon submitting.......we are also taking 100% donated art items to be featured on our website as part of our GALA in November.   See below for submission instructions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EMAIL LEOHOUSE@SIXSUMMITGALLERY with any questions.  Please do not call The Leo House or Highline Open Studios&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES-&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBLE WORK: Installations, Decorative, Interactive, Paintings, Photos works in all media. This show is open to all artists regardless of place of residence however you must deliver in person.  Live painters will have a separate entry process.  Please email fashion@sixsummitgallery.com with live proposals. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS:All work will be judged by email entry via fashion@sixsummitgallery.com. You MUST write [YOUR NAME]” IN THE SUBJECT OF EMAIL. YOUR NAME MUST BE THE SAME ON YOUR CREDIT/DEBIT CARD Example: Subject: FASHION SUBMISSION: John Doe. Files must be in .jpg format, 300 dpi, max 900 pixels in any dimension. File name should correspond to the title of the piece. PUT title, medium, artist, price, and size as JPEG FILE EXTENSION NAME.! . No accepted work may be removed prior to the show’s conclusion. ALL work must be for sale. You may not make holes in walls. Sculptors must bring their own pedestals or free standing is OK You are required to make your own labels. They must include Title, Medium,Price, and Your Name, with instagram tag, @sixsummitgallery  and on bottom "To purchase now  call or text Leo 917-573-0029 and we will come to you - www.sixsummitgallery.com"  clearly visible.  Purchases will take place during the show on our website- Customers can leave with art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Show Committee reserves the right to disallow the exhibition of any work which, in the opinion of the Committee, is considered detrimental to the good public image of the show and its sponsors, which is too fragile to handle, or which is not accurately represented by the photo submitted. Six Summit Gallery, We reserve the right to photograph work or use submitted images for your and our publicity. ENTRY FEES: Easily click on www.sixsummitgallery.com online store and go to ONLINE STORE-EVENTS SUBMISSION section and choose 2 submissions and one guest for  $50. Up to 5 submissions and 4 guests for $75-  Please call with any special situations. Artist receives 60% on accepted sold work. We may allow a standard shared discount up to 10% without notifying artist. We encourage artists to invite clients to the show. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;QUESTIONS CAN BE EMAILED ONLY TO: Fashion@sixsummitgallery.com Include your  Call Back Number!&lt;br/&gt;DO NOT CALL OR EMAIL THE MAJESTIC OR ART HEARTS FASHION,  DATES and TIMES Subject to Change AND WILL BE UPDATED ON OUR WEBSITE IN THE ARTIST CALL SECTION........www.sixsummitgallery.com &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE TO SUBMIT IS MARCH 5TH- (it may be extended a few days even though this ad will expire on March 5th- check the artist call section on www.sixsummitgallery.com for updates). &lt;br/&gt;Delivery: MARCH 21ST  – 3:30-4:15 - stay and help arrange art.&lt;br/&gt;Removal:  MARCH 24TH - as soon as last show starts up until midnight.&lt;br/&gt;...........................................................................................................................................................................................&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NEW YORK&lt;br/&gt;Submit  entries to leohouse@sixsummitgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS:All work will be judged by email entry via leohouse@sixsummitgallery.com. You MUST write [YOUR NAME]” IN THE SUBJECT OF EMAIL. YOUR NAME MUST BE THE SAME ON YOUR CREDIT/DEBIT CARD Example: Subject: FASHION SUBMISSION: John Doe. Files must be in .jpg format, 300 dpi, max 900 pixels in any dimension. File name should correspond to the title of the piece. PUT title, medium, artist, price, and size as JPEG FILE EXTENSION NAME.! . No accepted work may be removed prior to the show’s conclusion. ALL work must be for sale.  Sculptors must bring their own pedestals or free standing is OK (We also have room for sculpture in the outdoor garden- please specify if your work can be outside)  You are required to make your own labels. They must include Title, Medium,Price, and Your Name, www.sixsummitgallery.com – with call or text Leo 917-573-0029 clearly visible on the bottom below www.sixsummitgallery.com. Purchases will take place during the show on our website and ongoing for prize winners.- Customers can leave with art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Show Committee reserves the right to disallow the exhibition of any work or artist, which, in the opinion of the Committee, is considered detrimental to the good public image of the show and its sponsors, art which is too fragile to handle, or which is not accurately represented by the photo submitted. Six Summit Gallery,  We reserve the right to photograph work or use submitted images to help yours and our publicity. ENTRY FEES: Easily click on www.sixsummitgallery.com online store and go to ONLINE STORE-EVENTS SUBMISSION section and choose up to 5 submissions for $50 &lt;br/&gt;Please call 917-573-0029 with any special situations. Art must be wired and ready to hang and not exceed &lt;br/&gt;48" by 48". &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;QUESTIONS CAN BE EMAILED ONLY TO: leohouse@sixsummitgallery.com &lt;br/&gt;Include your Call Back Number!&lt;br/&gt;DO NOT CALL OR EMAIL THE LEO HOUSE&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE to Submit- March 4th&lt;br/&gt;Delivery: We will announce&lt;br/&gt;Removal:  Some artists on March 10th others will remain for month or more as prize.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6009c62e-690b-4892-89a4-723e6cf44939" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>