<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-28T02:16:57-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>4defa356-1f45-4c14-b40b-fe3840bbf5bf</id><title>7/15 - The Shape of Memories - Loft Artists 6th Annual Tri-State Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-05-28T02:16:57.771048+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Loft Artists Association&lt;br/&gt;📍 Stamford, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.loftartists.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This exhibition explores the theme of memory and the key role it plays in art. Most artists’ works, whether on a conscious or subconscious level, reflect certain personal experiences and histories. References to the past can be monumental, quotidian or intimate. Everyday objects or places take on new meaning depending on how they are interpreted or experienced. In Marcel Proust’s “Remembrance of Things Past,” the smell and taste of a madeleine cake triggers a flood of memories and transports the author to another time and experience in his life. The show will explore the various mnemonic devices artists use to create thought provoking connections and commentaries on the passage of time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Memory can be a very personal journey through one’s own timeline as well as a collective experience of togetherness. We are excited to offer this broad and very thought provoking theme for this exhibit. Work in all media will be considered, including collages or sculptures incorporating everyday found objects.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror / Curator: Arianne Faber Kolb, PhD is an art historian and independent curator. She was the Executive Co-Director of the Carriage Barn Arts Center in New Canaan, a curator in the J.Paul Getty Museum’s Paintings and Drawings Departments, and a researcher in the Paintings Department of the Metropolitan Museum of Art. She has curated numerous exhibitions and her published work includes a book on Jan Brueghel the Elder, articles on old master painting, exhibition catalogues of contemporary Cuban art, and two children’s books on New Canaan architecture and history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Entry Instructions:	Submitting entries for jurying will all be done through our website, loftartists.org. On our home page, you will see a button for “2019 Juried Exhibition – The Shape of Memories ”. That is the portal to our electronic entry system called EntryThingy. There is a form to sign up and log in, with videos explaining the process. All of the information for submitting will be posted there, and the interface is extremely simple. Payment is made there, through PayPal, at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4defa356-1f45-4c14-b40b-fe3840bbf5bf" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>