<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-12T21:15:52-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>6985bd3e-0fdd-43fa-889b-375f2f112714</id><title>5/1 - Become a West Elm LOCAL Artist</title><updated>2019-04-12T21:15:52.982541+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;West Elm&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://Www.westelm.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The West Elm Chelsea store is looking for New York-based artists to become a part of our Local program. As a featured maker your work will be displayed and sold in the heart of Chelsea, with a retailer committed to connecting our customer to independent artists and creators.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are currently curating a LOCAL wall art gallery, and looking for two-dimensional prints, paintings, drawings, or photography with a strong individual aesthetic and a commercial appeal. Ideal makers should be able to fulfill new orders from the store as work sells off the wall. Pricing for framed works should be under $750.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What is the West Elm LOCAL program?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At West Elm we believe in supporting great design and the power of making - from around the world to around the corner.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The West Elm LOCAL program began in 2013. The program launched as a new chapter in our commitment to quality craftsmanship and the communities where we work. West Elm LOCAL is all about supporting domestic manufacturing and stimulating local economies by tapping into the maker movement - supporting makers, artists and designers right in our own backyards.&lt;br/&gt;By creating a locally designed, locally made, locally sourced assortment in each of our stores, we’re establishing West Elm as an active community hub that offers a unique shopping experience. West Elm LOCAL anchors our customers by giving them a sense of their neighborhood and celebrating the place they call home.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Learn more about the program and find other LOCAL makers at &lt;a href="https://www.westelm.com/shop/local/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.westelm.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are looking forward to hearing from you New York!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit cover letter expressing your interest in this opportunity as well as a link to a current online portfolio or retail shop, including price ranges for your work. No jpegs or attachments please.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6985bd3e-0fdd-43fa-889b-375f2f112714" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>