<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-18T21:17:27-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>5de38678-ab8b-496c-980a-4ba566aac3f2</id><title>7/31 - Juried Exhibition &amp;quot;SHOW YOUR WORLD&amp;quot;</title><updated>2019-06-18T21:17:27.836381+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;RE:ARTISTE International Art Organization&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $39.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.reartiste.com/show-your-world-2019-juried-exhibition"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All entries are accepted. The digital installation is part of our art show: artwork of all participants is projected at the gallery during the entire show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Twenty Winners will display original work at the “Show Your World” exhibition in New York City in November 2019 at Gallery MC.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is more than just a plain exhibition. To promote our artists we host various art &amp; social events to attract a broader audience and your potential buyers. For artists, we organize networking meetups, workshops, consultations. This festival-like art show attracts thousands of visitors - YOUR ART WILL BE SEEN. Show your art and make new connections. Meet new art enthusiasts and sell your art.&lt;br/&gt;Be exhibited in New York City - New York is considered a center of contemporary art life. The world famous art neighborhoods - Chelsea and Soho, Lower East Side and Bushwick, Dumbo and Williamsburg - are located in New York City. The city hosts more than 1500 galleries and hundreds of art shows each year. New York is the place where you can view internationally renowned artworks along with witnessing how modern art emerges. Get the chance to show your world and art to thousands of visitors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;"The artist's job is to be a witness to his time in history." - Robert Rauschenberg&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art is a non-verbal language understood by people speaking different mother tongues. It conveys both historical and social facts, lifestyle, inspiration, and feelings. We’ve been creating a dialogue among artists from various cities and countries.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our Fifth (!) Annual Art Competition and Juried Exhibition “SHOW YOUR WORLD” is open to artists of various media around the globe. Artists of all career levels are welcome. Painters, photographers, mixed media artists from more than 40 countries took part in the previous four editions of “Show Your World”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EVALUATION: The Jury Panel represented by gallery board members, curators, exhibiting artists, art business professionals is evaluating our 5th International Juried Exhibition “Show Your World”. Find out more about the Jurors here.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;INSPIRATION: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Being traditional or rebellious, figurative or conceptual artist, SHOW YOUR WORLD, views, ideas:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Show YOUR World – happy or sad, active or laid back, open or intimate&lt;br/&gt;Show what only artists can depict – feelings, emotions, or relationships&lt;br/&gt;Show wildlife, nature, or urban landscapes&lt;br/&gt;Show what’s close to your heart or what destroys your comfort&lt;br/&gt;Show your inspiration – whether it’s a person, a place, a book, or another work of art&lt;br/&gt;Show your childhood or your future&lt;br/&gt;Show the world you love, hate, or dream about&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS: Entries must be in JPEG format, no larger than 1400 x 1800 pixels, and under 2MB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following disciplines are accepted:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Painting&lt;br/&gt;Drawing/Illustration&lt;br/&gt;Photography&lt;br/&gt;Mixed Media and 3-D Art including Ceramics and Textile&lt;br/&gt;Digital Art&lt;br/&gt;Installation&lt;br/&gt;Performance&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE include your show statement – it will help the jurors and curators understand your work better.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: JULY 31, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION: As soon as your entry is submitted you receive a popup web page confirming your submission. The finalists will be announced on the RE:ARTISTE website by October 1, 2019 and will be personally notified via email. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;COPYRIGHT: The submitting artists own the copyright to their competition entries as their author(s). By submitting an entry to the art competition the artist gives RE:ARTISTE permission for the entry to be used on the RE:ARTISTE website and its social media channels. The artist gives RE:ARTISTE the right to use his/her name and city of residence for the sole purpose of identifying the artist as the author of the entry. The entry fee is not refundable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Entries must be in JPEG format, no larger than 1400 x 1800 pixels, and under 2MB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following disciplines are accepted:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Painting&lt;br/&gt;- Drawing/Illustration&lt;br/&gt;- Photography&lt;br/&gt;- Mixed Media and 3-D Art including Ceramics and Textile&lt;br/&gt;- Digital Art&lt;br/&gt;- Installation&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE include your show statement – it will help the jurors and curators understand your work better.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info please email at info@reartiste.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5de38678-ab8b-496c-980a-4ba566aac3f2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>93ca110e-bab7-4ab0-b514-b23d1e5be7b3</id><title>6/30 - New American Paintings 2019 Pacific Coast Competition</title><updated>2019-06-18T21:17:27.836343+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;New American Paintings&lt;br/&gt;📍 Boston, MA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Painting&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.newamericanpaintings.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New American Paintings 2019 Pacific Coast Competition&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are pleased to be accepting applications for New American Paintings' 2019 review of painters working in the pacific coast United States. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists from the following states are eligible to apply:&lt;br/&gt;AK, CA, HI, OR, and WA&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JUROR: Christine Y Kim, Associate Curator of Contemporary Art,&lt;br/&gt;Los Angeles County Museum of Art&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TO APPLY YOU WILL NEED:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;* 1) Four jpegs of your work (no larger than 1200 pixels at their greatest dimension)&lt;br/&gt;* 2) A credit card for the entry fee of $50 (You may also take advantage of a special artist's offer: $99, which includes your application fee and a one year subscription to the magazine).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We define the activity of painting broadly. All styles and media are welcome as long as they involve, or are conceptually related to the activity of painting. Works must be original and cannot be editioned.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/93ca110e-bab7-4ab0-b514-b23d1e5be7b3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>352d395f-826a-49db-b5cc-2811606897b2</id><title>7/31 - Nuclear Awareness Poster Contest</title><updated>2019-06-18T21:17:27.836273+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Stevens Institute of Technology&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hoboken, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Design Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/SSVDDBKrzkP3NH4R7"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What can you do in the event of a nuclear detonation? More than most people think. The Reinventing Civil Defense Project poster competition is looking for artists, designers, and other creative people to make bold, accurate, and potent visuals that can change how people see their role in the nuclear world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHO CAN ENTER: Anyone! We especially encourage students, designers, and artists, but anyone can enter. You may enter as an individual designer or a team.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: July 31, 2019, 11:59pm EDT.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRIZES: A variety of monetary prizes will be awarded, up to $1,000. Your work will also be featured in the Reinventing Civil Defense August 2019 Workshop at the Stevens Institute of Technology. Teams that receive an award will split the total prize.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JUDGING: Your work will be judged by a panel of experts in the fields of design, nuclear weapons, risk communication, and other related fields. Posters will be judged on their visual potency (aesthetics, legibility), their message potency (communication), and their technical accuracy (major technical errors will be penalized).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO ENTER: Submit your document through the Google Form here. If you have difficulty submitting the file, or questions about the submission process or contest guidelines, please e-mail poster@reinventingcivildefense.org.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FILE REQUIREMENTS: &lt;br/&gt;       Single File Upload per submission&lt;br/&gt;       24in. x 36in. @ 300 dpi&lt;br/&gt;       Acceptable files types: TIFF or  PDF&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your name or other identifying information should not appear on the poster itself — the judging will be done anonymously.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THE MESSAGE: The message we’re looking to get out is that:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A single nuclear detonation in a city would be destructive and devastating, but most Americans — even those very nearby — would survive, and need to cooperate in recovery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In the event of a nuclear detonation, there are strategies that can improve the chances of those in the near area to avoid becoming a casualty.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Nuclear weapon risk should be part of public understanding, and not ignored because people either believe it cannot happen (it can), or that it is totally unsurvivable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What are the strategies for survival? The slogan that US government agencies like to use is: “Get Inside. Stay Inside. Stay tuned.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GET INSIDE. In the event of an imminent nuclear detonation, or in the aftermath of a detonation, getting indoors is always an improvement, versus being outside. If one has the time to be picky, the center core of large buildings, and basements, are the best sorts of structures. But any indoor structure is better than being outdoors or in an automobile.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;STAY INSIDE. If you’ve survived the immediate blast, and the structure you are in is not itself a danger (it isn’t on fire, it isn’t about to collapse, etc.), then you should stay inside until you hear official instructions to do otherwise. You should definitely not try to evacuate on your own: nuclear fallout can create invisible hazards out of doors, and your car (much less on foot) does not provide any significant protection from it. Furthermore, if hundreds of thousands of people try to self-evacuate at the same time, they will snarl the roads, creating conditions that actively inhibit evacuation and the work of emergency responders. You don’t have to stay inside for hundreds of years — but you might need to stay inside for up to three days (72 hours), until the rates of radioactivity decrease.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;STAY TUNED. It isn’t clear how easy it will be to get official information after a nuclear detonation (telephone networks might not work, for example), but you try to have a plan to get information without going out of doors. This might mean acquiring an emergency radio, for example. Again, in the case that one cannot get information from officials, you should expect to stay indoors for up to 72 hours.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You don’t have to use this slogan in your poster, but it’s useful to understand what it means about what people ought to do (and what it says they should not do).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The main “scenario” we are targeting this message for is for a single nuclear detonation in a city, as you might get from nuclear terrorism or from an attack by a state without many nuclear weapons (like North Korea). We are not giving preparedness advice for a “major” nuclear exchange (like US vs. Russia or US vs. China) which complicates the situation considerably.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RESOURCES: The following resources are recommended reading, and contain many useful sources of inspiration and expertise. Resources can be found on Poster Contest Main Web Page here: &lt;a href="https://reinventingcivildefense.org/poster-contest/" target="_blank"&gt;https://reinventingcivildefense.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FINE PRINT: The poster authors retain copyright of their work, but by entering your artwork into this contest, they agree to give the Reinventing Civil Defense Project and the Stevens Institute of Technology a non-exclusive, non-commercial license to use it for any purposes to do with the Reinventing Civil Defense Project workshop and research on risk communication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit material here: &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/SSVDDBKrzkP3NH4R7" target="_blank"&gt;https://forms.gle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/352d395f-826a-49db-b5cc-2811606897b2" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>