<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-07T08:16:30-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>291d099f-de8b-4e51-a88c-65b593a2a6d2</id><title>6/5 - Call for Artists - 12th Annual Portal: Governors Island (formerly Governors Island Art Fair)</title><updated>2019-05-07T08:16:30.035335+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;4heads&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/05/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.4heads.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York’s Largest Independent Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: June 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;"The Art Fair for the 99%" -New York Times&lt;br/&gt;Seeking independent artists worldwide working in all disciplines; Painting, Photography, Sculpture, Installation, Video, and Sound Art. Submit your work for the 2019 Portal: Governors Island (formerly Governors Island Art Fair) opening this September. Portal: GI - New York’s largest independent exhibition - will once again feature scores of artists of exceptional talent, and each will be awarded an exhibition room or large outdoor space in the historic and beautifully dilapidated buildings of Colonels Row. The lines between artwork and its environment are blurred across the lawns and landmark houses of bucolic Governors Island. Founded by 4heads, a group of New York artists, Portal: GI champions an art fair model that puts the artists first. &lt;br/&gt;Once selected by 4heads jury, your exhibition space is free. The entire massive event is free to the general public. And as an emerging or established artist, you are free to present your work, your way, at this acclaimed independent art fair in New York City. Because 4heads works hard to keep artists’ costs to a bare minimum, gallery scouts, journalists and collectors know that this is where to find the freshest talent, and they come back every year to see what’s been discovered. Many past Portal/GIAF artists have launched their art careers here. We hope you can too. - 4heads&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Heads up! - 4heads is specifically seeking outdoor artists working in all disciplines&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply at: &lt;a href="https://4heads.slideroom.com/" target="_blank"&gt;https://4heads.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More Info at: &lt;a href="http://www.4heads.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.4heads.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: June 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Application Fee: $45  -  No Additional Charges&lt;br/&gt;Fair Dates: Every Weekend in September 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Email: info@4heads.org&lt;br/&gt;Apply at: &lt;a href="https://4heads.slideroom.com/" target="_blank"&gt;https://4heads.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More Info at: &lt;a href="http://www.4heads.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.4heads.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: June 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Application Fee: $45  -  No Additional Charges&lt;br/&gt;Fair Dates: Every Weekend in September 2019&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/291d099f-de8b-4e51-a88c-65b593a2a6d2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>709447bd-2beb-40f2-89af-fc4578068579</id><title>6/22 - Meed3: When Photography Ruled the Streets</title><updated>2019-05-07T08:16:30.035294+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Gallery19&lt;br/&gt;📍 Chicago , IL, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/22/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=6515"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gallery19 announces a call for entries for our Third annual juried competition, Meed3: When Photography Ruled the Streets. Photographers at all experience levels are invited to submit work.  Artists selected as finalists will have their work exhibited (and available for purchase*) at Gallery19 for the month of July 2019. ** As competition judge, Ahmed Ozsever, artist and educator, will review all entries, select finalists, and announce the winner at an opening reception at Gallery19, on July 12th, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;THEME: When Photography Ruled the Streets&lt;br/&gt;Gallery19 and juror Ahmed Ozever delve into the ever-changing world of street photography. There is no clear definition of street photography, but for this competition we will define street photography as the preservation of special moments of our time, in which artists make accessible to future generations.  These images are a documentation of who we are and where we have been.  Street photography fully immerses the viewer into a different time and experience.  Our hope is that artists of all levels will submit work that will tell stories like street photographers Vivian Maier and William Eggleston.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;THE PAYOFF:&lt;br/&gt;The winner of Gallery19 Meed3 will receive a solo show at Gallery19 for the month of August 2020.  The winner will also have a one-year contract with Gallery19, which includes exposure on the gallery’s website, ongoing multi-media, promotion, including social media, participation in gallery programming (openings, events, artist talks, etc.), and direct sales efforts.  In addition, Ahmed Ozsever will mentor the winner for a full year August 2019 through August 2020, by reviewing and evaluating work product, and assisting in development of a gallery-ready exhibition, all culminating in a solo exhibition at Gallery19.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/709447bd-2beb-40f2-89af-fc4578068579" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4af36470-2a41-40f8-8bb0-c46d02bbce6f</id><title>7/3 - Call for Artists for 106th Annual National Exhibition</title><updated>2019-05-07T08:16:30.035267+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Allied Artists of America&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/03/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $55.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://alliedartistsofamerica.org/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists: Oil, Watermedia, Pastel, Graphics &amp; Sculpture  Allied Artists of America.  Seeks entries for 2019 106th Annual National Exhibition Aug 29 - Sep 15 at Salmagundi Club, 47 Fifth Ave.NYC. Top award: $3,000 and over $25,000 in awards are given. Juror of Elizabeth Allan, Curator, Collections &amp; Exhibition at the Morven Museum &amp; Garden, NJ. To submit entries:  &lt;a href="http://www.juriedartservices.com/index.php?content=event_info&amp;event_id=1560" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.juriedartservices.com&lt;/a&gt; • mitzura.salgian@alliedartistsofamerica.org  Deadline July 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To submit entries:  &lt;a href="http://www.juriedartservices.com/index.php?content=event_info&amp;event_id=1560" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.juriedartservices.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Prospectus: &lt;a href="https://static1.squarespace.com/static/5101f15be4b0202016c752b8/t/5ca78e7b085229e9b17b45b0/1554484859690/Prospectus+Allied+Artists+2019+-+Revised.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;https://static1.squarespace.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;mitzura.salgian@alliedartistsofamerica.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4af36470-2a41-40f8-8bb0-c46d02bbce6f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8b62498e-b470-4637-ab30-3313a18dac43</id><title>5/30 - Under the Viaduct Public Art Opportunity</title><updated>2019-05-07T08:16:30.035237+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Mural Arts Philadelphia&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.muralarts.org/artist-resources/calls-to-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The City of Philadelphia Division of Housing and Community Development (DHCD) is seeking artists or artist teams to create public artworks in the areas in and around three SEPTA Regional Rail line underpasses in the North Central Choice Neighborhood in North Philadelphia. The artworks are part of a major, multifaceted investment in physical, community and economic activities in the area of the Norris Apartments, a historic public housing development that is being redeveloped as part of the North Central Choice Neighborhood Implementation Grant.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We expect to select one artist / artist team for each of the three locations, but that could change depending on the responses we receive. The artworks will largely be executed as large-scale murals due to the limitations of using other materials in these particular locations. The development of the artwork concepts and the creation of the artworks should involve engagement with local residents, including a community advisory committee.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Site budgets range from $75,000 to $300,000. The commission is being managed by Mural Arts Philadelphia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Download full RFQ and application instructions at &lt;a href="https://www.muralarts.org/artist-resources/calls-to-artists/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.muralarts.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8b62498e-b470-4637-ab30-3313a18dac43" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e1466d75-c72d-4550-8e50-37627d39bdfd</id><title>5/20 - Blackbird Gallery looking for Artists for PRIDE Exhibition.</title><updated>2019-05-07T08:16:30.035204+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Blackbird Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York , NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackbird.gallery/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New gallery located in Chelsea is looking for artists to showcase work for PRIDE exhibtion.  This exhibition is meant to examine gender, sexuality, race and ethnicity and how it has shaped the artists work. Art made by LBGTQ+ community and PRIDE themed will also be considered. Work will be on view the month of June to coincide with the celebration of PRIDE. A closing reception will be held PRIDE weekend. Exhibition will be on view from June 6th through July 1stl.  All mediums welcome. This is an open call for all visual artists. There is no fee to apply. Questions? Please email and don't be shy!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit 3-5 images of work, related websites and social media links. Must be LGBTQ+ friendly! Work must be LGBTQ+ Friendly.&lt;br/&gt;Please  email shows@blackbird.gallery with any questions. Happy PRIDE 🏳️‍🌈&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e1466d75-c72d-4550-8e50-37627d39bdfd" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>296b413c-8776-4608-a625-8ce3767c5f8e</id><title>6/30 - *NYS Arts Professionals* Submit Your Art for Take Back the Walls</title><updated>2019-05-07T08:16:30.035148+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Rochester Contemporary Art Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Rochester, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.rochestercontemporary.org/exhibitions/take-back-the-walls/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calling all NYS Arts Professionals! Rochester Contemporary Art Center (RoCo) announces Take Back the Walls, a juried exhibition of artworks by New York State artists who also work in museums, galleries and arts organizations. This new, statewide project will highlight the many talented creatives employed by New York’s numerous arts institutions and galleries, yet are often behind the scenes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RoCo invites employees of museums, visual art spaces and galleries to come into the light and take back the walls to which they have dedicated so much. Anyone who is employed by an arts organization in New York State is invited to submit work for display in Take Back the Walls. This exhibition is juried by Karlos Carcamo, a multidisciplinary artist and a framer at The Museum of Modern Art in NYC. There is a $10 registration fee per artist. Each artist may enter up to 6 submissions (artworks). RoCo will aim to exhibit a small body of work by each selected artist. Submissions will be accepted through Sunday, June 30 at 5pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To learn more about this call, visit: &lt;br/&gt;http://www.rochestercontemporary.org/exhibitions/take-back-the-walls/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We invite current employees of museums, visual art spaces and galleries in New York State to submit their artwork for exhibition. Both 2D and 3D works of all mediums are accepted. This call excludes past employees and family members of the employee.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We decided to use ArtCall in order to keep the submissions organized and to easily facilitate guest jurying. Registration fees will pay for the service and the juror(s). To Register and Login: thewalls.artcall.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/296b413c-8776-4608-a625-8ce3767c5f8e" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>