<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-01T10:48:10-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>fcc79c3a-0087-45f7-aec2-01c9ddaf7e7d</id><title>2/28 - Arte Natura</title><updated>2019-02-01T10:48:10.281828+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Limner Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hudson, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/28/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.slowart.com/prospectus/natura.htm"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARTE NATURA is a thematic exhibition based on art inspired from the natural world. The exhibition will be held at the Limner Gallery, May 9 - June 1, 2019 and is open to all artists working in any media. All interpretations of the theme are acceptable, including landscape, fruits, vegetables, flowers and fauna and to human figuration as part of the natural environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application is via email, instructions are on the prospectus:&lt;br/&gt;http://www.slowart.com/prospectus/natura.htm&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fcc79c3a-0087-45f7-aec2-01c9ddaf7e7d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2f9fa504-6150-4710-95e1-7a434838c74b</id><title>3/3 - Folksy: Cultural Traditions &amp;amp; Outside Visions</title><updated>2019-02-01T10:48:10.281785+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Annmarie Sculpture Garden&lt;br/&gt;📍 Dowell, MD, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/03/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://annmariegarden.wufoo.com/forms/folksy-cultural-traditions-outside-visions/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join us as we explore the wide realm of folk art, outsider art, and visionary art - and other artistic expressions that are often situated outside the world of mainstream fine arts. This exhibit invites artists to submit works that highlight the unconventional, the authentic, and the self-taught. What materials and perspectives are artists exploring? How are artists blurring the lines between fine and folk, mainstream and outsider?  What cultural traditions, personal histories, or social commentaries inspire their work? What identities and issues are finding a voice? How does this work challenge our ideas and address the human condition? These and other ideas and expressions will find a home in this exciting new exhibit opportunity. All media welcome; small to large-scale; indoor and outdoor. Cash awards to be presented. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror:  to be announced; to be drawn from the Smithsonian Institution&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Annmarie Sculpture Garden &amp; Arts Center, In Association with the Smithsonian Institution&lt;br/&gt;13470 Dowell Road/99, P.O. Box 99, Dowell, MD  20629&lt;br/&gt;www.annmariegarden.org     t. 410-326-4640     art@annmariegarden.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2f9fa504-6150-4710-95e1-7a434838c74b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>05824ef4-7c35-4f99-b697-06e7d86b78a5</id><title>3/15 - ArtFP</title><updated>2019-02-01T10:48:10.281745+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;BRIC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $5.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.bricartsmedia.org/artist-opportunities/exhibition-open-calls/artfp"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BRIC ArtFP is an open request for proposals (RFP) from emerging and established local visual artists to explore and expand the possibilities of their work. With this commissioning program led by BRIC’s Contemporary Art program, artists receive honorariums and production fees for exhibition of their work in the Project Room or Hallway spaces of BRIC House. This opportunity includes assistance with development time, installation, marketing, documentation, and more.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTISTS WILL RECEIVE:&lt;br/&gt;* An honorarium&lt;br/&gt;* Production fees&lt;br/&gt;* Exhibition space in either the Project Room or Hallway space of BRIC House&lt;br/&gt;* Technical and installation support&lt;br/&gt;* Artistic mentoring&lt;br/&gt;* Printed announcements and promotional support&lt;br/&gt;* Photography of exhibition&lt;br/&gt;* Opening reception&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PROJECT ROOM&lt;br/&gt;The Project Room is a separate small gallery adjacent to the main gallery at BRIC House. Project Room exhibitions are 6-weeks long and highlight solo/collaborative projects by emerging and established artists whose work encompasses a rich range of themes and media. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dimensions: 24 x 12 ft.&lt;br/&gt;Honorarium: $600&lt;br/&gt;Production Fees covered by BRIC: up to $500&lt;br/&gt;Installation Time: 3-4 days with assistance of an art installer for 2 days&lt;br/&gt;Project Room Layout&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HALLWAY&lt;br/&gt;Hallway Commissions provide space for solo/collaborative projects by emerging and established visual artists to create wall and ceiling-based installations. Hallway exhibitions are 8-10 weeks long. A highly trafficked, but not completely white box space, we seek artists for the Hallway who are excited by the opportunity to share their work with the public in alternate spaces. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dimensions: 55 running ft.&lt;br/&gt;Honorarium: $250&lt;br/&gt;Production Fees covered by BRIC: up to $500&lt;br/&gt;Installation Time: 1-2 days with art installer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SELECTION CRITERIA:&lt;br/&gt;* We are looking for Brooklyn or New York City-area visual artists who are developing new work that is relevant to diverse Brooklyn audiences.&lt;br/&gt;* Of particular interest are single-artist proposals to create installations in our Project Room and Hallway spaces.&lt;br/&gt;* Projects will be chosen through a panel review that will take place in April 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;TO APPLY: &lt;br/&gt;To apply for the BRIC ArtFP, please fill out and submit the online Application Form via SlideRoom: &lt;br/&gt;https://bric.slideroom.com/#/login/program/46747&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications require a project description, artist bio(s), and work samples.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/05824ef4-7c35-4f99-b697-06e7d86b78a5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2cda3627-fe28-4287-af97-242431ada035</id><title>3/25 - Request for Qualifications: Austin Peay State University</title><updated>2019-02-01T10:48:10.281680+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Austin Peay State University - Department of Art + Design&lt;br/&gt;📍 Clarksville, TN, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.apsu.edu/art-design/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Project Description: Austin Peay State University’s Department of Art + Design seeks to commission an original work of art for a new green-space on campus, located directly adjacent to the new Art + Design Building. The goal of the artwork is to enhance public space and to promote the department’s vision to provide a creative environment that enables students to ask questions, think critically, and participate in a global society. Goals for the artwork include site responsiveness, engagement with the student community, durability, and aesthetic interest. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Austin Peay State University: Austin Peay State University is located on an urban campus that for more than 180 years has been used for educational purposes and on which the buildings of five colleges have stood. APSU is located in Clarksville, Tennessee, the state's fifth largest and youngest city. The school is named after former Tennessee Governor Austin Peay, a Clarksville native. Austin Peay is a four-year public, masters level university offering more than 62 majors and 108 different concentrations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Site Description: The work will be sited adjacent to the university’s new Art + Design Building.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Budget: $120,000 - this budget does not include ongoing maintenance or repair for the work. The budget does include design fees, fabrication, installation, material costs, and all other related fees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application requirements:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Cover letter describing your interest in the project, your general approach to public artwork, a brief description of your work’s overall themes, and any relevant project experience. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Professional resume/bio with contact information: name, address, phone number, email address, and website if available. Your bio should include a list of public/commissioned artworks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Portfolio of up to 10 images, including images of the projects listed above, that demonstrate your ability to complete a project on this scale&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An annotated image list corresponding to the slides. Include title, date, media, size, client, location,and project budget. Please include information relevant to this commission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A detailed timeline for completion. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Incomplete Applications will not be reviewed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selection Process:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RFQs will be reviewed by the members of the public art committee. Up to three finalists will be short-listed and issued a request for proposals, with a stipend of $1500.00 per finalist. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each artist selected as a finalist will provide the following materials to the committee: concept drawings and a scaled model, thematic description/interpretation, a maintenance plan for the piece, and a detailed budget and timeline.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The committee will select finalists based on strength of past work as shown in application materials, and a demonstrated ability to design and install works of a similar scale/scope. The Committee will make a final selection based on the thematic and formal strength of the proposal.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The committee’s choice for final selection is subject to approval by the University President and administration at APSU. The artist(s) selected shall be expected to collaborate closely with site engineers, landscape architects, and any necessary party for the successful installation of the project, including the community.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Timeline:&lt;br/&gt;Call to Artists Announced/RFQ Released: February 2019&lt;br/&gt;Submittal deadline for RFQ Response: March 25, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Selection of Finalists: April 2019&lt;br/&gt;Installation of Artwork: TBD&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility: This RFQ open to all artists regardless of race, color, creed, gender, gender variance, sexual orientation, national origin, age, religion, marital status, political opinion or affiliation, or mental or physical disability. Artists working in any media are eligible to apply. Austin Peay State University is committed to equality and inclusion on our campus. To this end, people of color, LGBTQIA individuals, and differently-abled persons are highly encouraged to apply.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2cda3627-fe28-4287-af97-242431ada035" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>