<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-20T17:14:37-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>bdcb0a67-aa83-4afb-be31-f28cc8687a35</id><title>3/17 - Far and Wide National Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-02-20T17:14:37.042044+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Woodstock Artists Association &amp;amp; Museum&lt;br/&gt;📍 Woodstock, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.woodstockart.org/art-submission-calendar/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open to all artists living and working in the United States.&lt;br/&gt;Online applications only.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Kimberly Camp, former President and CEO of the Barnes Foundation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists are invited to submit up to 5 works that are innovative in form and content or that have been created within the parameters of traditional genres but nevertheless break new ground. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: May 11 - June 9&lt;br/&gt;Artists Reception: Saturday, May 18, 4-6pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Awards&lt;br/&gt;- The Arthur Harris Best in Show Award ($500)&lt;br/&gt;- Nicholas Buhalis Award for Artistic Excellence in Abstract/Figurative or Figurative Work ($500)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Media &amp; Size Limitations:&lt;br/&gt;Works in the following media will be considered:&lt;br/&gt;Painting&lt;br/&gt;Drawing&lt;br/&gt;Original Prints (Traditional and digital. No reproductions of works existing in other media.)&lt;br/&gt;Photography&lt;br/&gt;Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2-D works should not exceed 36 inches on the longest dimension (38 inches including frame). &lt;br/&gt;3-D work must be no greater than 36 x 36 x 36 inches&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/bdcb0a67-aa83-4afb-be31-f28cc8687a35" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>643ee409-ca18-4ce5-a9ce-9abd539801a0</id><title>4/10 - Open Call to raise money for women immigrants and refugees</title><updated>2019-02-20T17:14:37.042009+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;FeLT NYC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.feltnyc.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you an artist and want to help immigrant women and refugees? Do you believe that education can empower individuals and communities? Do you want some exposure of your work at the same time? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are FeLT NYC: a community organization dedicated to supporting women immigrants and refugees through FREE English language courses and a variety of practical workshops. It is all run by volunteers and donations. Please visit www.feltnyc.org for more information and pictures. You can also look us up on Twitter, Instagram and Facebook&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FeLT NYC is calling for artists to DONATE artwork for a silent auction for its fundraiser on April 25th, 2019 at The Parish of Calvary – St. George’s near Gramercy Park. This would enable us to collect funds to keep programs running for immigrant and refugee women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to help immigrant and refugee women, please follow the submission instructions below:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The theme of the fundraiser is We Are America: Today's immigrants and refugees.  Please take this theme in any direction you would like. We accept any work that relate to this theme or FeLT's core mission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please submit the following to director@feltnyc.org :&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- 1-3 images.  (only .JPGs, please!). &lt;br/&gt;- Please include title, medium, dimensions, and price. &lt;br/&gt;- Artist statement and bio&lt;br/&gt;- Link to your website&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE is April 10th.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We will contact artists that get chosen on April 16th and will give further information about drop off and other logistics. If your work gets selected, please make sure it is ready to hang. We have staff to do the hanging, but if you want to be involved in the process, we you are free to hang your own pieces! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are looking forward to your submission!&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/643ee409-ca18-4ce5-a9ce-9abd539801a0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>46d7036f-237d-4d6d-b2ac-fde83682c697</id><title>3/10 - 4th Annual Drawing Marathon: Entrants Sought</title><updated>2019-02-20T17:14:37.041950+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Binghamton University&lt;br/&gt;📍 Binghamton, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Drawing&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ABOUT: Co-sponsored by the Department of Art and Design, United Health Services, the Binghamton University Fleishman Career Center and the Vice Provost’s Office for Undergraduate Education. The Drawing Marathon offers Binghamton University students, alumni and community artists (18 and over) a unique opportunity to compete for 24 hours to produce a finished figure drawing in the museum. It is a chance to discover one’s artistic second wind, when powerful creative energy is released at the very time physical energy diminishes. This second wind reinvigorates both mind and body, and can result in a rewarding, even spectacular artistic creation. &lt;br/&gt;WHEN: Friday, April 5, 10:00 am–Saturday, April 6, 10:00 am (24 hours with regular breaks).&lt;br/&gt;EVENT DETAILS: A clothed, live model, basic charcoal drawing materials, paper (72” x 48”), and easel will be provided. Light refreshments will be provided. Participating artists are responsible for all other expenses incurred, e.g., transportation, special foods. Artists are urged to consider the mental and physical aspects of this endeavor and must feel that they can safely participate. Dressing in layers of comfortable clothing is recommended.  The event is held in a public setting so that visitors may observe artists at work throughout the  24-hour marathon period. Participants are expected to spend most of the 24 hours in the museum drawing and taking frequent scheduled breaks. &lt;br/&gt;AWARDS:  Two cash prizes will be awarded on the morning of Saturday, April 6: the jury prize of $1000 and the people’s prize of $500. The people’s prize will be awarded on the basis of qualitative comments received by visitors to the marathon as well as statements posted on the Binghamton University Art Museum Facebook age. In addition to these prizes the Binghamton University Fine Art Society (BUFAS) will give a basket of art supplies to one artist demonstrating the most creative or  innovative approach to drawing.&lt;br/&gt;TIMELINE:  The competition will commence Friday, April 5 at 10:00 am. At the end of every hour there will be 15-minute break for the model and participants. Every four hours there will be a 30-minute break. An award ceremony will follow shortly after the competition concludes on Saturday, April 6 at 10:00 am. The drawings will remain on view in the museum through Tuesday, April 9. Participants must retrieve their finished drawings by Saturday, April 13.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION: Artists should send one pdf file with up to 10 samples of their best figure drawings, along with the following contact information: name, address, phone number and email. Please provide answers to the following questions: &lt;br/&gt;~ Are you comfortable with media (video and&lt;br/&gt;photography) documenting you and your artwork&lt;br/&gt;if selected?&lt;br/&gt;~ Do you have interesting a story, a personal&lt;br/&gt;challenge you’ve overcome, or anything special&lt;br/&gt;we should be aware of?&lt;br/&gt;Send your application to: drawing@binghamton.edu. There is no fee. The jury will select the strongest 10-12 competitors among the applicants. Only 10-12 artists will be selected and invited to compete. The competition is open to all students, alumni and community artists (aged 18 and over). The deadline for submitting an application is March 10. No applications will be accepted after this date.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/46d7036f-237d-4d6d-b2ac-fde83682c697" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>