<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-05T02:17:08-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>8994cfef-fbab-457b-82be-21f768e81eff</id><title>7/13 - New Directions 2019: 35th Annual National Juried Contemporary Art Exhibition</title><updated>2019-06-05T02:17:08.499718+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Barrett Art Center (Dutchess County Art Association)&lt;br/&gt;📍 Poughkeepsie, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/13/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.barrettartcenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Directions 2019: 35th Annual National Juried Contemporary Art Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Akili Tommasino, Associate Curator, Modern and Contemporary Art, Museum of Fine Arts, Boston.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Deadline: July 13, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: September 28 - November 9, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$500 Juror’s Prize, $200 Second Prize, $125 Honorable Mention &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;New Directions is a premier national exhibition of new approaches in contemporary art today. Artists are encouraged to submit new works that embrace cutting-edge practices and/or traditional styles in innovative ways. We welcome 2D media, 3D sculpture, video, and installation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Now in its 35th year, New Directions brings contemporary art to an atypical venue - the intimate galleries of Barrett Art Center’s 1840s Greek Revival townhouse. Former domestic spaces remodeled as galleries create a visually-compelling setting for contemporary and cutting-edge work.  Maximum dimensions: 72"&lt;br/&gt;Submitting Entries:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BAC Members: $35 for the first three images plus $5 for each additional image.&lt;br/&gt;Non-members: $50 for the first three images plus $5 for each additional image.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applications are submitted through www.callforentry.org (CaFE)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Access this call: &lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=6683" target="_blank"&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8994cfef-fbab-457b-82be-21f768e81eff" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>02b9219a-39c4-48dc-9674-70cf059f03c0</id><title>6/5 - Call for Artists - 12th Annual Portal: Governors Island (formerly Governors Island Art Fair)</title><updated>2019-06-05T02:17:08.499681+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;4heads&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/05/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.4heads.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York’s Largest Independent Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: June 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;"The Art Fair for the 99%" -New York Times&lt;br/&gt;Seeking independent artists worldwide working in all disciplines; Painting, Photography, Sculpture, Installation, Video, and Sound Art. Submit your work for the 2019 Portal: Governors Island (formerly Governors Island Art Fair) opening this September. Portal: GI - New York’s largest independent exhibition - will once again feature scores of artists of exceptional talent, and each will be awarded an exhibition room or large outdoor space in the historic and beautifully dilapidated buildings of Colonels Row. The lines between artwork and its environment are blurred across the lawns and landmark houses of bucolic Governors Island. Founded by 4heads, a group of New York artists, Portal: GI champions an art fair model that puts the artists first. &lt;br/&gt;Once selected by 4heads jury, your exhibition space is free. The entire massive event is free to the general public. And as an emerging or established artist, you are free to present your work, your way, at this acclaimed independent art fair in New York City. Because 4heads works hard to keep artists’ costs to a bare minimum, gallery scouts, journalists and collectors know that this is where to find the freshest talent, and they come back every year to see what’s been discovered. Many past Portal/GIAF artists have launched their art careers here. We hope you can too. - 4heads&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Heads up! - 4heads is also seeking outdoor artists working in all disciplines&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply at: &lt;a href="https://4heads.slideroom.com/" target="_blank"&gt;https://4heads.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More Info at: &lt;a href="http://www.4heads.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.4heads.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2018 Video (this helps you understand our spaces): &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/LrcQtWcB7Ks" target="_blank"&gt;https://youtu.be&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: June 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Application Fee: $45  -  No Additional Charges&lt;br/&gt;Fair Dates: Every Weekend in September 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply at: &lt;a href="https://4heads.slideroom.com/" target="_blank"&gt;https://4heads.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More Info at: &lt;a href="http://www.4heads.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.4heads.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2018 Video (this helps you understand our spaces): &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/LrcQtWcB7Ks" target="_blank"&gt;https://youtu.be&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: June 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Application Fee: $45  -  No Additional Charges&lt;br/&gt;Fair Dates: Every Weekend in September 2019&lt;br/&gt;Contact Email for Questions: info@4heads.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/02b9219a-39c4-48dc-9674-70cf059f03c0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>fbd6e705-6624-41a8-acc0-5b622a192945</id><title>7/31 - Create! Magazine MFA Edition Call for Art</title><updated>2019-06-05T02:17:08.499636+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.createmagazine.com/callforart"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine is pleased to announce an open call for its first annual MFA Edition. We are now accepting applications from current candidates and recent graduates from 2017 - 2019.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Create! Magazine is an independent contemporary arts magazine focused on highlighting the work of talented emerging and mid-career creatives from across the globe. We are pleased to announce our next call for artists for a custom designed two-page spread in our publication (both print &amp; digital) that will feature your artist biography, website, and two images of your artwork. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Have your work seen by our 125,000+ readers and followers around the world, including leading galleries, art fairs, collectors, curators, writers, art consultants, and more. Don’t miss this opportunity to put your work out there and connect with a new audience!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY: MFA graduates from the past two years and current candidates from both the US and abroad, of all genders, ethnicities, and from all backgrounds are welcome to apply. We accept works in any medium: painting, sculpture, digital art, printmaking, fiber/textile art, photography, mixed media, installation, etc. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS: 3+ jpeg images of different artworks, a text document with a bio and artist statement, website or social media link, and your email address. If your work is three-dimensional, you may include additional images of installation views or detailed shots at no extra cost. Please see our Submittable form for further details. Please note that for best results, artists should include works from the same series per each submission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTISTS: If your work is selected, you will receive a custom designed two-page spread in both the print and digital versions of the magazine that will include your artist biography, website, and two images. Published artists will be sent a complimentary digital issue and will be listed as a participating artist in your issue on both our website and social media. We also promote artists individually via blog and social media posts that reach over 125,000 total followers worldwide. All featured artists will automatically be considered for any upcoming curatorial projects, not limited to art fairs, exhibitions, and gallery projects organized by our team. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;WHERE TO FIND US: Print copies of Create! Magazine are available in our online shop and at several global retail locations in London, New York, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Amsterdam, Stockholm, Chicago, Philadelphia, Ft. Lauderdale, Wilmington (DE), and more. Digital issues can always be purchased on our website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fbd6e705-6624-41a8-acc0-5b622a192945" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6964e1f3-96a0-412c-841d-10a2a9a0955c</id><title>WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW! Open Call Fro artists Friday June 14th 2019</title><updated>2019-06-05T02:17:08.499478+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our &lt;br/&gt;June 14th  People's Choice Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday,June 14th, 2019 from 8pm- 12am.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, May 30th, 2019 at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For this show, we let the people decide, which means everyone who attends votes for the winners! We pass out ballots at the door and guests who attends choose the winners! It is always one of our most well attended nights, boasting record art sales and a large community of fellow artists and art lovers!&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of local bands!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, June 13th at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces already this past year. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com @ Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Facebook:  www.facebook.com/events/302426043994914/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6964e1f3-96a0-412c-841d-10a2a9a0955c" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>