<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-01T20:14:51-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>e22ce79f-6cb3-4c87-89c3-0afb60b937cf</id><title>3/14 - Love Triangle: For the Love of Geometry</title><updated>2019-03-01T20:14:51.208229+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;1milliondiamonds&lt;br/&gt;📍 Morganville, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/14/18 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/1milliondiamonds/?hl=en"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEEP SPACE GALLERY &amp; 1 MILLION DIAMONDS PRESENT&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LOVE TRIANGLE: For the Love of Geometry&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A  Summertime Juried Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On view June 27th - July 20th&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepting applications now through March 14, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1milliondiamonds and Deep Space Gallery are both turning 3 this year!  In celebration, we are joining forces to produce our first collaborative, juried exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What we are looking for:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Geometric abstraction&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Do you think in shapes?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Does your work fit into the aesthetic world of 1MILLIONDIAMONDS?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Originals only&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any size up to 36 x 36”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any medium (digital, sculpture, paintings, works on paper, photography)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Up to 5 works, with high resolution images of each&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork Information List including title, medium, dimensions (H x W x D), year produced, retail price&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist bio and CV, links to online presence (IG, website, etc.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Information for Artists:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$25 submission fee to submit 3 works*&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;       *only one piece of artwork from each artist selected will be exhibited in             the gallery show, so send us your strongest work!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$5 each to submit additional pieces for consideration (up to 2 additional)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All works must be ready to hang&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All works must be available for purchase&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All sales will be split 50/50 (Love Triangle/Artist)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Must submit by March 14, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juried selections will be made by April 25th and notifications will be sent out in the week that follows.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juried exhibition will take place at Deep Space Gallery in Jersey City, NJ, and will be on view from June 27th through July 20th.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Transportation of artwork to and from the gallery will be the sole responsibility of the artist.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please fill in the highlighted fields below, click the gray “Submit” button, and then click the yellow “Click to Complete Submission” button to finalize. (If it doesn't open on one click, click it again.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please submit your Artist CV/Bio/Artist Statement and Artwork  information list as one document in .pdf form&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist Benefits:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Inclusion in featured summertime gallery show at DS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Featured on 1milliondiamonds &amp; DS online platforms*&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;       *Note that all submissions will be considered for features online&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Inclusion in print magazine/catalog of the show&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Inclusion in gallery programming including artist panels, workshops, and networking events&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Love Triangle Jurors&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Debra Lynn Manville, curator and founder of 1milliondiamonds&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Keith VanPelt, owner and cofounder of Deep Space Gallery&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Works selected for in-gallery exhibition and/or online features will be chosen from those works submitted in your initial application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions, please email: deepdiamondlovetriangle@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e22ce79f-6cb3-4c87-89c3-0afb60b937cf" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>5972d098-85b9-48c3-afa1-b5c9f34c2642</id><title>5/1 - Helpful Discomfot</title><updated>2019-03-01T20:14:51.208199+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hidden Currencies&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $5.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://hiddencurrencies.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hidden Currencies presents hécatombe, an extension of the collective through print. We are seeking open calls for our 1st edition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For hécatombe’s first edition we are examining the implications of discomfort and it’s potential to inspire growth, regression, fear, and hope. Discomfort can reflect a projected incongruence of identity, fueled by the pressures of society and self. This discomfort can be at the epicenter of our dissonance from society: we now face the question if it is the individual or the society which should be made to feel uncomfortable. If so, what is the utility of discomfort for each party? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In approaching this topic and examining your work please consider:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;How discomfort helps you?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;How do people benefit from each other's discomfort?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Who do you want to see uncomfortable? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Where do you want to be uncomfortable?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;_____________________________________________________________________________________&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Hidden Currencies is an interdisciplinary collective consisting of artists, musicians, dancers, sculptors and scientists. It was founded in early in May of 2017. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The reason for the inception of the Hidden Currencies is three fold:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is an interdisciplinary creative community to prompt artists to explore new dimensions of their art through critiques, demonstrations, and workshops. Artists of different mediums give valuable feedback that will stem from their various backgrounds. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;In the midst of a climate that commoditizes art and music, it is important to create a network of individuals who can hold each other accountable to their ethical standards of making art. This community will facilitate growth outside of what could be attained independently. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To work with local communities to establish a connecting point for the next generation to engage with art in a variety of mediums.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;_____________________________________________________________________________________&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Those who are selected to participate in our first magazine will be invited to the release party in New York City. Location and date to be announced in line with release of the publication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are accepting submissions from any medium which explore this theme to be printed in our first edition, including but not limited to: writing, painting, sculpture, photography, installations, games, data sets, experiments, multimedia, etc. This is limited to media which can be printed within our pages. For video and music submissions we have the capability to include a QR Code. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An email sent to info@hiddencurrencies.com with:&lt;br/&gt;Up to 5 images with the longest edge being 1000p (jpg.) &lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement (300 words)&lt;br/&gt;Link to your website or portfolio&lt;br/&gt;$5 entry fee to be paid over paypal to info@hiddencurrencies.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5972d098-85b9-48c3-afa1-b5c9f34c2642" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c89ebb9c-a392-48a0-97bc-88204737b525</id><title>4/2 - Call for Entries -- Ebb &amp;amp; Flow: the power of water</title><updated>2019-03-01T20:14:51.208169+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Annmarie Sculpture Garden&lt;br/&gt;📍 Solomons, MD, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/02/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://annmariegarden.wufoo.com/forms/artist-application-ebb-flow-the-power-of-water/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vital to Earth and all known forms of life, water holds awesome powers of creation, destruction, and transformation. This exhibit invites artists to submit works that explore the power, meaning, and majesty of water, from its chemical composition to its economic importance, to its terror and allure. All media welcome; small to large-scale works; indoor and outdoor works to be included in the show. Cash awards to be presented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juror:  to be announced; to be drawn from the Smithsonian Institution&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Deadline to apply: April 2, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Notification of decision: April 9, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Delivery of artwork: May 8-12, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Annmarie After Hours Opening: May 24, 2019, 5-8pm&lt;br/&gt;Exhibit: May 24 - September 2, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Artwork Return/Pick-up: September 3-7, 2019&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c89ebb9c-a392-48a0-97bc-88204737b525" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2a4ac7a9-ba41-4286-b576-f981bd14fea5</id><title>3/31 - Call to Artists: 3rd Annual Juried Photography Show</title><updated>2019-03-01T20:14:51.208135+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Spencertown Academy Arts Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Spencertown, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.spencertownacademy.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the first time in three years, photographers submitting to the annual juried photo show will not need to abide by a preconceived theme. Based on past shows, it’s clear we have a talented pool of photographers, and we want to attract as many as we can by not constricting creative vision. We look forward to the variety that will produce a great show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;Submissions will be accepted from residents of Columbia County, NY and the following surrounding counties: Rensselaer, Albany, Schenectady, Ulster, Dutchess and Greene in NY, Litchfield and Fairfield in CT, and Berkshire in MA.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE VENUE&lt;br/&gt;Housed in a historic landmark 1847 Greek revival schoolhouse, Spencertown Academy Arts Center presents a variety of arts and cultural programming to an audience of local residents, second homeowners, and tourists from the Hudson Valley and Berkshire regions. Programs include: exhibitions of fine arts and craft; musical performances; spoken word, poetry and drama; workshops and classes. The Academy is located at 790 Rt. 203, Spencertown, NY 12165.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Academy, including the gallery, is a not-for-profit institution supported by membership, public and private donations and grant funding. A volunteer committee comprised of professional artists and curators administers the Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Gallery comprises two exhibition spaces: the larger space is approximately 38’ X 15’ and the smaller is 16’ X 15’. Both rooms have abundant natural light as well as track lighting and 9.5’ ceilings.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR&lt;br/&gt;Bonnie Yochelson is an independent curator and art historian specializing in the history of photography. She is former Curator of Prints and Photographs at the Museum of the City of New York and teaches in the MFA Photography, Video and Related Media Department at the School of Visual Arts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AWARDS&lt;br/&gt;The guest juror will curate the show and bestow First, Second and Honorable Mention Awards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOW TO ENTER&lt;br/&gt;All submissions must be made online through Showsubmit.com at SAACPhotoShow. Complete guidelines, entry forms and instructions for submission are detailed there.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Up to 4 images may be submitted. The Juror will select no more than 2 images per artist. Maximum size of entry is 40 inches, which is determined by measuring from outer edges of height and width of frame. Photographs must not have been previously exhibited at the Academy. Work created in the last three years is preferred.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;INSTRUCTIONS FOR SUBMISSION&lt;br/&gt;Crop the image to exclude mat, frame, or extraneous material. Make a copy of this image (SAVE AS). Keep the original for your own records.&lt;br/&gt;Resize the copy image with a resolution of 300 dpi to a length of 900 pixels on the longest side.&lt;br/&gt;Save this copy now with a new filename, as follows: Lastname_firstinitial_phototitle.&lt;br/&gt;You may have to alter the title as it appears in the filename of the image file only. For example, if your name is Jane Doe and your photograph is titled Early Sunday Morning, the filename you would give to the digital image&lt;br/&gt;is: Doe_J_EarlySundayMorning.jpg.&lt;br/&gt;During the entry process, you would type in the actual Title of the photograph as Early Sunday Morning when asked for the Title, Price, Size, etc.&lt;br/&gt;For each image you are asked to supply a brief description of how the piece will be hung.&lt;br/&gt;If your display for the image does not involve a frame, you must still give a frame size that is larger than the image size or the entry system will not accept the image; just add .5 inch to width and height and we will recognize it.&lt;br/&gt;Save the image as a high quality jpg. (Use the “Save As” function to select jpg and the highest quality.) The image title will now end with .jpg For example: Doe_J_EarlySummerMorning.jpg&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEE&lt;br/&gt;Members $30 and Non-Members $40. This fee covers submission of up to 4 pieces.&lt;br/&gt;You can become a member @www.spencertownacademy.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ACCEPTANCE&lt;br/&gt;Notification of acceptance will be on April 8 by email. No substitutions of accepted work will be allowed. All work must remain in the gallery until pick-up on Monday, July 15 or Tuesday, July 16.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SALES&lt;br/&gt;All work must be for sale. Based on our sales experience from previous shows, we encourage photographers not to exceed $500 for their work although, officially, there is no price restriction. The Academy receives a 35% commission on any work sold.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DISPLAY INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;Attach appropriate hardware for hanging. Gallery staff will not attach wire, hangers, clips or other hardware. Ensure corners of frames, whether metal or wood, are tightly joined. Glass must be free and clear of smudges, stray debris or paper that slipped in during framing, or anything that will detract from viewing. Mats, if used, must be clean or will be turned away for replacement.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions and assistance with entry should be directed to: Joe Baker&lt;br/&gt;email: jbaker@showsubmit.com Phone: 413-528-5134&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For all other questions about the show, contact Show Chair Lynn Rothenberg at art@spencertownacademy.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2a4ac7a9-ba41-4286-b576-f981bd14fea5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b7447a11-2b96-4d4e-81ca-ab94e5ee00c7</id><title>4/8 - THE FACE OF CLIMATE CHANGE</title><updated>2019-03-01T20:14:51.208097+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Converge Las Cruces&lt;br/&gt;📍 Las Cruces, NM, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/08/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.convergelascruces.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Face Of Climate Change&lt;br/&gt;A Photographic Exhibition at the Southwest Environmental Center&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Converge Las Cruces, exhibiting at the Cottonwood Gallery at the Southwest Environmental Center in Las Cruces, New Mexico, announces The Face of Climate Change, a juried group photography exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Global warming, rising sea levels, shrinking habitats and extreme weather are all well known effects of climate change. The exhibition: The Face of Climate Change, will examine through a photographers eye the changes occurring around us everyday. The exhibition seeks to document, comment and share our current visual environmental status. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition will run from May 1, 2019 to June 14, 2019 at the Southwest Environmental Center, a non-profit  grassroots conservation organization based in Las Cruces, New Mexico. (www.wildmesquite.org). 10% of the entry fees will be donated to further The Southwest Environmental Center mission to protect and restore native wildlife and their habitats in the Southwestern borderlands, through advocacy, education and on-the-ground projects&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Rules/Guidelines&lt;br/&gt;The photographers who are selected into the exhibition will be asked to provide a high resolution JPEG file for Converge Las Cruces gallery to print. Each image selected will be sized at 300 dpi 14" (4200 pixles) on the long side. We will professionally print one image each on lustre paper using a Epson archival ink jet printer. The images will be printed on 16” x 20” lustre paper and hung with a top and bottom print hanger. All exhibition prints will be kept in a flat file after the close of the exhibition to further promote the participating photographers. Converge Las Cruces will shred all gallery prints after one (1) year.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee: &lt;br/&gt;$35.00 (Entry includes up to 4 images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application for submission can be found at: &lt;br/&gt;https://thefaceofclimatechange.artcall.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b7447a11-2b96-4d4e-81ca-ab94e5ee00c7" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>80593127-7ab9-4200-b8e5-7b3954de89c3</id><title>4/23 - Opposites: A National Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-03-01T20:14:51.208022+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Attleboro Arts Museum&lt;br/&gt;📍 ATTLEBORO, MA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/23/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.AttleboroartsMuseum.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call for Artists: OPPOSITES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A National Juried Exhibition at the Attleboro Arts Museum - Attleboro, MA&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On view June 12–July 12, 2019. Opening Reception: June 15th, 2-4pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Open to all mediums, sizes and interpretations of OPPOSITES. The Attleboro Arts Museum asks, “What’s the difference?”  A call for artists to explore opposition in nature, qualities, direction, result, or significance.  Six prizes of $100 each will be awarded.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Guidelines: Each artist may submit up to two different entries of original artwork (we cannot accept giclée reproductions). All mediums and  interpretations of OPPOSITES from US artists will be juried. There is no size limit, however all entries (both 2D &amp; 3D) cannot weigh over 100 lbs each. Work must not have been previously exhibited at the Attleboro Arts Museum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Specifications: Each artist may submit a maximum of two different entries. Artists can submit 2D, 3D, installation, audio or video work. If selected, all technology for video or audio pieces must be supplied by the artist. Each file must be named with the title of the piece and the artist’s last name (example: SavorySweet_Jones.jpg).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry fees: $18 covers payment for up to two entries for Museum members; $25 covers up to two entries for non-members. You can join as a member when you pay for your submission(s).  All fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Deadline: Tuesday, April 23rd at 11:59 PM, Mountain Time (MT). Entries that are emailed or hand-delivered will not be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notification of Decision: All artists will receive notification of the juror’s decision sent to the email address that they have provided by Tuesday, May 14th at 7 PM, MT. Additionally, all accepted works will be posted on www.attleboroartsmuseum.org.  All artists are expected to check the in-box of the email that they provided and/or the Museum’s website listing for notification of the juror’s decision. Please no inquiries.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IF YOUR ARTWORK IS ACCEPTED:&lt;br/&gt;(All artists submitting work should familiarize themselves with the guidelines and dates listed below. There are no exceptions to these requirements. Thank you for your cooperation).  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Delivery of All Accepted Work: To properly record and install all accepted pieces, all work (and detailed hanging instructions, if applicable) must be delivered between May 15th and June 1st, from 10 AM – 3 PM, EST.  We’re closed Sundays &amp; Mondays, and Saturday, May 25th. We cannot accept your artwork before May 15th or after June 1st. Accepted work can be either hand-delivered or shipped to the Attleboro Arts Museum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Installation artwork must be delivered within the timeframe listed above&lt;br/&gt;Artists with installations that require their assembly are asked to return to the Museum at time that is agreed upon with Museum staff&lt;br/&gt;Artists are asked to provide all installation hardware and necessary equipment&lt;br/&gt;You can arrange to send a representative to deliver and/or pick up your artwork for you. The Attleboro Arts Museum is not responsible for making these arrangements for exhibiting artists.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Once artwork is delivered it cannot, for any reason, leave the gallery until the exhibition concludes.  Please make note of the exhibition dates.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Wet paint will not be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Mark all accepted artwork with the artist’s name, address, city/state/zip, phone, email, title of piece, dimensions (w x h x d), weight (no more than 100 lbs) and sale price (if applicable). Download an OPPOSITES Loan Agreement and Delivery Checklist from www.attleboroartsmuseum.org and submit with your accepted artwork.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists are responsible for all payments associated with the shipping of their work.  All shipped work must include: 1) $10 handling fee – per piece, 2) Pre-paid return shipping label, 3) Payment of shipping vendor’s pick-up fee, 4) A photo of your art on the outside of your package, 5) A completed OPPOSITES Loan Agreement and Delivery Checklist.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Send to: Attleboro Arts Museum, OPPOSITES, 86 Park St., Attleboro, MA, 02703.  Fees are non-refundable. Checks payable to Attleboro Arts Museum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Presentation: All accepted work must be framed, gallery-wrapped or finished on the edges and ready to hang at delivery with a sturdy wire hanging system. See the Museum’s website Exhibitions &amp; Events/Framing Guidelines for details. We recommend neutral frames and white or off-white mats. Any pieces that do not match the juror’s decision, or are not the piece that was accepted, will not be installed, and will be returned COD.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sales: All art sales are subject to the Museum’s commission of 30% for Museum members, 40% for non-members. Work does not need to be for sale.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Insurance: The Attleboro Arts Museum will insure all work from the date of arrival at the Museum through the stated pick-up dates. The maximum insurance amount covers up to an artist’s value of $2000, with a $500 deductible payable by the artist. The Museum is not responsible for loss or damage in shipping, or for insuring art during shipping. Art left beyond the final pick-up date of July 17th at 3 PM EST, will not be insured.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In-person Pick-up of Exhibited Work: July 13th, July 16th and 17th; 10 AM – 3 PM, EST. Work left beyond July 17th at 3 PM, EST will be charged $5 per day per piece, payable at late pickup.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Return of Work–Shipped by the Museum: All work will be packed and shipped by July 19th. You must enclose pre-paid shipping labels for the return of your work (that also covers the shipping vendor’s pick-up fee) and a $10 handling fee per piece. Checks payable to Attleboro Arts Museum.  If you are within driving distance we would appreciate an in-person pick-up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=5654" target="_blank"&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/80593127-7ab9-4200-b8e5-7b3954de89c3" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>