<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-13T15:48:28-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>6002bcf2-7474-40d6-a62f-77a71dcd3655</id><title>3/16 - Crystal Park Open Call for outdoor artwork</title><updated>2019-02-13T15:48:28.078641+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Crystal Park&lt;br/&gt;📍 Holmes, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/16/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.crystalpark.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artwork on the rocks along the trail - A creative look for the rock trail&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The rock trail starts from the Crystal Park gate and is about 0.6 mile with rocks placed along the two sides of the trail. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Artists are invited to propose artwork to be placed on/with the rocks as long as the artwork doesn’t obstruct the trail nor cause any safety concern. &lt;br/&gt;•	Please consider the nature outdoor setting. Materials that can withstand the weather and be integrated with the environment are preferred. &lt;br/&gt;•	Selected artist will have access to woodshop and metal shop to fabricate the work if needed. (Fabrication facility location: Flushing, Queens, NY)&lt;br/&gt;•	Crystal Park will provide assistance for the artist to install the work. &lt;br/&gt;•	Artist fee: $5,000&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Please submit the following documents:&lt;br/&gt;o	Drawings or/and rendering images/videos of the proposed artwork&lt;br/&gt;o	Project statement&lt;br/&gt;o	Detailed description of the artwork&lt;br/&gt;o	Artist bio and resume&lt;br/&gt;o	Artwork sample images (Maximum 20 images in jpeg, each under 5MB)&lt;br/&gt;o	Estimated budget&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Email the submission to &lt;br/&gt;info@crystalpark.org by March 16th 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Images and videos of the rock trail:&lt;br/&gt;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1ZaCmYh3Lk7Aw7k4hfK3ntRn8BtpC6MA-&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information about Crystal Park:&lt;br/&gt;www.crystalpark.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please address any question to: &lt;br/&gt;info@crystalpark.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;info@crystalpark.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6002bcf2-7474-40d6-a62f-77a71dcd3655" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f465d717-f518-4c8d-8b02-6eb2966416e3</id><title>3/10 - OPEN CALL: Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists</title><updated>2019-02-13T15:48:28.078599+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Friend of The Artist&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.friendoftheartist.com/application/?utm_source=NYFA&amp;amp;utm_medium=NYFA&amp;amp;utm_campaign=9"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FOA is a publication dedicated to elevating the work of emerging artists around the world. Our publication releases as a hardcover art book every quarter. It includes the work of artists who work in a variety of mediums, informative articles, and interviews. Accepted artists will have a four page spread of their work, information, and artist statement. Volume 9 will be juried by Alice Bonno, Erika B. Hess, Masha Vlasova, and FOA staff.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Volume 9 will be printed in hardback on premium color paper and are available online through booksellers like Amazon, Barnes and Noble, and are available in catalogs for libraries and bookstore distribution.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details of the Volume 9 Open Call:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Winners Receive&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3 works published in Volume 9, complimentary digital copy of publication, social media post of work, Discounts on publications for family and friends, and free digital access to future publications&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$25 for 5 Images&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;March 8, 2019 (midnight, CST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists of all academic disciples are welcome to apply. This includes painting, sculpture, photography, installation, new media, and performance art. Please do not submit videos since we are unable to publish.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guest Jurors&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Alice Bonnot&lt;br/&gt;Erika B. Hess&lt;br/&gt;Masha Vlasova&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Alice Bonnot is an independent curator and art consultant based in London. She is the co-founding director of Picnic, a contemporary art space occupying a long window in the Aylesham Centre in Peckham, London, and the founding director of the Zone d’Utopie Temporaire (Z.U.T.) residency programme, a nomadic annual residency addressing the notion of Utopia as a vehicle for artistic and critical comment. With this residency she curated exhibitions and events in Paris, London, Athens and Lisbon.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As an independent curator Alice organised a broad range of exhibitions for galleries, institutions and artist-run spaces. Her current exhibition Hyper Mesh(18 Jan – 23 Feb 2019) at Assembly Point, London, is an exhibition that brings together new work from eight international artists; Jonathan Baldock, Pauline Bastard, fleuryfontaine, Holly Hendry, Jessie Makinson, Morgan Wills and Fani Parali. The exhibition explores contemporary notions of identity, and sets out to examine how identity structures could be re-imagined or reconstructed. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Previous exhibitions include: Engine, Picnic, London, 2018,Bored but secured, Wozen, Lisbon, 2018,  Acts of disruption, The Concept Space, London, 2018, A series of pocket Utopias, Yellow Brick and Snehta, Athens, 2017, Right Through You, The Koppel Project Hive, London, 2017, Le corps comme activateur d’art numérique, Le Carreau du Temple, Paris, 2015, Prix Canson finalists, Palais de Tokyo, Paris / co-curated with Mr Laurent Boudier, 2015. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Erika B Hess  is a painter based in Columbus, OH recognized for her use and interest in color. Hess’s work has been exhibited nationally including Prince Street Gallery in NYC, Last Projects in Los Angles, CA, and Boston Center for the Arts in Boston, MA. In 2017, she had two solo exhibitions, “The Line Between the Past and the Present,” at the Musa Collective, Allston MA and “Viewing Light,” at Newton Free Library, Newton, MA. Her work has been featured in various publications including, Poets and Artists, Fresh Paint, Charles River Journal and Post Industrial Complex, a book released by the Museum of Contemporary Art Detroit. Her work was selected by John Seed to be featured in, “Fifty Memorable Artists 2015”. She has served on panels such as Cleveland Institute of Art’s, “Feminism Now: Exposing the Truth”, was a visiting juror for Dayton Visual Art Center’s 2016-2018 biennial, and is a recurring juror for the Walker Art MFA Prize at Boston University. Hess is a co-founder of Musa Collective, an artist collective in Boston and is the creator of I Like Your Work podcast, a podcast dedicated to interviewing artists, curators and collectors. Hess received her MFA from Boston University.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Masha Vlasova is an interdisciplinary artist, filmmaker, and educator. She holds a BFA from the Cooper Union and an MFA from Yale School of Art. She is a recipient the Fulbright Fellowship in Filmmaking, Alice Kimball Fellowship and the JUNCTURE Art and Human Rights Fellowship at Yale Law School. Her works have been exhibited and screened at Smack Mellon, Anthology Archives, and Abrons Arts Center in New York, Vox Populi and Temple University in Philadelphia, Carpenter Centerfor the Visual Artsat Harvard University among others. Her latest curatorial project “Women Filmmakers at the Intersection of Documentary, Video Art, and Avant Garde,” premiered at Indiana University Cinema in Bloomington, IN Fall of 2018. Her forthcoming essay about monument rotation will be published in a collection titled Monument Culture: International Perspectives on the Future of Monuments in a Changing World by the American Association for State and Local History/Rowman &amp; Littlefield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at friendoftheartist.com/application&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Email contact@friendoftheartist.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f465d717-f518-4c8d-8b02-6eb2966416e3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8f1f9a24-9742-4158-9b4c-d28a877b7d73</id><title>3/15 - Young Curators, New Ideas V</title><updated>2019-02-13T15:48:28.078542+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Detroit Art Week&lt;br/&gt;📍 Detroit, MI, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://detroitartweek.org/young-curators-new-ideas-v"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call for Exhibition Proposals&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Detroit Art Week(July 16 –21, 2019), an annual self-guided tour and citywide celebration of contemporary art in Detroit produced by Olu &amp; Company, is now accepting applications from independent curators for the 5th iteration of “Young Curators, New Ideas.” In 2008, Detroit Art Week Founding Director, Amani Olu, established “Young Curators, New Ideas” to promote and support emerging curatorial voices. After a six-year hiatus, “Young Curators, New Ideas V” will take place from Wednesday, July 17 to Sunday, July 21, 2019 at Trumbull &amp; Porter Hotel Detroit, our exclusive hospitality partner. The deadline to apply is January 30, 2019.For more information and to apply, please visit &lt;a href="https://detroitartweek.org." target="_blank"&gt;https://detroitartweek.org.&lt;/a&gt; Featuring 12 independent curators selected from an international open call, “Young Curators, New Ideas V” will shine a light on the cultural, artistic, social and political transformations initiated by women, LGBTQIA and gender-non-conforming individuals through their creative, and at times independent, curatorial practices. With a sense of relevance and urgency, these multifaceted and dynamic micro-exhibitions will consider contemporary issues that exist at the intersection of curatorial practice and artistic production. Within a 256 square-foot hotel room, each curator will present one to two artists whose work is a thoughtful and provocative discussion on the most pressing issues of our time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Since its inception, “Young Curators, New Ideas” has presented exhibitions by 31 independent curators featuring 104 artists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Requirements&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Applicant Curriculum Vitae&lt;br/&gt;• Narrative Bio – up to 200 words&lt;br/&gt;• A short synopsis of the exhibition – up to 75 words&lt;br/&gt;• Detailed exhibition proposal – up to 1000 words&lt;br/&gt;• Artist 1 Bio – up to 200 words, CV, website or Insta&lt;br/&gt;• Artist 2 Bio – up to 200 words, CV, website or Insta&lt;br/&gt;• All applications submitted will be considered final. Applicants will not be permitted to edit an application once it has been sent. We will disqualify all incomplete or duplicate applications.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note: &lt;br/&gt;• There is no “save” option. Save your application in a separate document before submitting. &lt;br/&gt;• We will not accept applications after March 15, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;• We will not accept proposals nor applications via email.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8f1f9a24-9742-4158-9b4c-d28a877b7d73" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>