<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-08-02T09:18:27-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>c30d12fb-bf88-4b8c-bb20-b34d406fee31</id><title>9/1 - Sanctuary Cities and the Politics of the American Dream - Call for Entry</title><updated>2019-08-02T09:18:27.976500+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Creative Arts Workshop&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Haven, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.creativeartsworkshop.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creative Arts Workshop invites all artists, activists, thinkers and dreamers to explore the concept of sanctuary and its attendant concerns: issues of place, dislocation, migration, human rights and morality, cultural identity and belonging. While the exhibition will primarily focus on the display of visual and performing work, we are also collecting scholarship and writing by poets, academics, social workers, service workers, healthcare providers, and other individuals working in non-art sectors who are contemplating the challenges the immigrant community has been facing. The exhibit will be curated by Luciana McClure and on view from October 3 - November 9, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please complete our online application at &lt;a href="http://www.creativeartsworkshop.org/sanctuary-entryform" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.creativeartsworkshop.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Direct questions to Luciana McClure at McClure.luciana@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c30d12fb-bf88-4b8c-bb20-b34d406fee31" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ad73b393-893b-4ed3-a2a2-6b674e548d2a</id><title>9/9 - Request for Qualifications Golden Triangle BID &amp;amp;  Smithsonian American Women&amp;#39;s History Initiative</title><updated>2019-08-02T09:18:27.976442+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Golden Triangle Business Improvement District&lt;br/&gt;📍 Washington, DC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2JZsmZo"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calling all emerging and mid-career artists. The Golden Triangle Business Improvement District (BID) and the Smithsonian American Women’s History Initiative invite you to submit your qualifications to be considered for a public art project to be installed along Connecticut Avenue in 2020. We’re seeking one project that aims to pay tribute to women and their history in our shared public spaces. The artworks will be located in the heart of DC’s central business district on the Connecticut Avenue Median (at K Street NW). &lt;br/&gt;Both new and existing works are eligible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Budgets of up to $35,000 will be considered for the projects. Fees for artists/artist teams cannot exceed 20% of the total project budget. Up to five semi-finalists may be selected to create concept proposals. Finalists will receive a design proposal stipend.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT The Smithsonian American Women’s History Initiative&lt;br/&gt;The Smithsonian launched the Smithsonian American Women’s History Initiative—Because Of Her Story—in 2018. The initiative is one of the country’s most ambitious undertakings to research, collect, document, display and share the compelling story of women, which is inclusive of all persons who identify as female or have a history of being designated female but identify differently.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More info on the Smithsonian American Women’s History Initiative at: www.womenshistory.si.edu/about &lt;br/&gt;More info on Golden Triangle Arts at: www.goldentriangledc.com/initiatives-public-art/ &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All qualifications must be submitted online here:&lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2JZsmZo&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: September 9, 2019, 11:59PM (EDT)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOW TO SUBMIT YOUR PROPOSAL&lt;br/&gt;Materials must be submitted electronically via Jotform by: &lt;br/&gt;11:59PM (EDT) on September 9 2019.&lt;br/&gt;Submit here: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2JZsmZo" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;QUESTIONS?&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Karyn Miller, Public Space Activation Curator &lt;br/&gt;Golden Triangle Business Improvement District&lt;br/&gt;kmiller@goldentriangledc.com or 202-684-8924&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ad73b393-893b-4ed3-a2a2-6b674e548d2a" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>