<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-09T06:48:21-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>916dd2a5-da06-4dbe-ab72-af584a22d549</id><title>2/21 - Grennpoint Gallery February People&amp;#39;s Choice Salon Show- WIN $200 AND A SOLO SHOW!</title><updated>2019-02-09T06:48:21.553358+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our February People's Choice Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, February 22nd, 2019 at 8pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, February 21st, 2019 at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;For this show, we let the people decide, which means everyone who attends votes for the winners! We pass out ballots at the door and everyone who attends chooses the winners! It is always one of our most well attended nights, boasting record art sales and a large community of fellow artists and art lovers!&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of local bands!&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, February 21st at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces in the $150-$500 range. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/916dd2a5-da06-4dbe-ab72-af584a22d549" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>47be78c0-bb97-4da6-b170-627c86a80f35</id><title>3/14 - Photography Series and Repetition</title><updated>2019-02-09T06:48:21.553295+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.sitebrooklyn.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photography Series and Repetition &lt;br/&gt;May 3, 2019 – June 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This show seeks to exhibit the diverse and exciting ways that photographers use sequence and series in their work. Repetition and seriality are built into the every level of photography from the production process, to its aesthetic theory, to the real-life practice of taking pictures. Photographs are often seen as representations or repetitions of reality itself, all while photography itself shapes modern consciousness just as much as it re-creates it. Site:Brooklyn is looking for work that actively engages with all aspects of repetition and series in photography. This might include subject matter, formal qualities, method, presentation, and much else.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Elisabeth Biondi has been an independent curator, writer. Before that she was the Visuals Editor of The New Yorker for 15 years, where she shaped the look of the publication by establishing a group of staff photographers, commissioning both masters and emerging talent. She built the magazine’s reputation for its use of photography, for which it received numerous awards, including two National Magazine Awards. Her independent curation includes Subjective/Objective and Under the Bridge for the New York PhotoFestival and New Yorker Fiction/Real Photography at Steven Kasher Gallery in Chelsea. Most recently she was a judge in the eight-episodes Sky Arts ‘Master of Photography’, which aired in May/June/July of 2018.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: February 7, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: March 14, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: March 23, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: May 3 – June 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, May 3, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in photography. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $35.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by March 14, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:&lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2E07jCW&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 60” X 60” X 6” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Photographs printed and mounted on aluminum, plexiglass, sintra and dibond require a cleat for hanging.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;5. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Photography Series and Repetition” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2E07jCW" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/47be78c0-bb97-4da6-b170-627c86a80f35" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>