<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml</id><title>open-calls-7</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>34af0358-8ac2-4e73-9a08-dad10f5b41fb</id><title>10/25 - OPEN CALL FOR ARTISTS - AUTUMN IN NY ART FAIR</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756648+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;INTERNATIONAL ART FESTIVAL&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.newartfestival.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call for Artists&lt;br/&gt;IAF Exhibition &amp; Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;23 Warren Street, Tribeca, New York City&lt;br/&gt;November 7-10, 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Register at our website:  &lt;a href="http://newartfestival.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://newartfestival.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Upload several images representative of your work and add your artist statement.&lt;br/&gt;Pay the $10 Application Fee to submit your application&lt;br/&gt;This fee will be credited towards the participation fee, upon application approval.&lt;br/&gt;We will review your work and will be in touch very soon.&lt;br/&gt;(Check the email with which you register at &lt;a href="http://newartfestival.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://newartfestival.com&lt;/a&gt; website).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Participation at the IAF exhibit is subject to approval by the IAF Curators and the receipt of the full payment. If you are approved for participation, you need to prepay for the exhibition wall space that you require.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For complete information please follow this link: &lt;br/&gt;http://newartfestival.com/page/termsconditions2019.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/34af0358-8ac2-4e73-9a08-dad10f5b41fb" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>20c8db5f-c6a5-4aae-a81d-4eb951dd9b8d</id><title>11/6 - New Prints 2020/Winter Exhibition Open Call</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756620+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;International Print Center New York&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Printmaking&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://ipcny.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Prints 2020/Winter will be the 61st presentation of IPCNY's New Prints Program. Established in 2000, the New Prints Program is a biannual, juried open call for prints and print-based work created in the preceding twelve months. Artists selected for the exhibition will also be invited to apply for IPCNY's New Prints Artist Development Program consisting of three opportunities: an artist residency, artist mentorship program, and sponsored coursework.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juried by Ariana Barat, artist, activist, and Printmaking Facilities Manager at Parsons School of Design; Gregory Burnet, artist, Master Printer, and Owner of Burnet Editions, New York; Orit Mardkha-Tenzer, artist, graphic designer, and instructor of graphic design at City College of New York; and Keris Salmon, visual artist and storyteller.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply online today at ipcny.submittable.com. We encourage you to apply as early as possible. The deadline is 11:59PM EST on Wednesday, November 6, 2019. Applications received after the deadline will not be accepted. There is no fee to apply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION GUIDELINES&lt;br/&gt;– Artists who have exhibited in New Prints within the past 2 years (New Prints 2018/Winter, 2018/Summer, 2019/Winter, and 2019/Summer) may NOT submit their work for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;– Editioned prints, unique printed works, printed installations, artist’s books, print-based animations, and ephemeral formats are eligible.&lt;br/&gt;– Photography or direct reproductions of other artworks, such as drawings or paintings, are NOT eligible.&lt;br/&gt;– Prints must have been completed within 12 months of the beginning of the open call. (Works created before September of 2018 are NOT eligible.)&lt;br/&gt;– Open internationally, no nationality requirements.&lt;br/&gt;– Artists may submit up to 3 works. Publishers and presses may submit up to 3 artists, with 3 works per artist.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;IMAGE REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;– Images should be in jpeg format, 72 dpi with longest dimension a maximum of 1,000 pixels. &lt;br/&gt;– Animations may be submitted as MP4, MOV, or FLV files. &lt;br/&gt;– Each file should be named as follows: artist's last name_first name_entry number. (For example: smith_john_01.jpg, smith_john_02.jpg, etc.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit your work at ipcny.submittable.com.&lt;br/&gt;For any questions, contact megan@ipcny.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/20c8db5f-c6a5-4aae-a81d-4eb951dd9b8d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7dabb657-2b54-474c-8720-18efe1dbbe07</id><title>11/4 - FALL SALON - Open Call for Art</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756592+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open&lt;br/&gt;📍 LIC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/04/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open is proud to announce our 4th Annual Salon as part of our recurring Fall Open Studios and Salon event.  We invite artists of all disciplines and mediums to participate in our Salon which will be on show at LIC Arts Open's Gallery ONE at The Factory LIC, 30-30 47th Ave, LIC, 11101.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We accept all disciplines including painting, sculpture, photography, video, installation and multi-media however video equipment is not provided and if your project requires technology please state so on the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are encouraging as many artists as possible to show in our 8000 sq foot gallery in one of LIC's signature buildings, The Factory.  It is likely that we will only reject work if it is not to a professional standard because we would like the exhibition to be as fully inclusive as possible and there is no 'theme'.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline Nov 4th 2019&lt;br/&gt;Notification Nov 6th 2019&lt;br/&gt;Reception November 14th 5pm - 8pm&lt;br/&gt;Please note there is an application fee which offsets the installation costs and helps to pay for the refreshments. If you have previously participated please select option 2 otherwise if new to LIC Arts Open please select option 1.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork should be dropped off on November 9th &amp; 10th between the hours of 2 -5 pm only.  We cannot accept work at other times.&lt;br/&gt;Work must be ready to hang and we do not allow shipping; all work must be hand-delivered on the designated times and dates.&lt;br/&gt;Gallery commission is 25% please price accordingly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply using this form : &lt;a href="https://www.jotform.com/trimistopheles/fall-salon-open-call" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;  You will need to cut and paste this into your browser&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7dabb657-2b54-474c-8720-18efe1dbbe07" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7ae6a65f-d7f5-410a-85ab-fbb44eea661b</id><title>10/17 - OPEN CALL: PURO COLOR! 2 at La Bodega Gallery in Brooklyn, NY</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756564+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;La Bodega Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.labodega-gallery.com/opportunities-1#/puro-color-2"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;La Bodega Gallery opened the doors with a mission to build bridges (not walls!) and bring people, art and ideas together to our Brooklyn community and beyond. We are committed to reaching out to underrepresented artists and providing a place to showcase their work. This show we are reaching out to artists of color who live in NYC.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Back by popular demand!! “PURO COLOR!” a color filled exhibition which promotes the talents of NYC artists of color who offer their unique perspectives through the use of colorful pigments. 2D and 3d work welcome! Curated by Miguel Ayuso.&lt;br/&gt;*****This year we will be adding a video component with a screening curated by Tiffany Joy Butler and Hot Cabinet. Videos will be included in a special screening on the night of the opening (directly afterwards) and then be played on a continuous loop during the run of the exhibition on a monitor in the gallery space. To submit video please visit our website for details&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition dates: &lt;br/&gt;November 1st – December 2nd, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION DEADLINE: &lt;br/&gt;10/17 11:59:59 pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: &lt;br/&gt;La Bodega Gallery, 695 5th Ave Brooklyn, NY &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Contact: &lt;br/&gt;submission.gallerylabodega@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Eligibility&lt;br/&gt;NYC ARTISTS ONLY. ALL SUBMISSIONS MUST BE RECEIVED BY 10/17 11:59:59 pm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to apply:&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;1. Submissions must be via email at submission.gallerylabodega@gmail.com. We require you to upload 1 - 3 images, your CV, and artist statement. Submission does not guarantee acceptance into the exhibition, all entrants will be notified on October 24th, 2019 (Video submissions must be made separately, please visit labodega-gallery.com for more details)&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 2. Cost of submission is $10 for up to 3 entries and $5 per every entry thereafter (maximum 5). It is a non-refundable fee and no changes of images can be made after you submit. Your submissions do not guarantee inclusion into a show.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 3. Your JPEGs data files must be labeled: First name Last &lt;br/&gt; name_Title of the piece_Medium_Height x Width in inches.jpg making sure that underscores go between your name and the name of the piece: (Jane Doe_Self-Portrait_Oil_32x40in.JPG). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  Artwork Submissions- Things to include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-Art work images (Correctly Labeled)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-Image list with a short description of each image (please also include dimensions &amp; medium)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-Artist Statement&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-CV&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-Submission Fee ($10 via paypal submission.gallerylabodega@gmail.com or via Venmo @LaBodega-Gallery)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Rules:&lt;br/&gt;Types of art accepted&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 4. All two-dimensional work including photography, paintings, drawings, digital, mixed media, fabric art, chalk, ink, pastels, wax, graphite and printmaking. Essentially, if we can hang it on a wall, we will consider your art for acceptance. We will also accept free standing sculptures and small sculptures that can fit on a pedestal. The maximum size for each piece submitted needs to be less than 40 inches on the longest side. Video work is accepted, details for video submissions on our website.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Shipping + presentation&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 5. If your submission is accepted, you will be notified with information for drop off or shipping your artwork(s) to the gallery. Please take care to ship your artwork carefully with padding and in ther event that it does not sell we will return it to you in the same box with the same padding. Artist is responsible for shipping cost both to/from the gallery (in the event the. work does not sell). The return postage can be a label or a bill of lading from either UPS, Fedex or UPS included with your artwork.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 6. All artwork must be received at least 3 days before the art reception.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 7. All works must be prepared and ready to hang. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Gallery commission&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 8. La Bodega Gallery retains the right to represent an artist in a sale of the artwork that was accepted and exhibited for the duration of the exhibition. All artworks will be offered for sale. The gallery takes a 50% commission on all sales.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 9. Accepted entries are represented by La Bodega Gallery for the duration of the exhibition, and artworks will be promoted on our website and other social media.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Gallery installation rules&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 10. La Bodega Gallery reserves the right to refuse to hang an artwork or exhibit it if it is radically different from the image that was submitted.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Copyright&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 11. Artist maintains copyright.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7ae6a65f-d7f5-410a-85ab-fbb44eea661b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ab6480fe-c317-4e0c-96bb-32b0c6c81a9d</id><title>10/15 - ASK Presents 2020 - Performing Arts open call</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756536+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arts Society of Kingston (ASK)&lt;br/&gt;📍 Kingston, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Performing Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.askforarts.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be a part of the ASK Presents 2020 performing arts season! Submit a proposal to perform a full-length work in ASK's 99-seat theater during our 2020 season (March-November). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each selected artist will receive a week of rehearsal time in the space, 3 performances (Fri, Sat and Sun) and 60% of the ticket sales. There is no fee to apply or perform!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To apply for our 2020 season, please fill out the online form:&lt;br/&gt;https://forms.gle/PCzxtPo9pDHv9bi78&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, email brent@askforarts.org or call 845.338.0333. Or visit us online at askforarts.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ab6480fe-c317-4e0c-96bb-32b0c6c81a9d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>67e583d2-af46-4113-b6fd-281ff145867f</id><title>10/13 - OPEN CALL: Publication Opportunity in Volume 11| Friend of The Artist</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756501+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Friend of The Artist&lt;br/&gt;📍 Dallas, TX, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/13/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.friendoftheartist.com/volume-11-application"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply to have your work considered in Volume 11 by Friend of the Artist. FOA is a quarterly book dedicated to elevating the work of emerging artists around the world. Our publication releases every quarter and includes the work of artists who work in a variety of mediums. Accepted artists will have a four-page spread of their work, information, and artist statement. Volume 11 will be guest juried by Anna Mikaela Ekstrand, Angeliki Kim Jonsson, and Adele Smejkal and will be available in our store and online retailers including Amazon and Barnes and Noble.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted Artists Receive&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted artists will have three works published in Volume 11, will receive a complimentary digital copy of the publication, social media post of work, discounts on books for family and friends, and free digital access to future publications.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$30 for 5 Images&lt;br/&gt;or&lt;br/&gt;$50 for 5 Images + Book&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;October 13, 2019 (midnight, CST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists of all academic disciples are welcome to apply. This includes painting, sculpture, photography, installation, and performance art. Works must be submitted in a printable format.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guest Jurors&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Anna Mikaela Ekstrand&lt;br/&gt;Editor-in-Chief Cultbytes and Independent Curator&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Angeliki Kim Jonsson&lt;br/&gt;co-founder of Art/choke and founder of DYNAMISK&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Adele Smejkal&lt;br/&gt;co-founder of Art/Choke, Client Liason at Sotheby’s London, and founder of @as_artjournal&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror bios:&lt;br/&gt;Anna Mikaela Ekstrand&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Anna Mikaela Ekstrand is a Swedish/Guyanese independent curator and publisher living in New York City. Although she curates across mediums, she is especially interested in exploring equitable ways to disseminate performance art. Anna Mikaela served as co-/curator for the performance art events 'Tales Of Tales' (106 Rivington, 2019), ’Grebnellaw: Sperming The Planet' (House of Yes and The Oculus, 2018), and 'Your Decolonizing Toolkit' (MAW, 2016). She has held curatorial positions at Metropolitan Museum of Art, Solomon R. Guggenheim, Bard Graduate Center, and Museum of Arts and Design. Deeply vested in research, she has worked on over a dozen in-museum and off-site art and design related exhibitions and their catalogs. Anna Mikaela is the founding editor-in-chief of Cultbytes, an online art publication that focuses on interdisciplinary and non-hierarchical art criticism. She holds dual MA degrees, in Design History, Material Culture, and Decorative Arts from Bard Graduate Center and in Art History from Stockholm University.&lt;br/&gt;Instagram: @cultbytes @annamikaela_x&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Angeliki Kim Jonsson &amp; Adele Smejkal&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are two art enthusiasts and professionals with a diverse experience of working in the art world. Angeliki Kim Jonsson is the founder of DYNAMISK an Independent consultancy that offers Curating and Art Advisory. Alongside DYNAMISK she also hosts “In Conversation with..” which is an ever growing series of vibrant and unique conversations with pioneering individuals from the art world. Adele Smejkal works for Sotheby’s London and is also a freelance journalist and the founder of @as_artjournal, an Instagram based page about art. Through a shared passion for art and presence on social media, we have formed our friendship and partnership. Our story, vision, and thinking alike inspired us to create the Art/choke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Questions? Email contact@friendoftheartist.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/67e583d2-af46-4113-b6fd-281ff145867f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ad5a7c54-d83d-4441-a16e-adb6996d62c3</id><title>11/10 - Call For Artists! 2019 Catalyst Small Works Show</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756473+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Catalyst Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Beacon, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.catalystgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th annual Catalyst Small Works, December 7, 2019 – January 12, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Painting, drawing, printmaking, photography, sculpture, mixed media of many kinds will be considered. No video. 16" max size. Full guidelines on website, or see below. Two part submission: 1) Submit entry fee via Square or check; 2) Email images and complete info to gallery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit up to four quality jpegs (labeled w/your last name and/or title) to info@catalystgallery.com. Include in the email your name, email, address, phone number, website, instagram, and title/media/dimensions/price of each work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry fee is $30 for up to four images. Fee is payable by credit card through this link to Square: https://squareup.com/store/catalyst-gallery or by check (payable to Catalyst Gallery and mailed to Catalyst Gallery, 137 Main St, Beacon NY 12508). You may include 1 additional image per 3D work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guidelines for Submissions&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Size must be no larger than 16″ in any direction for 2D including frame, and 20″ for 3D. The work must arrive clean, professional and ready to hang. This may mean wired or with hardware attached. 3-D pieces must be self-supporting or wall-mounted.&lt;br/&gt;Works on paper must be framed or mounted. It is helpful if images include frame (if any) or description of proposed framing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Price limit is $500. When selecting &amp; pricing your work, please consider that affordability will increase the likelihood of sales during the holiday season. This is a fun and popular show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Gallery retains a 25% commission on sold work. Artists will receive payment after the show closes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We encourage early entries. Deadline to submit images via email is Sun Nov 10, 11:59 pm EST. Accepted artists will be notified which works have been selected. Notifications to all entrants will be emailed by Sun Nov 17.&lt;br/&gt;If high-quality prints/cards/select objects are available of similar works by accepted artists, we may offer them for sale (unframed, priced and in clear bag w/backing) in our shop; the same 25% commission applies. Indicate interest and brief description.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Delivery of Work&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If accepted, artists must deliver work in person, or ship. Drop-off dates will be Sat Nov 23, Sun Nov 24 and Sun Dec 1 (10am-12pm), and Mon Dec 2 (6-8pm). Shipped work must arrive by Dec 2.&lt;br/&gt;Accepted artists must notify us beforehand if you plan to ship your work and we will provide the address. Do not ship to gallery. Artists must cover all shipping expenses. A computer-generated return label for return of work must be enclosed. Pre-paid shipping arrangements must be made through UPS, FedEx, or USPS. Gallery is not responsible for work arriving damaged or late. Great care will be taken with all work, but artists are responsible for insuring their own work if they wish. **The gallery proprietors retain the final word on what will be in the exhibition and how the art will be installed.**&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The opening reception is Sat Dec 7, 6-9pm. Also open til 9 for Beacon’s Second Sat, Dec 14. Gallery hours will be Fri-Sun 12-6pm with additional hours tba. There will be a closing reception Sat Jan 11, 5-8pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Return of Work&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Pick-up dates will be Sun Jan 12 (4-7pm), Mon Jan 13 (10am-12pm and 5-7pm). Other arrangements can be made if necessary. Unsold work must be picked up unless return shipping has been arranged. If work is not picked up by Jan 31 it will become property of the gallery.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ad5a7c54-d83d-4441-a16e-adb6996d62c3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0935f480-70db-4d22-bad2-7ef4bfdb3acf</id><title>10/10 - Open Call All Mediums! WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!  Friday Oct 11th 2019</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756445+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our Oct&lt;br/&gt;11th Open Call Juried Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, Oct. 11th , 2019 from 8pm- 12am.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, Oct. 10th, 2019 at 8pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is a Juried Salon style show. We have a panel of esteemed judges who will choose the winners! &lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We'll have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of Musical Guests.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up their work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, Oct 10th at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces already this past year. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com  Instagram: @ Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Facebookhttps://www.facebook.com/events/505946763471078/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0935f480-70db-4d22-bad2-7ef4bfdb3acf" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>596ce1c1-0fa6-478b-99f9-972930816152</id><title>10/7 - Request for Artist Proposals</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756416+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;FringeArts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Performing Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/07/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.fringearts.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FringeArts seeks Artists to submit proposals for large scale, public-practice performance that will be presented in the 24th annual Fringe Festival in September 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FringeArts defines public-practice performance as participatory work in which Philadelphia residents with a myriad of relationships to the arts perform a piece for an audience. FringeArts received a New Audiences New Places grant from the William Penn Foundation in the spring of 2018. This grant, titled Fringe Populi: Building Audiences through Public Performance, seeks to “build new audiences through large-scale public practice works [that] generate both wide attention through scale, spectacle, and resonance of content,” and that provide “more focused, deeper engagement with individuals recruited to participate in the work.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Previous examples of public practice pieces stewarded by FringeArts include Le Grand Continental (2012, Sylvain Émard), 100% Philadelphia (2014, Rimini Protokoll), Gala (2016, Jerôme Bel), Le Super Grand Continental (2018, Sylvain Émard), and Úumbal: Nomadic Choreography for Inhabitants (2019, Mariana Arteaga). The 2020 Fringe Populi piece will be the culminating performance in the Fringe Populi New Audiences New Places grant that aims to break down perception barriers which keep the Philadelphia public from engaging in contemporary performance.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Artist’s piece should aim to engage between 100-250 performers at varying levels of engagement and commitment. Artist proposals will provide a clear outline of project dramaturgy, recruitment, rehearsal structure, and performance. The priorities of the Fringe Populi project are to cultivate wide encounters of contemporary performance with the Philadelphia public, present work that is free and outdoors, and to engage with civically-activated spaces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposal applications open on Monday, September 9th and are due back to FringeArts by 5:00pm on Monday, October 7th. Please read the Fringe Populi Requirements and Guidelines closely before starting your application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To apply, please fill out this form.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Email programming@fringearts.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proposal applications open on Monday, September 9th and are due back to FringeArts by 5:00pm on Monday, October 7th. Please read the Fringe Populi Requirements and Guidelines closely before starting your application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To apply, please fill out this form.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Email programming@fringearts.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/596ce1c1-0fa6-478b-99f9-972930816152" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>480aab15-53f4-401c-b67c-f4c5af509429</id><title>10/1 - PhotoWeek NYC,  [October 14-19th] *OPEN CALL FOR PHOTOGRAPHERS BASED IN NYC*</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756386+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Pollinate Art + Martin Bough Project&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/gssX3PkC3AcFRvj1A"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deadline: Apply by October 3rd, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: October 14-19th, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Free submission entry&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Pollinate and The Martin Bough Project is excited to present the first edition of PhotoWeek NYC that will feature 15 photographers exhibited in 15 local businesses' storefronts. Artworks will be available for purchase online thanks to QR codes that visitors and passersby will be able to scan with their smartphones. 100% of the sales will go to the artists.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Concept:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PhotoWeek is New York City’s street-wide photography exhibition that works directly with local businesses and undeveloped land to help drive foot traffic to the stores that give the city its unique character. Starting on 27th Street (Fashion Institute of Technology) and finishing on 14th Street, 7th Avenue (The New School) the exhibition will provide a platform to the city’s aspiring artists and photographers by giving them a unique way to showcase their work. A reinvention of the retail experience, PhotoWeek will provide a reason for New York residents to re-engage with the businesses on their block by building community, driving commerce, and fostering creative collaboration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Drawing on the PhotoWeek Friends and Family we will host pop-up walking tours (1 per day) hosted by influencers from the creative and business community. Tour guides include award-winning entrepreneurs (Gary Vaynerchuk, Bonin Bough), advertising world luminaries (David Droga, Hannah Broffman), Grammy Award-Winning musical artists (Wyclef Jean), c-suite executives from creative businesses (Adobe, Kodak, Canon USA).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility: Artists must be located in NYC. We embrace diversity and encourage photographers from all backgrounds to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists must have photos already printed but we will provide frames. We have 16x20 inch black frames available and mats precut for 8" × 10" prints. We will have art handlers to help for the installation but we welcome and encourage the artists to help out during installation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected photographers will be notified through email on October 7th&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Pollinate: &lt;br/&gt;Pollinate is a platform dedicated to connecting emerging artists with their audiences online and in real life, through exhibitions hosted in underutilized spaces and local venues. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About The Martin Bough Project: &lt;a href="http://instagram.com/martinboughproject" target="_blank"&gt;http://instagram.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*Submit 5-10 photos by October 3rd through the website link*&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/480aab15-53f4-401c-b67c-f4c5af509429" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>21347d5d-51be-4b71-952f-d724d3bdc9b4</id><title>10/5 - The NO!ART Show</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756358+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;THE CENTER FOR CONTEMPOARY POLITICAL ART&lt;br/&gt;📍 Washington, DC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/05/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.politicsartus.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This open call exhibition will present original works of art that 1) picture politically-motivated hate; 2) protest politically-inspired hate; and 3) graphic designs for a national symbol to be worn or otherwise displayed by those individuals,organizations and businesses which repudiate hate and reject its use as a political tactic and/or central tenant of a political party or movement's appeal or a political leader's philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists resident in the United States, 17 years of age or older, are eligible to submit one or two works of art for the jury's consideration. INSTRUCTIONS and ELECTRONIC ENTRY FORM are found at www.politicsartus.org/entries. For additional information, artists may  contact Charles Krause by email or text: charles@politicsartus.org or 202-412-2324&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/21347d5d-51be-4b71-952f-d724d3bdc9b4" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>5c2a06fa-40d8-491a-9216-edb54dbe97a0</id><title>11/13 - Barrett National Juried Solo Shows 2020</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756326+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Barrett Art Center (Dutchess County Art Association)&lt;br/&gt;📍 Poughkeepsie, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/13/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.barrettartcenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barrett Solo Shows 2020&lt;br/&gt;Entry Deadline: November 13,  2019&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Ashley James, Assistant Curator, Contemporary Art, Brooklyn Museum&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Barrett Art Center offers opportunities for established and emerging artists to exhibit their work in our historic gallery setting.  In 2020, BAC will host four (4) solo shows in our Crenson Gallery, held in conjunction with exhibitions in the main galleries.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Opening Receptions on first day of show, Saturday, 3-6pm&lt;br/&gt;2020 Show Dates:&lt;br/&gt;January 25 – March 7&lt;br/&gt;May 16 – June 20&lt;br/&gt;October 10 – November 14&lt;br/&gt;November 28 – December 19&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Barrett Art Center seeks solo show proposals for shows: drawing, painting, pastel, printmaking, photography, sculpture, fiber, digital and mixed-media works are eligible. This presents a unique opportunity for a solo show in a landmark historic townhouse from the 1840s.  We invite proposals of both contemporary and traditional approaches that create a visually-compelling complement, or counterpoint, to Barrett Art Center’s 1840s Greek Revival townhouse architecture.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror: Ashley James&lt;br/&gt;Ashley James comes to the Brooklyn Museum from the Department of Drawings and Prints at the Museum of Modern Art, where she was a Mellon Research Consortium fellow assisting on the forthcoming Charles White and Adrian Piper retrospectives. James is a Ph.D. candidate in the Departments of African American Studies; English Literature; and Women’s, Gender, and Sexuality Studies at Yale University. She holds an M.A. and an M.Phil. in English Literature and an M.A. and an M.Phil. in African American Studies from Yale. At Yale she co-curated the 2014 University Art Gallery exhibition Odd Volumes: Book Art from the Allan Chasanoff Collection. She writes broadly on modern and contemporary literary and visual arts practices, and her dissertation reconsiders the relationship between politics, art, and blackness in the late 1960s.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Four proposals will be chosen to exhibit in the Crenson Gallery for shows in 2020. Criteria for review will include technical and artistic execution, a cohesive body of work or coherent theme, and overall artistic merit.  Gallery size and structural capacity will also play a role in submission selection.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Marketing strategies employed for exhibition include: Press releases submitted to print and electronic media outlets in the Hudson Valley with consistent local newspaper coverage. Online: weekly newsletter; page on website; Facebook &amp; Instagram.  Barrett Art Center hosts over 4,000 annual visitors and its e-newsletter has over 2,500 subscribers.  Artists may present an artist talk during the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notification of decisions will be sent to applicants on or about the first week of December, via email coming from CaFE&lt;br/&gt;Artists selected to present Solo Shows are required to pay a gallery fee to support Barrett community programming and the upkeep of our historic building. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Exhibition Dates and Gallery Fees:&lt;br/&gt;January 25 – March 7:   BAC Members - $125; Non-Members - $150&lt;br/&gt;May 16 – June 20:   BAC Members - $125 Non-Members - $150&lt;br/&gt;October 10 – November 14:   BAC Members - $125 Non-Members - $150&lt;br/&gt;November 28 December 19:   BAC Members - $120; Non-Members - $140&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Entries may be submitted to Call for Entry: &lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=7011" target="_blank"&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5c2a06fa-40d8-491a-9216-edb54dbe97a0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c77577c2-afbc-48ff-b208-b82d7a46740c</id><title>10/10 - New Orleans Exhibitions, Residencies, and Publishing, with $$, Travel, and More!</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756293+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Antenna&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Orleans, LA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://antenna.submittable.com/submit"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EXHIBITIONS DEADLINE: 10/10&lt;br/&gt;FEE: $35&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Individual Visual Artists or Collaboratives working in any media are encouraged to apply to the Antenna:: Exhibition Open Call. Selected artists receive: a solo show for the 2020 calendar year, include funding for travel, $1,000 honorarium (to be split with collaborations), accommodations in Antenna’s residency space, and the publishing of an exhibition catalog, artist book, or other similar ephemera to be determined in collaboration with the artists and Antenna’s Paper Machine. Exhibition opportunities are also available for Louisiana Residents and for projects exploring the intersections of visual and literary arts. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RESIDENCIES &lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: 10/25&lt;br/&gt;FEE: $35&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Antenna offers two residency opportunities for Artists and Writers to produce new work in New Orleans. The Antenna::Spillways Residency aims to develop creative feats within the greater New Orleans region, supporting ambitious works that question, transform, or expand the vibrant visual and literary culture of the area. Residents are selected based on past work, provided resources for an initial visit, and from their visit experience encouraged to develop a proposal for a project. A limited group of projects are then selected for development, which are supported in an open ended process and given the time and resources needed for them to thrive. The Paper Machine Publishing Residency provides funding, space, and time for artists and writers to produce a print based project during a month in New Orleans at Antenna’s center for creator publishing, Paper Machine. Residents explore the possibilities of prints, publications, or multiples, and have the time to develop a focused project on a variety of cutting edge and traditional print equipment with the assistance of Paper Machine staff. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BOOKS: &lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: 10/17&lt;br/&gt;FEE: $20&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Antenna publishes new Comic Books, Chapbooks, or Guidebooks, all through open call processes. Check out current works produced by Antenna here: &lt;a href="https://antenna.works/book-order" target="_blank"&gt;https://antenna.works&lt;/a&gt; Selected projects receive funding, project development support, and books!  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To see the work of Antenna created from open call opportunities such as these visit: &lt;a href="https://www.antenna.works/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.antenna.works&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All application information and guidelines can be found at: &lt;a href="https://antenna.submittable.com/submit" target="_blank"&gt;https://antenna.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c77577c2-afbc-48ff-b208-b82d7a46740c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ac388f37-5137-484b-ad7c-e253b6baa6b4</id><title>10/20 - Group Exhibition at Trestle Gallery curated by The Rib</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.756250+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Trestle Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.trestlegallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trestle Gallery Open Call: Group Exhibition curated by The Rib&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application deadline: October 20th, 2019, 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Emerging and mid-career artists are invited to submit their work for consideration in our January 2020 exhibition organized by our Guest Curators: Leah Triplett Harrington, Lindsey Stapleton, and Corey Oberlander of The Rib!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Rib is an online art publication decentralizing criticism and coverage of contemporary art. Launched in the fall of 2017, The Rib publishes commentary and criticism in the form of reviews, editorials, interviews, and essays that connects artists, spaces, curators, and advocates working outside of major arts communities in the United States.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Leah Triplett Harrington is the founding editor of The Rib. She is currently Assistant Curator for Now + There, a Boston non-profit for public art. Her writing has most recently appeared in The Rib as well as Flash Art, Hyperallergic, and The Brooklyn Rail. In 2017, she was a finalist for the Rabkin Prize for Arts Journalism. Leah has lectured at Boston University, Montserrat College of Art, Stonehill College, Tufts University Art Gallery, and the University of Massachusetts, Amherst.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lindsey Stapleton is the co-founder and director of GRIN, a recently closed contemporary gallery located in Rhode Island. Now based in Atlanta, she is an independent curator and the Creatiive Director of The Rib.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Corey Oberlander is the co-founder and director of GRIN, a recently closed contemporary gallery located in Rhode Island. Now based in Atlanta, he works as Collection Manager for a Private Art Collection.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Installation Dates: January 13-15th 2020 | Opening Reception: Friday, January 17, 7-9pm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All applications must be through our Submittable page.&lt;br/&gt;http://trestlegallery.submittable.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- 2D and 3D artworks of all media are accepted for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;- You may submit up to 3 works for consideration&lt;br/&gt;- Images must be in .JPG or .JPEG format, 1000 pixels on longest side, titled: LastnameFirstname_Title.jpg&lt;br/&gt;- Media can be submitted in .MOV, .MPG4, or .GIF format, titled: Lastname_Firstname_Title.mpg4&lt;br/&gt;- CV, Statement, and Bio must be submitted in PDF form, titled: LastnameFirstName_CV.pdf; LastnameFirstName_Statement.pdf; LastnameFirstName_Bio.pdf; &lt;br/&gt;- Trestle splits all sales 70/30, with 70% going to the artist.&lt;br/&gt;- National and international artists are welcome to apply. As a non-profit we don't have a shipping budget, so should an artist be selected they will have to cover the cost of shipping to and from the gallery.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ac388f37-5137-484b-ad7c-e253b6baa6b4" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>984856bb-a06b-43c1-ba29-2b51c7ad6116</id><title>10/9 - OPEN CALL to Damaged Art Exhibition: A Student Loan Restoration Project NYC</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755459+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Damaged Art&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.damaged-art.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damaged Art is a student loan restoration project which aims to help artists combat crippling student loan debt so that they may move forward with their careers. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A hope for a way out of the vicious cycle. Accepted artists into the Damaged Art exhibit will have their works for sale for the price of their full, outstanding student loan debt — not only to alleviate their financial burden, but to bring a new awareness to the realities these artists are faced with. This selection will be done by a panel of esteemed judges with cultural and artistic significance in New York City and beyond to bring further awareness to this important cause and uplift the burgeoning talent it threatens to stifle. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The time has come to expose the corruptness of the student loan system in the United States. Damaged Art has an agenda to unveil the scandalous nature that loan companies have used to unknowingly sign students up for a lifetime fairytale deal with the devil. Many students have no choice but to sign up for loans that lead to enormous interest rates, monthly payments that are akin to extortion, and constant harassment that threatens their livelihood.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Damaged Art is an exhibit conceived and curated by New York artist, Cheryl Georgette. For years she has assisted fine artist Vera Lutter in New York City and Los Angeles, in which she was an artist and resident at LACMA. Prior to working as an assistant, she worked various positions in the photography and art industry: Ruby Bird Studio, Gowanus Darkroom, The Studio at the Darkroom, Alt Citizen, and Animazing Gallery. The exhibit will focus on New York artists, but has plans to expand to other cities nationwide to continue bringing awareness to young talent and the hardships they face in order to be able to create. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Damaged Art is a submission based art show. Open call is Sept 17-Oct 9. The exhibition will be held at lower east side gallery, 98 Orchard on November 8-10. Stay tuned for more details.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To apply for the exhibition, click on the "Apply Now" button on the Damaged Art website. www.damaged-art.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork submitted to DAMAGED ART for the exhibition must be unique works by the artist, no limited editions will be accepted. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists may submit 1 - 3 works of art for consideration. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Must Submit Artist Statement and Student Loan Story: Please provide a paragraph, no longer than 200 words, of your personal journey with student loan debt.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You must provide an estimated amount of your entire student loan debt: a combination of federal and private loans. Personal loans do not apply. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit website and/or social media links.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DAMAGED ART will notify you by October 21st if your work is accepted in the exhibition. We may request to see additional work, or ask that you elaborate on your story, if necessary. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selection process will be determined by esteemed Judges, the week of October 14, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Announcement of accepted artists is Monday, October 21, 2019. Accepted artists then MUST provide verification of the amount of their TOTAL student loan debt: including federal, private and any loans in default. Prove your student loan debt amount by sending current statements, and DAMAGED ART will determine the price of your artwork, factoring in an interest that may accrue.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If accepted into the exhibition, we will require that you verify your student loan debt. It is understandable that your estimated student loan amount submitted for the Open Call may differ to the actual owed debt. Please do not let that discourage showing us the actual amount owed. The exhibition’s purpose is to pull off the bandaid, and show and tell your financial story. You are not alone. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Student Loan Debt accrued from personal loan borrowing need not apply. I apologize for this, but as this is the 1st Damaged Art Exhibition, it is best to keep to legal contracts at this time. If part of your student loan debt was covered through personal reasons, please define that amount in the application. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please see Terms &amp; Conditions on website&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/984856bb-a06b-43c1-ba29-2b51c7ad6116" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6d925571-3770-46d9-97a6-7c8d0d4b1b8f</id><title>10/10 - 10th Annual Manifest Prize: $5,000 Cash Award</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755433+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cincinnati based non-profit arts organization and gallery, Manifest, invites visual artists to submit works of any media, any genre/style, any size. The Manifest Prize is open to everyone. The only limitation is that entries must represent original works of visual art of any kind and be available and capable of being exhibited in one of Manifest's five galleries. One work will be selected for the award, featured in the gallery, and published. Ten semi-finalist works will also be recognized and published.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THE WINNING WORK WILL BE REVEALED AT THE GALLERY ON DECEMBER 12th DURING THE PREVIEW EVENT (7-9pm)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Early Deadline Entry Fee (Oct 1): $40 for up to five entries submitted. $5 per each additional entry. &lt;br/&gt;Final Deadline Entry Fee (Oct 10): $60 for up to five entries submitted. $5 per each additional entry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To view the full prospectus visit &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/one." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email questions to info@manifestgallery.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6d925571-3770-46d9-97a6-7c8d0d4b1b8f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2dd33fcc-2369-478a-b15d-4273306f7230</id><title>10/7 - Small Works 2019</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755407+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Main Street Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Clifton Springs, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/07/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.mainstreetartsgallery.com/submissions.html"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A national juried exhibition of small works (12 inches or smaller in any direction*). Open to artists working in all media excluding video/sound and installation art. This 6th annual exhibition is open to all U.S. residents 18 years or older.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Anna Kaplan, gallery owner and curator at Anna Kaplan Contemporary in Buffalo, NY.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A total of $2,000 in cash awards, "Best in Show" receives $1,000!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Dates&lt;br/&gt;• Submission Deadline: Monday, October 7, 2019&lt;br/&gt;• Notification: Week of October 21, 2019&lt;br/&gt;• Work due to gallery: By Nov. 15, 2019&lt;br/&gt;• Exhibition Dates: Nov 30, 2019–Jan 3, 2020&lt;br/&gt;• Opening Reception: Saturday, December 7, 4–7pm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mainstreetartsgallery.com/submissions.html" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.mainstreetartsgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2dd33fcc-2369-478a-b15d-4273306f7230" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a7686108-b8d4-441d-8e25-00db8fbc75b8</id><title>10/31 - BEYOND AFFECT</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755379+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Petcoke Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Detroit, MI, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEYOND AFFECT&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;How does affect theory tie into political activism?&lt;br/&gt;How do we move beyond affectation and into palpable transformation?&lt;br/&gt;How does the location of Fort Wayne, built upon a Pottawatomi burial ground, jutting close to the Canadian border on the Detroit river, in the shadow of the Marathon Oil Refinery inform us? What is its narrative, how did this narrative inform Detroit’s present moment, what is and how do we shape/reimagine Detroit’s/ the United States future narrative? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no fee for submitting artwork.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Indigenous artists are encouraged to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;New media and performance proposal are encouraged. We currently cannot offer stipends.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition will take place inside various buildings of Fort Wayne during the winter months. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition dates are TBA and dependent on artists availability.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submissions can be emailed to Olivia at petcokegallery@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please email Olivia at petcokegallery@gmail.com with submissions, proposals, and questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a7686108-b8d4-441d-8e25-00db8fbc75b8" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1e0dd286-b56e-4597-a9d0-2d47449750e7</id><title>10/21 - Drawing</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755347+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drawing&lt;br/&gt;December 13, 2019– January 11, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Drawing has been radically transformed in the last 100 years, as countless artists reimagined the traditional concepts of drawing and expanded the medium's definition beyond gesture and form. This expanded definition included mark-making that ventured off the paper, into multimedia, film, sculpture and much else. However, in recent years, many artists have returned to a more gestural and representational mode. In this new and dynamic tension between tradition and experimental visions, Site:Brooklyn is looking for works, across all mediums and processes, which showcase the diversity and range of drawing’s place in contemporary art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Olga Valle Tetkowski is currently deputy director at The Drawing Center in NYC. HAS HAS HELD POSITIONS AS administrator of curatorial projects and curator at the Bard Graduate Center NYC, assistant curator at the Museum of Art and Design, Urban Glass and Paul Robeson Galleries at Rutgers University.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: September 15, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: October 21, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: October 31, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: December 13, 2019– January 11, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, December 13, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in drawing across all mediums. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original work may be submitted. The fee is $35.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by October 21, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION: &lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2lQc5fQ&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 72” X 60” X 12” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;4. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Drawing” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2lQc5fQ" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1e0dd286-b56e-4597-a9d0-2d47449750e7" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1589c3c5-8a8c-44a9-8719-589789812903</id><title>9/30 - Artfare Submissions Program</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755321+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Artfare, Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artfare.com/for-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artfare is a platform that allows artists and patrons to connect through our iPhone app (artfare.com/app).  Patrons can follow artists, request studio visits, and purchase work posted by our curated group of professional artists. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artfare allows artists to present their work to a broad audience and connect with patrons both digitally and in person through studio visits, exhibitions and events. Using our app, artists can also discover and communicate with other artists and curators, and work together to independently organize exhibitions and events.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artfare artists are based in NYC and actively make and show their work. Our group is carefully curated and  selective. In addition to quality and maturity in the work, we seek artists with professional track records and career ambition. We aim to create a well rounded program that represents all voices and mediums. Please browse the app and artfare.com to get a sense of our mission and artist list. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our tools and services allow artists to:&lt;br/&gt;1. Easily share links to your available works and facilitate sales from your studio, both on and offline&lt;br/&gt;2. Build a following of potential patrons and curators in a professional context&lt;br/&gt;3. Receive tax documents at year end and let Artfare collect, file, and pay sales tax on your behalf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you would like to submit your work for consideration please do so by September 30 via this link:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://artfare.slideroom.com/#/login/program/48475&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1589c3c5-8a8c-44a9-8719-589789812903" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>abe5363b-5a91-4e17-b91f-6cf3a418010f</id><title>9/30 - Call For Artists &amp;quot;Body Beautiful&amp;quot; A Group Show at The Untitled Space, NY</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755288+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Untitled Space&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://untitled-space.com/artist-opportunities/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BODY BEAUTIFUL &lt;br/&gt;A Group Show // November - December 2019&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: September 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Group exhibition, “Body Beautiful,” curated by gallery director Indira Cesarine, will feature artworks across a variety of mediums including painting, drawing, and sculpture, that highlight the power of the figure with an emphasis on body positive depictions of the human form. Throughout the canon of art history, the human figure has been a central theme, as we grapple with our own existence, feeding a desire to self represent and to understand our place in the universe. This exhibition will present works by contemporary artists who address the figure not just as an object of beauty, or a subject of anatomy, but rather elaborate on contemporary themes of body positive depictions of the human form, including all body types, ages and genders, celebrating diversity as well as the timeless beauty of the body.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What is Body Positivity? The body-positive movement, which dates back to early Victorian reforms against the corset, 1960’s initiatives against fat-shaming, and more recently via social media with influencers challenging unrealistic standards of beauty, is “rooted in the belief that all human beings should have a positive body image, while challenging the ways in which society presents and views the physical body. The goal of the movement is to address unrealistic beauty standards and to build the confidence of oneself and others. The movement sets forth the notion that beauty is a construct of society, and poses that this construct should not infringe upon one's ability to feel confidence or self-worth. The movement states that neither fat-shaming nor skinny-shaming is acceptable, and that all body types can and should be celebrated.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The “Body Beautiful” exhibition is open to artists of all genders. Works will be considered in any medium, including painting, drawing, sculpture, photography, mixed media, video, and performance amongst others. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The group show will take place at The Untitled Space gallery in Tribeca, New York, as well as online on Artsy. The exhibit is open to submissions until September 30, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE UNTITLED SPACE&lt;br/&gt;The Untitled Space is an art gallery located in Tribeca, New York in a landmark building on Lispenard Street. Founded in 2015 by Indira Cesarine, the gallery features an ongoing curation of exhibits of emerging and established contemporary artists exploring conceptual framework and boundary-pushing ideology through mediums of painting, sculpture, printmaking, photography, video and performance art. The gallery is committing to exploring new ideas vis-à-vis traditional and new mediums and highlights a program of women in art as well as special events aligned with our creative vision.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT CURATOR INDIRA CESARINE&lt;br/&gt;Indira Cesarine’s curatorial for The Untitled Space gallery includes includes solo shows for artists Sarah Maple, Rebecca Leveille, Alison Jackson, Fahren Feingold, Kat Toronto aka Miss Meatface, and Jeanette Hayes as well as group shows “IRL: Investigating Reality”, "EDEN" and "(HOTEL) XX" at SPRING/BREAK Art Show; ”SECRET GARDEN” presenting the female gaze on erotica; “SHE INSPIRES,” a group show of 60 artists exhibiting works honoring inspirational women; internationally-celebrated group shows “UPRISE/ANGRY WOMEN,” and “ONE YEAR OF RESISTANCE” responding to the political climate in America, as well as numerous other critically-acclaimed exhibitions. She is additionally the founder of globally distributed publication “The Untitled Magazine.” Recent press on Indira Cesarine &amp; The Untitled Space includes Vogue (US), Vogue Italia, CNN, Forbes, Newsweek, W Magazine, Harper’s Bazaar, Teen Vogue, New York Magazine, i-D Magazine, Dazed and Confused, and The New York Times among many others. View recent articles: http://untitled-space.com/featured-press&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Visit us online for more info and application: http://untitled-space.com/artist-opportunities/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit us online for more info and application: http://untitled-space.com/artist-opportunities/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*If you have previously exhibited with The Untitled Space please contact us for a (no fee) returning artist application.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/abe5363b-5a91-4e17-b91f-6cf3a418010f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ea78967f-e802-4fe8-9a07-43b416c7ad5b</id><title>10/3 - INTERNATIONAL CALL FOR ART, ArtMaze Magazine Special Anniversary Edition: Issue 15</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755262+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtMaze Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍  , United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/03/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artmazemag.com/call-for-art/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art Maze Magazine is an independent artist-run and ad-free international print and online publication dedicated to showcasing and promoting experimental and progressive contemporary art, which reflects modern society and its environment, provokes conversation and action; fosters innovation and diversity of mediums which make today’s art scene so intriguing and versatile.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: Artists are welcome to submit works in any medium: painting, drawing, sculpture, ceramics, printmaking, photography, textile, installation, mixed media, digital, film (only jpg + link to video) etc. All visual art mediums are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists or any art organisations on behalf of artists from all countries are welcome to submit their works for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each submitted artist, wether selected for a publication or not, will receive a digital copy of the magazine's issue which he/she applied for.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: October 3rd, 2019 (12:00 AM, midnight: end of the day 3rd October - Eastern Standard Time)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUEST CURATOR: Brigitte Mulholland, curator and director of Anton Kern Gallery, NYC&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO APPLY: www.artmazemag.com/call-for-art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DISTRIBUTION: Physical and digital copies of ArtMaze Mag are distributed worldwide via bookshops, galleries and online. More info: &lt;a href="http://artmazemag.com/shop/" target="_blank"&gt;http://artmazemag.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selected artists will be asked for high resolution images and will be published in the next print and digital issue of ArtMaze Magazine. Each (selected) artist will receive a 1 or 2-page spread in print and digital (PDF) magazine including bio, statement, website, and 1-5 featured artworks. All submitted artists will receive a complimentary PDF copy of the magazine and all published artists will be promoted on our website/social media. Physical copies of Art Maze Magazine are printed to the highest quality in London, UK.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ea78967f-e802-4fe8-9a07-43b416c7ad5b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>51b3ed45-f182-4229-a0d7-c3ee3c186a99</id><title>11/8 - Call to Artists</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755236+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Galerie 255&lt;br/&gt;📍 Palm Beach, FL, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Painting&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/08/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Limited opportunity for few select abstract or abstract like, visual artists/sculptors, to show in new contemporary gallery headquartered in Palm Beach- specializing in Scandinavian/European modernist artists.  Additional opportunities for show in traveling pop-up exhibits both in Manhattan and Miami Beach, in near future.  Larger scale works for all, preferred. Commissions paid with terms of agreement, required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send 2-3 high resolution images and brief CV summary to email address provided. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;No phone calls please.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/51b3ed45-f182-4229-a0d7-c3ee3c186a99" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>40e3f62d-8d01-45d9-aa60-b2af5b3acf17</id><title>10/31 - OPEN CALL: Solo Exhibition at Maake Projects</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755209+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Maake Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 State College, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.maakemagazine.com/soloshow"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call: SOLO EXHIBITION at Maake Projects in State College, PA&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: October 31st, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists working in all media are encouraged to apply for this open call. Artists will be given a one-month solo exhibition at our new project space in central PA. Artists will be awarded a $500 honorarium for exhibition related expenses. We will provide assistance for a public opening reception event for the exhibition. Please submit the following materials in order to be considered for this opportunity. Please contact us at info@maake.org with any questions regarding your application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMIT&lt;br/&gt;Submission materials:&lt;br/&gt;• Up to 8 images of work &lt;br/&gt;• CV &lt;br/&gt;• Short statement &lt;br/&gt;• Short bio &lt;br/&gt;• Social Media info &lt;br/&gt;• Exhibition proposal (under 500 words)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility &amp; Terms: &lt;br/&gt;• Artists may submit up to 8 works&lt;br/&gt;• Artists working in all media are welcome to apply&lt;br/&gt;• Artists must be 18 years old or older to apply&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee $20&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information visit: www.maakemagazine.com/soloshow&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please contact us with questions at info@maake.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/40e3f62d-8d01-45d9-aa60-b2af5b3acf17" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8a8fd430-61f4-45e7-b2f7-0793d89e51e2</id><title>10/15 - SculptureTucson 2020 Sculpture Show and Sale</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755177+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SculptureTucson&lt;br/&gt;📍 Tucson, AZ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sculpturetucson.org/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sculpture Tucson annually hosts Arizona’s largest juried Sculpture Show &amp; Sale the first weekend in April.&lt;br/&gt;Proceeds from the Show and Sale go toward the purchase of sculpture for public art in and around Tucson as well as funding public art and education.&lt;br/&gt;If you want to apply, you must do so by October 15, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;Each application will be juried by an internationally recognized panel of artists.&lt;br/&gt;Though hundreds of artists will apply, only 60 will be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;If you are accepted, you will:&lt;br/&gt;Have a 10 ft. x 15 ft. space to exhibit your work under a communal tent.&lt;br/&gt;Be provided up to 3 pedestals.&lt;br/&gt;Be permitted to exhibit up to 15 pieces of sculpture at a time.&lt;br/&gt;Receive a catalog including your work as well as work from all the participating artists. You may be invited to participate in our “Artist Talk” series of lectures.&lt;br/&gt;All sales will be processed by SculptureTucson.org which will retain 30% commission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;br/&gt;• Artists are required to email their completed Application Packet and pay the $15 application fee no later&lt;br/&gt;than 11:59 PM PST October 15, 2019. Email Application Packet to: sculpturetucson@gmail.com.&lt;br/&gt;• The completed Application Packet must include the following:&lt;br/&gt; 1. Application Form - A copy of the application form is attached to this PDF and is available for&lt;br/&gt;download at: www.SculptureTucson.org/call-to-artists&lt;br/&gt; 2. Artist Statement - Up to 1/2 page. Microsoft Word or PDF format.&lt;br/&gt; 3. Images - Up to 15 images of your own 3-dimensional work currently available for sale. Images do not&lt;br/&gt;need to be of the exact work you will be bringing to the show but must be representative of your body of&lt;br/&gt;work. Do not include more than 2 images per piece. JPEG or PDF images only. For attachments greater&lt;br/&gt;than 20MB, please email a link to your application materials on a document-sharing website of your&lt;br/&gt;choice (DropBox, WeTransfer, Google Drive, etc.)&lt;br/&gt; 4. Image List - Include title, year, dimensions, materials, price and brief description if needed. Label the&lt;br/&gt;image list to coordinate with each image number. Microsoft Word or PDF.&lt;br/&gt;IF YOU ARE ACCEPTED&lt;br/&gt;● If you are accepted, we will notify you by November 15, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;● Individual sculptors who are accepted and available to attend the duration of the show will be charged a&lt;br/&gt;$100 booth fee.&lt;br/&gt;● Individual sculptors who are accepted and not available to attend the duration of the show will be&lt;br/&gt;charged a $150 booth fee. You will still be responsible for manning your space for the duration of the show.&lt;br/&gt;● A very limited number of spaces will be available for galleries. Galleries that are accepted will be charged&lt;br/&gt;a $250 booth fee. Only work from the artists in the gallery that have been accepted to participate will be&lt;br/&gt;permitted to be exhibited. You will be responsible for manning your space for the duration of the show.&lt;br/&gt;● If you participated in the 2019 show, please do not bring the same pieces as last year. At least 50% of your&lt;br/&gt;work should be work that was not previously exhibited.&lt;br/&gt;● SculptureTucson will make available at no cost up to 3 pedestals per artist. Pedestals are stored on site&lt;br/&gt;and artists are responsible for picking them up prior to the show. A $50 deposit is required for the pedestals&lt;br/&gt;which is fully refundable once they are returned after the show.&lt;br/&gt;● The Annual SculptureTucson Festival Show &amp; Sale occurs on April 3-5, 2020 as follows:&lt;br/&gt;Friday, April 3 from 5:00 pm - 8:00 pm (Patron’s Event)&lt;br/&gt;Saturday, April 4 from 9:30 am – 4:00 pm&lt;br/&gt;Sunday, April 5 from 9:30 am – 4:00 pm&lt;br/&gt;● If you are accepted, pay your booth fee, but then find that you are not able to participate in the show, you&lt;br/&gt;will get your booth fee back if you notify SculptureTucson at least 60 days before the show.&lt;br/&gt;● Applicants are responsible for transport of all sculpture to and from the show site.&lt;br/&gt;● Applicants who are selected to participate agree to the use of their submitted images by SculptureTucson&lt;br/&gt;for the promotion of the annual SculptureTucson Festival Show &amp; Sale in digital as well as printed materials.&lt;br/&gt;LARGE SCULPTURE INFO&lt;br/&gt;SculptureTucson encourages participants to exhibit large sculpture. If you intend to exhibit large sculpture&lt;br/&gt;that requires special assistance to place, please indicate that on the Application Form so that we can arrange&lt;br/&gt;for forklift assistance.&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT DATES&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline October 15, 2019 11:59 PM PST&lt;br/&gt;Artists Notified of Results November 15, 2019&lt;br/&gt;SculptureTucson Festival April 3-5, 2020&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO CONTACT US&lt;br/&gt;Questions regarding the application and exhibition process should be sent to: sculpturetucson@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;Logistics prohibit us from directly answering every question from every applicant. If you have a question,&lt;br/&gt;check the FAQ section of our webpage. We will regularly post frequently asked questions and their answers.&lt;br/&gt;THE FINE PRINT STUFF&lt;br/&gt;Only complete applications will be reviewed by SculptureTucson. Incomplete or partial applications&lt;br/&gt;will not be considered.&lt;br/&gt;SculptureTucson has the right to accept or reject any/all applicants.&lt;br/&gt;Submission of an application does NOT guarantee or constitute acceptance to participate in the&lt;br/&gt;Annual SculptureTucson Festival Show &amp; Sale.&lt;br/&gt;SculptureTucson does not and shall not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion (creed),&lt;br/&gt;gender, gender expression, age, national origin (ancestry), disability, marital status, sexual&lt;br/&gt;orientation, or military status, in any of its activities or operations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8a8fd430-61f4-45e7-b2f7-0793d89e51e2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>95b30521-1c23-48aa-b812-00c8b1b56508</id><title>10/22 - Green</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755145+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/22/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Green&lt;br/&gt;December 13, 2019– January 11, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Green is a complex color: a symbol of life, luck, and hope, but also disorder and greed. Until recently, green was a challenging color to produce. Not surprisingly, the color has been associated with all that is fluid and changing: childhood, love, and money. It was during the Romantic period green became the color of the natural environment. What does green mean today? Site:Brooklyn is looking for work, across all mediums and utilizing all processes, which engage with green.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Eva Díaz is currently Associate Professor of Contemporary Art History at Pratt. Prior to coming to Pratt she taught at the Whitney Museum Independent Study Program, Sarah Lawrence College, and Parsons; she also worked as the curator at Art in General. Her writing has appeared in magazines and journals such as The Art Bulletin, Artforum, Art Journal, Art in America, Cabinet, Frieze, Grey Room, Harvard Design Magazine, and October. Her book, The Experimenters: Chance and Design at Black Mountain College, was released in 2015 by the University of Chicago Press.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: September 16, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: October 22, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: November 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: December 13, 2019– January 11, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, December 13, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in drawing, painting, printmaking, wall mounted sculpture, collage, and video.&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $35.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by October 22, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2lVSZFf" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 72” X 60” X 12” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;4. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Green” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2lVSZFf" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/95b30521-1c23-48aa-b812-00c8b1b56508" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f6362f14-bde7-4965-8500-6e2896677cbc</id><title>11/1 - Open Call- Juried 3 Person Exhibition</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755104+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tiger Strikes Asteroid&lt;br/&gt;📍 philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.tigerstrikesasteroid.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEN CALL FOR A 3-PERSON JURIED SHOW&lt;br/&gt;JANUARY 9 – FEBRUARY 15, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Entry Deadline: November 1, midnight &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Link: &lt;a href="https://tigerstrikesasteroid.submittable.com/submit/2ab82685-9e3c-4d98-a17f-1c7ff3f58c5a/phl-open-call-2019-three-person-exhibition" target="_blank"&gt;https://tigerstrikesasteroid.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Tiger Strikes Asteroid is a network of artist-run spaces with locations in Philadelphia, New York, and Los Angeles. Each space is independently operated and focuses on presenting a varied program of emerging and mid-career artists. Our goal is to collectively bring people together, expand connections and build community through artist-initiated exhibitions, projects, and curatorial opportunities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CALENDAR&lt;br/&gt;September 22: Submissions begin&lt;br/&gt;November 1: Submission deadline, midnight &lt;br/&gt;November 6: Notification of accepted works&lt;br/&gt;January 4-5: Delivery of accepted works, 12noon-7pm&lt;br/&gt;January 9- February 15: Exhibition dates&lt;br/&gt;January 9: Opening reception, 6-9pm&lt;br/&gt;February 13: Closing reception, 6-9&lt;br/&gt;February 16: Pick up of all work, 12noon-7pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEE: $25 &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition is open to artists age 18 and older. International artists are also welcome to apply but are responsible for all shipping costs. At least one of three artists included in this exhibition will be local to the Philadelphia area.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SPECIFICATIONS&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition is open to works in all media. Wall pieces must be wired for hanging. Installation pieces must be received ready for installation with proper hanging devices attached and thorough instructions where necessary. Audio/Video artists need to provide a monitor and/or other equipment. Accepted work cannot be substituted and must be available for the duration of the exhibit. All work must be ready to hang. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;Submit up to 6 JPEG digital images to Submittable. &lt;br/&gt;¥	File dimensions: no smaller than 1920 pixels on the longest side&lt;br/&gt;¥	File resolution: 72 ppi/dpi (standard web resolution)&lt;br/&gt;¥	File size: 5 MB maximum&lt;br/&gt;¥	Video: upload a still image and provide a link to the video in the image description box.&lt;br/&gt;¥	File labeling: Each image should be numbered and include your first and last name and the image title. Example: 1_Toni_Basil_Untitled.jpg; 2_Toni_Basil_DreamBoat.jpg; etc&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HONORARIUM&lt;br/&gt;Each artist will receive $150 honorarium.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING/DELIVERY OF ARTWORK&lt;br/&gt;The artist is responsible for the cost of shipping or mailing artwork to and from Tiger Strikes Asteroid using Fed-X, UPS or Post. A return shipping label and return postage must be included with the artwork. Artwork may also be hand-delivered to and picked up from Tiger Strikes Asteroid on the appropriate dates during the scheduled times.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SALE OF ARTWORK&lt;br/&gt;Tiger Strikes Asteroid retains a 30% commission on all art sales made during the exhibition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://tigerstrikesasteroid.submittable.com/submit/2ab82685-9e3c-4d98-a17f-1c7ff3f58c5a/phl-open-call-2019-three-person-exhibition" target="_blank"&gt;https://tigerstrikesasteroid.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;email philadelphia@tigerstrikesasteroid.com with questions&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f6362f14-bde7-4965-8500-6e2896677cbc" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c9b986ed-28b2-45ec-b8f1-c512aa8e8a8c</id><title>10/10 - Framed: Portrait Photography</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755080+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on portrait photography at Black Box Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c9b986ed-28b2-45ec-b8f1-c512aa8e8a8c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ae313b92-0688-40f9-8bcd-778632bc1b31</id><title>9/30 - Red Bull Arts Detroit Curatorial Fellowship</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755051+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Red Bull Arts Detroit&lt;br/&gt;📍 Detroit, MI, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://redbullarts.com/detroit/apply/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red Bull Arts Detroit is committed to holistically supporting the arts locally and nationally. As such, we seek to provide alternative exhibition platforms to the vast network of independent curators who offer new ways of seeing, understanding, and experiencing artists and their works. The program creates an opportunity for a curator to realize an exhibition concept and bring it to the public in Detroit. The selected curator will demonstrate in their proposal a level of engagement and thoughtfulness about how their exhibition engages with the local city and community, and why it should take place in Detroit. Red Bull Arts Detroit will support the curator in the execution of the exhibition and its public programming. The exhibition will open in July of 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Curator receives access to our 12,000 square foot gallery for their exhibition as well as financial, production, and marketing support to execute their vision. For Detroit-based curators, the fellowship will provide travel and accommodation for five trips for planning purposes outside of the city in advance of the exhibition. For non-Detroit based curators, Red Bull Arts Detroit will provide travel for three trips to Detroit in advance of the exhibition for planning purposes, three-trips to Detroit during the exhibition for programming purposes, and accommodations in Detroit during visits. The selected curator will receive a $5000 fee. The budget for the production of the exhibition is $15,000 along with funding for three-to-four public programs. Outside of the $15,000, Red Bull Arts Detroit will provide in-kind support that includes local installation staff, staffing for gallery hours, access to technology for use in exhibition (list of available technology is at - &lt;a href="http://redbullarts.com/detroit/exhibition-equipment-and-technology/" target="_blank"&gt;http://redbullarts.com&lt;/a&gt;), printing wall texts (labels and vinyl) as well as gallery guides, and installation documentation of the exhibition. The curator should plan for the $15,000 exhibition budget to cover any artist fees, production fees for works or installation materials, artist travel, shipping and handling of art works, commissioning of new writing or texts, and any other materials or labor otherwise required for the production of their exhibition concept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Guidelines&lt;br/&gt;- The Red Bull Arts Detroit Curatorial Fellowship takes place once a year&lt;br/&gt;- Applications are open August 19th – September 30th, 2019, with selected projects presented in July of 2020.&lt;br/&gt;- Applicants should regularly curate contemporary art exhibitions, drawing from the disciplines of visual, sound, or performance art.&lt;br/&gt;- Applicants must submit a CV, Statement of Purpose, and project proposal. The project proposal should detail the curatorial project the applicant hopes to realize with Red Bull Arts Detroit with as much detail as possible, including the exhibition concept, a budget proposal, considerations related to the planning, production, and presentation of the exhibition, and at least one example of public programming on the occasion of the exhibition. Proposals should be a maximum of four-pages in length. The selected curator’s proposal is subject to feasibility review with the Red Bull Arts Detroit staff once selected and does not guarantee that all aspects of the selected project will be delivered.&lt;br/&gt;- While the Program is open to all professional curators from disparate backgrounds, successful applicants will demonstrate exceptional talent in their field, and a demonstrated dedication to the issues surrounding contemporary art.&lt;br/&gt;- Curators are able to apply once per calendar year&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ae313b92-0688-40f9-8bcd-778632bc1b31" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>12056b55-26e8-4864-82bd-9640a3edc0ab</id><title>10/11 - Call for Artists! 15th Annual Small Works Show!</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.755023+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;440 Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://gallery440.squarespace.com/call-for-entries"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;440 Gallery announces the Call for Entries for the 15th annual Small Works Show 2019. This national juried exhibition celebrates the innovation of artists who create work on a small scale, in a broad range of media and styles. The exhibition will be on display in the 440 Gallery, Park Slope, Brooklyn space from Wednesday, December 4 through Sunday, December 29, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the juror:&lt;br/&gt;John Gagné is the founder of Gagné Contemporary, a gallery focused on emerging and mid-career New York artists. He is an art advisor to galleries and collectors, and often leads clients to artist studios and gallery districts all over the city. As an independent curator John has selected and exhibited artists in Manhattan and Brooklyn. He also consults with a number of non-profits, notably Arts Gowanus and Arts in Bushwick, helping organizations launch and stage arts events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open to artists who are at least 18 years old at the time of entry and who have a US shipping address. Work must be no more than 12 inches (12”) in any direction including the framing or mounting, or video monitors. The artwork may represent any subject matter. All media—including oils, acrylics, watercolors, pastels, drawings, sculpture in any medium, collage, printmaking, photography and digital media—will be considered. Accepted work must be suitably framed, wired and ready for hanging. Works on paper must be framed under plexiglass or glass. Maximum weight of sculpture: 30 pounds. Wall mounted monitors must be provided for videos. These eligibility requirements will be strictly enforced and work will be refused if it does not comply with the requirements.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/12056b55-26e8-4864-82bd-9640a3edc0ab" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0bcee547-ebfa-4156-bd97-c8e23d401ceb</id><title>12/3 - Rosalie Gardiner Jones Monument</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.754992+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;New York State Office of Parks, Recreation and Historic Preservation&lt;br/&gt;📍 Albany, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/03/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.nysparks.gov"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New York State Office of Parks, Recreation and Historic Preservation (OPRHP) is interested in commissioning a figurative or abstract work of art, not necessarily a sculptural portrait, of Rosalie Gardiner Jones that captures her unrelenting dedication to women’s rights. Bidders are encouraged to develop their own understanding of the context of her life and her achievements. The key objectives are to create a lasting tribute to Rosalie Gardiner Jones that is integrated with the Cold Spring Harbor State Park site and utilizes materials that are durable and require minimal maintenance and care.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jones was an outspoken advocate for woman’s suffrage, most often on the grass roots level. She not only&lt;br/&gt;travelled across Long Island with her yellow “Suffrage Wagon,” she also campaigned for women’s suffrage&lt;br/&gt;in New York City, Washington, DC, and across the country. Most famously, she led a “hike” from the Bronx&lt;br/&gt;to Albany in December 1912 to present a petition to the newly elected governor urging that women be given&lt;br/&gt;the right to vote. Two months later, “General” Jones led her “Army of the Hudson” on another march or&lt;br/&gt;“pilgrimage” from Newark, New Jersey, to Washington, DC, to participate in the famous suffrage parade on&lt;br/&gt;the eve of Woodrow Wilson’s inauguration. Jones and her followers wore long brown pilgrim capes for this&lt;br/&gt;march and their second hike up the west side of the Hudson to Albany in 1914. These marches gained extensive publicity for the suffrage cause in newspapers throughout the country and resulted in General&lt;br/&gt;Jones becoming a national celebrity. She spoke for suffrage in Missouri, Montana, Nebraska, Nevada, and&lt;br/&gt;New Jersey. Jones also led parades on Long Island, flew over Staten Island in a bi-plane dropping suffrage&lt;br/&gt;leaflets, and campaigned throughout New York State in a yellow suffrage automobile, spreading the gospel&lt;br/&gt;of Votes for Women. Jones was born in New York City, but spent much of her life in the family mansion on&lt;br/&gt;the west side of Cold Spring Harbor, opposite what is now Cold Spring Harbor State Park.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The monument to memorialize “General” Jones should engage the public. It should communicate the&lt;br/&gt;strength and courage exhibited by Jones as she endeavored to make women’s suffrage a reality through its&lt;br/&gt;materiality, its form and its setting. The proposed monument should consider the terrain and underground&lt;br/&gt;structures, flora and fauna at the site, as well as views and access to the street, parking lots, and waterfront.&lt;br/&gt;The design of the site should welcome visitors to linger near the artwork to contemplate women’s suffrage&lt;br/&gt;and equal rights for all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply through the New York State Contract Reporter website:  &lt;a href="http://www.nyscr.ny.gov/adsOpen.cfm?ID=77B04B69-54CD-48B7-A966-053D540DDB16." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nyscr.ny.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An optional, but highly recommended, site visit is scheduled for October 8, 2019, at 1pm.  Interested artists should register by October 7, 2019, at 4pm with our office by email:  contracts@parks.ny.gov.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0bcee547-ebfa-4156-bd97-c8e23d401ceb" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a4b6c3c4-781c-4218-af07-e4c36af68f98</id><title>10/2 - Storefront Media Gallery Call for Artists</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.754964+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;4Culture&lt;br/&gt;📍 Seattle, WA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Digital/Electronic Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/02/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://4Culture.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;4Culture's Storefront Media Gallery—formerly called e4c—brings dynamic media art to an urban audience on the go. Apply to show your work on our screens, visible to the thousands of pedestrians, bicyclists, and bus riders that pass by our offices every day!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at 4Culture.org. For more information please contact Heather Dwyer heather.dwyer@4culture.org&lt;br/&gt;(206) 263-1597&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a4b6c3c4-781c-4218-af07-e4c36af68f98" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e4eca857-194f-4394-8e77-9a5a0196a0f0</id><title>11/11 - Photowork: Beyond 20/20, 33rd Annual National Juried Photography Exhibition</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.754933+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Barrett Art Center (Dutchess County Art Association)&lt;br/&gt;📍 Poughkeepsie, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.barrettartcenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;$500 Juror’s Prize, $200 Second Prize, $125 Honorable Mention&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Shoair Mavlian, Director, Photoworks UK&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Deadline: November 11, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notification: First week of December.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates:   Saturday, January 25 - Saturday, March 7, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Photowork: Beyond 20/20 will celebrate prescient social commentary as well as engagement with issues relating to contemporary photography. Submissions should embrace excellence in cutting-edge and/or traditional processes. Past winners of this annual national exhibition have worked with small to large format cameras, pinhole cameras, silver gelatin prints, pigment prints, chromogenic prints, and everything in between. Remember, it's possible to have better than 20/20 vision, Barrett Art Center looks forward to seeing your submissions.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Photowork is an annual exhibition of contemporary photographs curated from photographers throughout the United States and jurored by leading curators, critics, and processionals in the field. Photowork celebrates its 33rd year in 2020, and BAC is proud to welcome Shoair Mavlian, Director, Photoworks, UK  as this year’s juror. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submitting Entries: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Non-members: $45 for the first three images plus $5 for each additional image.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BAC Members: $35 for the first three images plus $5 for each additional image.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Members, please email info@barrettartcenter.org or call us at 845-471-2550 for coupon code.  To become a member, visit, www.barrettartcenter.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror, Shoair Mavlian&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shoair Mavlian is director of Photoworks and curated the 2018 Brighton Photo Biennial 'A New Europe'. From 2011 - 2018 she was Assistant Curator, Photography and International Art at Tate Modern, London, where she curated the major exhibitions ‘Shape of Light: 100 Years of Photography and Abstract Art’ (2018), 'The Radical Eye: Modernist Photography from the Sir Elton John Collection' (2016), 'Conflict, Time, Photography' (2014), 'Project Space: A Chronicle of Interventions' (2014) and 'Harry Callahan' (2013).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; While at Tate Modern she also researched acquisitions and curated displays from the permanent collection including ‘Dayanita Singh’ (2017), 'Lynn Cohen and Taryn Simon' (2017), 'Sirkka-Liisa Konttinen' (2016), 'Close Up: Identity and the Photographic Portrait' (2015), 'Charlotte Posenenske and Ursula Schulz-Dornburg' (2014), 'Lewis Baltz and Minimalism' (2012), and 'New Documentary Forms' (2011).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Recent independent curatorial projects include the exhibition 'Don McCullin: Looking Beyond the Edge' (Les Rencontres d'Arles, 2016) and 'In flux' (Kanellopoulos Cultural Centre, Greece, 2015 and Getxo Photo 2017).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Shoair has a background in fine art photography practice and the history of photography focusing on the twentieth century. She has a strong interest in photography relating to conflict and memory, Central and Latin American photography and emerging contemporary practice. Recent publications include 'Ursula Schulz-Dornburg: The Land In Between' (Mack 2018) and 'Catherine Wagner: Place History and the Archive' (Damiani 2018).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applications can be made online through Call For Entry:&lt;br/&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=7010&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e4eca857-194f-4394-8e77-9a5a0196a0f0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4ce7402e-44bf-46c1-abd9-b111221488f2</id><title>10/16 - Open Call for Midnight Moment—chance to show moving-image art on 60+ screens in Times Square!</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.754904+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/16/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.TSq.org/Arts"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts invites you to submit original moving-image artwork to Midnight Moment, the world’s largest, longest-running digital art exhibition synchronized on electronic billboards and newspaper kiosks throughout Times Square nightly from 11:57pm to midnight. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for submissions: October 16, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;Learn more about submission guidelines here: TSq.org/MMSubmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open applications for the Midnight Moment program are accepted through the online Slideroom portal. Please review submission guidelines and access the portal here: TSq.org/MMSubmission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have any questions about your proposal, please email arts@tsq.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4ce7402e-44bf-46c1-abd9-b111221488f2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1aacd8c2-28b8-4ce8-8bbd-ea9cb0bbc43b</id><title>10/6 - BECOME A MEMBER OF THE SCULPTORS GUILD</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.754873+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sculptors Guild&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sculptorsguild.org/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mission of the Sculptors Guild is to promote, encourage, and support sculptors and sculpture through personal interaction, exhibitions and community outreach.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Sculptors Guild roster includes prominent national and international contemporary artist members. The guild membership is known to have included some of the most famous Sculptors of our time- before they actually became famous! Including: Louise Nevelson (1954), Louise Bourgeois (1955), David Smith (1940), Lin Emery (1976), Jose Ruiz De Riviera (1938), Chaim Gross (1938), George Rickey, Ibram Lassaw, Carole Feuerman, Tom Doyle and so many more.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Membership in the Sculptors Guild is obtainable by professional sculptors of high creative ability. Membership can be by invitation and/or by submission to the Admissions Committee that reviews applications twice a year.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WE NOW HAVE 3 LEVELS OF MEMBERSHIP: FULL Membership, INTERNATIONAL FULL Membership and APPRENTICE Membership. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An annual membership fee of $300 for FULL Membership, $500 for INTERNATIONAL FULL Membership, and $75 for APPRENTICE Membership is due at the time of acceptance to the Guild. Upon acceptance, members may inquire about payment options.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Sculptors Guild was founded in 1937 and is  one of the oldest artist-run organizations in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For application details please visit: &lt;a href="https://www.sculptorsguild.org/join" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.sculptorsguild.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1aacd8c2-28b8-4ce8-8bbd-ea9cb0bbc43b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0ef1af87-948c-4e90-a8ba-8c4d04290c4a</id><title>9/30 - Request for Qualifications - City of Houston Civic Art Program</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.754828+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Houston Arts Alliance&lt;br/&gt;📍 Houston, TX, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://houstonartsalliance.com/opportunities/public-art/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Civic Art Program of the City of Houston Mayor’s Office of Cultural Affairs (MOCA) requests the submission of qualifications from artists or artist-teams to design, fabricate, and install an outdoor artwork that will be a tribute to the life and legacy of educator and civic leader Barbara Jordan.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Through a contract with the City of Houston Mayor’s Office of Cultural Affairs (MOCA), Houston Arts Alliance is charged with managing the Civic Art process to select and commission an artist or artist team to design and build the memorial in honor of Barbara Jordan for the African American Library at the Gregory School. HAA is calling for eligible artists or artist teams across the country to submit their qualifications to be considered for this commission. Eligible Houston-area artists are strongly encouraged to apply. See the application for more details.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exterior Permanent Artwork&lt;br/&gt;Budget: Up to $235,000&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: Monday, September 23, 2019 at 11:59pm CST&lt;br/&gt;Location: 1300 Victor Street, Houston, TX 77019&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility: United States&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Link and instructions can also be found on the HAA website, &lt;a href="http://houstonartsalliance.com/opportunities/public-art/" target="_blank"&gt;http://houstonartsalliance.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;contact civicart@haatx.com for questions&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0ef1af87-948c-4e90-a8ba-8c4d04290c4a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d65e62d9-a343-4bb2-b0ff-b1577974d80c</id><title>10/11 - TIME BOMBS: An International Call for Works About Anxiety and/or Impending Disaster</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.754794+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/timebombs"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cincinnati based non-profit arts organization and gallery, Manifest, invites visual artists to submit works about anxiety, impending disaster, fear, worry, etc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We live in a world increasingly enervated by the sense that at any moment everything could change, generally for the worse. Individuals, communities, political subcultures, social media spheres, even whole countries are each, it would seem, a ticking time bomb…&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Where is the fuse, the key or trigger? How can we detect and diffuse such intense energy-pockets bent on total destruction? Anxiety and fear are like a virus. Perhaps the solution is to acknowledge, examine, and then contain and discard them. Maybe art can help with this by providing an encapsulation of the subject, something that safely externalizes the issue, providing release. And maybe Time is the key…&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This exhibit has no defined expectation for type or style of work to be considered or selected. Submissions can range from the most traditional realism to the most conceptual, abstract, or experimental.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$40 for up to FOUR entries submitted. $5 per each additional entry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To view the full prospectus and entry form visit &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/timebombs." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email inquiries to info@manifestgallery.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d65e62d9-a343-4bb2-b0ff-b1577974d80c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6617c1de-cab1-4998-935d-94cbebdf69a7</id><title>10/7 - Public Art Opportunity: American Legion Memorial Stadium Rennovation</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.754751+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arts &amp;amp; Science Council&lt;br/&gt;📍 Charlotte, NC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/07/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Arts &amp; Science Council (ASC) is accepting qualifications from professional artists or teams of artists in response to a public art opportunity for Mecklenburg County’s American Legion Memorial Stadium renovation. ASC is seeking artists or teams of artists with a demonstrated record of creating memorial sculpture.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The selected artist/s will be asked to create an artwork that memorializes the American Legion and its service to military service members, veterans, and their families. The desired artwork will include, but  is not limited to, representations of the human figure. This artwork will become a signature feature of American Legion Memorial Stadium and should create an atmosphere of reverence that persuades visitors and passers-by to pause and reflect on the service and history of the American Legion.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The memorial will be proudly sited at the front entrance of the stadium along Charlottetown Ave. – adjacent to Independent Park and connected via the Little Sugar Creek Greenway. Positioned along the stadium security fence, the memorial is accessible from both outside and inside the stadium. The artwork for the memorial will be integrated into a terraced slope. This terrace will include signage for American Legion Memorial Stadium and insignia representing the five branches of the military.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Finalists will have the opportunity to meet with stakeholders from Mecklenburg County American Legion posts, Park and Recreation staff, and the project design consultants in order to learn more about the site and scope for the memorial. Each finalist will be tasked with creating a conceptual proposal for the memorial artwork, and the commissioned artist will be selected based on their proposal and qualifications.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork created for this project should be constructed of durable materials and designed in coordination with staff from Mecklenburg County Park and Recreation and Asset and Facility Management, the Historic Landmarks Commission, Jenkins Peer Architects and LandDesign, and representatives from various Mecklenburg County American Legion posts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Review the full application and submit qualifications at: &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.artsandscience.org&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6617c1de-cab1-4998-935d-94cbebdf69a7" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4e0c11b5-c06b-40e2-9288-512287aace60</id><title>10/4 - Charlotte Douglas International Airport Concourse A Expansion–Phase II</title><updated>2019-10-08T13:27:02.754689+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arts &amp;amp; Science Council&lt;br/&gt;📍 Charlotte, NC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/04/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CLT Concourse A - Phase II Art Program is comprised of 2 opportunities for permanent, integrated artworks, each with differing budgets dependent on the projects’ respective size, prominence of location, and anticipated material and fabrication needs. The final project locations and scopes identified in the RFQ will be determined by ASC in close collaboration with CLT Airport and the project design team, with careful consideration of input from the selected artists or artist teams. Please refer to the full RFQ for a more complete understanding of the various Concourse A - Phase II art project areas, objectives and associated budgets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The complete RFQ can be found at &lt;a href="http://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.artsandscience.org&lt;/a&gt; . All applications should be submitted online at &lt;a href="https://asc.slideroom.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://asc.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4e0c11b5-c06b-40e2-9288-512287aace60" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>