<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml</id><title>open-calls-7</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>1003fd76-f045-4f5c-85fe-838a7630068e</id><title>12/20 - Japan Day Art Contest 2020</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.678739+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Japan Day Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.japandaynyc.org/artcontest2020"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan Day is inviting all visual artists to submit their work to Japan Day Art Contest to select our Japan Day Official Artist 2020. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are accepting submissions that incorporate all of the three themes of New York, Japan, and Central Park. The chosen artwork will become the official image of Japan Day @ Central Park 2020, and will be used for collateral materials including poster, program, flyer, and T-shirts. Several artists will receive honorable mentions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Japan Day Official Artists will receive a round trip ticket for two (2) to Japan, provided by ANA and Digital camera, provided by Nikon Inc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All winners will be announced in late March/early April 2020. The awards will be presented on the day of event in May 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RULES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Art must incorporate all of the following three themes: “New York,” ”Japan,” and “Central Park.”&lt;br/&gt;- Size must be 24" tall x 18" wide.&lt;br/&gt;- Only two-dimensional media is accepted.&lt;br/&gt;- Only one submission per artist will be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;- All entries must be the original work of the entering artist.  &lt;br/&gt;- Artwork which has been submitted to previous contests and/or previously shown or published is not eligible. &lt;br/&gt;- Artwork does not need to include the Japan Day logo or any text related to the event.&lt;br/&gt;- Artwork that violates copyrights, intellectual property rights, and/or any related rights of a third party, is not eligible. (For example, the use of existing anime characters would be a violation of copyrights.)&lt;br/&gt;- Art must not contain explicit sexuality, violence, or any discriminatory elements.&lt;br/&gt;- The final layout and design of the poster, flyer and other publicity materials will be created and approved by Japan Day Inc.  Artist’s approval is not required for publication.&lt;br/&gt;- By submitting their artwork, artists grant Japan Day Inc. the right to use their work for the purpose of marketing, exhibition and other Japan Day-related uses. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please visit the website (http://www.japandaynyc.org/artcontest2020) for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1003fd76-f045-4f5c-85fe-838a7630068e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4ff24684-9e28-429f-83de-f8f1c08e1879</id><title>1/6 - Beam Center Seeks Ambitious Project Proposals for New Hampshire and Brooklyn</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.678713+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Beam Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/06/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://beamcenter.org/updates"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the last 15 years, Beam has conducted an international search for spectacular project ideas to be built at Beam Camp in New Hampshire. For the first time this year, we are putting out calls for two big ideas for two places: one for camp in New Hampshire and one to be built in Brooklyn as our 2020 NYC Beam Project.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Beam Projects are spectacular collaborations between visionary big thinkers and the Beam Community of youth and creative and technical experts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What we’re looking for in Beam Project Proposals:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Projects coming from creative individuals and teams, including but not limited to Artists, Designers, Architects, Builders, Engineers, Musicians, Fabricators &amp; Technologists.&lt;br/&gt;• Big ideas that culminate in a unique, ambitious, and spectacular artwork in a public space&lt;br/&gt;• Utilize a range of materials and a range of fabrication processes&lt;br/&gt;• Proposals that communicate a clear vision (sketches, diagrams, and other visuals are always helpful) and represent your/your team’s expertise&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For details on each call and to submit a proposal:&lt;br/&gt;New Hampshire Project Call -  &lt;a href="https://beamcamp.org/projectproposal" target="_blank"&gt;https://beamcamp.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;New York City Project Call - &lt;a href="https://beamcenter.org/nycbeamprojectproposal" target="_blank"&gt;https://beamcenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Individuals and teams can apply for one or both projects. Proposal deadline for both is Monday, January 6, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://beamcenter.org/updates" target="_blank"&gt;https://beamcenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4ff24684-9e28-429f-83de-f8f1c08e1879" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0dd25bc4-2205-4268-aeae-8961f1c8356d</id><title>11/3 - Light The Night – Pink  Fundraiser  Call For Artists</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.678686+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Lighthouse Court Reporting Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 Remsenburg, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/03/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When:&lt;br/&gt;November 16, 2019 from 6:00 – 9:00 pm &lt;br/&gt;Where:&lt;br/&gt;2 Main Street, Sayville NY 11782- THORNHILLS BUILDING&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Call for artists to showcase their art for a local fundraiser. A one-night fundraiser where a portion of the art sale proceeds will go to &lt;br/&gt;           The Carol M. Baldwin Breast Care Center, Stony Brook, NY 11790.&lt;br/&gt;•	Special attention given for Long Island artists who’ve been affected by breast cancer that would like to help families and communities understand the impact of breast cancer. &lt;br/&gt;•	Additionally,  opencall extended to Long Island and NYC artists interested in this one-night exhibit in Sayville.&lt;br/&gt;•	Deadline for entries is Sunday, November 3rd, 2019. Artists must be able to transport and pick up unsold artwork to the gallery space in Sayville independently.&lt;br/&gt;•	Lighting ceremony accompanies the fundraiser, lighting the iconic neon Thornhill’s Pharmacy sign for the first time nearly 70 years. The Thornhill’s Pharmacy building has been renovated and will host the fundraiser.&lt;br/&gt;•	Call Matthew LaPiana at 716-812-7504 for details.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call Matthew LaPiana at 716-812-7504 for details.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0dd25bc4-2205-4268-aeae-8961f1c8356d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cd6d55fb-432b-41a8-94ec-14c5d2ece214</id><title>12/10 - Portrait: Identity and Expression</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.678652+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $37.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Portrait: Identity and Expression&lt;br/&gt;January 31– February 29, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Portraiture hinges on the question of whom deserves to be shown. Beginning with religious and royal iconography, produced under systems of patronage, portraits were meant to immortalize the divine, powerful, and wealthy. However, what it means to make a portrait — its subject, form, method, and medium — has expanded beyond those previous confines. There has been a democratization of both subject matter, and practitioners. In reconceptualizing many of the old categories, as well as ushering in a variety of new ones, successive generations of artists have interrogated our received images of race, class, beauty, gender, sexuality. Site:Brooklyn is calling for works, across all mediums, that engage with the increasingly complex intersection between portrait and identity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Claire Voon is a freelance arts journalist and critic who lives in Chicago. Her writing has appeared in publications including the New York Times, ARTnews,The Art Newspaper, Artsy, New York magazine, and Garage. She was formerly an assistant editor at Chicago Magazine and a staff writer at Hyperallergic.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: October 26, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: December 10, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: December 19, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: January 31– February 29, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, January  31, 2020 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in drawing, painting, printmaking, sculpture, collage. photography, video. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $37.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by December 10, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2orZdhz" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 72” X 60” X 24” D&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;4. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the Ink “Portrait: Identity and Expression, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2orZdhz" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cd6d55fb-432b-41a8-94ec-14c5d2ece214" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6971b7c7-84c7-4bb7-b79f-a294aedeb532</id><title>11/25 - Summit Public Art:  Call for Artists Spring 2020</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.678607+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Summit Public Art&lt;br/&gt;📍 Summit, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://summitpublicart.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call for Artists for Spring, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: November 25, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art&lt;br/&gt;Summit, New Jersey&lt;br/&gt;summitpublicarts@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art is a volunteer-based, city organization whose mission is to bring public art to public spaces in Summit. Since its inception in 2002, Summit Public Art has installed over 100 diverse temporary works of art from artists of national and international renown, as well as emerging artists. The artists’ works span across a broad range of media from metal to glass, from stone to wood to fiber. Summit Public Art has also installed four permanent public art works, including stained glass panels in the bus shelters and the gateway project, Silver Sentinel by Douwe Blumberg.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SPA’s Artwork Theme for 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The theme for artwork installations for 2020 is Light and Motion. This theme should be viewed as a general direction, and we welcome interpretation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art’s Temporary Art Program&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork for the 2020 cycle will be installed from April - early July.&lt;br/&gt;Installations typically remain in place for twelve months.&lt;br/&gt;Installation sites are typically situated in downtown Summit, in city parks, and other high visibility locations. &lt;br/&gt;SPA provides identifying signage for artwork at the site.&lt;br/&gt;SPA provides public relation opportunities.&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art provides an honorarium to support the artist’s project and related expenses, including installation and de-installation.  For this call, honorariums of up to $5000 are being offered. &lt;br/&gt;Artwork is insured by the City of Summit while on display.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Review Process&lt;br/&gt;All art installation proposals are reviewed by the Art Selection Committee with subsequent approval required by the full Summit Public Art Board. Once approved, finalists’ proposals are submitted to the City of Summit for final approval. Upon final approval by the City, the artist enters into a contractual agreement with the City of Summit. &lt;br/&gt;The deadline for submission is November 25, 2019.  All artists will be notified of SPA’s decision by the end of December, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Requirements&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art welcomes proposals for our upcoming installation cycle and asks artists to provide the following, using our Artist Proposal Form found online here.  Please submit your proposal by email to summitpublicarts@gmail.com by November 25, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s résumé or CV, including information and details about educational background, previous work, gallery showings, and past experience in public art exhibits.&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s Statement conveying your vision as an artist and your body of work in 150 words or less.&lt;br/&gt;Project Description highlighting your creative intentions, including how your artwork interprets the theme. &lt;br/&gt;Digital images of proposed artwork, as well as 3 to 5 images of past work in jpeg format.  Include an associated image list including title, date of completion, medium, dimensions, and location. Each image should be no larger than 500 MB, with the total digital presentation not to exceed 1 GB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork for consideration should avoid:&lt;br/&gt;Fragile and easily damaged or breakable materials such as paper or glass.&lt;br/&gt;Sharp edges, points, projections, or pinch-points, which may cut, puncture or cause injury by impact, catching passing pedestrian clothing or entrapment of limbs.&lt;br/&gt;Overhead parts, which present a hazard to pedestrian traffic. Artwork should follow minimum sign height requirements in areas where pedestrian traffic is likely.&lt;br/&gt;Unsafe climbing opportunities for children/adults.&lt;br/&gt;Obstruction of any traffic control device.&lt;br/&gt;Cynical, pornographic, and otherwise obscene artwork deemed inappropriate for general audiences.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All work must be suitable for outdoor display in the Northeastern United States, with its variety of climatic conditions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following non-artistic items will not be considered: &lt;br/&gt;Reproductions of original works of art&lt;br/&gt;Decorative, ornamental, or functional elements.&lt;br/&gt;“Art objects” which are mass-produced of standard design.&lt;br/&gt;Directional or other functional elements such as super-graphics, signs, color coding, or maps.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s Responsibilities&lt;br/&gt;Fabrication, transportation, installation, and deinstallation. Tools, materials and equipment are not provided by Summit Public Art.&lt;br/&gt;Timely and proper installation and removal of artwork. &lt;br/&gt;Technical reports prepared by a licensed engineer, if needed.&lt;br/&gt;Maintenance of artwork, if necessary.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the City of Summit&lt;br/&gt;Summit is home to more than 21,000 with approximately 175,000 people who live within a five mile radius.&lt;br/&gt;The city is a major transport hub visited by over 17,000 visitors daily.&lt;br/&gt;Summit is a diverse community with residents who speak more than 35 languages.&lt;br/&gt;The city is an economically and culturally diverse community -- the Visual Arts Center of NJ, Reeves-Reed Arboretum, Summit Playhouse, plus many other arts and cultural organizations call Summit home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Requirements&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Summit Public Art welcomes proposals for our upcoming installation cycle and asks artists to provide the following, using our Artist Proposal Form (found on Summit Public Art website:  summitpublicart.com).  Please submit your proposal by email to summitpublicarts@gmail.com by November 25, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s résumé or CV, including information and details about educational background, previous work, gallery showings, and past experience in public art exhibits.&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s Statement conveying your vision as an artist and your body of work in 150 words or less.&lt;br/&gt;Project Description highlighting your creative intentions, including how your artwork interprets the theme. &lt;br/&gt;Digital images of proposed artwork, as well as 3 to 5 images of past work in jpeg format.  Include an associated image list including title, date of completion, medium, dimensions, and location. Each image should be no larger than 500 MB, with the total digital presentation not to exceed 1 GB.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6971b7c7-84c7-4bb7-b79f-a294aedeb532" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>670f34d1-7077-4d0a-88f2-512f9236c352</id><title>11/17 - CALL FOR ART  THE BIG SHOW: ALL ANIMALS WELCOME, Deadline for Submission: 11/17/19</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.678581+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Drawing Rooms&lt;br/&gt;📍 Jersey City, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.drawingrooms.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All professional artists, anywhere, are invited to submit work for consideration in Drawing Rooms 2019 year-end fundraiser exhibit, THE BIG SHOW: All Animals Welcome, 12/13/19 - 2/8/20.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THEME: The earliest art images known to man were cave paintings which depicted animals to help tell the story of their lives, giving animals a mythic and symbolic presence. Artists have continued to be interested in animals as subject matter. Peaceable Kingdom by Edward Hicks takes its theme from a passage in the bible which tells of the animals gathering together in harmony, Guernica by Picasso tells a story of war, Deborah Butterfield’s horses are a metaphorical substitute for herself, Louise Bourgeois’ spiders allude to the strength of her mother, and were used as a symbol of nurturing and protection. Animals are of great importance as companions to humans, bringing joy and comfort into our lives. We cherish animals as part of our families, and also consider them our friends and protectors. Animals, insects and even micro-organisms have important roles in the ecosystem, co-existing and balancing each other out. Some animals and insects help to reduce negative impacts on the globe, addressing issues such as global warming and pollution. Animals deserve our respect. Issues around extinction and the care and treatment of animals are of the utmost importance. How are artists incorporating animals into their artwork today? What meaning is placed upon animals and how are animals used as image, symbol and metaphor in artists works today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All media accepted, up to 30-inches, although a few larger works may be considered.&lt;br/&gt;No fee to submit. $40 hanging fee for accepted artists which includes a copy of Drawing Rooms 2019 Yearbook.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please learn more about the call here and how to submit: &lt;br/&gt;http://www.drawingrooms.org/the-big-show-2019-call.html&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/670f34d1-7077-4d0a-88f2-512f9236c352" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>37afdce1-0425-4ac4-87e8-74c9aa4ad010</id><title>12/31 - Artfare Submissions Program</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.678550+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Artfare, Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artfare.com/for-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artfare is a platform that allows artists and patrons to connect through our iPhone app (artfare.com/app).  Patrons can follow artists, request studio visits, and purchase work posted by our curated group of professional artists. We started out in NYC early 2019 and have recently started accepting submissions from LA, Chicago, and Miami.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artfare allows artists to present their work to a broad audience and connect with patrons both digitally and in person through studio visits, exhibitions and events. Using our app, artists can also discover and communicate with other artists and curators, and work together to independently organize exhibitions and events.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artfare artists are based in NYC and actively make and show their work. Our group is carefully curated and  selective. In addition to quality and maturity in the work, we seek artists with professional track records and career ambition. We aim to create a well rounded program that represents all voices and mediums. Please browse the app and artfare.com to get a sense of our mission and artist list. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our tools and services allow artists to:&lt;br/&gt;1. Easily share links to your available works and facilitate sales from your studio, both on and offline&lt;br/&gt;2. Build a following of potential patrons and curators in a professional context&lt;br/&gt;3. Receive tax documents at year end and let Artfare collect, file, and pay sales tax on your behalf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you would like to submit your work for consideration please do so by September 30 via this link (please choose you city from the menu):&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://artfare.slideroom.com/&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/37afdce1-0425-4ac4-87e8-74c9aa4ad010" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6c4295ac-eb8a-4752-9610-c85536bbbcdf</id><title>Open Call All Mediums! WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!  Friday 8th 2019</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.678470+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our Nov 8th Open Call Juried Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, Nov 8th , 2019 from 8pm- 12am.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, Nov. 7th, 2019 at 8pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is a Juried Salon style show. We have a panel of esteemed judges who will choose the winners! &lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We'll have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup ofMusicalGuests &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/394062041476736/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up their work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINES:&lt;br/&gt;Submissions must be received by 8pm Thurs Nov 7th &lt;br/&gt;REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF DEADLINE IS THURSDAY, Nov. 7th at 11pm. &lt;br/&gt;Works must arrive to the gallery by 11pm. We do not accept works shipped in the mail and must be dropped off in person.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces already this past year. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com  Instagram: @ Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/394062041476736/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6c4295ac-eb8a-4752-9610-c85536bbbcdf" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c5ba5985-af38-4516-a6f8-ce0f7a2e3aed</id><title>12/15 - Open Call for Papers: 2020 Nasher Prize Graduate Symposium</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.678430+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Nasher Sculpture Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Dallas, TX, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.nashersculpturecenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nasher Sculpture Center Announces the 2020 Nasher Prize Graduate Symposium Open Call for Papers&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Symposium to address the work of 2020 Laureate, Michael Rakowitz; University of North Texas’s Dr. Nada Shabout to moderate&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DALLAS, Texas (October 28, 2019)—Nasher Sculpture Center announces an open call for participation in the 2020 Nasher Prize Graduate Symposium, which aims to expand scholarship on the field of contemporary sculpture in its many forms. Submissions should address themes related to the work of the 2020 Nasher Prize Laureate Michael Rakowitz. This year’s symposium will be moderated by Dr. Nada Shabout of University of North Texas, founding president of the Association for Modern and Contemporary Art from the Arab World, Iran and Turkey.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The Nasher Prize Graduate Symposium, addresses a broad audience of art historians and museum professionals, allowing symposium participants to receive feedback from fellow presenters, the moderator, the keynote speaker, and audience members. Students selected to present papers will also have their work published in the annual symposium compendium, together with the paper delivered by the keynote speaker, yet to be announced.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Since his career began in the late 1990s, Michael Rakowitz’s dynamic body of work has involved intensive research, resulting in an array of objects, environments, films, and publications that seek to reclaim, reposition, or refocus complicated aspects of material and cultural histories or events. He has especial interest in refugee and migrant populations, particularly from the Middle East. Often durational in nature, his projects frequently enlist the participation of collaborators or the public to create objects or events, making the work as much participatory as it is material.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Since 2003, Rakowitz’s work has considered his own heritage as an American descendent of the Iraqi Jewish diaspora with projects that include, among other efforts, research into the archeological artifacts and sites that have been destroyed or compromised due to political conflict. His ongoing project The invisible enemy should not exist, begun in 2007, seeks to recreate the thousands of artifacts that were looted or destroyed in the raiding of the National Museum of Iraq, Baghdad in 2003, as well as artifacts decimated by ISIS in 2015 during a destructive spree on cultural sites and institutions throughout Iraq. For this, Rakowitz solicits the help of communities of people to remake each of the artifacts, at their original scale, using images and information from the University of Chicago’s Oriental Institute database. Employing packaging from Middle Eastern food products and Arabic newspapers in combination with simple sculptural means, such as papier-mâché, the ancient objects are recreated as colorful, text- and image-laden sculptures that the artist has described as “ghosts”.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Suggested Topics for the 2020 Nasher Prize Graduate Symposium:&lt;br/&gt;–Provisional architecture within sculpture&lt;br/&gt;–Archaeology and the politics of cultural heritage&lt;br/&gt;–Food in social practice and community-healing&lt;br/&gt;–Traditional sculptural methods in contemporary sculptural practice&lt;br/&gt;–Transmissions of skill or expertise as forms of resistance to cultural erasure&lt;br/&gt;- Social media and e-commerce sites as paths of research&lt;br/&gt;- Artistic responses to the destruction of cultural patrimony&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Complete proposals must include the following:&lt;br/&gt;–Contact information, participant’s field and university affiliation, and CV&lt;br/&gt;–Paper title and abstract of no more than 200 words, and 3 to 5 keywords&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposals are due by Sunday, December 15, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;Send submissions and questions to symposium@nashersculpturecenter.org&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;We hope to notify successful applicants by January 13, 2020. Registration information will follow.&lt;br/&gt;With proof of need, eligible candidates may be considered for scholarship funding to offset travel costs.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;About Michael Rakowitz, 2020 Nasher Prize Laureate&lt;br/&gt;Michael Rakowitz was born in 1973 in Great Neck, New York; he lives and works in Chicago, Illinois and is professor of art theory and practice at Northwestern University. He studied at Purchase College, State University of New York, where he received a BFA in 1995 and at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, graduating with a Master of Science in Visual Studies in 1998. His recent retrospective opened at the Whitechapel Gallery, London, in 2019, traveling to Castello di Rivoli Museo d’Arte Contemporanea, Rivoli-Torino and, in 2020 is scheduled to open at the Jameel Art Centre, Dubai. It was preceded by Backstroke of the West, a survey exhibition at the Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago in 2018.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;He has exhibited in venues including dOCUMENTA(13), The Museum of Modern Art, New York; MoMA/PS1, New York; Tate Modern, London; MassMOCA; Castello di Rivoli; the 10th and 14th Istanbul Biennials; the Sharjah Biennials 8 and 14 ; the Tirana Biennale; and Transmediale 05.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Rakowitz is the recipient of many awards and honors, including the 2018 Herb Alpert Award in Visual Arts, a 2012 Louis Comfort Tiffany Foundation Biennial Award, a 2008 Creative Capital Grant, the Sharjah Biennial Jury Award, a 2006 New York Foundation for the Arts Fellowship Grant in Architecture and Environmental Structures, the 2003 Dena Foundations Award, and the 2002 Design 21 Grand Prix from UNESCO.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;About Nada Shabout, moderator&lt;br/&gt;Nada Shabout is a Professor of Art History and the Coordinator of the Contemporary Arab and Muslim Cultural Studies Initiative at the University of North Texas, Denton, Texas, U.S.A. She is the founding president of the Association for Modern and Contemporary Art from the Arab World, Iran and Turkey. Shabout is the Project Advisor for the Saudi National Pavilion, Venice Biennale 2019. She is the author of Modern Arab Art: Formation of Arab Aesthetics, University of Florida Press, 2007; co-editor with Salwa Mikdadi of New Vision: Arab Art in the 21st Century, Thames &amp; Hudson, 2009; and co-editor with Anneka Lenssen and Sarah Rogers of Modern Art in the Arab World: Primary Documents, Museum of Modern Art, New York, 2018.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Shabout was the curator of Sajjil: A Century of Modern Art, Interventions: A dialogue between the Modern and the Contemporary, 2010; co-curator of Modernism and Iraq, Wallach Art Gallery, Columbia University, 2009, and curator of the traveling exhibition, Dafatir: Contemporary Iraqi Book Art, 2005-2009. Her awards include: Writers Grant, Andy Warhol Foundation 2018; The Presidential Excellency Award, UNT 2018; The American Academic Research Institute in Iraq fellow 2006, 2007; MIT visiting Assistant Professor, spring 2008, and Fulbright Senior Scholar Program, 2008 Lecture/Research fellowship to Jordan.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;For images, please follow this link: &lt;a href="https://www.dropbox.com/sh/el7d53y01em6edf/AABXzijbOsied5R-hCI53MOEa?dl=0" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.dropbox.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;About the Nasher Sculpture Center&lt;br/&gt;Located in the heart of the Dallas Arts District and designed by architect Renzo Piano, the Nasher Sculpture Center is home to the Raymond and Patsy Nasher Collection, one of the finest collections of modern and contemporary sculpture in the world, featuring more than 300 masterpieces by Calder, de Kooning, di Suvero, Giacometti, Gormley, Hepworth, Kelly, Matisse, Miró, Moore, Picasso, Rodin, Serra, and Shapiro, among others. On view in the light-filled galleries and amid the garden grounds is a rotating selection of works from the Collection, as well as important exhibitions of modern and contemporary sculpture, including Sightings, a series of small-scale exhibitions and site-specific installations that explore new work by established and emerging artists. In addition to the indoor and outdoor gallery spaces, the Center contains an auditorium, education and research facilities, a cafe, and a store. For more information, visit www.NasherSculptureCenter.org.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Media Contact:&lt;br/&gt;Lucia Simek&lt;br/&gt;Manager of Communications and International Programs&lt;br/&gt;Nasher Sculpture Center&lt;br/&gt;LSimek@nashersculpturecenter.org&lt;br/&gt;+1 214 242 5177&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete proposals must include the following:&lt;br/&gt;–Contact information, participant’s field and university affiliation, and CV&lt;br/&gt;–Paper title and abstract of no more than 200 words, and 3 to 5 keywords&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposals are due by Sunday, December 15, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;Send submissions and questions to symposium@nashersculpturecenter.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c5ba5985-af38-4516-a6f8-ce0f7a2e3aed" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3ee34df3-5600-442d-8dfd-cf1834abc49f</id><title>11/10 - stARTup Art Fair Los Angeles 2020: Call for Artists</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.678378+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Startup Art Fair LLC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Venice, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.startupartfair.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;stARTup Art Fair Los Angeles is a contemporary hotel art fair for independent artists.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our three-day fair is February 14-16, 2020 at the hip and stylish The Kinney in Venice, with easy access to Venice Beach, Santa Monica and Marina Del Rey. stARTup LA takes place concurrently with Frieze LA and the Art Los Angeles Contemporary gallery fairs nearby. Participating artists will have a fantastic opportunity to expose new work to a myriad of collectors, curators, gallery owners, art consultants, and writers who will be coming to the city for a weekend of contemporary art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The core mission of stARTup Art Fair is to provide a marketplace that gives artists the power to present and sell work on their own terms. All sales proceeds belong 100% to the artists.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications for stARTup Art Fair Los Angeles will be accepted through November 10, 2019. Those selected from the open application process will each take over a hotel room for the course of three days to present a solo show of their work. Through its democratic, online application, artists get the opportunity to have their work reviewed by an impressive Selection Committee of diverse art world professionals.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There are application and exhibitor fees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and to apply, visit: &lt;a href="https://www.startupartfair.com/apply-for-la-2020" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.startupartfair.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3ee34df3-5600-442d-8dfd-cf1834abc49f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3faaf5a2-6807-4290-970e-7295e56fdc4b</id><title>Open Call For Artists</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677543+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Mahlstedt Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Rochelle, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://jam415.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEN CALL FOR ARTISTS - INTERNATIONAL&lt;br/&gt;Mahlstedt Gallery is currently accepting submissions for 2019-2020 and is sending out a call to artists, at all stages in their art careers, from around the world to submit their portfolios for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;We are accepting submissions from  visual artists, digital artists, illustrators, and photographers.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Mahlstedt Gallery is proud to represent talented, international artists, helping them achieve success in one of the most exciting regions of the global art community. Representation is offered to talented artists at every stage of their career, and acceptance is granted on the basis of a portfolio review carried out by the Mahlstedt Gallery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit 6-8 jpegs of work to opencall@jam415.com Artwork should be accompanied by title, medium, and dimensions.&lt;br/&gt;First and Last Name&lt;br/&gt;Direct Phone&lt;br/&gt;Email&lt;br/&gt;Artists website&lt;br/&gt;Links to any of your social media platform&lt;br/&gt;Your biography&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3faaf5a2-6807-4290-970e-7295e56fdc4b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>485ecf1c-1834-4d96-bab5-514a271626d9</id><title>12/9 - Ink:New Prints</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677514+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Printmaking&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $37.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ink: New Prints&lt;br/&gt;January 31– February 29, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is seeking work for its upcoming printmaking exhibition. We are looking for a wide variety of work, in order to best represent that state of contemporary printmaking. We are accepting work in a number of mediums, including serigraphy, letterpress, calligraphy, etching, woodcut, lithography, linocut, drypoint, mezzotint, mono-print, solar plates and book-making. Digital and photographic elements may be used only as a supporting element.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Laura G. Einstein is currently Manager of the Mezzanine Gallery at The Metropolitan Museum of Art. She has more than thirty years’ experience in curating and museum work. Einstein has worked as Interim Head and Assistant Curator of the Asian Art Department at Yale University Art Gallery and lecturer at The Metropolitan Museum of Art and at the IBM Gallery of Science and Art, among other institutions. Einstein served as Executive Director at the Center for Contemporary Printmaking in Norwalk, Connecticut. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: October 25, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: December 9, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: December 18, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: January 31– February 29, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, January  31, 2020 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in printmaking,  This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $37.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by December 9, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:  &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2pR5bZT" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 72” X 60” X 6” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. &lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;4. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Ink:New Prints” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:  &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2pR5bZT" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/485ecf1c-1834-4d96-bab5-514a271626d9" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>59a017da-d9c5-42d0-b2dc-744b7df56c8e</id><title>11/15 - OPEN CALL - WINTER MARKET - VENDORS - ARTISTS - ARTISANS - MAKERS - CREATIVES</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677490+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Local Project&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://localproject.org/winter-market-open-call-2019/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking for artists and artisans to sell original hand-made or designed objects at our 3rd Annual Winter Market that will take place on Saturday December 7, 2019 from 12pm-7PM at THE LOCAL HOSTEL in LIC 1302 44th AVE.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no fee for application.&lt;br/&gt;Application DEADLINE: Nov 15, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Artist will be notified in a few days as they submit.&lt;br/&gt;Local Projects takes NO commission on any sales unless other wise.&lt;br/&gt;LP will:&lt;br/&gt;– Provide tables and chairs (you must bring your own tablecloth if you want one).&lt;br/&gt;– Provide promotional material, printed posters, hashtags, newsletter, FB Event.&lt;br/&gt;– Help provide an audience but vendors are encourage to help spread the word.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMIT :&lt;br/&gt;– 2-5 low res images&lt;br/&gt;– Your website or social media platforms, and explain what will you like to sell and your preference for either full or half table,&lt;br/&gt;$100 One table 2 chairs&lt;br/&gt;$50 Half table one chair&lt;br/&gt;(wall space NOT included)&lt;br/&gt;to OPENCALL@LOCALPROJECT.ORG including WINTER MARKET 2019 in the subject&lt;br/&gt;Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;– Vendor is responsible for the transportation in and out on time provided.&lt;br/&gt;– Commit to be present for the market from 11:00 till end&lt;br/&gt;– Sell original art, handmade or designed objects by you.&lt;br/&gt;– Pay Table fee as soon as accepted&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/59a017da-d9c5-42d0-b2dc-744b7df56c8e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>371a2da8-278b-433e-bcbf-d9b7f776f014</id><title>1/6 - Operator for the Harlem African Burial Ground Memorial &amp;amp; Cultural Center RFEI</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677465+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;NYCEDC&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/06/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://edc.nyc/operator-harlem-african-burial-ground-memorial-cultural-center-rfei"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York City Economic Development Corporation (NYCEDC) in collaboration with the NYC Department of Cultural Affairs (DCLA) released a Request for Expressions of Interest (RFEI) to select a non-profit arts or cultural organization to operate a memorial and cultural education center at the site of a historical African Burial Ground associated with the former Reformed Low Dutch Church of Harlem dating back to the late 17th century.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The historical burial ground was discovered in the early 2000s beneath the East 126th Street Metropolitan Transportation Authority Bus Depot. The public memorial will be located outdoors at the location of the historical burial ground and the cultural education center will be housed in an adjacent building. The cultural education center could include elements such as a visitor center, exhibitions explaining the history of the site, and community space for programming inspired by the Burial Ground. The cultural education center is intended to offer a variety of public programming and activities, which may include artist workshops, artists-in-residence, visiting scholars and thought leaders in arts and culture, advocacy, literacy and social justice.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NYCEDC plans to designate an operator for the Cultural Education Center and Outdoor Memorial to participate in the Project on the basis of factors stated in the RFEI which include, but are not limited to: the quality of the proposal, experience of key staff identified in the proposal, demonstrated successful experience in performing services similar to those encompassed in the RFEI, and the financial capacity of the respondent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;INQUIRIES&lt;br/&gt;Optional informational sessions will be held at 12pm at NYCEDC and at 6:30pm at The Silberman School of Social Work at Hunter College on Thursday, November 7, 2019. Those who wish to attend either session should RSVP by email to HABG_RFEI@edc.nyc on or before October 31, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Respondents may submit questions and/or request clarifications from NYCEDC no later than 5pm on Thursday, November 14, 2019. Questions regarding the subject matter of this RFP should be directed to HABG_RFEI@edc.nyc. For all questions that do not pertain to the subject matter of this RFEI please contact NYCEDC’s Contracts Hotline at (212) 312-3969. Answers to all questions will be posted by Friday, November 22, 2019, to edc.nyc/rfps.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;Detailed submission guidelines and requirements are outlined in the RFEI, available as of Monday, October 21, 2019. The RFEI is available for in-person pick-up between 9:30am and 4:30pm, Monday through Friday, from NYCEDC, One Liberty Plaza, 165 Broadway, 14th floor, New York, NY 10006. To download a copy of the solicitation documents please visit edc.nyc/rfps. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RESPONSES ARE DUE NO LATER THAN 4pm on Monday, January 6, 2020. Please submit five (5) sets of your expression and one (1) digital copy USB flash drive of your expression of interest to:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NYCEDC, One Liberty Plaza, 165 Broadway, New York, NY 10006&lt;br/&gt;Attention: Maryann Catalano, Chief Contracting Officer, Contracts.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/371a2da8-278b-433e-bcbf-d9b7f776f014" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f309d1dd-e853-4fc0-8423-cdf58e61c738</id><title>11/15 - Mobius Photo Winter Portfolio Competition</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677442+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Mobius Photo LLC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.mobiusphoto.co/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;8-10 images surrounding a specific theme, vision or story&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About :: Mobius Photo is an online platform dedicated to the curation of emerging and established photographers through quarterly photography competitions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;How It Works :: Submissions are open for 6 week periods. Winners are announced 2 weeks after the closing date. Selected works live on the website for the following year.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Follow us on social at @mobiusphoto (instagram) &lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/MobiusPhotoCo/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.mobiusphoto.co/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply at &lt;a href="https://www.jotform.com/MobiusPhoto/winter-2019-portfolio-submission" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f309d1dd-e853-4fc0-8423-cdf58e61c738" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7a7b7b75-6d14-486c-8ef0-de42be12202d</id><title>12/16 - The Art of Diversity</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677419+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Bridgeman Images&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/16/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.enterbsa.com/usa-home"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enter the Bridgeman Studio Award 2019 and you could win a £5000 cash prize, plus the winning artwork will be turned into a limited edition print and exhibited in London in March 2020. 5 runners-up will also receive £500 cash and have their works exhibited in the London exhibition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enter the Bridgeman Studio Award 2019 and you could win a $6000 cash prize, plus the winning artwork will be turned into a limited edition print and exhibited in London in March 2020. 5 runners-up will also receive $600 cash and have their works exhibited in the London exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JUDGES&lt;br/&gt;Zak Ove - Artist &amp; Curator&lt;br/&gt;Sinta Tantra - Artist&lt;br/&gt;Victoria Bridgeman - CEO - Bridgeman Images&lt;br/&gt;Verizon Media&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7a7b7b75-6d14-486c-8ef0-de42be12202d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>be7d6785-a907-4a2e-8df7-ea07fa595957</id><title>11/15 - WEATHERED: An International Call for Works About Wear or Signs of Time Passing</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677395+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/weathered"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cincinnati based non-profit arts organization and gallery, Manifest, invites visual artists to submit works which in some way address or reflect the theme of weathered.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Japanese concept of wabi-sabi includes the appreciation for the ingenuous integrity of natural objects and processes. Time wears all things. Literally taken weathering is an aspect of the elements, but not without time. Wind, rain, sun, fire, and ice, and even mechanical means, transform everything. Weathering then is the process by which things in our world, and the world itself, are in the process of always becoming. In appreciating such processes one becomes aware of the signs of surviving age, stress, life, the toll of an ordeal or accomplishment, and existence itself. Through weathering a compelling narrative unfolds.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists are encouraged to take a broadly creative view in interpreting the theme as it applies to their work. Submissions can range from the most traditional realism to the most conceptual, abstract, or experimental.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$40 for up to FOUR entries submitted. $5 per each additional entry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To view the full prospectus and entry form visit &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/weathered." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email info@manifestgallery.org with questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/be7d6785-a907-4a2e-8df7-ea07fa595957" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1775b078-a8e8-4c0f-a18f-ee759eb00984</id><title>11/15 - EXPO 39 Juried Competition and Exhibition</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677371+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;bj spoke gallery, Huntington, NY&lt;br/&gt;📍 Huntington, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.bjspokegallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a juries show accepting entries for all visual fine arts media, including video,and will consider works of all artists living within the United States.  The juror is Linda Kavaliunas, Curatorial Assistant at the Museum of Modern Art in New York.  Artists may submit up to 6 images and/or 2 short videos.  Accepted artists will have from one to 8 pieces included in a show in March of 2020 at the bj spoke gallery in Huntington, NY.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All entries will be made through www.callforentry.org.  Details and a complete prospectus will be found at &lt;a href="http://www.bjspokegallery.org/expo-39/." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bjspokegallery.org&lt;/a&gt;  Artists are expected to ship or deliver their work and provide insurance if they so wish.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1775b078-a8e8-4c0f-a18f-ee759eb00984" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>06cb88cf-3f8e-423f-a686-900f4c0832a9</id><title>10/27 - National Juried Exhibition Lycoming College</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677342+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Lycoming College&lt;br/&gt;📍 Williamsport, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/27/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.lycoming.edu"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call for Entry: No Entry Fee&lt;br/&gt;National Juried Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;Lycoming College Downtown Art Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Blurred Expectations&lt;br/&gt;Lycoming College Art Gallery, located in Downtown Williamsport, Pennsylvania, is seeking submissions for their National Juried Exhibition, Blurred Expectations. &lt;br/&gt;Criminals! Subordinate! Uneducated! These are a few of many terms that are commonly associated with black people. This exhibition gives black artists an opportunity to rewrite the script that has been forced upon them by showing a side that is often ignored.  Though many people do not agree with such associations, these stereotypes are still at the forefront of media and society which creates division within black communities and their multiethnic counterparts. This exhibition blurs the line between how black people are portrayed and who they truly are outside of their race. By focusing on the artistic interests of black artists, viewers not only reflect on the many forms that inspiration and creativity can take but challenge the false portrayals of black people in society.&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;Professional artists as well as student artists are encouraged to enter. Entries must represent original works of art that address the stated theme. There is no size restriction, other than what can fit through our gallery doors. There is no restriction governing date of completion.&lt;br/&gt;MEDIA&lt;br/&gt;All media (2D and 3D) will be accepted including video. Please follow the submission guidelines below.&lt;br/&gt;NO ENTRY FEE&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION OF IMAGES AND IMAGE LIST&lt;br/&gt;Lycoming College Gallery will retain the submitted images of accepted artwork and reserves the right to use the images in publications and gallery publicity. Beyond such use, the artist retains full copyright of exhibited work.&lt;br/&gt;Still images should be sent as jpegs and be at least 1000px at their widest dimension, but not exceed 2MB each. The filename format is indicated below.&lt;br/&gt;Send entries to lycocampusartgallery@lycoming.edu&lt;br/&gt;Email Subject Line: Blurred Expectations_Last Name&lt;br/&gt;A maximum of five works accepted. Please label each image with &lt;Lastname&gt;.&lt;Number&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please include an accompanying image list with the following information: Artist Name, Number that corresponds to jpeg entry number, Title, Media, Size, Value (must include value for insurance purposes even if the work is NFS)&lt;br/&gt;For video submissions, please link directly to online or downloadable content that does NOT require a login, password or membership to view. These may be in the form of Youtube, Vimeo, or personal websites. Links to video entries must remain valid and active through the notification of jury results.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important dates:&lt;br/&gt;10/27 (Midnight) Submission Deadline&lt;br/&gt;11/4 Notifications of Results&lt;br/&gt;11/14 Latest date for artwork arrival&lt;br/&gt;11/22 Opening reception 5-8pm&lt;br/&gt;1/24  Last day of show&lt;br/&gt;Artwork will be shipped within a week after the show ends&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shipping Artwork and Return of Work&lt;br/&gt;All work accepted for the exhibition must arrive ready to install. Works not gallery ready, or not exhibiting good craftsmanship, may be eliminated from the final exhibition. Accepted work that differs significantly from the entry images or suffers from poor presentation choices, will be disqualified. Please note that professional level presentation and craftsmanship is a requirement. Work may be hand delivered or shipped. Shipped works must be sent in an easily reusable container/packaging with return shipping prepaid. All work must arrive at the gallery by the specified date (see calendar above). Accepted work will remain on display for the duration of the exhibition. The artists are responsible for all shipping costs to and from the gallery. &lt;br/&gt;Ship Accepted Work To: &lt;br/&gt;Lycoming College &lt;br/&gt;Art Department&lt;br/&gt;Impending Future Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;700 College Place&lt;br/&gt;Williamsport, PA&lt;br/&gt;17701&lt;br/&gt;Sales &lt;br/&gt;Lycoming College does not take a commission for works sold at their galleries. If a work is not for sale please indicate with NFS value in appropriate space on the consignment sheet. Lycoming College will put potential collectors in touch with the respective artists but will not negotiate sales. &lt;br/&gt;Liability&lt;br/&gt;All entries will be handled with the best care possible, but Lycoming College is not responsible for loss or damage of any kind cause during shipping. Works will be insured while on gallery premises only. Insurance covers theft, vandalism, damage caused by gallery visitors or staff as stated in our insurance policy. Also not covered is damage caused to work by failure of the artwork itself, its installation systems provided by the artist, disintegration/degradation due to the quality of materials or craftsmanship. By entering into this show, the artist agrees to abide by all rules and regulations as set by exhibition guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still images should be sent as jpegs and be at least 1000px at their widest dimension, but not exceed 2MB each. The filename format is indicated below.&lt;br/&gt;Send entries to lycocampusartgallery@lycoming.edu&lt;br/&gt;Email Subject Line: Blurred Expectations_Last Name&lt;br/&gt;A maximum of five works accepted. Please label each image with &lt;Lastname&gt;.&lt;Number&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please include an accompanying image list with the following information: Artist Name, Number that corresponds to jpeg entry number, Title, Media, Size, Value (must include value for insurance purposes even if the work is NFS)&lt;br/&gt;For video submissions, please link directly to online or downloadable content that does NOT require a login, password or membership to view. These may be in the form of Youtube, Vimeo, or personal websites. Links to video entries must remain valid and active through the notification of jury results.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;lycocampusartgallery@lycoming.edu&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/06cb88cf-3f8e-423f-a686-900f4c0832a9" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>39e9d925-7d85-4593-a11f-bba114fddb65</id><title>10/31 - Call To Digital/Video Artists For Public Artworks At Davidson College</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677318+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Davidson College&lt;br/&gt;📍 Davidson, NC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Digital/Electronic Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.davidsoncollegeartgalleries.org/uncategorized/announcing-call-to-digital-video-artists-for-exhibition/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARTISTS INVITED TO SUBMIT DIGITAL/VIDEO ARTWORK FOR EXHIBITION AT DAVIDSON COLLEGE&lt;br/&gt;The Van Every/Smith Galleries at Davidson College (Davidson, North Carolina) are pleased to announce a call to artists for submissions of digital and video art. The selected works will be presented in an exhibition beginning January 2020 on a large-format video wall in the atrium of the E. Craig Wall Jr. Academic Center, a hub for transdisciplinary learning on the campus of Davidson College. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists are invited to submit work that complements the spirit of cross-disciplinary collaboration, healthy debate, and creative investigation that is alive on the Davidson College campus. The submission deadline is October 31, 2019 at 11:59PM EST. Artists may submit up to three artworks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION DETAILS&lt;br/&gt;Work by professional artists will be selected for exhibition by a panel of Davidson College community members, including members of the Art Collection Advisory Committee, professors, staff, and students. Selected artworks will be screened in groups of 3-5 for 6 weeks each beginning in January 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE VIDEO WALL&lt;br/&gt;The Davidson College Art Galleries manage a large-scale video wall comprised of 16 screens (approximately 9 feet tall x 16 feet wide) at the E. Craig Wall Jr. Academic Center. The video wall primarily shows the work of professional artists, but, on particular days, visually engaging student and faculty projects are also screened. The space is also used for occasional presentations by guest lecturers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMIT YOUR WORK BY FILLING OUT THIS FORM: &lt;a href="https://form.jotform.com/92316056000140" target="_blank"&gt;https://form.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CONTACT FOR QUESTIONS: Elizabeth Harry, elharry@davidson.edu&lt;br/&gt;**Do not send submissions by email. Use the submission form linked above**&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/39e9d925-7d85-4593-a11f-bba114fddb65" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e7e6c5bf-9eec-4968-b98a-c483a04f4191</id><title>12/5 - 57th Annual Juried Competition</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677294+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Masur Museum of Art&lt;br/&gt;📍 Monroe, LA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/05/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.masurjuried.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Masur Museum of Art in Monroe, Louisiana invites contemporary artists working in any medium to enter the 57th Annual Juried Competition. Best in Show receives $1,000, and total awards are $3,200. Entry fee is $10/artwork (min 2/max 5 artworks). Online entry deadline: December 5, 2019 at 5pm CST. The exhibition will be on view in our historic building from February 27 – May 9, 2020 with an opening reception on February 28. This year, work will be judged by Allison Glenn, Associate Curator of Contemporary Art at the Crystal Bridges Museum of American Art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline is 5pm Central Time on December 5, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Visit www.masurjuried.org for complete rules and to enter!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please see www.masurjuried.org/rules for complete rules, eligibility, and entry instructions. Contact info@masurmuseum.org for call 318-329-2237 with questions or for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e7e6c5bf-9eec-4968-b98a-c483a04f4191" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cbd338ca-2fa0-4d33-9508-15a97769dec4</id><title>11/15 - One Week Residency in Nashville Tennessee in January 2020</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677270+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Barbershop Theater&lt;br/&gt;📍 Nashville, TN, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Performing Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://thebarbershoptheater.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Barbershop Theater is seeking performing artists of any genre to come to Nashville Tennessee for one week. We will give you a space to rehearse in, and one weekend of performances. We will help advertise the event, and you will keep 100% of the door. We are a very small 40 seat black box theater with Qlab, LED lights, and isolatable sound. Last year we hosted an arts collective who ran an installation, and two one-person shows that eventually went on to the Edinburgh Fringe Festival. All 3 were from New York. We unfortunately can not help with travel, but can possibly help with housing depending on your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please email us a description of your performance, an artist statement, and any media/web presence that you have.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cbd338ca-2fa0-4d33-9508-15a97769dec4" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>986a9acc-c4aa-43ef-b3fb-7c510b7a9f47</id><title>11/1 - CALL FOR SUBMISSIONS - The Contemporary Print Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677243+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;PrintAustin&lt;br/&gt;📍 Austin, TX, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Printmaking&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="printaustin.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PrintAustin is thrilled to announce the open call for its 7th annual juried international exhibition, The Contemporary Print. Presented in collaboration with Big Medium, this year’s exhibition will be juried by Claudia Zapata and be held at Big Medium gallery during PrintAustin 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Contemporary Print is a survey of traditional printmaking techniques and innovative approaches in contemporary printmaking. While non-traditional or digital output is accepted as a print element, submissions must utilize traditional print media as their primary technique. These include lithography, relief, intaglio, silkscreen, photo polymer plate (i.e. SolarPlates), and monotype.Solely digital and photographic prints are not eligible. For questions regarding eligible media, please contact admin@printaustin.org.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION DATES: January 17 – February 15, 2020&lt;br/&gt;OPENING RECEPTION: Friday, January 17, 7-10pm&lt;br/&gt;VENUE: Big Medium, 916 Springdale Road, Bldg 2 #101, Austin, Texas&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT PRINTAUSTIN&lt;br/&gt;PrintAustin is an artist-led nonprofit organization working with organizations and individuals throughout the Austin visual arts community to showcase traditional and contemporary approaches in printmaking during its annual festival, held January 15 through February 15.&lt;br/&gt;Visit www.printaustin.org to learn more about our open calls, and other exhibition and collaboration opportunities. You may also find us on Instagram, and Facebook.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT BIG MEDIUM&lt;br/&gt;Big Medium is a 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization dedicated to supporting and promoting contemporary art in Texas. Big Medium produces the East Austin Studio Tour, the West Austin Studio Tour, the Texas Biennial, and presents innovative exhibitions throughout the year in the Big Medium Gallery. Big Medium provides affordable studio space to artists, and partners with various organizations in Texas to help foster the arts and facilitate an inclusive cultural dialogue between artists and their communities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR&lt;br/&gt;Texas-born curator, artist, and doctoral candidate, Claudia Zapata, joins us from the Smithsonian American Art Museum, where she currently acts as the Latinx art curatorial assistant in support of their upcoming exhibition ¡Printing the Revolution! The Rise and Impact of Chicano Graphics, 1965-Now. Claudia's passion for Chicanx and Latinx art, and identity-based exhibitions has inspired her previous work as the Curator of Exhibitions and Programs at Mexic-Arte Museum, the Co-Founder of the Puro Chingón Collective, and now the pursuit of a Ph.D. in Rhetorics of Art, Space and Culture at Southern Methodist University.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AWARDS&lt;br/&gt;* The PrintAustin Award $500 cash       &lt;br/&gt;*The Blick Art Materials Award $150 Gift Certificate courtesy of Blick Art Materials&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;Open to local and international artists 18 years or older. Any 2-D or 3-D work including ceramics, sculpture, mixed media, and artist books that uses printmaking as the sole or primary technique in its execution are eligible. Work cannot exceed 72 inches (183 cm) in any direction. Works that have exhibited in past The Contemporary Print exhibitions are not eligible to be considered for this year’s exhibition. We appreciate your cooperation in helping us provide a fresh and current survey of printmaking today.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information and a complete list of guidelines, visit printaustin.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/986a9acc-c4aa-43ef-b3fb-7c510b7a9f47" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>51ab738d-ba74-4358-ba5a-e976c1431e50</id><title>11/22 - CURATORIAL APPLICATION NOW OPEN | SPRING/BREAK Art Show NYC + Los Angeles 2020</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677210+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SPRING/BREAK Art Show&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/22/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $100.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.springbreakartshow.com/2020-application/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SPRING/BREAK Art Show is now accepting submissions by curators until November 22, 2019, midnight (your time), for the upcoming 2020 exhibitions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2020 THEME | IN EXCESS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“The more the merrier.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;                          - Traditional&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The term ‘tipping point’ is used frequently in current affairs in regards to a variety of topics. Environmental extinction predominantly first and foremost, but also resumed economic stability, political divisiveness, information overloads, cancel culture mania, all are together thought to be at every manner of places along an axis of toppling the heck over, with varying ideas circulated as to which side of their scales are too overstuffed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art and entertainment feel indistinguishable from one another, piled together as “content”, which is consistently billed as in overwhelming supply from creators both amateur and professional; News peppers everyday moments through our devices’ push notifications and peer updates; tech-aided romantic possibilities appear infinite, as do all the other seductions of a globalized world—people to meet, people to follow, things to buy and eat and do. (Should one be able to afford it…For better or worse, then, the ‘too much’-ness of everything is certainly on the mind. In line with these grumblings of overmuch, SPRING/BREAK Art Show 2020 seeks similar inquiries into the paradoxes and nuances of ‘more’. For both upcoming New York and Los Angeles shows, IN EXCESS is actively searching for exhibitions dealing with virtues and/or limitations of maximalism, materialism, digression, hysterical realism, capitalism, encyclopedii, redundancy, consumerism, the over-foot-noted and the overlabored. Submissions may or may not include touchstones on multimedia, multiracial, or multiverse theories and perspectives; environmentalism, globalization, and future shock; the baroque, the Simulacrum, the epic, human play, the hall of mirrors, or any manner of other meditations on the Anthropocene and its anxieties; and, maybe—where we can find them—joys.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The pleasure of ‘more is more’ may be explored through the joyously overindulged overabundance of ideas, forms, perspectives. Aesthetically, ‘the bigger, brighter, busier, the better’ was once the zeitgeist with the intent to create, not a nauseous geegaw of consumer pleasures, but an impression that rattled complacency—generating, instead, awe, surprise, wonder; a sense of the infinitude of our World. Where is our awe now in all this excess? Where is the new Rocaille? Is it any good? Is it a spectre of Greed or Good? How much is not enough, and when is too little too soon?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;References in the current and former art landscape include, but are not limited to, Peter Saul’s rambunctious hypercolor paintings of interwoven political brutality, Joyce Kozloff’s reframing of “women’s work” in her P &amp; D movement pieces and their extension over into, and reframing by, artist Liz Collins, William Powhida’s art world cartography of complicit capitalism. Marco Brambilla crafts sprawling video pop cultural hells and heavens, packed with re-appropriated movie characters all fighting each other for a place in the pantheon, Mickalene Thomas constructs dizzying pastiche domiciles where tactile textiles, personal experience, and the figure from memory converge, authors like Thomas Pynchon and Zadie Smith jam-pack characters into stories teeming with a dance of detritus both intimate and historical; Stan Brakhage deploys the barrage for the sake of recalibrating our vision, Anselm Kiefer, with his fussy gigantic meditations, employs scale to save our soul. Robert Breer’s lightning speed animations stagger in their short running time pummel, Azikiwe Mohammed toils to find overstocked thrift store tapestries of Black utopias, and for Alison Zuckerman, art history, digital self-documentation, and Photoshop fiddling all find themselves locked, arm-in-arm, in triplicate.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Wilde suggested moderation in art and life was a fatal thing. But how does it support or subvert our consumptive excesses? Like Gittes once said to Mulwray, “how much better can you eat? What can you buy that you can’t already afford?”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;People, go for baroque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION GUIDELINES + CURATORIAL REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There are separate applications for the New York City and Los Angeles shows. Please note that curators may apply to both the New York City and Los Angeles shows and will need to submit separate applications for each show to be considered for either and/or both. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications will be accepted by independent curators, galleries and non-profit organizations during the application period between October 1 - November 22, 2019. The online application form will be available during those dates until November 22, 2019 at 11:59pm your time. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;No proposals nor applications will be accepted via email.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION FEE&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is a non-refundable application fee of $100.00 per application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our mission is to create an unique environment for showcasing independent curators by providing free exhibition space to each selected curator, and therefore, require an application fee to cover our administrative fees for processing the applications.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHO MAY APPLY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1) INDEPENDENT CURATORS: Independent Curators may submit an application for the 2020 SPRING/BREAK Art Show, including a curatorial proposal related to the theme of IN EXCESS, sample images of art work, a curatorial statement and additional information necessary to complete the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that artists may apply as an Independent Curator only if they are applying with a group show or a solo show of another artist's work. An artist may not apply with their own art work in a solo show, but must have a curator who applies on behalf of him/her/they.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is NO FEE for the exhibition space if you are selected as an independent curator.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2) GALLERIES + PROJECT SPACES + NON PROFIT ORGANIZATIONS: Applicants affiliated with a gallery or project space/non-profit organization may submit a curatorial proposal comprised of artists from the gallery's roster and this curatorial proposal will fall into our SPECIAL PROJECT section. If you have an affiliation with a gallery, project space or non-profit organization, please define your affiliation/title and include the full roster of artists in the application below for our reference.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Special Project section was initated in 2015 as a way to invite established, new and recently closed galleries to participate in the show. We encourage participants in the Special Project section to explore the theme in full and to go beyond what they typically would do in a traditional art fair environment. In 2019, there were 26 Special Projects as part of the program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each Special Project contributes a fee to participate, which helps to cover the production costs of the event.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information on applying at an Independent Curator, Gallery or a Non-Profit Organization, please visit our website for more details:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;http://www.springbreakartshow.com/2020-application/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED CURATORIAL APPLICATIONS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission of an application does not guarantee participation. We will review applications in December and notify selected curators by the beginning of January, if not before. If we have any questions about your proposal, we will contact the primary curator listed on the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each curatorial proposal will be given one (1) room/space for exhibiting artworks. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected curators will receive a consignment agreement to review and complete. All artworks included in the show must be included in and subject to the terms of the consignment agreement. Artworks that are not listed on the consignment agreement will not be permitted on the show premises. If you have any questions about the consignment terms, please contact us for details.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/51ab738d-ba74-4358-ba5a-e976c1431e50" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2ea35be1-32e0-48cd-b4ba-8168a5f24f40</id><title>10/26 - CALL FOR ENTRY - Skeleton Crawl Art Show</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677173+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Skeleton Crawl Art Show&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/26/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skeleton Crawl is an annual one day art experience in Brooklyn NY, showcasing emerging and established artists in 2D/3D works and performance centered around all things spooky. The event is an opportunity to bring artists together in a spirit of collaboration and creativity. It operates with a party/fair-like vibe while still being tasteful and experimental. Costume prize, Monster caricatures, Cash bar, &amp; a PhotoBooth are all elements that will be a part of this experience along with curated works on walls and a formal perfomance. Works in this show will be available for sale with 100% of the price going to the artist. This is an opprtunity to share work that normally doesn't get exposure and does not need to be cohesive with the other pieces submitted or the artist's regular style.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a juried show. All works chosen for the show need to be delivered by mail or in/person by November 1 in frames or hanging structure with hanging hardware already attached. If mailed, return shipping needs to be prepaid. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Theme: Spooky or Surreal&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Anna Russell - BFA in Photography (2008) / Printmaking &amp; Dance focus&lt;br/&gt;Deadline to submit: SATURDAY, OCTOBER 26 @ 11pm&lt;br/&gt;Show Date: Saturday, November 2 @8pm&lt;br/&gt;1-3 images or works&lt;br/&gt;No application fee&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;**All artists included in show who are local to NYC will have free entry to the event&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2ea35be1-32e0-48cd-b4ba-8168a5f24f40" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>025bb2a8-b126-47a7-87a7-af88d68df26c</id><title>10/24 - October 25th People&amp;#39;s Choice Open Call Salon Show- WIN 200$ and A SOLO SHOW</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677144+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/24/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our October 25th People's Choice Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, October 25th , 2019 from 8pm- 12am.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, October 24th, 2019 at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For this show, we let the people decide, which means everyone who attends votes for the winners! We pass out ballots at the door and guests who attends choose the winners! It is always one of our most well attended nights, boasting record art sales and a large community of fellow artists and art lovers!&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of local bands!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, Oct. 24th at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces already this past year. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com  Instagram: @ GreenpointGallery&lt;br/&gt;Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/greenpointgallery/events/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/025bb2a8-b126-47a7-87a7-af88d68df26c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>515ef61c-eba5-433d-8b74-9de5260f1a2d</id><title>12/2 - Call For Emerging Artists: Create! Magazine International Print Issue Winter 2020</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677116+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 PHILADELPHIA, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/02/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://createmagazine.com/callforart/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CREATE! MAGAZINE IS PLEASED TO ANNOUNCE AN OPEN CALL FOR THE WINTER 2020 EDITION. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists are welcome to submit work in any medium, style, or theme to issue #19, which will launch by February 2020 and will be available in international shop locations. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUEST CURATORS FOR ISSUE 19&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ALEXIS YUEN&lt;br/&gt;Art Advisor and Founder of The Art Diplomat&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MARIE-ODILE FALAIS&lt;br/&gt;Art Historian, Influencer, &amp; Gallery Manager&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT CREATE! MAGAZINE&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Create! Magazine is an independent contemporary arts magazine focused on highlighting the work of talented emerging and mid-career creatives from across the globe. We are pleased to announce our next call for artists for a custom designed two-page spread in our publication (both print &amp; digital) that will feature your artist biography, website, and two images of your artwork.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Have your work seen by our 125,000+ readers and followers around the world, including leading galleries, art fairs, collectors, curators, writers, art consultants, and more. Don’t miss this opportunity to put your work out there and connect with a new audience!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHERE TO FIND THE MAGAZINE: Print copies of Create! Magazine are available in our online shop and at several global retail locations in London, New York, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Amsterdam, Stockholm, Chicago, Ft. Lauderdale, Wilmington (DE), and more. Digital issues can always be purchased on our website. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTISTS: If your work is selected, you will receive a custom designed two-page spread in both the print and digital versions of the magazine that will include your artist biography, website, and two images. Published artists will be sent a complimentary digital issue and will be listed as a participating artist in your issue on both our website and social media. We also promote artists individually via blog and social media posts that reach over 125,000 total followers worldwide. All featured artists will automatically be considered for any upcoming curatorial projects, not limited to art fairs, exhibitions, and gallery projects organized by our team. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: December 2, 2019 (Midnight EST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: Artists 18 and older from the US and abroad, of all genders, ethnicities, and from all backgrounds are welcome to apply. We accept works in any medium: painting, sculpture, digital art, printmaking, fiber/textile art, photography, mixed media, installation, etc. A college degree is not required to participate in this open call. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS: 3+ jpeg images of different artworks, a text document with a bio and artist statement, website or social media link, and your email address. If your work is three-dimensional, you may include additional images of installation views or detailed shots at no extra cost. Please see our Submittable form for further details. Please note that for best results, artists should include works from the same series per each submission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION FEE: $35 for 3 images (non-refundable*)&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/515ef61c-eba5-433d-8b74-9de5260f1a2d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f1ddb754-7f6f-4243-82a6-487b019fee1f</id><title>10/31 - Holiday Art Fair &amp;amp; Postcard Fundraiser - Enter to Win a Solo Exhibition or Cash Prize</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677088+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LiC-A @ The Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 LIC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.licartists.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OFF THE WALL II - LiC-A's Second Annual Holiday Art Fair style Exhibition and Holiday Postcard Fundraiser&lt;br/&gt;For $40 Artists can submit 5 artworks for a chance receive their own space to hang a mini salon wall in our 12,000 sq ft gallery. Works can be replaced with new work once sold. OFF THE WALL will be on view form Nov 7, 2019 - Jan 12, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THE POSTCARD FUNDRAISER:&lt;br/&gt;Artists can submit 4" x 6" drawings, photographs, paintings, printmaking, and mixed media post cards on card stock or heavyweight paper. Artwork can be of any theme but Holiday themes are suggested.  Up to five works will be accepted (to increase your chance of winning the popular vote!) which can be in the form of a single, diptych, triptych, etc. There will be a $10.00 entry fee per postcard (help support Long Island City Artists (LiC-A!) A popular vote will be conducted throughout the run of the show, with the winner receiving a solo show at Plaxall Gallery and the runner up winning $200 cash. Winner to be announced by December 1st, 2019. Only original artwork will be accepted!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fee: $10.00 per work submitted (to help support our gallery programming!)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: October 30th, 2019 11:59 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Address: Plaxall Gallery, 5-25 46th Avenue, Long Island City, Queens - between Vernon and 5th Street. The entrance to the gallery space is on the parking lot (west) side of the building at the second loading bay.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please e-mail info@licartists.org with any questions.&lt;br/&gt;Note: Because all works are accepted, you do not need to submit photos of your work. Please have all your information on the back of each piece: your name, website or email, title of piece, medium, price.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Link for Holiday Postcard Fundraiser:&lt;br/&gt;https://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_lica_holiday_postcard_exhibition&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Link for OFF THE WALL II&lt;br/&gt;https://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_off_the_wall&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f1ddb754-7f6f-4243-82a6-487b019fee1f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>022df5f6-71df-46a4-8bb6-1454b5776064</id><title>11/3 - OpenCall Artist &amp;amp; Designers</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677046+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;PIS Global Culture&lt;br/&gt;📍 new york, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/03/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The memo is the abbreviation of the memorandum. It means to convey and record the most important information in the most concise way. Life is full of aesthetics, and artists use their unique ways to capture, transform, present, present and express the beauty of their own eyes. The Design Memo exhibition is designed to allow artists to discover the most distinctive aspects of their art and present their most iconic works of art most succinctly.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are Looking for the Next Big Design and Art Talents&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Exhibition with Pop-up Shop for one month from Nov 9th-Dec 1st, at SoHo, New York&lt;br/&gt;- Professional shopping guide to selling works and products.&lt;br/&gt;- Domestic and foreign buyers,designer gathering points, buying stores, brand business resources docking.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Solo Workshop during the exhibition (one section 1-1.5hours)&lt;br/&gt;- 100+ local press coverage &lt;br/&gt;- A free three-month membership to CADA&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; -Compete to Win "Most Promising Artist" and "Most Promising Designer"  Award from CADA&lt;br/&gt;- Winning talents will get podcast and Youtube interviews and much more&lt;br/&gt;- Winning talents will have the chance to participate NYFW in February 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-The opportunities to get to know professionals who can write you recommendation letters&lt;br/&gt;- The opportunity to get access to the Pop Up Store in the future&lt;br/&gt;- Participating artists are invited to attend the Award Launch Party and Award Party&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Innovative, complete and original artworks or design works.&lt;br/&gt;-Fashion design/accessory design/product design/installation works/sculpture/painting/ photography, etc. (at least five pieces in a set of complete work) &lt;br/&gt;- The exhibition is a series of works for each artist. Each artist can register up to three works. The size of non-fashion works cannot exceed 20" x20" (50cmx50cm).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The organizing committee will select 100 artists from all deliverers to participate in this exhibition of the most potential artists. Twenty artists will be selected to participate in this exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please send the following application materials to Events@nycpis.com&lt;br/&gt;Creator's profile: photo, resume, contact information (mail + phone), personal valid ID, a screenshot of the work materials (name, material, size, creation age) and work description, registration fee payment voucher to be displayed.&lt;br/&gt;The subject heading of the email should be marked: "XXX (name) Design Memo application&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application fee&lt;br/&gt;Submit ¥70 registration fee from the link (scan the QR code above). International artists can pay $10 registration fee from the quick pay channel:&lt;br/&gt;PIS Global Culture Inc&lt;br/&gt;Info@nycpis.com&lt;br/&gt;$200 participation fee will be paid after being selected&lt;br/&gt;(If two pieces/looks are selected for $400, three pieces/looks are selected for $600.&lt;br/&gt;Up to three works per person)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The application materials will be reviewed by the CADA organizer to make the final decision. The specific number of people and the number of works will be released by the official CADA platform. The finalists will receive emails to inform the next step. Places are on a first-come, first-served basis. If the organizing committee finishes the selection in advance, the open call will end early.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application deadline: October 31st, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Awards announced last date: November 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening:  November 9- December 1st&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/022df5f6-71df-46a4-8bb6-1454b5776064" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a583cf40-91c1-4f48-9232-53391240242e</id><title>11/8 - Vision: Color Photography</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.677011+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/08/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on color photography at Black Box Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a583cf40-91c1-4f48-9232-53391240242e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b79d570e-2a64-409b-ae16-ddaf79d26f0b</id><title>Call for Artists - Multiple Projects</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.676900+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;MTA Arts &amp;amp; Design&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://mtaarts.submittable.com/submit"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MTA Arts &amp; Design seeks images of artists’ previous work to review in consideration for four new permanent Percent for Art projects to be fabricated in durable materials. An approved fabricator will be translating the final artwork design into the identified medium, therefore an artist’s prior experience, or lack thereof, with these materials will not be taken into consideration when reviewing images. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The budget for design and fabrication of the artwork for the station is to be determined, and will include an artist fee. As part of this fee, the selected artist will be required to submit a budget, produce final designs, select a fabricator and oversee the fabrication and installation of the artwork, with project management by MTA Arts &amp; Design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit up to 20 images at mtaarts.submittable.com along with a short application form, a bio, CV, and brief artist statement. All artists interested in being considered for projects must apply through the online program at mtaarts.submittable.com. Please direct inquiries for MTA Arts &amp; Design to arts@mtahq.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b79d570e-2a64-409b-ae16-ddaf79d26f0b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cad2f9a6-7f7f-4980-bb41-515afb06e722</id><title>12/20 - Open Call for Artists - &amp;quot;The Blues&amp;quot;</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.676872+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Painting Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.thepaintingcenter.org/juried-exhibitions"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Blues&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Curated by Lisa Pressman and Kathy Cantwell&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Blue is a primary color which lies between violet and green on the spectrum of light. “The Blues” can describe a state of mind. Feeling blue can refer to being melancholic and depressed. Conversely, blue is known to calm the mind and body. The color blue can slow human metabolism and can produce a meditative effect. In nature, blue is reflected in the sky, water, earth, and fire. It is associated with open spaces, intuition, imagination and inspiration.“The Blues describes music; such as rhythm and blues, bluegrass and jazz.  Blue is associated with ideology like the democrats and blue states. “Blue has no dimension, it is beyond dimensions.” - Yves Klein&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Painting Center in Chelsea is interested in work in all media (under 36” in any direction) featuring blue and its various shades for this juried exhibition. The exhibition will be highly publicized with a catalogue of artists works.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: January 28 – February 22, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: December 20, 2019 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notification Date: December 30, 2019 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork Shipping/Delivery Dates: January 21 – 25, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Thursday, January 30, 2020 from 6 - 8 pm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://thepaintingcenter.slideroom.com/#/login/program/51583" target="_blank"&gt;https://thepaintingcenter.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Fee: $40 for 1 to 5 images.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Size Limitation: Artwork that exceeds 36" in any dimension will not be considered.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Image Requirements: JPEGs must be 72 dpi. They should be at least 1600 pixels in any direction. Maximum file size for any individual image is 5 MB.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cad2f9a6-7f7f-4980-bb41-515afb06e722" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>768c3237-2ab3-47c5-bd70-b2968e9c8efc</id><title>11/10 - ELEMENTS 2020 Call for Artists</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.676843+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Mural Brigade&lt;br/&gt;📍 Fairfax, VA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Interdisciplinary/Hybrid&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://muralsatmason.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Mural Brigade is embarking on our next project exploring the dynamic relationships between art, humanity, and the ELEMENTS: EARTH, WATER, FIRE, AIR. This open theme invites meaningful creative interpretations of contemporary society and our relationship with the environment from a variety of perspectives. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The three focus areas of ELEMENTS are:&lt;br/&gt;1. Location-specific environmental issues, such as the California Wildfires or the Flint Water Crisis&lt;br/&gt;2. Creative, sustainable infrastructure such as an innovative way to divert/reuse campus plastic waste, alternative power, a way to reuse storm/gray water, or a plant-material mural to clean the air, that will lessen the eco-footprint of the campus&lt;br/&gt;3. Art that promotes environmental consciousness from lenses such as consumption, commoditization of natural resources, intersectionality and human rights( Ex. EcoFeminism, Environmental Racism), and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Links to apply:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Student Artists: &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/frJyrFyq4krgonRh6" target="_blank"&gt;https://forms.gle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Professional Artists: &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/AyQEUcSGkxLM2kgh7" target="_blank"&gt;https://forms.gle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/768c3237-2ab3-47c5-bd70-b2968e9c8efc" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e46970dd-aed0-44ab-b041-0a07ab807b9e</id><title>11/6 - Ink, Press, Repeat: National Juried Printmaking and Book Art Exhibition</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.676808+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;William Paterson University Galleries&lt;br/&gt;📍 WAYNE, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Printmaking&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.wpunj.edu/coac/gallery"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL FOR ENTRIES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ink, Press, Repeat: National Juried Printmaking and Book Art Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Ruth Lingen&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates:&lt;br/&gt;January 27 – March 27, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submissions Deadline:&lt;br/&gt;Wednesday, November 6, 2019 (11:59 p.m. EST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE COMPETITION&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Since 2001, the University Galleries at William Paterson University has organized a juried printmaking exhibition featuring traditional and digital print media and book art. One artist will be selected to have a future solo exhibition at the University Galleries. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ruth Lingen lives and works in New York City, where she has established a distinguished twenty-five year career as a master printer and book artist. Lingen has collaborated with over 70 celebrated artists and writers, including Jim Dine, Kiki Smith, Leonardo Drew, Shepard Fairey, Robert Ryman, Mary Heilmann, Jessica Stockholder, Jane Hammond, Claes Oldenburg, Robert Creeley and Matthew Day Jackson. She was the founding director of Pace Paper (a Brooklyn papermaking facility for Pace Prints) from 2008 through 2018, and continues to consult on special projects for Pace Prints, as well as direct Line Press Limited, a workshop in Brooklyn devoted to artist books and small-scale print editions. She has received lifetime achievement awards in both papermaking and the book arts. Her personal practice is based in language, sometimes combined with a historical twist, and employs hand-set type and letterpress, often combined with lithography and handmade paper. Her work can be found in the collections of the Metropolitan Museum of Art, The Getty, the Brooklyn Museum, the Walker Museum, as well as over 35 libraries, including the New York Public Library and the Harvard University Library.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;TIMELINE&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submissions Deadline:&lt;br/&gt;Wednesday, November 6, 2019 (11:59 p.m. EST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notification:&lt;br/&gt;Thursday, November 21, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Receipt of Work Deadline:&lt;br/&gt;Wednesday, December 11, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;Open to all artists residing in the United States. Works must have been completed within the past two years (2018 - 2019) and may not exceed 60 inches. Work previously shown at the William Paterson University Galleries will not be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTWORK REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;All accepted work requires proper framing and should be ready to be hung (except for book art which will be displayed on pedestals or shelves). The Juror reserves the right to reject any work found to be unacceptable upon arrival.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SALES&lt;br/&gt;The University retains a 20% commission for all artwork sales.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY&lt;br/&gt;All work shown at the gallery will be insured for the duration of the exhibition. The gallery cannot insure works in transit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;The cost of shipping or hand-delivering works to and from the gallery is the responsibility of the artist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSION PROCESS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please submit your digital application through the “Apply Now” link below. Artists may submit up to 3 artworks for consideration. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMAGES&lt;br/&gt;Please upload no more than 3 images total. (You may submit multiple images for a single work if you are not submitting 3 separate artworks.) Each image file should not exceed 4MB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please label your image files in the following format: “LastName_TitleofWork” (If you include a detail or alternate view as one of your images, you may label it “LastName_TitleofWork_detail” or “LastName_TitleofWork_2”. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMAGE LIST&lt;br/&gt;Please upload an image list with thumbnails of each artwork and specs all on the same document. Do NOT include your name on this document. Please include for each artwork: Title of Artwork, Year, Medium, and Dimensions (framed and unframed, if applicable).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTIST STATEMENT and CV/RESUME&lt;br/&gt;Artists may also upload an artist statement and CV as separate documents. Please DO NOT include your name on the artist statement. You may include your name on your curriculum vitae. Please follow the same file format: “LastName_Statement” and “LastName_CV”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note: This is a blind jury. File names will be adjusted accordingly. The juror will be able to view your images, image list, and artist statement, but not your CV. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contact:  Gallery Manager Emily Johnsen, johnsene@wpunj.edu or (973)720-2654&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e46970dd-aed0-44ab-b041-0a07ab807b9e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c04b7147-748a-451d-aaa0-b0cfcc439bdd</id><title>12/19 - 2020 Socrates Sculpture Park Annual Emerging Artist Fellowship</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.676769+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Socrates Sculpture Park&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://socratessculpturepark.submittable.com/submit/148680/2020-socrates-annual-fellowship-application"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;‘Call and Response: Making Monuments Now’&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In light of recent debates about monuments and some recent removals, Socrates asks artists to propose prototypes for new monuments for New York City for presentation beginning in the fall of 2020. Artists are invited to consider and respond to the following considerations and questions:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As symbols of Confederate and Colonial power are currently being destroyed, dismantled, reconfigured, or exiled from public view, what new representations should fill their void? What monuments should be created to reflect today’s values and our desire to project those into the future? Who or what should be given the space, representation, and honor in these new monumental artworks? More specifically, as the reconfiguration of monuments in public space reflects the process of history writing, what histories of New York should be remembered or recovered?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What kind of monument might shape public consciousness in the creation of civic agents empowered with social and political self-determination? What kind of monument might best to serve and preserve the reclamation of New York’s under-recognized or repressed histories? How might monument-makers resist the obdurate, authoritarian chauvinist impulses that commonly accompany traditional representational strategies of monuments?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This open call will be the major component of Socrates Sculpture Park’s year-long engagement with recent discourse on the current state and future of monuments in the United States. It is a thematic adaption of ‘The Socrates Annual Fellowship’ and exhibition, and incorporates an extended selection process and production timeline as well as inclusion in an exhibition publication.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;These monument prototypes for New York City will be presented alongside three new commissions for speculative monuments for America by major artists, and a collective monument for Queens created by participants in the Park’s after-school program for teenagers: Socrateens.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fellowship recipients will receive a $5,000 production grant to support their project a $1,000 honorarium and four-months of seven-days-a-week access to the resources and fabrication facilities of the Park’s outdoor artist studio.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist Fellows are responsible for the fabrication, transportation (if necessary) and installation of their works. Socrates will provide limited technical and installation assistance during a three-week installation period, M-F, 10AM – 6PM. Specifics of installation assistance will be discussed with each artist selected.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SITE &amp; CONTEXT&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Before preparing their applications, artists are strongly encouraged to visit Socrates – a unique New York City public park located on the East River waterfront in an industrial area of Long Island City, Queens – and to explore Socrates’ website and exhibition archive to learn about the history and context of the organization. Visiting the Park will give applicants a better sense of the factors that effect installations in the Park and help impart insights into the available facilities – from the tools and equipment in Socrates’ artist studio to the resources of the surrounding neighborhood.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;REVIEW PROCESS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;‘The Socrates Annual Fellowship program’ is based on a competitive, open application process. Completed on-line applications must be submitted by the deadline (Monday, November 25, 2019 by 11:59pm) and will be reviewed by the Socrates exhibition department and outside curatorial advisors. Ten to twelve artists will be selected for the 2020 program. Artists are selected based on the compelling nature of the project proposed, clarity of intent, unique approach to the site, and public context.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Following the recommendations of the curatorial advisors, Socrates staff will contact applicants individually to discuss proposed projects before confirming the final selection in early 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FELLOWSHIP&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Once accepted, Socrates staff members will meet with each Artist Fellow to discuss project proposals in detail and begin to assist with the development, engineering, and installation of the work. A group meeting for all Artist Fellows and Socrates staff will take place one evening in late winter of 2020, followed by an on-site orientation and individual progress meetings throughout the Fellowship to assess progress, troubleshoot issues, and review next steps. Selected works are subject to final approval by Socrates staff and must meet safety requirements to be able to withstand the effects of weather and public use.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fellowships are awarded to artists whose careers and artistic practices would benefit from the opportunity. Artists who are enrolled in a school, college, or university at the time of application are NOT eligible for ‘The Socrates Annual Fellowship’ program. Artists who have applied before, but never shown at Socrates, are eligible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Information Session:  Tuesday, October 22, 2019 (Time &amp; Location TBD)&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: Monday, November 25, 2019 by 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;Notification: January 2020&lt;br/&gt;Fellowship: April 2020 – September 2020&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition: October 2020 – March 2021&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Socrates Sculpture Park has been a model of public art production, community activism, and socially inspired place-making for more than 30 years. Known for fostering ambitious and visionary artworks, Socrates has presented more than 1,200 artists on its five waterfront acres, providing them the financial support, materials, equipment, and space necessary to create large-scale works in the public realm. Open 365 days a year from 9am till dusk, the Park is a center of cultural programming – as a producer of contemporary sculpture exhibitions, a presenter of a multi-disciplinary performances, an arts educator, and a venue for healthy outdoor activities  – all offered completely free of charge to the public. The Park’s existence is based on the belief that reclamation, revitalization and creative expression are essential to the survival, humanity and improvement of our urban environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We only accept proposals submitted through our online portal provided above. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT DATES&lt;br/&gt;Information Session:  Tuesday, October 22, 2019 Monday October 21, 6:30-7:30 PM&lt;br/&gt;Triangle Arts Association&lt;br/&gt;20 Jay Street, Suite 317/318, Brooklyn, NY&lt;br/&gt;RSVP to curatorial@socratessculpturepark.org by Oct 18&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: Monday, November 25, 2019 by 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;Notification: January 2020&lt;br/&gt;Fellowship: April 2020 – September 2020&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition: October 2020 – March 2021&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DOCS TO DOWNLOAD:&lt;br/&gt;1. Application Instructions&lt;br/&gt;2. FAQs&lt;br/&gt;2. Equipment List&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c04b7147-748a-451d-aaa0-b0cfcc439bdd" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>34af0358-8ac2-4e73-9a08-dad10f5b41fb</id><title>10/25 - OPEN CALL FOR ARTISTS - AUTUMN IN NY ART FAIR</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.676733+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;INTERNATIONAL ART FESTIVAL&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 10/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.newartfestival.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call for Artists&lt;br/&gt;IAF Exhibition &amp; Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;23 Warren Street, Tribeca, New York City&lt;br/&gt;November 7-10, 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Register at our website:  &lt;a href="http://newartfestival.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://newartfestival.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Upload several images representative of your work and add your artist statement.&lt;br/&gt;Pay the $10 Application Fee to submit your application&lt;br/&gt;This fee will be credited towards the participation fee, upon application approval.&lt;br/&gt;We will review your work and will be in touch very soon.&lt;br/&gt;(Check the email with which you register at &lt;a href="http://newartfestival.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://newartfestival.com&lt;/a&gt; website).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Participation at the IAF exhibit is subject to approval by the IAF Curators and the receipt of the full payment. If you are approved for participation, you need to prepay for the exhibition wall space that you require.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For complete information please follow this link: &lt;br/&gt;http://newartfestival.com/page/termsconditions2019.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/34af0358-8ac2-4e73-9a08-dad10f5b41fb" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>20c8db5f-c6a5-4aae-a81d-4eb951dd9b8d</id><title>11/6 - New Prints 2020/Winter Exhibition Open Call</title><updated>2019-11-02T13:27:38.676673+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;International Print Center New York&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Printmaking&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://ipcny.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Prints 2020/Winter will be the 61st presentation of IPCNY's New Prints Program. Established in 2000, the New Prints Program is a biannual, juried open call for prints and print-based work created in the preceding twelve months. Artists selected for the exhibition will also be invited to apply for IPCNY's New Prints Artist Development Program consisting of three opportunities: an artist residency, artist mentorship program, and sponsored coursework.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juried by Ariana Barat, artist, activist, and Printmaking Facilities Manager at Parsons School of Design; Gregory Burnet, artist, Master Printer, and Owner of Burnet Editions, New York; Orit Mardkha-Tenzer, artist, graphic designer, and instructor of graphic design at City College of New York; and Keris Salmon, visual artist and storyteller.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply online today at ipcny.submittable.com. We encourage you to apply as early as possible. The deadline is 11:59PM EST on Wednesday, November 6, 2019. Applications received after the deadline will not be accepted. There is no fee to apply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION GUIDELINES&lt;br/&gt;– Artists who have exhibited in New Prints within the past 2 years (New Prints 2018/Winter, 2018/Summer, 2019/Winter, and 2019/Summer) may NOT submit their work for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;– Editioned prints, unique printed works, printed installations, artist’s books, print-based animations, and ephemeral formats are eligible.&lt;br/&gt;– Photography or direct reproductions of other artworks, such as drawings or paintings, are NOT eligible.&lt;br/&gt;– Prints must have been completed within 12 months of the beginning of the open call. (Works created before September of 2018 are NOT eligible.)&lt;br/&gt;– Open internationally, no nationality requirements.&lt;br/&gt;– Artists may submit up to 3 works. Publishers and presses may submit up to 3 artists, with 3 works per artist.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;IMAGE REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;– Images should be in jpeg format, 72 dpi with longest dimension a maximum of 1,000 pixels. &lt;br/&gt;– Animations may be submitted as MP4, MOV, or FLV files. &lt;br/&gt;– Each file should be named as follows: artist's last name_first name_entry number. (For example: smith_john_01.jpg, smith_john_02.jpg, etc.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit your work at ipcny.submittable.com.&lt;br/&gt;For any questions, contact megan@ipcny.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/20c8db5f-c6a5-4aae-a81d-4eb951dd9b8d" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>