<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-03T14:16:24-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>f8c567f8-64a1-47ce-865b-55d06d015165</id><title>5/31 - Create! Magazine Call For Art: Summer 2019 Print Edition</title><updated>2019-05-03T14:16:24.609460+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.createmagazine.com/callforart"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine is an independent contemporary arts magazine focused on highlighting the work of talented emerging and mid-career creatives from across the globe. We are pleased to announce our next call for artists for a custom designed two-page spread in our publication (both print &amp; digital) that will feature your artist biography, website, and two images of your artwork. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Have your work seen by our 125,000+ readers and followers around the world, including leading galleries, art fairs, collectors, curators, writers, art consultants, and more. Don’t miss this opportunity to put your work out there and connect with a new audience! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE CURATOR: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Nina Blumberg, Art Consultant | Samuels Creative&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Nina Blumberg is a full-time art consultant at the New York City-based firm Samuels Creative. Outside of work, she fills her time with freelance social media contemporary art clientele and projects, most recently engaging with the art technology space. Nina received her BA in Art History from the University of Virginia and her MA from FIT’s “Art Market: Principles &amp; Practices” program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Nina is also the founder of @Artstagram__,the contemporary art world Instagram account that covers art happenings and exhibitions in NYC and beyond. She enjoys engaging with art on a constant basis in both a personal and professional capacity. She can also be counted on to (overshare) life updates with original content and dad jokes on various social media platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY: All artists 18+ from both the US and abroad, of all genders, ethnicities, and from all backgrounds are welcome to apply. We accept works in any medium: painting, sculpture, digital art, printmaking, fiber/textile art, photography, mixed media, installation, etc. A university degree is not required to participate in our open call. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS: 3+ jpeg images, a text document with a bio and artist statement, website or social media link, and your email address. Please see our Submittable form for further details. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTISTS: If your work is selected by our guest juror, you will receive a custom designed two-page spread in both the print and digital versions of the magazine that will include your artist biography, website, and two images. Published artists will be sent a complimentary digital issue and will be listed as a participating artist in your issue on both our website and social media. We also promote artists individually via blog and social media posts that reach over 125,000 total followers worldwide. All featured artists will automatically be considered for any upcoming curatorial projects, not limited to art fairs, exhibitions, and gallery projects organized by our team. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHERE TO FIND: Print copies of Create! Magazine are available in our online shop and at several global retail locations in London, New York, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Amsterdam, Stockholm, Chicago, Ft. Lauderdale, Wilmington (DE), and more. Digital issues can always be purchased on our website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f8c567f8-64a1-47ce-865b-55d06d015165" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>