<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-03T06:17:47-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>7aa676ed-63fc-4d25-ad11-caa784b00ff0</id><title>7/15 - OPEN CALL! Stigma Unbound; Sex workers&amp;#39; art collective</title><updated>2019-07-03T06:17:47.076125+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Stigma Unbound&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.stigmaunbound.org/opencall"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stigma Unbound is looking for visual artists for our upcoming Brooklyn exhibition! Accepting all mediums! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Stigma Unbound, created in Dec 2017, is a sex workers' art collective based in Brooklyn, New York. Our mission is to provide platform, resources, and a safe communal space for the artistic expression of sex workers. At our events, sex workers lead discussions about issues important to the community and educate the public. Our collective includes artists who are people of color, queer, trans, and gender non-conforming, kink, and allies. We include “sex workers and allies” as a strategy to build a wider community, provide protection by allies, and to give artist deniability of status. Our greater mission is to help strengthen the sex worker community in New York City and educated the public about sex work. &lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;FOSTA/SESTA stands for Fight Online Sex Trafficking Act and Stop Enabling Sex Trafficking Act. Signed by President Trump on April 11, 2018, the bills are intended to hold online platforms accountable for the content of their creators and eliminate online sex trafficking. However, the bills became a suppressor to consenting and nonconsenting sex workers and police all social media users at large. This bill makes it difficult for sex workers to conduct business, take part in community activities, and share mutual aid, in online spaces. In this environment, Stigma Unbound felt that creating a safe space for the creative expression of sex workers was crucial.  &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Stigma Unbound has curated shows in various underground dungeons in Brooklyn, Anthology Film Archive, and Museum of Sex.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Note: Being exhibited at our events will NOT divulge your sex worker status. We accept artists in a wide variety of communities as an attempt to provide protection by allies and allow intersectional individuals deniability of status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To Apply &lt;br/&gt;fill out a forum at www.stigmaunbound.org/opencall and send to stigmaunboung@gmail.com with subject title OPEN CALL&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7aa676ed-63fc-4d25-ad11-caa784b00ff0" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>