<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-20T11:16:04-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>6e241b4c-96f3-4721-9e5b-5f5387f7ef4f</id><title>5/12 - Announcing our Open Calls for a Cause this Spring!</title><updated>2019-04-20T11:16:04.299480+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ground Floor Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 BROOKLYN, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/12/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://groundfloorbk.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ground Floor Gallery is pleased to announce two open call opportunities for local, New York City-based artists (don't worry out-of-state talents! You'll get an opportunity to submit this summer). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1) An Open Call for Earth Day: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In honor of Earth Day and all things repurposed, we are pleased to announce artist Angelica Bergamini’s solo exhibition, “From the City to the Cosmos” which kicks off at the gallery on Earth Day - April 22nd!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Save the Date for the Artist Reception: Friday, May 10th, 6-9pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists based in New York City: we want all of your unwanted paper materials/discards for the show! Angelica will create collaborative paper sculptures from your donated paper scraps during the run of the exhibition. She will accept all forms of used, neglected or undesired paper: anything from your sketches and proofs to notes and failed drawings/paintings or any other paper product that you consider "garbage."&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We're accepting your paper donations from April 25th - 28th, 2019! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2) Our Spring Pop-up Exhibition "Heirloom": &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ground Floor Gallery is pleased to announce our spring open call for “Heirloom,”  a pop-up show in honor of the season and the significance of family! As defined by Merriam-Webster Dictionary, an heirloom is: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1: a piece of property (such as a deed or charter) that descends to the heir as an inseparable part of an inheritance of real property&lt;br/&gt;2: something of special value handed down from one generation to another&lt;br/&gt;3: a variety of plant that has originated under cultivation and that has survived for several generations usually due to the efforts of private individuals.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In true Ground Floor Gallery fashion, “Heirloom” is an extension of our mission to connect emerging artists to new art buyers while - in our small way - supporting a cause we deem urgent. Each original artwork will be sold for $220; all sales will be accompanied by a certificate of authenticity; and, in honor of election year and the prospect of new beginnings - $20.20 from each sale will benefit RAICES: (The Refugee and Immigrant Center for Education and Legal Services) in their continued efforts to reunite immigrant families separated at the border. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: Sunday, May 12th, 2019, 11:59am&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SAVE THE DATE for the Opening Reception: Friday, May 17, 2019, 5-9pm &lt;br/&gt;“Heirloom” will remain on view through Monday, May 20th, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Two years ago, you all helped us raise over $1,000 for the Committee to Protect Journalists and we’re hoping your passion and sense of urgency to address this most pressing of issues resonates as strongly! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We will accept all submissions by up to 75 New York City-based artists in response to this theme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No phone calls. Submission Details on our Website: &lt;a href="http://groundfloorbk.com/news/1/" target="_blank"&gt;http://groundfloorbk.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Looking forward!&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6e241b4c-96f3-4721-9e5b-5f5387f7ef4f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9c8fdb9e-b398-49df-bcce-de2c0252a91b</id><title>5/4 - COME OUT: Celebrating 50 Years of Queerness in NYC</title><updated>2019-04-20T11:16:04.299442+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;One Art Space&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/04/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.oneartspace.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;June 28, 1969: The Stonewall Riots took place, a defining moment in queer history in NYC. This June join One Art Space and Project Reach in celebrating the 50th anniversary of Pride with a group show featuring 25 queer artists. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About One Art Space: &lt;br/&gt;Based in Tribeca, One Art Space provides local, international and contemporary artists a wide range of artistic expression to a targeted audience. Our Mission is to create a cultural event hub for the Tribeca community. Since 2011 our location has been fortunate to host talent from a wide range of contemporary art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Project Reach: &lt;br/&gt;Since 1971, Project Reach is a nonprofit that has created opportunities for youth - and adults who work with them - to incubate new approaches and strategies and to build institutions that address discrimination and injustice and place social control in their own hands. Organizing readiness, youth organizing, and community empowerment are the products of these opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please submit 3 jpeg images to submissions@oneartspace.com with the subject line COME OUT. &lt;br/&gt;Please submit the $35 application fee to paypal.me/oneartspace/35&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9c8fdb9e-b398-49df-bcce-de2c0252a91b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>5793f8eb-c796-41c1-9505-362f90a81597</id><title>4/29 - OPEN CALL: Artig Gallery Talent Development Program Exhibition</title><updated>2019-04-20T11:16:04.299379+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SHIM Art Network&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/29/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.shimartnetwork.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEN CALL FOR SUBMISSIONS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artig Gallery (www.artiggallery.com), the online gallery for emerging art based in Barcelona, Spain, and Berlin, Germany, is pleased to announce an open call for artists to join our new Talent Development Program as inaugural members, in partnership with SHIM Art Network!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In order to expand our presence in the US and work more closely with US based artists, Artig Gallery will be exhibiting a curated selection of works by a select group of artists chosen through our open call. This exhibition will take place at ODETTA Gallery in Bushwick, Brooklyn, a global hub of emerging art (www.odettagallery.com). The dates of this exhibition will be May 17th to June 2nd, with regular gallery hours on Fridays, Saturdays, and Sundays. Additionally, SHIM Art Network will host a digital exhibition via Artsy.net for the duration of the exhibition and extending for a 60-day period.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At the conclusion of the fair, the artists selected will be additionally considered for membership in our permanent Artig Gallery Talent Development Program, which will include professional development resources and an artist profile in the top digital sales platforms, Artsy and 1stdibs.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Full details about this unique opportunity to become a part of an international art project are below, and we welcome your application if you are interested in participating.&lt;br/&gt;____&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIM and Artig will administer an online open call application process for artists to submit their work for inclusion in the exhibition, according to the following terms and restrictions. Our curators will select up to 20 artists to participate in the exhibition, and SHIM Art Network and Artig agree to exhibit two artworks per accepted artist, to be curated by our teams.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;Membership in the Artig Gallery Professional Development Exhibitor Group is open to painters, photographers, illustrators, and sculptors under the age of 40 with a demonstrated level of skill and commitment to furthering their career as a professional artist, as demonstrated in their portfolio and CV. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In preparation of your application, we encourage you to visit artiggallery.com and determine if your work adheres in style and quality to the artists we currently represent. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Costs:&lt;br/&gt;Application Fee: $20&lt;br/&gt;To apply, please visit www.shhhim.com/artig to learn more and click the APPLY NOW button, which will direct you to the SHIM Artist Application for Exhibitor Groups. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIM Exhibitor Fee: $250&lt;br/&gt;If accepted to the exhibition, a one-time exhibitor fee will be applied for participation that includes the gallery space, representation by a salesperson, installation, and promotion via Artig and SHIM Art Network. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Optional Exhibitor Group Membership:&lt;br/&gt;After the conclusion of the exhibition, participating artists selected by Artig interested in collaborating with Artig Gallery, may be invited to join Artig Gallery’s Talent Development Program, with regular review periods for full representation with the gallery, basic access to Artsy and 1stdibs, and additional exhibition opportunities offered through SHIM.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Size Limits and Presentation:&lt;br/&gt;For our membership showcase presentation at ODETTA, accepted artworks will be limited to 2D works on paper or canvas, or wall-mounted works with shallow depths less than 1.5 inches, with a maximum height or width of 18 inches. These works will be presented together in a bold gridded frame presentation for exhibition visitors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Artist agrees to provide two artworks mounted or matted on a mat board or other rigid backing material with precise outside dimensions of 19.75 inches x 19.75 inches (50cm x 50cm), ready to be inserted into standard sized frames that SHIM will provide. Failure to deliver works ready for display according to these specifications may result in additional fees or exclusion from the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIM agrees to provide framing and installation for one of each artists’ two artworks, and presentation for the second artwork in a flat-file display in the booth accessible to exhibition visitors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shipping:&lt;br/&gt;The Artist agrees to provide SHIM and Artig two artworks to be exhibited, with all shipping and delivery costs to the gallery at the Artist’s expense. Receipt of artworks to be exhibited shall be arranged between the Artist and SHIM and Artig and will occur no later than May 10th, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Returns: &lt;br/&gt;The Artist agrees that return delivery of any unsold artworks after the conclusion of the exhibition will also be at the Artist’s expense. If not agreed otherwise, shipping will be done by a member of SHIM and artist will be charged the shipping fees. &lt;br/&gt;Artists may have the option to leave artworks in SHIM’s custody for a period of time to become eligible for future exhibitions, which will be agreed on between SHIM and the artist individually. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Artist agrees that neither SHIM nor Artig shall be responsible for any incidental damage to the artworks during shipment or while in SHIM’s or Artig's custody. SHIM agrees to provide shipping, handling, and installation services at a professional standard. The Artist agrees and acknowledges that any insurance coverage for the artworks during shipment or while in SHIM’s or Artig's custody will be the sole responsibility of the Artist.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Installation and Promotion:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIM and Artig agrees to provide digital and analog promotion for the Exhibitor Group in advance of the exhibition and continuing for 60-days after the conclusion of the exhibition , including a dedicated exhibition listing on SHIM's Artsy.net platform. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Artist, Artig, and SHIM mutually agree to cross-promote each other during the fair presentation via each other’s respective digital platforms (websites, social media, email marketing, etc) via standard info and copy to be drafted and provided by SHIM and Artig. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sales:&lt;br/&gt;SHIM agrees to process any and all sales during the exhibition on Artig’s and the Artist’s behalf, sold at prices to be agreed upon in advance between SHIM, Artig, and the Artist and according to SHIM's standard Terms of Service for Exhibitor Group Member Artists. SHIM agrees to compensate the Artist 90% of the final sale price of any sold artworks within 45 days of the conclusion of the sale. SHIM agrees to compensate Artig a sales commission of 10% of the final sale price of any sold artworks within 45 days of the conclusion of the sale vía Paypal or direct bank transfer&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline to Apply:&lt;br/&gt;Applications to be considered for the exhibition are due no later than end of day on April 29th, 2019. Applications received after April 29th will be considered for future Artig TDP enrollment periods. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We look forward to reviewing your submissions and we welcome any questions you may have to Juliana Sorondo at Artig (juliana@artiggallery.com ) or Wilson Duggan at SHIM (info.shhhim@gmail.com).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TO APPLY: Please visit www.shhhim.com/artig and follow the APPLY NOW Link, or visit SHIM's Artist Aplpicaton Page directly at &lt;a href="https://shhhim.wufoo.com/forms/shim-artist-application" target="_blank"&gt;https://shhhim.wufoo.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Select the Artig TDP in the menu, provide your contact and professional info and a selection of sample artworks, and submit your non-refundable application fee. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions or concerns may be directed to Wilson Duggan, SHIM Managing Director, at info.shhhim@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5793f8eb-c796-41c1-9505-362f90a81597" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>