<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-16T02:18:04-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>4acb97dc-9129-413d-9feb-ae49b921bc51</id><title>8/5 - open call - &amp;quot;Slow Art&amp;quot; group show at Village West Gallery in Jersey City</title><updated>2019-07-16T02:18:04.205228+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Village West Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Jersey City, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/05/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.villagewestgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scroll, swipe, move on - art and imagery today is too often fast and forgettable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The "Slow Art" group show will celebrate work that is thoughtful, rigorous and patient.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It's not just about complexity or tiny brush strokes - Slow Art can also be works of restraint and simplicity, the result of years of consideration, study and practice.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are pleased to have Diana Schmertz as our guest curator for "Slow Art."&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All forms of visual art will be considered - and, as always, Village West Gallery takes NO fees or commissions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The deadline to apply is midnight on August 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;The Slow Art group show will run from October 3-December 8, 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists must fill out this google form: &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/UKtjLXWkAfbA1uHv5" target="_blank"&gt;https://forms.gle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you do not have a google account, please fill out this form: &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/cSGnj9Bz3yQW4NRb9" target="_blank"&gt;https://forms.gle&lt;/a&gt; and email images to curator@villagewestgallery.com &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Here are artist FAQs: &lt;a href="http://www.villagewestgallery.com/artistfaq.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.villagewestgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4acb97dc-9129-413d-9feb-ae49b921bc51" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1da9e6f0-3b98-44e2-add5-ae464e86faa4</id><title>8/30 - Art in Times of Anxiety: 10th Annual International Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-07-16T02:18:04.205167+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The University of North Carolina at Pembroke&lt;br/&gt;📍 Pembroke, NC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.uncp.edu/departments/art/ad-gallery/call-entries-art-times-anxiety"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The University of North Carolina at Pembroke announces a call for entries for our 10th Annual International Juried Exhibition.   All interpretations of this year’s theme, “Art in Times of Anxiety” of are welcome in a variety of media, subjects, and approaches.  Artists are invited to submit two-dimensional, three-dimensional, installation or digital media (including video based media). Composition, technique, style, expression, and craft will be considered in the selection process.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All artists who are selected by this year’s juror will be displayed in the UNCP’s Art Department Gallery from Thursday, October 04 – Friday, November 01, 2019. Awards will be announced at the artists reception on Wednesday, October 9, at 5 p.m. Awards: $600 first prize, $200 second prize, and $100 third prize&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror:  Ralph Steeds&lt;br/&gt;Ralph Steeds has been included in over 200 national, international, and regional exhibitions since 1980. He has taught printmaking and drawing for over thirty years and is Professor Emeritus at the University Of North Carolina, Pembroke.  His work is in numerous public and private collections, and he is represented by Adam Cave Fine Art Gallery in Raleigh, North Carolina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eligibility: Open to all national and international artists. Works must be completed within the last three years and not have been previously exhibited at the A.D. Gallery. Artwork should be original, no mass produced prints or reproductions. Submitting artists must be at least 18 years of age.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each artist must submit work following the guidelines below. Entries must be submitted by mail or online along with application fee by midnight, August 30, 2019 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;• Email files to adgallery@uncp.edu&lt;br/&gt;• Title the e-mail: “Anxiety 10th Annual Juried Submission”&lt;br/&gt;• In the body of the e-mail please include the following:&lt;br/&gt;         Your Name&lt;br/&gt;         Address&lt;br/&gt;         Email address&lt;br/&gt;         Phone&lt;br/&gt;         Website address (if you have one)&lt;br/&gt;         Title, media, dimensions, date of each work submitted, &amp; insurance values&lt;br/&gt;         Optional: Description (max. 50 words) and/or methods used &lt;br/&gt;• Artists may enter up to 3 works (3 additional images may be submitted for details or 3-D works)&lt;br/&gt;• Please submit all images as attachments, do not drop them in the body of your email&lt;br/&gt;• Submitted images should be in JPEG format at 72 dpi&lt;br/&gt;• Submitted files should be no larger than 1024 pixels x 768 pixels&lt;br/&gt;• A full view of each submitted artwork is required&lt;br/&gt;• JPEG files should be named as follows: firstinitial_lastname_abbreviated title.jpg.&lt;br/&gt;•  For Video submissions, please send us the direct URL links to your video files.  All works must be no longer than 5 minutes.  If the work is accepted, you will be asked to submit the high quality .mov file &lt;br/&gt;• Please do not submit 35mm slides or CD&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An entry fee of $25.00 should be submitted by mail or online to complete your application.&lt;br/&gt;Checks or Money Orders payable to: UNCP, Art Department – A.D. Gallery&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Online payments may be made via donation to &lt;a href="https://braveweb.uncp.edu/opay/give/" target="_blank"&gt;https://braveweb.uncp.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Select “Area to apply gift,”  “Program or Department” and type “A.D. Gallery 10th Juried” in the please specify below text box.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Mail entries or entry fee payments by check should be sent to:&lt;br/&gt;Joseph Begnaud, A.D. Gallery Director&lt;br/&gt;UNC Pembroke&lt;br/&gt;Art Department&lt;br/&gt;P.O. Box 1510&lt;br/&gt;One University Drive&lt;br/&gt;Pembroke, NC 28372&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1da9e6f0-3b98-44e2-add5-ae464e86faa4" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>