<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-05T17:14:57-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>a2ad940f-b16b-4734-bbc9-2dc03bb8660b</id><title>4/5 - 89th Annual Juried Open Exhibition</title><updated>2019-03-05T17:14:57.973637+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;National Art League&lt;br/&gt;📍 Douglaston, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/05/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.nationalartleague.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AWARDS&lt;br/&gt;Over $2,000 in Awards will be presented at the Exhibition’s reception - First Prize $500, &lt;br/&gt;Second Prize $300 and Third Prize $200&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JUROR &amp; JUDGE&lt;br/&gt;Mitchell Goldberg, Director at the Upstream Gallery in NY, Board of Directors member at the NY Society of Etchers, accomplished artist&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;This call for submission is open to all artists 18 years of age or older. This is a juried exhibition for artists working in all traditional and non-traditional 2D and 3D media, including sculpture. All artwork must be original in concept, design and execution. Photography, film, video, computer art, reproductions (such as giclee, prints) are not acceptable unless used as part of a mixed media artwork or collage. Installation art or performance art are not accepted. No crafts (such as jewelry) or kit work. Artwork must not exceed 48 inches in any dimension including frame. Sculpture must not exceed 30 inches in any dimension.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition will be on display from May 6 – June 1, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEES - can submit 1 or 2 entries &lt;br/&gt;Members: $30 one entry, $10 second entry&lt;br/&gt;Non-Members: $35 one entry, $10 second entry  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more details, prospectus and entry form, visit our website: nationalartleague.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To download the prospectus and entry form visit our website: nationalartleague.org. Click "Exhibitions" on the navigation bar and go to the 89th Annual Juried Open Show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Prospectus will provide more details regarding submission guidelines and important dates, payment etc. Accepting website and mail submissions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For questions, email: nationalartleague@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a2ad940f-b16b-4734-bbc9-2dc03bb8660b" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>