<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-06-29T10:17:42-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>eb1ab527-7dc3-4450-9682-91b13b1eee08</id><title>8/7 - Small and Smaller</title><updated>2019-06-29T10:17:42.339239+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/07/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small and Smaller&lt;br/&gt;September 20– October 20, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brookyn is asking you to think small! In the contemporary art world, the notion that “bigger is better” is everywhere. From massive sculptural installations to giant canvases, the small, delicate, and pared down seem to have little place. Against such an idea, this show asks artists to go in the opposite direction and think about the intimacy and beauty of art that explores space, color, and form on a miniature scale. Site:Brooklyn is looking for works across all mediums — painting, photography, drawing, sculpture, video, and multimedia. Our goal is to exhibit a wide array of work, truly representing the expansive world of small art. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Heather Darcy Bhandari is an independent curator, adjunct lecturer at Brown University, and a consultant to several for-profit and nonprofit arts institutions. The second edition of her book, ART/WORK, was published by Simon and Schuster. She is on the board of directors of visual arts at Art Omi and the advisory boards of artfcity and Trestle Gallery in Brooklyn. From 2000 to 2016 she was a director of Mixed Greens, a commercial gallery where she curated over one hundred exhibitions while managing a roster of nearly two-dozen emerging to mid-career artists. Most recently, she was the Director of Exhibitions at Smack Mellon, a nonprofit in Brooklyn.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: June 26, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: August 7, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: August 15, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: September 20– October 20, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, September 20, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in drawing, painting, printmaking, sculpture, collage, photography, video and multimedia..&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $35.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by August 7, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:&lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/31YmvL1&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 12”  X 12” X 12” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;4. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/31YmvL1" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/eb1ab527-7dc3-4450-9682-91b13b1eee08" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7b04bbbb-abd2-4ae5-a2d1-74b8e643cf1c</id><title>7/21 - NOW Is the Future - OPEN CALL - Local Project</title><updated>2019-06-29T10:17:42.339183+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Local Project&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://localproject.org/open-calls/now-is-the-future-summer-open-call-2019/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open call Deadline: SUNDAY JULY 21 3pm&lt;br/&gt;Notification: July 22 &lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: August 1- 18&lt;br/&gt;Delivery of selected works: TBC via acceptance email &lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Thursday August: 1, 6-9pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are obsessed with the past but always thinking about the future, and as we live in the moment we always think that tomorrow will be better.&lt;br/&gt;We are looking for a representation of your perception of the future in the past -Visions of future cities, landscapes, personal hopes and dreams.&lt;br/&gt;So much we thought up as fiction has become real.&lt;br/&gt;How did you think of the future 1/5/10 years ago? &lt;br/&gt;Where are we headed?&lt;br/&gt;Where are you headed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;-Artwork must be original and come from you – the artist. (no digital reproductions).&lt;br/&gt;-Artist must live in NYC or NJ.&lt;br/&gt;-There is no entry fee to submit your work but accepted artists pay a hanging fee of $30, by cash, check or Venmo.&lt;br/&gt;-Hanging fees go directly toward the expenses of the exhibition and the reception.&lt;br/&gt;-Work must be ready to hang ie; frames or wired, no clips or pins –no size limit and prices bellow $1,000 ( we hold the right to make exceptions )&lt;br/&gt;-Please SUBMIT up to 4 images of the works you like to show, include title, year, dimension, material, and price along with submissions and embed title in jpeg to opencall@localproject.org including NOW IS THE FUTURE in the subject.&lt;br/&gt;-Jpegs must not exceed 2mb. Don’t send links to look at work.&lt;br/&gt;Local Project takes a 30% fee if your work is sold. Sales will be finalized at the end of each exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;-This exhibition will be Juried by LP curators John Baber and Carolina Peñafiel.&lt;br/&gt;-Once notified, you will be guided to drop off dates, payment must be done at drop off. &lt;br/&gt;-Artists are responsible for the drop-off and pick-up of any and all artwork. &lt;br/&gt;-Any artwork left without notice for more than a week after the end of the show at LP, Local Project will not be held responsible&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7b04bbbb-abd2-4ae5-a2d1-74b8e643cf1c" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>