<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-12T02:16:36-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>f1142491-cf23-48e4-9169-7d09105a6149</id><title>6/9 - NUDE: Exploring the Uncovered Human Form in Current Art</title><updated>2019-05-12T02:16:36.117494+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/09/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/nude"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cincinnati based non-profit arts organization and gallery, Manifest, invites visual artists and designers to submit works that in some way represent the uncovered human form. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The human body is a popular subject for many reasons, the most obvious being that it is us. Through all the permutations art has experienced across history, work of the body persists. We use the human nude to master skill, understand ourselves, and push social and psychological buttons for the sake of expression (sensual, delicate, political, aggressive, and so on). We intend for Manifest's ongoing annual NUDE project, now in its 11th year, to explore how our collective body is used today in art to achieve these goals and more.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This year we are happy to celebrate passing a decade of exploring the nude in contemporary art, and renew our invitation to artists to submit works in any media, of any style or genre (abstract, conceptual, realistic, etc.), and of any size, for consideration in Manifest's eleventh annual NUDE, an international competitive exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNUAL CASH AWARD: The annual Manifest Grand Jury Prize will result in the awarding of one significant cash prize ($2500) to a single work selected as the 'best of the entire season'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To view the full prospectus and entry form visit &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/nude." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f1142491-cf23-48e4-9169-7d09105a6149" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>