<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-16T03:15:58-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>a7d8d70e-b29c-4b41-bb81-b6af94903c7f</id><title>5/10 - Color Burst: A Picture Show</title><updated>2019-04-16T03:15:58.169849+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Bxo Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on color photography at Black Box Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a7d8d70e-b29c-4b41-bb81-b6af94903c7f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7b336a4b-bad0-4cb9-b6bb-fc3894e1f990</id><title>5/31 - Create! Magazine Call For Art: Summer 2019 Print Edition</title><updated>2019-04-16T03:15:58.169811+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.createmagazine.com/callforart"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine is an independent contemporary arts magazine focused on highlighting the work of talented emerging and mid-career creatives from across the globe. We are pleased to announce our next call for artists for a custom designed two-page spread in our publication (both print &amp; digital) that will feature your artist biography, website, and two images of your artwork. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Have your work seen by our 125,000+ readers and followers around the world, including leading galleries, art fairs, collectors, curators, writers, art consultants, and more. Don’t miss this opportunity to put your work out there and connect with a new audience! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE CURATOR: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Nina Blumberg, Art Consultant | Samuels Creative&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Nina Blumberg is a full-time art consultant at the New York City-based firm Samuels Creative. Outside of work, she fills her time with freelance social media contemporary art clientele and projects, most recently engaging with the art technology space. Nina received her BA in Art History from the University of Virginia and her MA from FIT’s “Art Market: Principles &amp; Practices” program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Nina is also the founder of @Artstagram__,the contemporary art world Instagram account that covers art happenings and exhibitions in NYC and beyond. She enjoys engaging with art on a constant basis in both a personal and professional capacity. She can also be counted on to (overshare) life updates with original content and dad jokes on various social media platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY: All artists 18+ from both the US and abroad, of all genders, ethnicities, and from all backgrounds are welcome to apply. We accept works in any medium: painting, sculpture, digital art, printmaking, fiber/textile art, photography, mixed media, installation, etc. A university degree is not required to participate in our open call. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS: 3+ jpeg images, a text document with a bio and artist statement, website or social media link, and your email address. Please see our Submittable form for further details. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTISTS: If your work is selected by our guest juror, you will receive a custom designed two-page spread in both the print and digital versions of the magazine that will include your artist biography, website, and two images. Published artists will be sent a complimentary digital issue and will be listed as a participating artist in your issue on both our website and social media. We also promote artists individually via blog and social media posts that reach over 125,000 total followers worldwide. All featured artists will automatically be considered for any upcoming curatorial projects, not limited to art fairs, exhibitions, and gallery projects organized by our team. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHERE TO FIND: Print copies of Create! Magazine are available in our online shop and at several global retail locations in London, New York, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Amsterdam, Stockholm, Chicago, Ft. Lauderdale, Wilmington (DE), and more. Digital issues can always be purchased on our website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7b336a4b-bad0-4cb9-b6bb-fc3894e1f990" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0947645a-0b03-4131-a680-24d6c22f4cab</id><title>4/30 - Wrong Side of the River Open Call for Exhibition Opportunities, Solo and Group</title><updated>2019-04-16T03:15:58.169775+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wrong Side of the River Projects&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://wrongsideoftheriver.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WSR Projects, an art space in Greenpoint, Brooklyn, is seeking underrepresented visual artists  to be considered for a group exhibition in May and potential future solo showings. Our aim is to build community and spotlight exceptional work.  We are looking for skill-based painting, drawing, sculpture, and multi-media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To apply please e-mail 3 to 5 high-res photos of work, your artist statement, and a link to pertinent website/social media accounts to wsrprojectspace@gmail.com. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The application fee is submitted through Venmo to either @jacobhickspainter or @buket-Savci.  Applications without payment will not be considered. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All applications are carefully reviewed, as artists ourselves we know the hardship and labor that goes into sustaining a creative life. No work will be discounted and we thank you for it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0947645a-0b03-4131-a680-24d6c22f4cab" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e544ab22-769f-4618-964c-55a10f104c3e</id><title>5/17 - Call for Artists! Juried Exhibition - Light - Deadline May 17</title><updated>2019-04-16T03:15:58.169704+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;440 Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://gallery440.squarespace.com/call-for-artists"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Light&lt;br/&gt;Juried Exhibition, Brooklyn, NY&lt;br/&gt;June 26 - July 26, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Whether we seek light as a physical object or observe it as a metaphysical presence, it is the play of light and shadow that uniquely informs our human vision. In simpler terms, light gives life; under certain circumstances light also facilitates destruction. Capturing light in visual terms has always been a crucial element in traditional painting. With multi-media, installation, and conceptual-based artwork, light takes on an equally important role for the artist.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jurors for the “Light” show are Lauren Hirshfield and Kat Ryals, &lt;br/&gt;Co-Directors of Paradice Palase in Bushwick, Brooklyn, NY.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JURORS:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lauren Hirshfield is an independent curator and artist living and working in NYC. She received a BFA in painting, arts management and art history from SUNY Purchase. Over the past five years she has freelanced as an arts administrator, assistant, and curator for organizations such as Superchief Gallery, 4Heads/Portal, POWRPLNT and ArtMoney. Her curatorial practice is fueled by the ephemeral, the ethereal and the tactile. She is interested in further democratizing the art world and strives to consider accessible ways the public can engage with art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Kat Ryals is an artist, curator and photographer based in Brooklyn, NY. She received a BFA in photography in 2010 from Savannah College of Art and Design, and an MFA in Visual Art and Museum Education from Brooklyn College. She has worked in the education department of several NYC museums and non-profits, including the Rubin Museum, the Museum of Arts and Design, and ArtsConnection. Ryals has shown her work nationally, and was included in recent group exhibitions with the Holocenter on Governor’s Island, Temporary Storage Gallery at Brooklyn Fireproof, and the Wassaic Project. She was a Fellow at Vermont Studio Center in January 2018, and a resident at the Wassaic Project in January 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;440 Gallery is an artist-run space in Park Slope, Brooklyn, dedicated to the creation, exhibition and sale of a wide range of work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Open to U.S. resident artists at least 18 yrs. old. All 2-D work must be suitably framed, wired and ready for hanging. Works on paper must be framed under plexiglass or glass. Canvases must be wired for hanging. All 3-D work must be able to hang securely on the wall, sit on a shelf, pedestal or the floor. Size limit for this exhibition is 40 x 40 inches.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ACCEPTANCE:&lt;br/&gt;Accepted work may be refused if it does not conform to the entered image. Absolutely NO SUBSTITUTIONS of accepted works will be allowed. All accepted work must remain in the gallery for the duration of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SALES:&lt;br/&gt;The gallery will take 40% commission on any work sold. Work not for sale must be marked “NFS"; no Price on request, ”POR" sales.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY FEE:&lt;br/&gt;The fee is $40 for 1 - 3 works, $5 for each additional work up to 6 works total. Entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ENTRY REQUIREMENTS: All entries must be submitted electronically. Judging will be done entirely from JPEGs. No other formats will be accepted. JPEGs should be at least 600 pixels but not greater than 1200 pixels in either direction. Maximum file size for any individual image is 2 MB. The size given for works should be the framed size. *Height must be given before width regardless of whether the work is a vertical or a horizontal. Entry form must be filled out completely. Your payment will serve as your acceptance of the terms and conditions stated in this prospectus. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMAGE LABELING: JPEG images MUST BE labeled as follows:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LAST Name_FIRST Name_The number that corresponds with that work's placement on the Entry Form (1st, 2nd, 3rd, etc.) smith_joe_1.jpg&lt;br/&gt;smith_joe_2.jpg&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Files mislabeled or lacking the artist's name will not be viewed by the juror.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DELIVERY OF WORK: Hand-delivered work will be accepted at the gallery ONLY on Saturday June 22, 12-6 and Sunday, June 23, 12 - 6 PM. Packaging must be removed from the gallery at the time of delivery. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shipped work must arrive at the gallery between Wednesday June 12 - Saturday, June 22, in a reusable container. A computer-generated return label for return of work MUST be enclosed. NO EXCEPTIONS. Pre-paid shipping arrangements must be made through UPS or FedEx websites. NO U.S. POSTAL SERVICE OR COD RETURNS. DO NOT SEND CASH, CHECK, STAMPS, OR CREDIT CARD INFORMATION FOR RETURN OF WORK. Keep in mind the gallery is closed on Monday and Tuesday and will not be able to accept deliveries on those days.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artworks that do not arrive by June 23 will not be hung.  No exceptions will be made.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;RETURN: Hand-delivered work must be picked up on July 27-28, 12-6 PM. Shipped works will be returned the week of July 29th. The gallery accepts no responsibility for work not retrieved on pick-up date, after 30 days the gallery may dispose of the work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY: Great care will be taken with all work, but artists are responsible for insuring their own pieces if they wish.  440 Gallery will not be responsible for any loss or damage to work while on the premises or in transit to or from the gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The submission of a work of art to this exhibition shall be understood to constitute an agreement on the part of the artist to the conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EVENT SCHEDULE:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;May 17                          Entry deadline at midnight&lt;br/&gt;June 9                            Notifications sent out by this date&lt;br/&gt;June 12-22                    Receipt of shipped work via UPS or FedEx&lt;br/&gt;June 22-23                   Hand delivery of work:  12-6 PM&lt;br/&gt;June 24                         Installation&lt;br/&gt;June 26                         Exhibition opens&lt;br/&gt;June 29                         Opening reception 5-8 PM&lt;br/&gt;July 26                           Exhibition closes &lt;br/&gt;July 27                           Pickup of hand-delivered work: 12-6 PM&lt;br/&gt;July 28                           Pickup of hand-delivered work: 12-6 PM&lt;br/&gt;Week of July 29            Return of shipped work via UPS or FedEx&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e544ab22-769f-4618-964c-55a10f104c3e" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>