<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-08T17:17:54-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>a04f5585-0b31-42e1-9471-513a37aa173a</id><title>7/31 - Create! Magazine MFA Edition Call for Art</title><updated>2019-07-08T17:17:54.303259+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.createmagazine.com/callforart"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine is pleased to announce an open call for its first annual MFA Edition. We are now accepting applications from current candidates and recent graduates from 2017 - 2019.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Create! Magazine is an independent contemporary arts magazine focused on highlighting the work of talented emerging and mid-career creatives from across the globe. We are pleased to announce our next call for artists for a custom designed two-page spread in our publication (both print &amp; digital) that will feature your artist biography, website, and two images of your artwork. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Have your work seen by our 125,000+ readers and followers around the world, including leading galleries, art fairs, collectors, curators, writers, art consultants, and more. Don’t miss this opportunity to put your work out there and connect with a new audience! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JUROR: Kate Mothes, Founder of Young Space&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Kate Mothes is founder and curator of Young Space, an independent, itinerant, online-offline contemporary art platform emphasizing early career and emerging artists. Kate received a Masters in Art History, Theory and Display from Edinburgh College of Art at the University of Edinburgh, and a Bachelors in Art History from the University of Wisconsin-Madison. In addition to online exhibitions, selected recent exhibitions include Wolves by the Road at Assembly House, Leeds, UK; Memory Palace at Hastings College, Hastings, Nebraska; BIG LINK at Standard Projects, Hortonville, WI; and Crocodile Tears at Morgan Fine Arts and Film Center, Brooklyn, New York. UK; Run Straight Through at Torrance Art Museum, Torrance, California. She has recently participated as a guest juror for BEERS London’s Contemporary Visions 2019, and was curator-in-residence at AucArt LAB, London, UK, in March 2019, and at PADA Studios in Lisbon, Portugal, in April 2019. When not traveling for exhibitions and projects, she is based in Northeast Wisconsin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY: MFA graduates from the past two years and current candidates from both the US and abroad, of all genders, ethnicities, and from all backgrounds are welcome to apply. We accept works in any medium: painting, sculpture, digital art, printmaking, fiber/textile art, photography, mixed media, installation, etc. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS: 3+ jpeg images of different artworks, a text document with a bio and artist statement, website or social media link, and your email address. If your work is three-dimensional, you may include additional images of installation views or detailed shots at no extra cost. Please see our Submittable form for further details. Please note that for best results, artists should include works from the same series per each submission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTISTS: If your work is selected, you will receive a custom designed two-page spread in both the print and digital versions of the magazine that will include your artist biography, website, and two images. Published artists will be sent a complimentary digital issue and will be listed as a participating artist in your issue on both our website and social media. We also promote artists individually via blog and social media posts that reach over 125,000 total followers worldwide. All featured artists will automatically be considered for any upcoming curatorial projects, not limited to art fairs, exhibitions, and gallery projects organized by our team. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;WHERE TO FIND US: Print copies of Create! Magazine are available in our online shop and at several global retail locations in London, New York, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Amsterdam, Stockholm, Chicago, Philadelphia, Ft. Lauderdale, Wilmington (DE), and more. Digital issues can always be purchased on our website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a04f5585-0b31-42e1-9471-513a37aa173a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>fbfd60d7-dded-471d-b773-418d3703d809</id><title>8/1 - Contested Spaces: 2019 Harnett Biennial of American Prints</title><updated>2019-07-08T17:17:54.303203+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;University of Richmond Museums&lt;br/&gt;📍 Richmond, VA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Printmaking&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=6720"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contested Spaces: 2019 Harnett Biennial of American Prints is the twelfth competitive national exhibition organized by the University of Richmond Museums. Submissions are encouraged by artists addressing the topic of “contested spaces” from both content and aesthetic perspectives. The theme provides an opportunity for artists to focus on their own understandings of “contested spaces” with a variety of interpretations, styles, and techniques. Open to all forms of prints, the exhibition is presented as a celebration and examination of contemporary printmaking by artists from throughout the United States. The Harnett Biennial will be on view from October 22 to December 6, 2019, in the Joel and Lila Harnett Museum of Art, University Museums.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All entries must be submitted through &lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=6720." target="_blank"&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fbfd60d7-dded-471d-b773-418d3703d809" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>