<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>ca3b77fa-9bac-401a-b840-ca088cc29b0c</id><title>3/14 - INTERNATIONAL CALL FOR ART, ArtMaze Magazine Spring Edition: Issue 12</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679819+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtMaze Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍  , United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artmazemagazine.submittable.com/submit/133107/international-call-for-art-artmaze-mag-spring-edition-12"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art Maze Magazine is an independent artist-run and ad-free international print and online publication dedicated to showcasing and promoting experimental and progressive contemporary art, which reflects modern society and its environment, provokes conversation and action; fosters innovation and diversity of mediums which make today’s art scene so intriguing and versatile.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: Artists are welcome to submit works in any medium: painting, drawing, sculpture, ceramics, printmaking, photography, textile, installation, mixed media, digital, film (only jpg + link to video) etc. All visual art mediums are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists or any art organisations on behalf of artists from all countries are welcome to submit their works for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each submitted artist, wether selected for a publication or not, will receive a digital copy of the magazine's issue which he/she applied for.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: March 14th, 2019 (12:00 AM, midnight: end of the day 14th March - Eastern Standard Time)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUEST CURATOR: Tristian Koenig, Melbourne-based Gallerist&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO APPLY: www.artmazemag.com/call-for-art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DISTRIBUTION: Physical and digital copies of ArtMaze Mag are distributed worldwide via bookshops, galleries and online. More info: &lt;a href="http://artmazemag.com/shop/" target="_blank"&gt;http://artmazemag.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selected artists will be asked for high resolution images and will be published in the next print and digital issue of ArtMaze Magazine. Each (selected) artist will receive a 1 or 2-page spread in print and digital (PDF) magazine including bio, statement, website, and 1-5 featured artworks. All submitted artists will receive a complimentary PDF copy of the magazine and all published artists will be promoted on our website/social media. &lt;br/&gt;Physical copies of Art Maze Magazine are printed to the highest quality in London, UK.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ca3b77fa-9bac-401a-b840-ca088cc29b0c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e39fed63-d69d-4ad1-8fc1-d167295ee629</id><title>6/15 - Rust Belt Biennial - open for photographic submissions</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679793+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Rust Belt Biennial&lt;br/&gt;📍 Wilkes-Barre, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.rustbeltbiennial.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to introduce the first RUST BELT BIENNIAL, a celebration of photography with work realized throughout the Rust Belt Region in all its manifestations. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This land, its people, the pride and the struggles, the patina of the past and above all, the histories and memories ingrained in the soil across the region. It is time to make new memories and new histories, while revisiting and reevaluating old ones; It is time to start a new dialogue about the state of photography and it’s social, cultural and political effects in our society; it is time to give back to the photographic community but also the region; it is time for you to join us! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For our an inaugural Biennial we are grateful to have Andrew L. Moore as competition juror.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are honored to collaborate with the Sordoni Gallery at Wilkes University, in Wilkes-Barre, Penn., where the Biennial will be held from August 27th to October 5h of 2019. Additional information regarding the dates of the main exhibition with lectures and presentations will be published in the Spring.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our juried competition is hosted in an agreement between LensCulture and Rust Belt Biennial.  Using the SUBMIT HERE button &lt;br/&gt;(https://www.lensculture.com/competitions/Rust-Belt-Biennial/events) &lt;br/&gt;on our website will redirect you to LensCulture so that you can sign up for an account and submit your entry through the online entry portal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use this link to skip our website and go directly to the submission form on LensCulture:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.lensculture.com/competitions/Rust-Belt-Biennial/events&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What are we looking for?&lt;br/&gt;We are looking for photographic bodies of works that explore the social and cultural realities that represent or make a commentary of this very important region within the American landscape. &lt;br/&gt;Additionally, we are looking for both in progress or fully realized photographic work in printed form.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Who is eligible?&lt;br/&gt;All are welcome to submit work that was created within the Rust Belt Region (New York, Missouri, Pennsylvania, Ohio, Indiana, Michigan, West Virginia, Illinois, Iowa, Wisconsin)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist information:&lt;br/&gt;Legal Name&lt;br/&gt;Artist Name if different&lt;br/&gt;Address&lt;br/&gt;Email Address&lt;br/&gt;Telephone&lt;br/&gt;Statement (up to 500 words)&lt;br/&gt;Bio (up to 300 words)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Image information and file requirements:&lt;br/&gt;Title format for each image: Title, caption(optional), location&lt;br/&gt;Date&lt;br/&gt;Medium (Print Type)&lt;br/&gt;File naming: First and last name, image title&lt;br/&gt;Example: John_Smith-Image_Title.jpg&lt;br/&gt;File format: JPG&lt;br/&gt;File dimensions: 2500 pixels on the longest side&lt;br/&gt;Color space: sRGB&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission fee:&lt;br/&gt;$35 for up to 25 images&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e39fed63-d69d-4ad1-8fc1-d167295ee629" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b5894a3b-52c1-4735-b2ab-9ae7eaf56fdc</id><title>5/1 - Flow</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679767+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Philadelphia Sculptors&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.philaflow.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philadelphia Sculptors seeks artists to create temporary outdoor floating sculptural installations for our Fall, 2019 exhibition "Flow," a collaboration with the Independence Seaport Museum. The exhibition will be sited in the boat basin adjacent to the Museum, located at Penn’s Landing on the Delaware River in Philadelphia and will run from October 11 – November 30, 2019. The intent of the exhibition is to unite art with the river, and with the Museum’s mission and programming.  Five juried artists, along with five invited artists previously selected, will interpret the river and how it affects, and is affected by, human and natural history; human and natural migrations; climate change and the environment; economic development; and political currents. The geographic focus of the show is on the Americas and we are seeking artists from Mexico, South and Central America, and Canada, along with artists from the US and its territories. The jurors will be Nato Thompson, and Teresa Jaynes. The exhibition is also co-sponsored by the Dina Wind Art Foundation. Accepted artists will receive a $2,000 honorarium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and how to apply, go to www.philaflow.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b5894a3b-52c1-4735-b2ab-9ae7eaf56fdc" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>baf7223d-18ff-4d2c-8ae1-bf0e8a9290f7</id><title>3/22 - Open Call for Solo Exhibitions and Curatorial Projects</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679740+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;CUE Art Foundation&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/22/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://cueartfoundation.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CUE’s Open Calls provide artists and emerging curators the opportunity and necessary resources to realize an exhibition at CUE’s storefront gallery in East Chelsea, New York.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each year, a panel of established artists and curators select two solo exhibitions and one curatorial project to be realized at CUE. Finalists are paired with a member of the selection panel, who works with them as a mentor throughout the process of planning and mounting the exhibition. CUE provides institutional guidance, generous honoraria, a shipping budget, and an accompanying exhibition catalogue with a critical essay by a participant in CUE's Art Critic Mentoring Program. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications are accepted once annually in the spring. The deadline for the current Open Call is March 22, 2019.    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SOLO EXHIBITION INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;CUE's Solo Exhibition Open Call is for artists who:&lt;br/&gt;-Have not had a solo show in a commercial NYC gallery within the last five years&lt;br/&gt;-Do not have current, consistent commercial gallery representation in the United States&lt;br/&gt;-Are not currently enrolled in a degree program&lt;br/&gt;-Have a demonstrated, consistent studio practice outside an academic setting for three or more years&lt;br/&gt;-Must currently live and work in the United States&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;-The exhibition program is open to artists working in all disciplines.&lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to artists who present ideas or topics that are not well-represented in the commercial sector.&lt;br/&gt;-CUE strongly encourages applications that contribute to our ongoing commitment to diversity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What Finalists receive:&lt;br/&gt;-Five-week solo exhibition at CUE Art Foundation in 2020&lt;br/&gt;-Curatorial support/mentoring from an established artist or curator on the selection panel&lt;br/&gt;-Opportunities to develop related public programming &lt;br/&gt;-32-page full color catalogue with essay produced through the Art Critic Mentoring Program and a statement by the curator&lt;br/&gt;-$5,000 unrestricted honorarium&lt;br/&gt;-An art shipping and art handling budget&lt;br/&gt;-Opening reception&lt;br/&gt;-Press materials and PR support &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CURATORIAL PROJECT INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;-Proposals must be conceptually rigorous and focus on artists, projects, and themes that are innovative, challenging, and engaging.&lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to proposals that demonstrate a creative approach to curatorial research methods and the exhibition plan, as well as those that present ideas or topics that are not well-represented in the commercial sector.&lt;br/&gt;-The proposal must include four or more artists, half of whom must qualify as under-recognized (no gallery representation and no solo exhibitions in a major venue within the past five years).&lt;br/&gt;-Curators may not include their own work in the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;-The curator and all proposed artists must live and work in the United States.    &lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to those in the beginning stages of their curatorial careers.&lt;br/&gt;-CUE strongly encourages applications that contribute to our ongoing commitment to diversity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What the opportunity includes:&lt;br/&gt;-Five-week exhibition at CUE Art Foundation in 2020&lt;br/&gt;-Curatorial support/mentoring from an established artist or curator on the selection panel&lt;br/&gt;-Opportunities to develop related public programming &lt;br/&gt;-Full color catalogue with essay produced through the Art Critic Mentoring Program&lt;br/&gt;-$2,500 unrestricted honorarium&lt;br/&gt;-$2,500 to divide amongst the participating artists and program speakers&lt;br/&gt;-$2,000 production budget&lt;br/&gt;-An art shipping and art handling budget&lt;br/&gt;-Opening reception&lt;br/&gt;-Press materials and PR support&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at &lt;a href="http://cueartfoundation.org/open-call" target="_blank"&gt;http://cueartfoundation.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, please visit our website or email Lilly Hern-Fondation, Programs Associate: lilly@cueartfoundation.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/baf7223d-18ff-4d2c-8ae1-bf0e8a9290f7" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6002bcf2-7474-40d6-a62f-77a71dcd3655</id><title>3/16 - Crystal Park Open Call for outdoor artwork</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679714+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Crystal Park&lt;br/&gt;📍 Holmes, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/16/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.crystalpark.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artwork on the rocks along the trail - A creative look for the rock trail&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The rock trail starts from the Crystal Park gate and is about 0.6 mile with rocks placed along the two sides of the trail. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Artists are invited to propose artwork to be placed on/with the rocks as long as the artwork doesn’t obstruct the trail nor cause any safety concern. &lt;br/&gt;•	Please consider the nature outdoor setting. Materials that can withstand the weather and be integrated with the environment are preferred. &lt;br/&gt;•	Selected artist will have access to woodshop and metal shop to fabricate the work if needed. (Fabrication facility location: Flushing, Queens, NY)&lt;br/&gt;•	Crystal Park will provide assistance for the artist to install the work. &lt;br/&gt;•	Artist fee: $5,000&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Please submit the following documents:&lt;br/&gt;o	Drawings or/and rendering images/videos of the proposed artwork&lt;br/&gt;o	Project statement&lt;br/&gt;o	Detailed description of the artwork&lt;br/&gt;o	Artist bio and resume&lt;br/&gt;o	Artwork sample images (Maximum 20 images in jpeg, each under 5MB)&lt;br/&gt;o	Estimated budget&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Email the submission to &lt;br/&gt;info@crystalpark.org by March 16th 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Images and videos of the rock trail:&lt;br/&gt;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1ZaCmYh3Lk7Aw7k4hfK3ntRn8BtpC6MA-&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information about Crystal Park:&lt;br/&gt;www.crystalpark.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please address any question to: &lt;br/&gt;info@crystalpark.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;info@crystalpark.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6002bcf2-7474-40d6-a62f-77a71dcd3655" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f465d717-f518-4c8d-8b02-6eb2966416e3</id><title>3/10 - OPEN CALL: Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679681+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Friend of The Artist&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.friendoftheartist.com/application/?utm_source=NYFA&amp;amp;utm_medium=NYFA&amp;amp;utm_campaign=9"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FOA is a publication dedicated to elevating the work of emerging artists around the world. Our publication releases as a hardcover art book every quarter. It includes the work of artists who work in a variety of mediums, informative articles, and interviews. Accepted artists will have a four page spread of their work, information, and artist statement. Volume 9 will be juried by Alice Bonno, Erika B. Hess, Masha Vlasova, and FOA staff.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Volume 9 will be printed in hardback on premium color paper and are available online through booksellers like Amazon, Barnes and Noble, and are available in catalogs for libraries and bookstore distribution.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details of the Volume 9 Open Call:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Winners Receive&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3 works published in Volume 9, complimentary digital copy of publication, social media post of work, Discounts on publications for family and friends, and free digital access to future publications&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$25 for 5 Images&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;March 8, 2019 (midnight, CST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists of all academic disciples are welcome to apply. This includes painting, sculpture, photography, installation, new media, and performance art. Please do not submit videos since we are unable to publish.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guest Jurors&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Alice Bonnot&lt;br/&gt;Erika B. Hess&lt;br/&gt;Masha Vlasova&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Alice Bonnot is an independent curator and art consultant based in London. She is the co-founding director of Picnic, a contemporary art space occupying a long window in the Aylesham Centre in Peckham, London, and the founding director of the Zone d’Utopie Temporaire (Z.U.T.) residency programme, a nomadic annual residency addressing the notion of Utopia as a vehicle for artistic and critical comment. With this residency she curated exhibitions and events in Paris, London, Athens and Lisbon.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As an independent curator Alice organised a broad range of exhibitions for galleries, institutions and artist-run spaces. Her current exhibition Hyper Mesh(18 Jan – 23 Feb 2019) at Assembly Point, London, is an exhibition that brings together new work from eight international artists; Jonathan Baldock, Pauline Bastard, fleuryfontaine, Holly Hendry, Jessie Makinson, Morgan Wills and Fani Parali. The exhibition explores contemporary notions of identity, and sets out to examine how identity structures could be re-imagined or reconstructed. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Previous exhibitions include: Engine, Picnic, London, 2018,Bored but secured, Wozen, Lisbon, 2018,  Acts of disruption, The Concept Space, London, 2018, A series of pocket Utopias, Yellow Brick and Snehta, Athens, 2017, Right Through You, The Koppel Project Hive, London, 2017, Le corps comme activateur d’art numérique, Le Carreau du Temple, Paris, 2015, Prix Canson finalists, Palais de Tokyo, Paris / co-curated with Mr Laurent Boudier, 2015. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Erika B Hess  is a painter based in Columbus, OH recognized for her use and interest in color. Hess’s work has been exhibited nationally including Prince Street Gallery in NYC, Last Projects in Los Angles, CA, and Boston Center for the Arts in Boston, MA. In 2017, she had two solo exhibitions, “The Line Between the Past and the Present,” at the Musa Collective, Allston MA and “Viewing Light,” at Newton Free Library, Newton, MA. Her work has been featured in various publications including, Poets and Artists, Fresh Paint, Charles River Journal and Post Industrial Complex, a book released by the Museum of Contemporary Art Detroit. Her work was selected by John Seed to be featured in, “Fifty Memorable Artists 2015”. She has served on panels such as Cleveland Institute of Art’s, “Feminism Now: Exposing the Truth”, was a visiting juror for Dayton Visual Art Center’s 2016-2018 biennial, and is a recurring juror for the Walker Art MFA Prize at Boston University. Hess is a co-founder of Musa Collective, an artist collective in Boston and is the creator of I Like Your Work podcast, a podcast dedicated to interviewing artists, curators and collectors. Hess received her MFA from Boston University.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Masha Vlasova is an interdisciplinary artist, filmmaker, and educator. She holds a BFA from the Cooper Union and an MFA from Yale School of Art. She is a recipient the Fulbright Fellowship in Filmmaking, Alice Kimball Fellowship and the JUNCTURE Art and Human Rights Fellowship at Yale Law School. Her works have been exhibited and screened at Smack Mellon, Anthology Archives, and Abrons Arts Center in New York, Vox Populi and Temple University in Philadelphia, Carpenter Centerfor the Visual Artsat Harvard University among others. Her latest curatorial project “Women Filmmakers at the Intersection of Documentary, Video Art, and Avant Garde,” premiered at Indiana University Cinema in Bloomington, IN Fall of 2018. Her forthcoming essay about monument rotation will be published in a collection titled Monument Culture: International Perspectives on the Future of Monuments in a Changing World by the American Association for State and Local History/Rowman &amp; Littlefield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at friendoftheartist.com/application&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Email contact@friendoftheartist.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f465d717-f518-4c8d-8b02-6eb2966416e3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8f1f9a24-9742-4158-9b4c-d28a877b7d73</id><title>3/15 - Young Curators, New Ideas V</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679656+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Detroit Art Week&lt;br/&gt;📍 Detroit, MI, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://detroitartweek.org/young-curators-new-ideas-v"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call for Exhibition Proposals&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Detroit Art Week(July 16 –21, 2019), an annual self-guided tour and citywide celebration of contemporary art in Detroit produced by Olu &amp; Company, is now accepting applications from independent curators for the 5th iteration of “Young Curators, New Ideas.” In 2008, Detroit Art Week Founding Director, Amani Olu, established “Young Curators, New Ideas” to promote and support emerging curatorial voices. After a six-year hiatus, “Young Curators, New Ideas V” will take place from Wednesday, July 17 to Sunday, July 21, 2019 at Trumbull &amp; Porter Hotel Detroit, our exclusive hospitality partner. The deadline to apply is January 30, 2019.For more information and to apply, please visit &lt;a href="https://detroitartweek.org." target="_blank"&gt;https://detroitartweek.org.&lt;/a&gt; Featuring 12 independent curators selected from an international open call, “Young Curators, New Ideas V” will shine a light on the cultural, artistic, social and political transformations initiated by women, LGBTQIA and gender-non-conforming individuals through their creative, and at times independent, curatorial practices. With a sense of relevance and urgency, these multifaceted and dynamic micro-exhibitions will consider contemporary issues that exist at the intersection of curatorial practice and artistic production. Within a 256 square-foot hotel room, each curator will present one to two artists whose work is a thoughtful and provocative discussion on the most pressing issues of our time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Since its inception, “Young Curators, New Ideas” has presented exhibitions by 31 independent curators featuring 104 artists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Requirements&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;• Applicant Curriculum Vitae&lt;br/&gt;• Narrative Bio – up to 200 words&lt;br/&gt;• A short synopsis of the exhibition – up to 75 words&lt;br/&gt;• Detailed exhibition proposal – up to 1000 words&lt;br/&gt;• Artist 1 Bio – up to 200 words, CV, website or Insta&lt;br/&gt;• Artist 2 Bio – up to 200 words, CV, website or Insta&lt;br/&gt;• All applications submitted will be considered final. Applicants will not be permitted to edit an application once it has been sent. We will disqualify all incomplete or duplicate applications.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note: &lt;br/&gt;• There is no “save” option. Save your application in a separate document before submitting. &lt;br/&gt;• We will not accept applications after March 15, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;• We will not accept proposals nor applications via email.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8f1f9a24-9742-4158-9b4c-d28a877b7d73" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>131c6025-dce0-42ff-94a0-b5ea434848ca</id><title>3/8 - Vision: Shadow and Light</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679631+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/08/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on shadow and light in photography.&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="http://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/131c6025-dce0-42ff-94a0-b5ea434848ca" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>accb40bf-c624-43c8-8512-a606271360b6</id><title>3/11 - OPEN CALL Maake Magazine ISSUE 9 curated by Hein Koh</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679587+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Maake Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.maakemagazine.com/submitissue9/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce our OPEN CALL for Issue 9 of Maake Magazine, curated by Hein Koh.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists making work in all media are encouraged to apply. There are no restrictions. Applicants can be based anywhere in the world. Applications will be accepted via Submittable at: &lt;a href="https://maakemagazine.submittable.com/submit" target="_blank"&gt;https://maakemagazine.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: March 11th, 2019 at 11:59 PM EST&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Curator:&lt;br/&gt;Hein Koh is an artist who lives and works in Brooklyn, NY. She graduated from Dartmouth College with a dual B.A. in Studio Art and Psychology, and received her M.F.A. in Painting from Yale University. She is a recipient of a Mid-Atlantic Arts Foundation Grant, and an Artists in the Marketplace residency at the Bronx Museum of the Arts. Her work has been reviewed in Artforum, Art F City, Time Out New York, Hyperallergic, and The Brooklyn Rail. She has also received additional press in The New York Times, The Wall Street Journal, The Atlantic, The Huffington Post, and The Washington Post, among other publications. Hein has also taught and/or lectured at the California College of the Arts, Tyler School of Art, Dartmouth College, Maryland Institute College of Art, and the School of Visual Arts, among other institutions. She currently has an installation at Rockefeller Center, in collaboration with the Art Production Fund, comprised of sculptures and digital murals. Hein is also currently working on a public art commission for the Bronx Children’s Museum, which is slated to open in February of 2020. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Maake:&lt;br/&gt;Maake Magazine is an independent, artist-run organization that was created to support contemporary artists and other artist-run projects. It is our mission to provide exhibition opportunities as well as both online and print publishing opportunities for emerging and mid-career artists. Through collaborations with artists, curators, artist-run groups, galleries and more, we facilitate projects that support dialogue and community and increase the visibility of the arts while defying geographic boundaries. For more information about our current projects and to read interviews with all of our featured artists, artist-run organizations, and more, visit www.maakemagazine.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Published Artists receive the following:&lt;br/&gt;•Work featured in printed Issue (two full pages) &lt;br/&gt;•One complimentary copy of Maake Magazine printed issue (US Only)&lt;br/&gt;•Feature posted on Maake's social media outlets, website and blog&lt;br/&gt;•Artist Interview and accompanying gallery of work posted on our website&lt;br/&gt;•Future consideration for upcoming exhibitions and projects&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility &amp; Terms:&lt;br/&gt;•Artists may submit up to 6 works.&lt;br/&gt;•Artists working in all media are welcome to apply.&lt;br/&gt;•Artists working anywhere in the world are welcome to apply.&lt;br/&gt;•Artists must be 18 years old or older to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee: $20&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;•6 images of work&lt;br/&gt;•CV&lt;br/&gt;•Short statement&lt;br/&gt;•Short bio&lt;br/&gt;•Social Media info&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, please visit: &lt;a href="http://www.maakemagazine.com/submitissue9/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.maakemagazine.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected artists will be asked for high resolution images suitable for the printed magazine. Artists selected by the curator will receive a 2-page spread including a brief statement, website, and 1–4 images in print, and up to 8 images online.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/accb40bf-c624-43c8-8512-a606271360b6" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>916dd2a5-da06-4dbe-ab72-af584a22d549</id><title>2/21 - Grennpoint Gallery February People&amp;#39;s Choice Salon Show- WIN $200 AND A SOLO SHOW!</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679535+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our February People's Choice Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, February 22nd, 2019 at 8pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, February 21st, 2019 at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;For this show, we let the people decide, which means everyone who attends votes for the winners! We pass out ballots at the door and everyone who attends chooses the winners! It is always one of our most well attended nights, boasting record art sales and a large community of fellow artists and art lovers!&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of local bands!&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, February 21st at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces in the $150-$500 range. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/916dd2a5-da06-4dbe-ab72-af584a22d549" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>47be78c0-bb97-4da6-b170-627c86a80f35</id><title>3/14 - Photography Series and Repetition</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679503+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.sitebrooklyn.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photography Series and Repetition &lt;br/&gt;May 3, 2019 – June 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This show seeks to exhibit the diverse and exciting ways that photographers use sequence and series in their work. Repetition and seriality are built into the every level of photography from the production process, to its aesthetic theory, to the real-life practice of taking pictures. Photographs are often seen as representations or repetitions of reality itself, all while photography itself shapes modern consciousness just as much as it re-creates it. Site:Brooklyn is looking for work that actively engages with all aspects of repetition and series in photography. This might include subject matter, formal qualities, method, presentation, and much else.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Elisabeth Biondi has been an independent curator, writer. Before that she was the Visuals Editor of The New Yorker for 15 years, where she shaped the look of the publication by establishing a group of staff photographers, commissioning both masters and emerging talent. She built the magazine’s reputation for its use of photography, for which it received numerous awards, including two National Magazine Awards. Her independent curation includes Subjective/Objective and Under the Bridge for the New York PhotoFestival and New Yorker Fiction/Real Photography at Steven Kasher Gallery in Chelsea. Most recently she was a judge in the eight-episodes Sky Arts ‘Master of Photography’, which aired in May/June/July of 2018.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: February 7, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: March 14, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: March 23, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: May 3 – June 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, May 3, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in photography. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $35.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by March 14, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION:&lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2E07jCW&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 60” X 60” X 6” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Photographs printed and mounted on aluminum, plexiglass, sintra and dibond require a cleat for hanging.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;5. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Photography Series and Repetition” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2E07jCW" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/47be78c0-bb97-4da6-b170-627c86a80f35" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>50de7620-e494-4cbf-b742-8a3a3ed2183c</id><title>3/31 - Create! Magazine Call for Art: Print Magazine Feature and Gallery Exhibition</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679474+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Create! Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia , PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.createmagazine.com/callforart"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CREATE! MAGAZINE IS PLEASED TO ANNOUNCE AN OPEN CALL FOR THE MAY/JUNE PRINT ISSUE CURATED BY PARADIGM GALLERY + STUDIO.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTISTS WILL BE PUBLISHED IN OUR INTERNATIONAL PRINT ISSUE. IN ADDITION, PUBLISHED ARTISTS MAY BE INVITED TO PARTICIPATE IN A GROUP EXHIBITION IN 2020 IN PHILADELPHIA. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JURY PANEL&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PARADIGM GALLERY + STUDIO®&lt;br/&gt;JASON CHEN AND SARA MCCORRISTON&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Paradigm Gallery + Studio® exhibits contemporary artwork from around the world with a focus on Philadelphia-based artists. Established February 2010, the gallery began as a project between co-founders and curators, Jason Chen and Sara McCorriston, as a space in which to create artwork, to exhibit the work of their peers, and to invite the members of the community to create and collect in a welcoming gallery setting. To this day the gallery still aims to welcome all collectors, from first time to lifelong, and continues to support accessible work that welcomes a wide audience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY: All international artists 18 and older, of all genders, ethnicities and from all backgrounds are welcome to apply. We accept works in any medium: painting, sculpture, digital, printmaking, fiber, photography, mixed media, installation and more. A university degree is not required to participate in our open call.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS: 3+ jpeg images, a text document with a bio and artist statement, website or social media link, email address. Please see form for further details.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED ARTISTS: Artists selected by the guest juror will receive a 2-page spread including a brief bio, website, and 2 images in print and digital formats. Published artists will receive a complimentary digital issue and will be listed with images, details and information on our website/social media for life. All featured artists will automatically be considered for any upcoming curatorial projects and exhibitions organized by our team. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHERE TO FIND: Copies will be available in our online shop and at several global retail locations in London, New York, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Amsterdam, Stockholm, Philadelphia, Ft. Lauderdale, Wilmington (DE), and more. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: March 31, 2019&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/50de7620-e494-4cbf-b742-8a3a3ed2183c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>77c3c30e-226c-4351-96d9-bb73a7135e36</id><title>3/12 - The Freedom Of Abstraction</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679443+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/12/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.sitebrooklyn.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Freedom of Abstraction&lt;br/&gt;May 3, 2019 – June 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The rise of abstraction meant freedom from the strictures and constraints of naturalism and representation. For some, it means stripping away the visual irrelevancies of nature in order to explore different subjects, an exploration of the artist’s own imagination, or finding the essential qualities a form observed in the real world. The freedom of abstraction rests on a paradox: the liberation of non-objective art often meant the new focus on order, form, and purity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE JUROR:&lt;br/&gt;Julia Halperin is executive editor of artnet News, where she oversees editorial operations for the world’s most widely read art news site and manages a staff of editors and writers in London, Berlin, and New York. Previously, she served as museums editor of The Art Newspaper, where she oversaw international coverage of museums and other major art institutions, and as news editor of Art + Auction magazine. Her writing has appeared in WIRED magazine, the New York Observer, and New York magazine. Halperin holds a BA in art history and English literature from Columbia University. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE GALLERY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DATES:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: February 6, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: March 12, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: March 21, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: May 3 – June 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, May 3, 2019 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in drawing, painting, printmaking, wall mounted sculpture, collage, and video.&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS AND FEES:&lt;br/&gt;Only original works may be submitted. The fee is $35.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by March 12, 2019 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;DIRECTIONS FOR ONLINE SUBMISSION: &lt;br/&gt;https://bit.ly/2MWjQKu&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PRESENTATION:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 60” X 60” X 12” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment.&lt;br/&gt;3. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. A label must be affixed to the back of the work that indicates which end is the top and includes the following: Artist Name, Title, Medium, Dimensions, and Price. This information must correspond with the Accepted image as listed on Notification form. No artwork may be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;5. Work cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SHIPPING:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;LIABILITY:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;SALES/COMMISSIONS:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;CONTACT/QUESTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ENTRY AGREEMENT:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Freedom of Abstraction” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2MWjQKu" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/77c3c30e-226c-4351-96d9-bb73a7135e36" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>5a34e246-8735-4838-9644-08539705565d</id><title>4/30 - Call for Papers: The Rachofsky Collection 2019 Graduate Symposium</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679416+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Rachofsky Collection&lt;br/&gt;📍 Dallas, TX, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://thewarehousedallas.org/education/the-rachofsky-collection-graduate-symposium-at-the-warehouse/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Rachofsky Collection announces an open call for submissions related to Japanese artist Jiro Takamatsu (1936-1998) for its 2019 Graduate Symposium at The Warehouse in Dallas, Texas. As an artist, teacher, and theorist, Takamatsu investigated the philosophical and material foundations of art in a variety of media, engaging with Minimalism through his background in Anti-Art and Neo-Dada. Takamatsu was a key member of the collective Hi Red Center (1963-1964) and of the movement Mono-Ha (1967-1979), and influential in developing conceptual art, performance art, and post-minimalism within Japan. &lt;br/&gt;	&lt;br/&gt;Students invited to present papers at the symposium will have the opportunity to access works in the collection during a two-day, partially-funded research visit during Summer 2019. Additionally, papers presented at the symposium will be published in a compendium together with the paper delivered by the keynote speaker, independent curator and writer Douglas Fogle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We invite master’s and doctoral students to present their scholarly work on a host of topics related to Jiro Takamatsu. Paper presentations should be 20 minutes in length. Complete proposals must include the following: &lt;br/&gt;•	A complete mailing address, email address, phone number, research field, and university affiliation of participant. &lt;br/&gt;•	Paper title and abstract of no more than 300 words that includes three to five keywords. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please visit our website for more information about the symposium, research visit, and for a list of works by Takamatsu in The Rachofsky Collection. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Send submissions and questions to caitlin@rachofskyhouse.org. Proposals are due by Tuesday, April 30, 2019. Successful applicants will be notified by May 15, 2019. Three students will be selected for the 2019 symposium.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5a34e246-8735-4838-9644-08539705565d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d4d10671-61f6-47ae-a3bd-bcc3ef01487e</id><title>4/1 - The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show - Open Call to Artists for Submissions</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679388+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Episcopal Church of the Heavenly Rest&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://heavenlyrest.wufoo.com/forms/z1hr8tsj0w3znbe/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Episcopal Church of the Heavenly Rest’s (CHR) new arts initiative’s mission is for CHR to shine as a community where artistic creativity of many forms is valued as a spiritual practice and a force for reconciliation. We aim to nurture artists, deepen our shared experience of their work, and invite the greater community of all faiths to explore our common humanity through the medium of art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CHR is hosting The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Theme: We All Belong&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Call for Submissions: We all draw inspiration from our communities. What does belonging mean to you?  We call on New York City artists to respond to the question and the community around them across media and styles. A committee will select works for the exhibition based on how well the artist responds to the theme within the criteria set forth in the registration form. Selected works will be exhibited at The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show.&lt;br/&gt;      &lt;br/&gt;Requirements: Open to New York City Artists (from one of the five boroughs) over the age of 21, work submitted must be appropriate for viewing of all ages. Submitted work must be complete and exhibition ready. To be considered, work must meet standards of quality determined by committee. Every work submitted must be accompanied by an artist contract provided by CHR at time of drop off. Artists must meet professional standards of composition and presentation of their work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Additional Information: The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show and opening reception will take place Thursday, May 9, 2019, 6 -8pm. Art will be exhibited in CHR’s Darlington Hall and Gallery Undercroft Exhibition Spaces from May 9 through September 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Instructions: submissions must be made online via the provided Registration Link or on the CHR website, &lt;a href="http://heavenlyrest.org/upcoming-events/" target="_blank"&gt;http://heavenlyrest.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d4d10671-61f6-47ae-a3bd-bcc3ef01487e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a41e6157-26d2-4ab9-91be-b2b1cef238ea</id><title>3/1 - Arcadia Earth 2019 - Calling All Sustainable Artists</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679358+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arcadia Earth&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.arcadia.earth"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ABOUT ARCADIA:&lt;br/&gt;Arcadia is a platform to raise awareness on sustainability through immersive art experiences, a solution driven marketplace and educational talks. Our mission is to gather like minded partners, brands, and organizations to create content and innovative sustainable solutions to connect with the new generation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THE OPPORTUNITY:&lt;br/&gt;We are looking for artists interested in creating immersive environment Installations to promote sustainability. The artwork will be displayed during a collective event. The event will be promoted with strong marketing strategy where all installations and their creators will be highlighted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THE INCENTIVES:&lt;br/&gt;- 3 grant levels: $2500, $5000, $7500. Apply to see what you qualify for.&lt;br/&gt;- Promotion and Marketing&lt;br/&gt;- Marketing Exposure - Social Media exposure &lt;br/&gt;- Arcadia web presence &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists will need to create immersive sustainable experiences by: &lt;br/&gt;1. Areas to Activate : activate an area of 15’ x 10’ more or less &lt;br/&gt;2. Materials used: upcycled / recycled / sustainable &lt;br/&gt;3. Messaging: sustainability and global warming&lt;br/&gt;4. Immersive/ Experiential: Teleport guests into an experiential and engaging environment using mixed media&lt;br/&gt;5. innovative: Use of new technologies such as Projection Mapping, VR, and AR&lt;br/&gt;6. Interactive: art experiences where guests can participate in creating or being part of the artwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSIONS&lt;br/&gt;Depending on the category artists will need to submit the following to Arcadia to review at ap@arcadia.earth :&lt;br/&gt;1.     IMMERSIVE / EXPERIENTIAL:&lt;br/&gt;	a. Example of the immersive installation (renderings, layout, photos etc.)&lt;br/&gt;	b. Materials being used&lt;br/&gt;	c.  A paragraph explaining the concept and message behind the piece&lt;br/&gt;2.     INNOVATIVE:&lt;br/&gt;	a. A link or video explaining the technology being used&lt;br/&gt;	b.  Materials being used (if applicable)&lt;br/&gt;	c.  A paragraph explaining the concept and message behind the piece&lt;br/&gt;3.     INTERACTIVE:&lt;br/&gt;	a.  A paragraph explaining the concept and message behind the piece&lt;br/&gt;	b.  A rendering/ reference of installation&lt;br/&gt;	c.  Materials being used&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a41e6157-26d2-4ab9-91be-b2b1cef238ea" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>30649a9c-30dc-490c-a495-2a8ca1788c18</id><title>3/11 - Sculptors Guild | Curator Call for Proposals</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679317+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sculptors Guild, Inc&lt;br/&gt;📍 NY, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sculptorsguild.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sculptors Guild&lt;br/&gt;Curator Call for Proposals&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Sculptors Guild is accepting curatorial proposals from emerging and established curators for consideration for Sculptors Guild member exhibition opportunities. We are looking for multiple curators for a number of upcoming opportunities in both indoor and outdoor, large-scale exhibition spaces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Sculptors Guild, an artist-run nonprofit 501c3 organization based in New York City, has had a vital presence for decades in New York City. Its mission is to promote, encourage, and serve as an advocate for sculpture and to make contemporary sculpture a relevant part of the cultural experience. It maintains a professional membership of acclaimed sculptors and is dedicated to the promotion of sculpture and sculptors through exhibitions and educational outreach programs. The Sculptors Guild has enjoyed a resurgence of interest by emerging sculptors of various divergent aesthetics. We are an alternative cultural institution, have a self-directed board, and are supported by our network of active artist participants.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A honorarium will be provided in exchange for curation, an essay and press release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PLEASE SUBMIT the following via  email with the Subject Line: Curatorial Proposal to SculptorsGuild@gmail.com:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1) A one page proposal maximum&lt;br/&gt;2) Resume&lt;br/&gt;3) 3-5 images or links to past projects&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Monday, March 11, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To view SG activities and member artwork please visit our website: &lt;a href="https://www.sculptorsguild.org" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.sculptorsguild.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;View DIGITAL CATALOGS of past exhibitions to get an overview of guild members at the following links:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2018 Catalog: politics of space&lt;br/&gt;http://www.blurb.com/bookstore/invited/7900789/0baae92e384e727bba47868a01973ce7d7766e5d&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2017 Catalog:    Currently 80&lt;br/&gt;https://www.sculptorsguild.org/s/CURRENTLY-80-CATALOG.pdf&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2016 Catalog:    American Twist&lt;br/&gt;https://www.sculptorsguild.org/s/2016-American-Twist-Catalog.pdf&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2015 Catalog:    Laws of Attraction&lt;br/&gt;https://www.sculptorsguild.org/s/2015-SG-LOA-CATALOG.pdf&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2014 Catalog:    Transformation&lt;br/&gt;https://www.sculptorsguild.org/s/SG_CATALOG_V18-ONLINE-nmwx.pdf&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/30649a9c-30dc-490c-a495-2a8ca1788c18" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7d83b0cc-d994-4918-8932-06554b023bea</id><title>&amp;quot;...dream again&amp;quot;  Open Call</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679072+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Secret Theatre in association with LIC Artists Inc&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.secrettheatre.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call for an LIC Arts Open collaboration with The Secret Theatre&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Hosted by LiC-A at the Plaxall Gallery and curated by Norma Homberg&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: The Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition on View: March 7th, 2019 to March 31st, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Reception: Saturday, March 9th, 7-10PM&lt;br/&gt;Mediums: Paintings, collage, and wall sculptures only. Please, no installation work.&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee: $15.00 for LiC-A members, $30.00 for non-members&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline : Friday, February 22, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition concept: &lt;br/&gt;When submitting to this exhibition running alongside the Secret Theatre’s production of William Shakespeare’s The Tempest, think darker shades of blues and purples. Think medium and larger scale work - small works will get lost in this exhibition. Your work will be part of an incredibly strong Fine Art Exhibition and sets the backdrop for a full length, immersive production of The Tempest while the play is in session in the evenings at the gallery. We are going for monochrome paintings, storm and magical realism. Please avoid overly 'busy' or “whimsy” artwork.&lt;br/&gt;The curator is also looking for artwork which would be specifically for Caliban’s cave. The cave has precious treasures stored in little nooks which Gallery visitors can open and explore.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This form is for artists to submit images of their work for consideration. The final selection of work will be determined by the curator.  To show your full range, we suggest submitting the maximum of five works. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission fee (non-refundable) is $30 for non-members, $15 for members.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS: Please include images of your work to be submitted using the instructions below:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s contact information (Note: address, email, phone will not be published)&lt;br/&gt;Up to 5 images, JPEGs only, under 1 MB each; 72dpi is adequate, image width not to exceed 1024 pixels on the longest side. Label each file as follows: LastName_FirstName_TitleOfWork.jpg. Example: Smith_Jane_Tranquility.jpg.&lt;br/&gt;Description of Work. Descriptions must include: Uploaded Title, date, medium, dimensions (H x W x D) price. For example: “Tranquility”, 2018, Oil on Linen, 20 x 16 inches, $700.00.&lt;br/&gt;Note: Artist's name, website, description of work and price will appear on exhibition wall labels exactly as entered in this form. Please proof your entries before submitting the form. No other personal information will be printed. Accepted artwork may be featured on our website.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DELIVERY DATES: all selected artwork must be delivered to the Plaxall Gallery: Saturday, March 2nd from 12-5PM, Sunday, March 3rd from 12-8PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION DEADLINE: Friday, February 22nd 11:59 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOTIFICATION OF ACCEPTANCE: February 26th&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PICK UP DATE: Sunday, March 31st 7th 5-8PM and Monday, April 1st 10AM-1: 30 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;OPENING RECEPTION: Saturday, March 9th, 7-10PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ADDRESS: Plaxall Gallery, 5-25 46th Avenue, Long Island City, Queens - between Vernon and 5th Street. The entrance to the gallery space is on the parking lot (west) side of the building at the second loading bay.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please e-mail info@licartists.org with any questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PLEASE APPLY HERE:  &lt;a href="http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_dream_again" target="_blank"&gt;http://licartists.formstack.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please do not reply to the email address listed here.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7d83b0cc-d994-4918-8932-06554b023bea" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d95ce4d5-ab1e-4bdf-b5fd-85db11907468</id><title>3/29 - Real Art Awards</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.679020+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Real Art Ways&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hartford, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/29/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.realartways.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emerging artists living and working in New England, New York or New Jersey who are no more than three years removed from a full-time educational program, or artists with less than five years of exhibition experience are eligible to apply to this call. Artists working in all media are welcome. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NO ENTRY FEE.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Six artists will receive: &lt;br/&gt;- $2,500 prize&lt;br/&gt;- Solo exhibit at Real Art Ways in 2019 or 2020&lt;br/&gt;- Exhibition publication with commissioned essay and documentation &lt;br/&gt;- Curatorial assistance&lt;br/&gt;- Opportunity for an artist talk&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JURORS: &lt;br/&gt;Terry Jenoure, Artist / Curator, Director, Augusta Savage Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Olu Oguibe, Artist / Critic&lt;br/&gt;Will K. Wilkins, Executive Director of Real Art Ways&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This project is supported in part by an award from the National Endowment for the Arts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and submission guidelines, including image and video requirements, download the submissions guide at realartways.org.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions?&lt;br/&gt;Please address questions to: Neil Daigle-Orians, Visual Arts Coordinator, norians@realartways.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d95ce4d5-ab1e-4bdf-b5fd-85db11907468" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8a524bd2-6c51-4841-91d0-ece1a125e9fc</id><title>2/20 - Call for Entries: Reimagining Region</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.678988+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Art School of Columbia County&lt;br/&gt;📍 Ghent, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.artschoolofcolumbiacounty.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reimagining Region: The Hudson Valley has been a site of intersecting cultures, movement, migration, environmental innovation, and resettlement. Artists have depicted and responded to this for generations, creating a rich regional artistic heritage.  In an upcoming juried show, the Art School of Columbia County is exploring the idea of region: its boundaries (real or perceived), the role of artists in documenting and defining region and identity, the concept of a regional school, and the connection between artists and community.&lt;br/&gt;Artists age 18 and up living or working in within a 100 mile radius of Ghent NY, are invited to apply to ASCC’s juried regional show exploring the theme of Reimagining Region.  &lt;br/&gt;Works will be selected for artistic merit and how they explore and relate to the selected theme.&lt;br/&gt;Selected artists may be chosen to participate in ASCC’s 5th annual ARTalks series, featuring a guided panel discussion and reception.  Work in the exhibit will be viewed as part of an educational program on Saturday, April 6, “Slow Art Day,” an international day held to promote mindfulness and deep engagement with art in museums and educational institutions.  An artists’ reception is April 6 from 5- 7 pm. The reception is free and open to the public and refreshments are served.&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Kate Menconeri, Curator/Director of Exhibitions and Collections, Thomas Cole National Historic Site (Catskill NY).  Ms. Menconeri has curated exhibits of both historical and contemporary artists, including collaborations with Kiki Smith.  She holds a MA is Curatorial Studies from Bard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All applicants: first submit application fee via this page: &lt;a href="http://artschoolofcolumbiacounty.org/product/application-for-juried-show-due-feb-20" target="_blank"&gt;http://artschoolofcolumbiacounty.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;OR, join as a member of ASCC&lt;br/&gt;OR submit indicating you are a current member.&lt;br/&gt;Joining as an ASCC member provides opportunities for 5 exhibits per membership year.&lt;br/&gt;Work may be for sale: 70% to the artist, 30% to ASCC.  NFS permitted, but no POR please.  &lt;br/&gt;Notification of accepted artworks: March 4, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Email up to 5 works only as JPGs to: artschoolofcolumbiacounty@gmail.com  subject line Juried Show 2019.  3-D work may submit one additional view of a submitted artwork.  Video applicants: link to up to 5 works online.  &lt;br/&gt;1) Include in the email up to 200 words stating how the body of submitted work relates to the theme of Reimagining Region.  &lt;br/&gt;2) Attach your artist’s CV/resume&lt;br/&gt;3) Save/title all images as: artist first initial, last name and number: e.g. Jane Smith = jsmith_1.jpg, jsmith_2.jpg, etc.&lt;br/&gt;Images must be no larger than 1200 pixels on the largest side and at no less than 75 dpi (300 dpi recommended).  The file size may not exceed 5MB.&lt;br/&gt;4) Within the body of the email, include for each work submitted the following details:&lt;br/&gt;Number of submission (e.g. 1-5)&lt;br/&gt;Title&lt;br/&gt;Medium&lt;br/&gt;Height/Width/Depth/Weight&lt;br/&gt;Year completed&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that all accepted works must be stable, and framed/mounted and wired for wall hanging.  For 3-D work and special installations, some pedestals are available at ASCC.  In some cases, ASCC may ask artists to provide a plain white or off-white pedestal. Video installation must provide their own equipment for viewing (no online access onsite at ASCC).  Please visit ASCC or call us for more information about our gallery spaces. In accordance with best curatorial practices, ASCC Board members and staff will not apply for consideration for juried shows.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;By US Mail: print  8 x 10″ images of up to 5 works for consideration plus additional requested information to ASCC, 1198 Rt 21 C, Ghent NY 12075.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Reception: Saturday April 6   5-7 pm.  All refreshments provided.&lt;br/&gt;Additional receptions for viewing work Sundays April 14 and 28 as part of ARTalks series.&lt;br/&gt;Pick-up: Thursday May 9  9 am – 6 pm or Saturday May 11 12- 4 pm&lt;br/&gt;Drop-off of accepted artwork: Thursday March 28 9 am – 5 pm (preferred) or appointments available on Saturday March 30.  If accepted, work must be hand delivered to and picked-up from ASCC.  We are unable to accept shipped works or courier services which leave packing materials behind.  Video installations must set-up and demonstrate work and provide written instructional sheet to ASCC staff.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8a524bd2-6c51-4841-91d0-ece1a125e9fc" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>ced35fb2-3427-4fee-8a35-b543c08bfd7c</id><title>2/22 - Open Call for an Exhibition Focusing on Experiences &amp;amp; Perspectives of Mental Health</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.678954+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Long Island City Arts (LIC-A)&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/22/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="www.licartists.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call for an Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;Focusing On Experiences &amp; Perspectives of Mental Health&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_inside_outside&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: The Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;                5-25 46th Avenue, Long Island City, NY 11101&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition on View: March 7th, 2019 to April 7th, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Reception: Saturday, March 9th, 7-10PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee: $20.00 for LiC-A members, $40.00 for non-members&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit artwork to &lt;a href="http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_inside_outside" target="_blank"&gt;http://licartists.formstack.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Mediums: All Mediums - original art or limited signed and numbered reproductions&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition concept: &lt;br/&gt;An open call for artwork reflecting the many experiences and perspectives of Mental Illness. Visually communicating Mindfulness, Contemplation, or Meditation, as well as the experience of healing, suffering, and the stigma of mental health from the outside looking in or from the inside looking out.  &lt;br/&gt;Artwork can reflect personal experience, journeys, depiction of mental health or what mental health means to you. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please e-mail info@licartists.org with any questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit Application to&lt;br/&gt;http://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_inside_outside &lt;br/&gt;or &lt;br/&gt;visit Long Island City Artist website  www.licartists.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All Mediums - original art or limited signed and numbered reproductions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ced35fb2-3427-4fee-8a35-b543c08bfd7c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>974a0855-7288-4deb-b724-c4dd7a79db87</id><title>4/1 - Juxtaposition: Contemporary Collage, A National Juried Art Exhibition</title><updated>2019-02-14T12:12:24.678890+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Barrett Art Center (Dutchess County Art Association)&lt;br/&gt;📍 Poughkeepsie, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juror: Marshall N. Price, Nancy Hanks Curator of Modern and Contemporary Art, Nasher Museum of Art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: April 1, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: Jun 8 – July 20, 2019 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$500 Juror’s Prize, $200 Second Prize, $125 Honorable Mention &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Barrett Art Center seeks submissions that explore contemporary collage.  Paper on paper is welcome however, given the overwhelming number of images and objects people are bombarded with each day, Barrett also welcomes submissions that use disparate objects, sources, and materials. This national juried exhibition welcomes all medias that encompass collage, assemblage, photomontage, digital collage, and mixed-media approaches that use found imagery, cut outs, typography, cut-and-paste, and installation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All submission through: &lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=6284" target="_blank"&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/974a0855-7288-4deb-b724-c4dd7a79db87" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>