<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-09T02:15:47-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>2bdbc21f-c68f-4fdc-9e2b-ac767f801759</id><title>4/30 - Art Installations for Art Hawaii International 2019</title><updated>2019-04-09T02:15:47.198883+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Art Hawaii International LLC&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.arthawaiifair.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ART HAWAII INTERNATIONAL: CALL TO ARTISTS for INSTALLATIONS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry deadline:                      April 30, 2019       &lt;br/&gt;Event Date:                            Nov 6-10, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Location:                                Honolulu, Hawaii &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Art Hawaii International:&lt;br/&gt;Art Hawaii International is a contemporary art fair with inaugural dates November 6-10, 2019, located in Honolulu at Hawaii Convention Center. The spectacular location will bring local visitors, as well as destination art travelers from around the world.&lt;br/&gt;AHI exhibitors include vetted international galleries, museums, art foundations, art publications, art films and art talks. The art fair program includes annual curatorial themes highlighting important subjects through art. AHI philosophy includes building better bridges to art knowledge for visitors through AHI proprietary app, kiosks and informational sources. We provide personal service for AHI attendees, especially Asia-centric visitors in their language, to obtain information on exhibitors and the artwork, to further cultivate art collectors, art lovers and art buyers.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Open to:&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Professional career artists, from any country worldwide, with exhibition history of no less than two years represented in an established contemporary gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Artists, from any country worldwide, who do not have gallery representation, but have an established history of creating professional artwork installations for no less than five years.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Art Installations:&lt;br/&gt;We are seeking immersive installations by artists to be exhibited in Art Hawaii International and public sites in Honolulu which align with the theme, “Art Ecosystem: Upcycled” (artwork created with upcycled, recycled, sustainable materials), as well as installations driven by technology, multi-media, light, sound, mapping, and immersive experiences. We are open to conceptual work influenced by environmental, political, social and cultural themes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Provided for the selected artists:&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  AHI to provide monetary allotment up to $1,000, depending upon the complexity, scale, dimension of work.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  AHI to provide the cost of shipping the artwork roundtrip, ($5,000 maximum), actual cost must be included in the proposal.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  AHI to provide one roundtrip coach airline ticket to Honolulu ($2,000 maximum) for the artist to install the artwork.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  AHI to provide three nights accommodation, ($200 per night maximum, $600 total) with other artists in Airbnb or other type of room accommodation.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Provided for selected artists who reside in Hawaii; must live and work in Hawaii year-round:&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  AHI to provide monetary allotment up to $2,500, depending upon the complexity, scale, dimension of work.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  AHI to provide the local cost of transporting the artwork roundtrip, actual cost must be included in the proposal&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  AHI to provide local Hawaii airfare and accommodation for artist if needed, three nights max.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Opportunity and promotion for the selected artists:&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Opportunity to sell the artwork installation (criteria listed below)&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Inclusion in press releases, social media, marketing&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Meet curators, collectors, galleries, artists and individuals in the art world&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Opportunity for artists to experience the art fair within the incredible location of Oahu, Waikiki Beach and proximity to visit other islands of Hawaii.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Space provided for the artwork:&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Artwork Installation area, approximate footprint size can range from 10 x 10 feet (3 x 3 meters), up to 30 x 30 feet (9 x 9 meters).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Criteria:&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  The artwork installation must not have been shown in more than one other art fair.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Artist shall be responsible, if the artwork installation sells at AHI, with their own invoice, installation cost to be determined for the final destination, insurance coverage, and any other artist business costs associated with managing the sales transaction. The artwork will be sold to client from the artist, not through AHI.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  If selected, the artist shall receive an agreement with an outline of responsibilities and deadline for shipment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSION PROCESS:  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Two methods to submit&lt;br/&gt;01. Email artistcall@arthawaiifair.com with a link to Dropbox, Google drive, Vimeo to submit files&lt;br/&gt;OR&lt;br/&gt;02. Email artistcall@arthawaiifair.com with attachments and/or links, not to exceed the file sizes indicated below&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Each email submission must have the following in the subject line: [Artist name], City &lt;br/&gt;&gt;  title of artwork installation&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Provide written information on the concept, process, materials used (2 pages maximum).&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Jpgs, Tiff, Png (3mb maximum each) and/or video links to view artwork installation, 15 images maximum. Include detail images, close-up of artwork installation. Include artist name, title, year, size, dimensions.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Provide artist bio, exhibition history and any other artist background information (no more than 5 pages, pdf).&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Provide shipping cost roundtrip, cannot exceed $5,000 inclusive with packing, crating, shipping and insurance. For international origination, professional shipper is required to manage documentation, customs, and potential shipping ATA Carnet.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Provide information on how the installation will be packed and unpacked. Include time required to install and to deinstall (how many hours for each phase).&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Provide information on medium and vulnerability of the artwork if exposed to light, heat, movement, and/or touch.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Indicate if the artwork installation can be indoors and/or outdoors.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Provide information on any special display requirements (darkness, light, hanging, height, barriers, other).&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Include if and where the artwork installation has been exhibited previously. Such as a gallery, public site, or other art fair.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Include any other history on the artwork installation and if it exists in other iterations, medium and/or editions, and location where it exists.&lt;br/&gt;&gt;  Include the price of the artwork installation, if it is for sale.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Due to the overwhelming response to this Artist Call, if you have any questions, please send by email to artistcall@arthawaiifair.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2bdbc21f-c68f-4fdc-9e2b-ac767f801759" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9ed968de-d801-4861-87b9-0b89ab50d73d</id><title>5/13 - Wave Hill Sunroom Project Space Open Call</title><updated>2019-04-09T02:15:47.198838+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wave Hill&lt;br/&gt;📍 Bronx, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/13/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.wavehill.org/arts/submission-guidelines/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wave Hill announces a Call to Artists for its 2020 Sunroom Project Space Program. The Sunroom Project Space is a venue for New York-area emerging artists to develop a site-specific project as a solo exhibition at Wave Hill. For 2020, we are starting a new initiative—a commission for an outdoor Sunroom Project that will take place every other year. The three exhibition spaces for 2020 are the windowed Sunroom, windowed Sun Porch (both in Glyndor Gallery) and an outdoor area that is visible from the gallery. Applicants must indicate indoor or outdoor location.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists are encouraged to respond to and engage with these unique spaces. We are also seeking artist projects that are participatory or interactive and engage Wave Hill’s surrounding communities of Riverdale, the Bronx, and New York City.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Four artists will be selected for solo shows that will be on view indoors for six weeks each from April through November 2020. For the indoor exhibition, work in all media will be considered. Selected artists will receive an honorarium of $1,800 and have 6 to 12 months to develop their ideas and create new work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A fifth artist will be selected for the outdoor area for summer 2020. For this outdoor installation, we ask that the work is constructed to withstand the elements and visitor interaction. The selected artist will receive an honorarium of $4000.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility: Open to emerging artists with a record of solid achievement and potential, for whom this opportunity might contribute to professional advancement, and who are not represented by a commercial gallery, not a student, and have not previously shown at Wave Hill. Because we encourage artists to spend time at Wave Hill developing their ideas, artists should live within a 50-mile radius of the Bronx.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An information session will be held at Wave Hill on Saturday, April 13 at 3 pm. Attendance is not mandatory to apply, but strongly encouraged. RSVP for the info session by e-mailing sunroomproject@wavehill.org.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists can submit applications using our online applications portal, SlideRoom, and must submit the following:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1.	Application with an artist statement, preliminary concept and indication of indoor or outdoor location&lt;br/&gt;2.	Résumé &lt;br/&gt;3.	Up to 10 work samples with optional concept drawing&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The deadline is May 13, 2019. For more information and to submit an application, please go to &lt;a href="https://www.wavehill.org/arts/submission-guidelines/." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.wavehill.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications will be reviewed by a jury that includes Wave Hill’s Curator of Visual Arts, an invited curator, and a previous Sunroom artist. The jury will develop a short list of artists for the curator to meet with for an interview. The curatorial staff will balance approaches and schedules to make a final selection. Decisions will be made by August 2019, and all artists will be contacted at that time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Interested artists are strongly encouraged to visit Wave Hill before applying.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Contact sunroomproject@wavehill.org or 718-549-3200, x397.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9ed968de-d801-4861-87b9-0b89ab50d73d" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b2ea629b-a3e3-47f1-ab47-b39f595a25c2</id><title>4/19 - Dusklit: Interactive Art Festival- 2019 Call for Art</title><updated>2019-04-09T02:15:47.198780+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dusklit: Interactive Art Festival&lt;br/&gt;📍 Sugar Loaf, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.dusklit.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dusklit is the East Coast's one night interactive art festival. With twilight as a backdrop, Dusklit features over 25 immersive installations, performances, and site-specific environments. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Now in its fourth year, Dusklit 2019 will take place Saturday, July 20, 5-9PM.  Past Dusklit projects include all media, from site-specific dance and sound art to life-size kinetic sculpture, VR, interactive plays, sensory deprivation chambers, and many other offerings. See www.dusklit.com for past festivals. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dusklit is presented outdoors on the historic Seligmann Homestead in Sugar Loaf, New York. Once home to the Surrealist Kurt Seligmann, and frequented by Marcel Duchamp, Kay Sage, and Max Ernst, the property carries a history of art and magic. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dusklit is organized by artists Cody Rounds and Olivia Baldwin.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CALL FOR ART&lt;br/&gt;Artists of all disciplines are invited to propose immersive or otherwise interactive projects for Dusklit 2019. Projects may take the  form of a roving performance/installation, or a stationary environment/installation/performance. Visitor participation must be essential to the work. Projects in which visitors act exclusively as audience will not be considered. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dusklit 2019 will take place outdoors on Saturday, July 20, 5-9pm, before, during, and after sunset. Artists should consider how the changing light of dusk will affect their project, and visitors' engagement with it.  All projects occur throughout the duration of the event (with artist breaks). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Due to the close proximity of installations, music and sound must be contained within ten feet of artists' plots.  PA systems are prohibited.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For full details, visit dusklit.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application deadline: Friday, April 19, 11:59PM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit dusklit.com to apply&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b2ea629b-a3e3-47f1-ab47-b39f595a25c2" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>