<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml</id><title>open-calls-7</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>a12d98a6-2663-4f00-9883-35efc4c72c9e</id><title>2/24 - La Bodega Gallery looking for portrait art</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.117015+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;La Bodega Art Space and Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/24/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.labodegastudios.com/opencall"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contemporary portraiture takes many forms and encompasses countless conceptual viewpoints, mediums and techniques that explore a myriad of subject matter. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At La Bodega Art Space and Gallery we are currently accepting submissions for the contemporary portraiture exhibition entitled (DE)PICT. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This open call is open to both emerging and established artists who create works of portraiture in any style or medium.  For this open call we are inviting to demonstrate their creative approach to portraiture. Portraits can be figurative, abstract or conceptual.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition dates: March 6th – April 5th,  2020&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline:  February 24th, 2020   11:59:59 pm&lt;br/&gt;Location: La Bodega Gallery, 695 5th Ave Brooklyn, NY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please follow the instructions to apply by visiting our website.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.labodegastudios.com/opencall&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a12d98a6-2663-4f00-9883-35efc4c72c9e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9a6d0b56-9c6e-4e46-a02b-23c2dad974e1</id><title>Open Call for Solo Show or Group Show curatorial proposals</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116937+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open&lt;br/&gt;📍 LIC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply to curate or exhibit at The Gallery LIC, a premier 2000 sq. foot art-space in the heart of New York located in The Factory. We are seeking curators and artist-curators for solo and group shows.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Successful applicants will be notified within 4 weeks of submission and will have 1 week to confirm. Exhibition contribution fee for confirmed shows is $500. This fee will cover curatorial support, installation, hospitality, signage and promotion. Exhibitions will run for three weeks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application fee $30&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note that all work must be hand-delivered to the Factory and ready to hang. Therefore, while we encourage artists from outside of the NYC metro-area to apply, please be aware we cannot accept work that is shipped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply with this form.  The form requires images.  If you are not sure which images would be relevant please submit an image from a previous show or exhibition:&lt;br/&gt;Please cut and paste into your browser:&lt;br/&gt;https://form.jotform.com/trimistopheles/-call-for-group-or-solo-show-partic&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9a6d0b56-9c6e-4e46-a02b-23c2dad974e1" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e72aaac9-74a6-4957-947b-2932322a06a4</id><title>3/23 - Call for Artists: Superfine! Art Fair | NYCx2: Myth</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116908+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Superfine! Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/23/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/sell-surreal-art-in-nyc"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists: there's a better way.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Level up your career. Learn how to build sales and a collector list from our marketing experts. Curate to sell with our friendly guidelines, and meet your next collector at our fair dedicated entirely to surrealist artists. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: 408 Broadway, New York, NY 10013&lt;br/&gt;Fair dates: April 30 - May 3, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: March 23, 2020. Booths are selling quickly, so we recommend applying early! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A whole year of exhibitions in one weekend.&lt;br/&gt;- 4-6,000 motivated, art-hungry visitors during the four days of the fair.&lt;br/&gt;- 25% of our visitors make a significant ($100-$2,500+) art purchase.&lt;br/&gt;- More than 50% of our exhibiting artists receive major media coverage.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Make art. Sell art. We do the rest.&lt;br/&gt;- Meet your next collectors in a friendly, welcoming space: the ideal environment to discover, collect, and sell art.&lt;br/&gt;- Innovative cost-saving and cost-spreading financing options that work with every artist's budget to make exhibiting and selling a reality.&lt;br/&gt;- Serious opportunities for features in Superfine!'s earned (press + PR), owned (website, blog, and social), and paid (advertising) media.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: Superfine! takes no commission on any artwork sold either in person at the fair or via our online E-Fair.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You’re the art-making expert. We’re the art-marketing experts.&lt;br/&gt;- The smartest and most sophisticated marketing engine in the industry: we get the eyes you want in front of your work. Our audience is 26-45, affluent ($120k+/year), and buying art now.&lt;br/&gt;- We're top drawer: a professional, courteous, and knowledgeable team of experts guiding you every step of the way. Exhibit and sell your work, and gain champions of your career.&lt;br/&gt;- Lead-up webinars and curatorial guidelines geared towards success. Take what you learn with you and make it work for you year-round.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Get to Know Us&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Founded by art collectors Alex Mitow and James Miille, Superfine! started out in 2015 as an alternative to boring, stuffy art shows and complicated art world politics. From the start, we caught flack from the art establishment when we broke down barriers and opened the gates to everyone from serious long-time art collectors to people who just love art and never thought they’d collect. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As it turned out, nobody cared about the art world and their politics. Our open and transparent approach worked: imaginations have been sparked and countless new collections have been jump-started at Superfine! fairs as we continue to spread our message of a more inclusive art market across the country. Since 2015, we’ve had one goal: produce badass, expertly curated art shows where über-talented, diverse global artists meet their new fans in iconic locations across the US and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have questions? Get in touch with us at exhibit@superfine.world. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Limited booth availability for our NYCx1: (wo)man and NYCx3: Magick shows -- dedicated entirely to female and LGBTQ+ artists respectively. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NYCx1: (wo)man: www.superfine.world/an-nyc-art-fair-for-female-artists&lt;br/&gt;NYCx3: Magick: www.superfine.world/magick&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e72aaac9-74a6-4957-947b-2932322a06a4" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d56185ea-3bd9-4823-9b13-b640ce802929</id><title>3/23 - New Media</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116880+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/23/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $37.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Media&lt;br/&gt;May 1, 2020– May 30, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn’s New Media exhibition is seeking artwork that explores artistic applications of new media and technologies as well as work that examines the relationship between media, technology, and culture. This includes video, digital, sound, animation, virtual reality, and all other new technologies. We are looking for work that does not conform to traditional boundaries of form, medium, or genre.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror:&lt;br/&gt;Yuge Zhou is a Chinese-born, Chicago-based digital artist and curator. As a curator, she directs the 3300-square foot 150 Media Stream, one of the largest new media and video art installations in Chicago since its launch in 2017. In this capacity, she has worked with over forty established and emerging media artists and institutions to create innovative programming each month that engages a cross-section of diverse communities.&lt;br/&gt;As an artist, she has exhibited her work nationally and internationally including a recent solo exhibition at Site:Brooklyn which was featured on HYPEBEAST. Her work has been the subject of various articles in such publications as New York Magazine, The Huffington Post, and Whitehot Magazine of Contemporary Art. Zhou received the 2017 Santo Foundation Individual Artist Award. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Gallery:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: February 15, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: March 23, 2020 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: April 1, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: May 1, 2020– May 30, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, May 1, 2020 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in all media. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Submissions and Fees:&lt;br/&gt;Only original work may be submitted. The fee is $37.00 for up to three (3) images or videos, $10 for each additional image or video. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by March 23, 2020 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Directions For Online Submission: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3bAhkpr" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Presentation:&lt;br/&gt;Media and video work must include all equipment. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shipping:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring the artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Liability:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Sales/Commissions:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Contact/Questions:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Entry Agreement:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “New Media” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3bAhkpr" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d56185ea-3bd9-4823-9b13-b640ce802929" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>48aff687-5ebb-49b4-bb96-5f968dd8a971</id><title>3/11 - Taking Pictures: 2020</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116855+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/11/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo with an open theme at Black Box Gallery. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/48aff687-5ebb-49b4-bb96-5f968dd8a971" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8affb02a-29ba-49be-979f-a747ee433f81</id><title>2/28 - Call For Artists: The Other Art Fair Chicago</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116829+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Other Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 Chicago, IL, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/28/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://chicago.theotherartfair.com/applications"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Other Art Fair returns to Chicago this summer for its third edition in a brand new, brilliant location, Skylight at the Board of Trade Chicago, May 27-30 2020  The Other Art Fair provides a unique platform for artists to showcase their work to gallerists, curators, critics and collectors. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Presented by leading online gallery Saatchi Art, the fair is recognized as the definitive place for buyers to discover exciting and emerging talent. In addition to artwork sales, these four days enable artists to launch their work in the contemporary art world, gauge the public’s response to their pieces and meet fellow artists for potential future collaborations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As part of our exciting collaboration with leading online gallery Saatchi Art, exhibitors will be presented as fair artists to an extensive network of curators, collectors, interior designers and international buyers via saatchiart.com/theotherartfair, social media and the Canvas blog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online now: &lt;a href="http://chicago.theotherartfair.com/applications" target="_blank"&gt;http://chicago.theotherartfair.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Deadline for applications: February 28, 2020&lt;br/&gt;There is no application fee. Stand fees start at $1,680 + sales tax.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions? Please contact Sasha Ali, Fair Assistant, sasha@theotherartfair.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8affb02a-29ba-49be-979f-a747ee433f81" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8185509b-3329-4089-b124-3c024549ab79</id><title>2/28 - OyG Projects: Open Call for Two Solo Exhibitions</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116801+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ortega y Gasset Projects&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/28/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.oygprojects.com/open-call-2020"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ortega y Gasset Projects is pleased to announce an Open Call for TWO Solo Exhibitions to open in September of 2020: one in the main gallery space at OyG and one in The Skirt, OyG's dedicated space for site-specific installation.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Both opportunities will include an opening reception on Saturday, September 12, 2020, $400 honorarium for each artist/proposal, and one programmed event (an artist talk or a closing event), and will be promoted on OyG social media outlets. OyG Co-Directors will work with the artists and make studio visits leading up to the opening of the exhibitions, if possible. The artists are required to fully participate in the exhibitions' installation and deinstallation.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Visual artists of all disciplines (and geographical locations) are encouraged to apply. The artists will be selected by the OyG Co-Directors based on the quality of their work and commitment to their practice. Artists are highly encouraged to specify which space they'd like to exhibit in, the main gallery space or The Skirt. The OyG Co-Directors will make the final decision.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An alternate list of candidates/runners-up will be posted on our website and considered for future programing at the gallery. Past/future exhibition artists that we discovered from our past Open Calls include: Cameron Granger, KT Duffy, Patrice Helmar, Jihyun Hong, Familien Iglesias,  Carl E. Hazlewood, Rose Nestler, Norm Paris, Ben Pederson, Padma Rajendran, Adam Liam Rose, Winnie Sidharta and Kuldeep Singh.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To see images of the space:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.oygprojects.com/spatial-specs&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline:&lt;br/&gt;Friday, March 13, 2020, Midnight, EST&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Opening reception: Saturday, September 12, 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ortega y Gasset Projects is an artist-run gallery founded in 2013, located within the Old American Can Factory building in the Gowanus section of Brooklyn. OACF is a 24-hour access building accessible by the D, R, N, W, F, G trains. For more information about OyG click here. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eleanna Anagnos (Mexico City / Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Clare Britt (Chicago, IL)&lt;br/&gt;Eric Hibit (Queens, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Leeza Meksin (NY, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Adam Liam Rose (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Nickola Pottinger (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Tiffany Smith (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Zahar Vaks (Brooklyn, NY)&lt;br/&gt;Lauren Whearty (Philadelphia, PA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IMAGES:&lt;br/&gt;10 images of work including: title, year, media and dimensions&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Size requirements:  Images (up to 5MB each), Video (up to 250MB each), Audio (up to 30MB each)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CV:&lt;br/&gt;2 pages max&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;REFERENCES:&lt;br/&gt;Please provide us with two references who can talk about your work and practice: name, title/organization, relationship, email address. We will only contact these individuals if need be.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PROPOSAL:&lt;br/&gt;Please describe your work and what you envision as your solo exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some things to consider: Why do you want a solo exhibition at OyG? What does this opportunity mean to you? If you're applying for the Skirt, please consider how your work will respond to/interact with the specific space.&lt;br/&gt;(300 words max).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please email oygsubmissions@gmail.com if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8185509b-3329-4089-b124-3c024549ab79" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6de99c11-d931-4922-bdc5-1598e724eafa</id><title>2/27 - 300K people per day - Port Authority Bus Terminal- TIMES SQUARE</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116771+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Six Summit Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/27/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.sixsummitgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Six Summit Gallery, a diverse fine art gallery with presence in the most prestigious markets in New York,&lt;br/&gt;Los Angeles, Miami and CT announce  a new temporary gallery on the First Floor Lobby of Port Authority Bus Terminal, the busiest bus station in the world, servicing nearly 100 Million people annually.  SSG has already installed 30 pieces of art and sculpture on the second floor south.  We are encouraging large art and wonderful proactive artists who will help turn this extraordinary opportunity into a must see location in NYC.  This gallery will be enclosed with a massive sculpture hanging outside on the opposite wall creating a striking and welcoming space. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About SSG- Fine Art Executive Direction and  Curation in largest markets including New York, Los Angeles and Miami. Current unprecedented installation in Hudson Yards, Port Authority NY, Dag Hammarskjold Plaza, Chelsea NY, Palm Beach, Miami, Art Basel, Ivoryton CT, Clinton CT. Curator Art Hearts Fashion,&lt;br/&gt;NY, LA and Miami, (largest ongoing multi location fine art and fashion platform in America)&lt;br/&gt;Venues/Charities have included- Saks Fifth Avenue, Pier 61 Chelsea, SBE Hotels- Delano, SLS LUX, &lt;br/&gt;Shore Club, YAI, African Wildlife Foundation, Chamard Vineyards,The Leo House, &lt;br/&gt;Make-A-Wish Foundation, The Yale Club, Middlesex Hospital, Wadsworth Atheneum and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit entries to port@sixsummitgallery.com SUBMISSIONS: All work will be judged by EMAIL ENTRY via port@sixsummitgallery.com. You MUST write [YOUR NAME]” IN THE SUBJECT OF EMAIL. YOUR NAME MUST BE THE SAME ON YOUR CREDIT/DEBIT CARD Example: Subject: HIGH LINE SUBMISSION: John Doe. Files must be in .jpg format, 300 dpi, max 900 pixels in any dimension. File name should correspond to the title of the piece. PUT title, medium, artist, price, and size as JPEG FILE EXTENSION NAME.!  No accepted work may be removed prior to the show’s conclusion. No work for sale on the property. Sales can be done offsite.  Sculptors must bring their own pedestals or free standing is OK  You are required to make your own labels- 4"x6" with SSG Logo. They must include Title, Medium,Price, and Your Name, @SixSummitGallery – with "Call or text our curator Leo @ 917-573-0029 #SIX SUMMITGALLERY" clearly visible on the bottom below. Purchases can take place on our website and ongoing.  The Show Committee reserves the right to disallow the exhibition of any work or artist, which, in the opinion of the Committee, is considered detrimental to the good public image of the show and its sponsors, art which is too fragile to handle, or which is not accurately represented by the photo submitted. Six Summit Gallery, We reserve the right to photograph work or use submitted images to help yours and our publicity. ENTRY FEES: Easily click on www.sixsummitgallery.com online store and go to PURCHASES- ART/SUBMISSION/TICKETS/EVENTS/ARTIST CALLS section and choose THE DOLLAR AMOUNT THAT CORRESPONDS TO YOUR ENTRY up to 4 submissions  for $50 (there is not a description of submission, only a dollar amount, we will know what show it is for) Please call 917-573-0029 with any special situations.   Art must be WIRED and ready to hang, very large work is OK, up to 50 pounds ok unless its sculpture QUESTIONS CAN BE EMAILED ONLY TO: port@sixsummitgallery.com Include your Call Back Number! DO NOT CALL OR EMAIL PORT AUTHORITY DEADLINE to Submit- Feb 27th  Delivery: will be announced.  Show duration and gallery hours will  be fluid, artists will be up at least one month and we may rotate the shows.  We are also looking for some artists to collaborate with media, promote, help, and possibly gallery sit for this once in a lifetime installation. All are subject to the rules and etiquette of Port Authority Bus Terminal and Six Summit Gallery, which will be sent upon acceptance.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6de99c11-d931-4922-bdc5-1598e724eafa" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7da7b7c4-33be-415f-9ec8-a8c216b40c4b</id><title>3/22 - National Open Call Visual Artists &amp;quot;Far &amp;amp; Wide &amp;quot;</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116718+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Woodstock Artists Association &amp;amp; Museum&lt;br/&gt;📍 Woodstock, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/22/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.woodstockart.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists are invited to submit up to five works that show deft handling of materials and clarity of vision. Our jurors will be looking for work, of any genre, that reflects both a vigorous studio practice and thoughtful glimpse into the artist’s inner life. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JURORS: Jackie Hoving and Andrew Prayzner,&lt;br/&gt;Co-directors, Tiger Strikes Asteroid, New York&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AWARDS: Arthur Harris Best in Show, $500&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for applications: March 22, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Notifications to artists (via e-mail): April 1&lt;br/&gt;Intake for accepted work at WAAM: Monday, May 11, 12:00 - 6:00 pm&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: May 16 - June 14&lt;br/&gt;Artists Reception: Saturday, May 23, 4-6pm&lt;br/&gt;Jurors' Talk - Saturday, June 6 at 4PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Introduced in 2017, FAR &amp; WIDE National is open to artists living anywhere in the United States. Because of its importance in the WAAM program as our flagship national show, the jurors are paramount to this exhibit and they alone establish the framework used to choose the work. This year’s jurors, Jackie Hoving and Andrew Prayzner, Co-directors of Tiger Strikes Asteroid, New York, are part of a national collective and run the TSA space in NYC, presenting a varied program with the goal of collectively bringing people together, expanding connections and building community through artist-initiated exhibitions, projects, and curatorial opportunities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Jurors&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Andrew Prayzner from Tiger Strikes Asteroid&lt;br/&gt;Andrew Prayzner is an artist, educator, and co-director of Tiger Strikes Asteroid NY. He has twice been a resident at Yaddo and holds an MFA from the University of Pennsylvania, and a BFA from the University of Hartford. Based in Brooklyn, NY, he has participated in numerous national and international group exhibitions including the Aldrich Museum (Ridgefield, CT), Housatonic Museum of Art (Bridgeport, CT), The Wassaic Project (Wassaic, NY), Scotty Projects (Berlin, Germany) and SFA Projects (New York, NY).  In the summer of 2015, Andrew was a resident at Studio Kura in Fukuoka, Japan. He concluded the residency with a solo exhibition of nocturnal drawings titled One Hundred Views of Nothing. In 2016, a solo exhibition titled Horizontals was presented in the project space at Morgan Lehman (New York, NY).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jackie Hoving from Tiger Strikes Asteroid&lt;br/&gt;Jackie Hoving lives and works in Brooklyn, NY. As a current co-Director of Tiger Strikes Asteroid in Brooklyn she has had the opportunity to curate several shows and was included in the Artist Run Satellite Show in Miami. Her Solo Show at Ripon College titled Presence included a large wall mural installation and portraits. She was also included in a traveling exhibition titled In Search Of… at Rhodes College, University of Kansas and then in Bushwick, NY at TSA Gallery. Her work was on view in shows at Storefront Gallery in Brooklyn and a show at the Drawing Museum in Sweden. Her solo-show at Rebekah Templeton Gallery in Philadelphia, titled Crypsis, featured two large wall mural installations that incorporated painting, printmaking, wallpaper, animation and collage. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists may submit up to 5 images (jpgs).  &lt;br/&gt;Works in the following media will be considered:&lt;br/&gt;-Painting&lt;br/&gt;-Drawing&lt;br/&gt;-Original Prints &lt;br/&gt;-Photography&lt;br/&gt;-Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;2-D works should not exceed 36" on the longest dimension (38 inches including frame). 3-D work must be no greater than 36 x 36 x 36". &lt;br/&gt;All work should be in good condition and ready to hang or install. Any special installation needs must be supplied by the artist for the duration of the show and should be noted in submission. All work must be the original conception and execution of the artist listed. No reproductions. WAAM reserves the right to reject works that do not comply with these guidelines or are otherwise found to be unsuitable for display.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Delivery of Accepted Artwork &lt;br/&gt;Artists living more than 50 miles from Woodstock are responsible for shipping their accepted work in sturdy, reusable boxes. Work must arrive by Monday, May 11, 2020 or it will not be included in the show. Please provide a barcoded preprinted PREPAID shipping label for the return shipping. WAAM will not be held responsible for any damage that occurs in transit.&lt;br/&gt;Artists living within driving distance of WAAM may hand-deliver accepted work or designate someone else to deliver it for them. Hand delivered work must be picked-up after the exhibition ends. Pick-up day is Monday, June 15, 12-6PM. Storage fees will be applied after that date. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sales &amp; Insurance&lt;br/&gt;The WAAM will encourage sales and takes a 40% commission. Artists should fill in retail price (including commission) on entry form. The WAAM provides insurance for works of art while on the premises. Artist is responsible for insurance covering loss or damage during shipping.&lt;br/&gt;Application fee: $15 for members/$35 for non-members&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions may be addressed to diane@woodstockart.org or by calling: 845-679-2940 x102&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This link will send applicants directly to our submissions page on Submittables.&lt;br/&gt;https://woodstockartistsassociationmuseum.submittable.com/submit&lt;br/&gt;For more information applicants may wish to view details art our website:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.woodstockart.org/far-wide-national-2020/&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7da7b7c4-33be-415f-9ec8-a8c216b40c4b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>abc1ea0f-20ad-4b23-b359-b30cef3fe6a0</id><title>2/28 - NYC-  HIGH LINE- West  CHELSEA Open Studios Tour - Over 50 stops on the Tour</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116690+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Leo House NYC/Six Summit Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/28/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.sixsummitgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HIGH LINE OPEN STUDIOS GRAND TOUR IN CHELSEA (Over 50 participants throughout Chelsea) AT &lt;br/&gt;THE LEO HOUSE - 332 W 23RD ST, NYC (between 8th and 9th Ave)-  High Line Salon&lt;br/&gt;This spring the High Line Open Studios presents its annual West Chelsea Gallery district artists’ open studios event Saturday and Sunday, March 7-8, 2020, in conjunction with the Armory Show at the Piers 92-94, March 5-8, 2020. &lt;br/&gt;Participation in West Chelsea Open Studios tour at the coolest NYC hotel/guesthouse you may have never heard of, on legendary 23rd ST west of the Chelsea Hotel and at the beginning of historic Chelsea Art District. We will have two opening receptions  March 7th and 8th from 12:00 - 6PM at 332 W 23rd St at&lt;br/&gt;The Leo House, which was established in 1889 by Pope Leo XIII whose miter and 8 other antiquities were  featured at The Met show "Heavenly Bodies: Fashion and the Catholic Imagination" with Vogue, Cardinal Gianfranco Ravasi, Donatella Versace, and Anna Wintour. We will be accepting both religious (non ironic) and non religious art. Prizes - Art will keep hanging  for sale for up to 8 weeks or more.  We will be donating portions of our proceeds of sales to The Leo House. Artists receive 50% of sales.  If you wish to donate all or portions of your submissions please specify upon submitting.......   See below for submission instructions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EMAIL LEOHOUSE@SIXSUMMITGALLERY with any questions.  Please do not call The Leo House, High Line, or West Chelsea Open Studios &lt;br/&gt;........................................................................................................................................................................................&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK Submit entries to leohouse@sixsummitgallery.com SUBMISSIONS:All work will be judged by EMAIL ENTRY via leohouse@sixsummitgallery.com. You MUST write [YOUR NAME]” IN THE SUBJECT OF EMAIL. YOUR NAME MUST BE THE SAME ON YOUR CREDIT/DEBIT CARD Example: Subject: HIGH LINE SUBMISSION: John Doe. Files must be in .jpg format, 300 dpi, max 900 pixels in any dimension. File name should correspond to the title of the piece. PUT title, medium, artist, price, and size as JPEG FILE EXTENSION NAME.!  No accepted work may be removed prior to the show’s conclusion. ALL work must be for sale. Sculptors must bring their own pedestals or free standing is OK (We also have room for sculpture in the outdoor garden- please specify if your work can be outside) You are required to make your own labels. They must include Title, Medium,Price, and Your Name, www.sixsummitgallery.com – with "Call or text our curator Leo @ 917-573-0029 #SIX SUMMITGALLERY" clearly visible on the bottom below. Purchases will take place during the show  on our website and ongoing.  Customers can leave with art. The Show Committee reserves the right to disallow the exhibition of any work or artist, which, in the opinion of the Committee, is considered detrimental to the good public image of the show and its sponsors, art which is too fragile to handle, or which is not accurately represented by the photo submitted. Six Summit Gallery, We reserve the right to photograph work or use submitted images to help yours and our publicity. ENTRY FEES: Easily click on www.sixsummitgallery.com online store and go to PURCHASES- ART/SUBMISSION/TICKETS/EVENTS/ARTIST CALLS section and choose THE DOLLAR AMOUNT THAT CORRESPONDS TO YOUR ENTRY up to 3 submissions for $35 or 5 submissions for $50 (there is not a description of submission, only a dollar amount, we will know what show it is for) Please call 917-573-0029 with any special situations.   Art must be WIRED and ready to hang and not exceed 48" by 48" or 30 pounds unless its sculpture QUESTIONS CAN BE EMAILED ONLY TO: leohouse@sixsummitgallery.com Include your Call Back Number! DO NOT CALL OR EMAIL THE LEO HOUSE DEADLINE to Submit- Feb 27th  Delivery: is March 7th at 10AM. We will announce Removal:&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/abc1ea0f-20ad-4b23-b359-b30cef3fe6a0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3c2526e3-f3d3-4833-9762-c7322fb286d1</id><title>3/20 - Mark Arts Abstract National Exhibition</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116663+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Mark Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 WICHITA, KS, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Painting&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/20/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.markartsks.com/callforartists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark Arts invites all North American artists to apply for the Abstract National Exhibition, May 8 – July 11, 2020. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists may submit any two-dimensional abstract, nonrepresentational works in any media including&lt;br/&gt;watercolor, oil, gouache, photographs, acrylics, inks, prints, graphite, etching, charcoal, pastel, collage, pencil, mixed media and others (excluding installation art). Artwork must have been created in the past two years. Works must be display ready with hardware included. Wrapped canvases are permitted. All entries must be for sale.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The juror is Roberta Dyer, an artist who lives and works in San Diego, California. She has enjoyed many forms of expression from sculpture to copper enameling and oil painting to mural assignments. Today, she focuses on figurative subjects in water media/collage that lean towards the abstract and non-representational, with an occasional foray into landscape and florals. Dyer is an award-winning, signature member of the San Diego Watercolor Society, Western Federation of Watercolor Societies and International Society of Acrylic Painters.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;First place will receive a $1,000 cash award, and patron purchase awards are also anticipated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at &lt;a href="https://www.markartsks.com/callforartists." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.markartsks.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3c2526e3-f3d3-4833-9762-c7322fb286d1" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9f8c4d79-92fb-4dfd-84f7-0bb2320acc93</id><title>3/18 - Realism:Encountering the Real</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116634+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/18/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $37.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Realism:Encountering the Real&lt;br/&gt;May 1, 2020– May 30, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Realism is the art of everyday life. Historically, realism heralded a move away from the historical and academic modes of art making and towards a concern with both naturalist styles and realistic subjects. Now, realism’s position in the art world is more complex. Once considered dated, more and more artists are using realist techniques in incisive and original ways. Site:Brooklyn is looking for works across all media that engage with the renewed importance of realism today.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror:&lt;br/&gt;Sara Roffino is the executive editor of Cultured magazine and was previously the managing editor of the Brooklyn Rail and the senior/executive editor of Art+Auction. She also works as a freelance editor and researcher for artists and art historians and is currently overseeing the archives and catalogue raisonné research for painter Larry Poons. Her writing has appeared in Art+Auction, the Brooklyn Rail, Modern Painters, Cultured, Bomb.com, Artnet News, Galerie, The Art Newspaper, Artsy, and Observer.com among other publications. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Gallery:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: February 10, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: March 18, 2020 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: March 27, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: May 1, 2020– May 30, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, May 1, 2020 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in all media. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Submissions and Fees:&lt;br/&gt;Only original work may be submitted. The fee is $37.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by March 18, 2020 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Directions For Online Submission: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2UEDH77" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Presentation:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 72” X 60” X 24” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment. No artwork can be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;Shipping:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring the artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Liability:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Sales/Commissions:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Contact/Questions:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Entry Agreement:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “Encountering the Real” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2UEDH77" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9f8c4d79-92fb-4dfd-84f7-0bb2320acc93" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7f6efd13-682b-4151-a627-74601d777319</id><title>3/9 - Open Call for Art Spaces @ Krasdale  theme: The Essential Line</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116605+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Art Spaces @ Krasdale&lt;br/&gt;📍 White Plains, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/09/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DISCRIPTION &lt;br/&gt;OVERVIEW&lt;br/&gt;We are currently seeking 2-dimensional artwork from artists for an upcoming Exhibition on the theme of The Essential Line. One of the most essential elements in art is line. But what makes line essential? And what is essential in any line that is made with paint, pencil, string, ink, wire, thread, hair, rope, paper or any other material? And if a work of art has 1, 20, 46, or 100 lines, which of them can be said to be essential and why? These are the kind of questions The Essential Line will explore through the work of art. &lt;br/&gt;The Exhibition is open to artists in the Hudson Valley, the New York Metro area and Westchester County. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE VENUE&lt;br/&gt;Works are hung in brightly lit foyers, executive offices and hallways enriching the day-to-day experience of all the employees. In 1984 Sig Balka, then general counsel at Krasdale Foods, founded Krasdale Galleries, now Art Spaces @ Krasdale. An avid collector himself, he had the idea of mounting exhibits so that employees, business visitors and the general public could be intellectually stimulated by changing exhibitions.  He found that the employees felt a part of something, which added to their quality of life. This continues today. &lt;br/&gt;Art Spaces @ Krasdale is a non-for-profit exhibition space.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-The exhibition will be on view from mid-May until mid-August at Krasdale’s Hunts Point Distribution Offices  and then travel to the Krasdale’s Executive Headquarters in White Plains through mid-November.&lt;br/&gt;-The exhibition will be composed of 2-dimensional work that is hung from picture railing using monofilament.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CURATOR&lt;br/&gt;Kirsten Kucer director and curator for Art Spaces @ Krasdale&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HONORARIUMS, FEES and ART SALES&lt;br/&gt;All selected artist will be given a honorarium of $100. There is no entry fee or sales commission. All sales will be made through direct contact between the client and the artist.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXTRAS &lt;br/&gt;A color catalogued is produced for each exhibition. A reception will be held at the White Plains office with access afterwards by appointment there and at the Hunts Point Distribution Center. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SHIPPPING&lt;br/&gt;Artists living in the New York metro area will have their work shipped and returned by Art Spaces @ Krasdale. Artists in the Hudson Valley will need to bring their art to Beacon, NY. It will be shipped to Art Spaces @ Krasdale  from Beacon and returned to Beacon. Westchester artists will need to bring their work to the White Plains office. All  work will be insured with the shipper and while at Art Spaces @ Krasdale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS &lt;br/&gt;IMAGES &lt;br/&gt;-Please submit up to 10 images. If the work is framed please note both sizes. All images should be 300dpi at 1200 pixels wide and sent as a jpg.&lt;br/&gt;-All entries must be made on line though artspacesatkrasdale@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;Please put Sports in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7f6efd13-682b-4151-a627-74601d777319" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4e6d083f-f049-4047-b616-392f826439c7</id><title>3/2 - NoMAA’s Open Call: Make Manhattan Count – 2020 Census PSA</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116577+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Northern Manhattan Arts Alliance&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/02/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.nomaanyc.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Northern Manhattan Arts Alliance (NoMAA), in partnership with the Manhattan Borough President’s Office ‘s Make Manhattan Count Initiative, seeks PSA (Public Service Announcement) video submission of 30 seconds to 2 minutes to encourage participation in the 2020 Census.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Awards of $500 – $750 will be given to the winning submission(s).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SPECIFICATIONS Video should address at least (2) of the following points:&lt;br/&gt;- Citizenship status is not part of the census. ALL RESIDENTS must be counted. &lt;br/&gt;- The census form can be completed in paper, by phone, or online for the first time in 2020.&lt;br/&gt;- Census numbers determine federal funding for community resources such as schools and hospitals.&lt;br/&gt;- Your information is confidential. Records are kept closed for 72 years.&lt;br/&gt;- Census workers will never ask for your Social Security number, bank information or anything related to political parties. &lt;br/&gt;- The form is available in 12 languages (online form) and 59 languages (support materials).&lt;br/&gt;- Enumerators (census workers) will never enter your home and can only ask for questions in the census form.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;TECHNICAL REQUIREMENTS:&lt;br/&gt;- Entries must be uploaded to Youtube, and Youtube url (website link) entered in submission form (example: &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/iuESazLXcQY" target="_blank"&gt;https://youtu.be&lt;/a&gt;).  INSTRUCTIONS HERE&lt;br/&gt;- Multi-lingual entries are encouraged.&lt;br/&gt;- Animations welcome.&lt;br/&gt;- Original works only.&lt;br/&gt;- Must be in landscape format (horizontal).&lt;br/&gt;- Length of 30 sec to 2 minutes. Selected video will be subject to editing by NoMAA.&lt;br/&gt;- Video must be clear and of good quality (dimensions 720 at minimum, a modern cell phone will be sufficient).&lt;br/&gt;- Sound must be audible.&lt;br/&gt;- Collaborations with artists in different disciplines welcome, including group submissions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEN CALL for all New York City artists. Northern Manhattan artists are strongly encouraged to apply. &lt;br/&gt;FREE online application:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.nomaanyc.org/events/nomaas-open-call-make-manhattan-count-2020-census-psa/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have any questions, call or email: &lt;br/&gt;(212) 567 4394    info@nomaanyc.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4e6d083f-f049-4047-b616-392f826439c7" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d292b466-6203-4238-bb28-a39c504160f4</id><title>2/24 - Call for digital artwork: digital illustrations, 3d printed objects, web art, digital photography, s</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116547+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;DAS NYC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Digital/Electronic Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/24/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.dasnyc.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAS NYC is currently accepting submissions for a contemporary digital art exhibition entitled “Computer Love”. This open call applies to both emerging and established artists who create art works using digital technologies in any style or medium. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For this open call we are inviting artists who demonstrate unique creative approaches to digital art. Digital art can be digital illustrations, 3d printed objects, web art, digital photography, sound, AI, projection mapping, VR and more. I'm very open-minded about what constitutes digital art (essentially any artwork requiring the use of a computer in its creation). If submitting video for consideration, your TOTAL RUNNING TIME MUST BE LESS THAN 3 MINUTES.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition dates: FEBRUARY 29th – MARCH 27th, 2020 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: February 23rd, 2020  &lt;br/&gt;Notification date: February 24th.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MUST BE ABLE TO DELIVER ARTWORK BY 27TH OF FEBRUARY. IF YOU CANNOT GET YOUR WORK TO ME, IN BROOKLYN, BY 27TH OF FEB DO NOT APPLY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DAS NYC&lt;br/&gt;56 Bogart Street &lt;br/&gt;Suite #115 &lt;br/&gt;Brooklyn, NY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring the artwork against shipping damage or loss. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Liability: DAS NYC  is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but DAS NYC assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance. Sales/Commissions: All artwork must be priced for sale. Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. DAS NYC will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed. Contact/Questions: Please direct all questions to info@dasnyc.com &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Agreement: With the submission of artwork into the “Computer Love” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If submitting video for consideration, your TOTAL RUNNING TIME MUST BE LESS THAN 3 MINUTES. Please submit link to no more than 3 projects.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All else, submit no more than 3 jpeg images. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please include artist name, title, year, dimensions/running time&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If desired, Submit no more than 200 word description about projects. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition dates: FEBRUARY 29th – MARCH 27th, 2020 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: February 23rd, 2020  &lt;br/&gt;Notification date: February 24th.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;MUST BE ABLE TO DELIVER ARTWORK BY 27TH OF FEBRUARY. IF YOU CANNOT GET YOUR WORK TO ME, IN BROOKLYN, BY 27TH OF FEB DO NOT APPLY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DAS NYC&lt;br/&gt;56 Bogart Street &lt;br/&gt;Suite #115 &lt;br/&gt;Brooklyn, NY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring the artwork against shipping damage or loss. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Liability: DAS NYC  is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but DAS NYC assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance. Sales/Commissions: All artwork must be priced for sale. Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit. DAS NYC will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed. Contact/Questions: Please direct all questions to info@dasnyc.com &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Agreement: With the submission of artwork into the “Computer Love” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions above.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d292b466-6203-4238-bb28-a39c504160f4" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b5a423f3-de70-4b3e-a597-fcc4ec805925</id><title>3/20 - PARADICE PALASE ANNUAL OPEN CALL SHOW</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116510+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;PARADICE PALASE&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/20/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.paradicepalase.com/opencall"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARADICE PALASE is excited to announce our 3rd annual open call exhibition! This year’s theme is "the sublime", and we'll be considering works that inspire awe, push boundaries, incite both a sense of horror and attraction, or otherwise go beyond our comfort zone. This year's guest juror is founder and director of Gloria's Project Space, Lauren Wolchik. We are seeking works from emerging and underrepresented artists 18 years+ who live in the United States and currently do not have gallery representation. Please read below for the show prompt, full eligibility, and more details, plus how to apply!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried show with a 1st place award of $300 USD plus 6-months of supporter benefits with us at PARADICE PALASE. Learn more about becoming a supporter at Withfriends.co/paradice_palase.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-------&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee: $15  |  $8 for Palase neighbors (see eligibility for details)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline to Apply: Friday March 20th, 2020 at 11:59 pm EST&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: May 8th - May 26th, 2020*&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application &amp; details: www.paradicepalase.com/opencall&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Prompt: &lt;br/&gt;The sublime denotes greatness, beyond all possibility of measurement or imitation. It is often described as unbounded or unlimited; of being beyond in some capacity. Most people equate great art with great beauty. But it is untrue that only beautiful things can be great. The sublime itself goes beyond beauty. It can inspire both awe and fear and provokes feelings of transcendence, precisely why it is often used to describe great works of art or the awesomeness of our natural world. The 18th century author Joseph Addison identified three pleasures of the imagination: greatness, uncommonness, and beauty. For the 2020 edition of our Open Call - a noteworthy election year here in the United States - we will consider submissions that evoke a sense of greatness, and of what our expectation of greatness truly can be. Whether physical, moral, intellectual, spiritual, or otherwise, we seek to learn your vision of the remarkable and the unique. We’re ready to overcome fears, move beyond the status quo, and let greatness shine bright. Artists creating works that inspire awe, push boundaries, incite both a sense of horror and attraction, or otherwise go beyond our comfort zone are encouraged to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Acceptable Artwork:&lt;br/&gt;Painting, photography, prints, works on paper, 3D sculpture, fiber arts, sound, and video. All works on paper (including photography) MUST be in a non-ornamental frame - either white, black, or light wood -  unless explicit reasoning as to otherwise can be presented. Explanation can only relate to the content or aesthetic of the work. Artwork must be no larger than 36 inches in any direction, no longer than 2 min in length, and weigh no more than 20 lbs.     &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About PARADICE PALASE:&lt;br/&gt;We are a curatorial project based in Brooklyn, NY that confronts limitations in the art world by championing an artist-first, community-minded and inclusive model. We curate group exhibitions, produce free &amp; low cost programs &amp; events, and offer artist-forward retail items to build a symbiotic network of patrons and creators. Our programming supports emerging and underrepresented artists with a flare of the bold and brilliant. Founded in 2017 by Kat Ryals and Lauren Hirshfield, PARADICE PALASE is the love child of “DIY” and art world utopia.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Guest Juror:&lt;br/&gt;Lauren Wolchik is an independent curator, producer, and the Founder &amp; Director of Gloria’s, a project space in Ridgewood, Queens, that showcases work by underrepresented artists. She has produced events at institutions including MoMA PS1 and Pioneer Works; curated shows at New York venues including Silent Barn, IDIO Gallery, and The Living Gallery; and was a Guest Curator at the Elizabeth Murray Artist Residency in 2019 and an Artist-in-Residence at Silent Barn in 2015. Wolchik is currently the Exhibitions &amp; Production Manager at David Zwirner Gallery and previously managed the studios of Lawrence Weiner and David Byrne. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;Artists 18 years and older living and working within the United States who do not have gallery representation are welcome to apply. Artworks must be an original work produced by the artist applying and must have been completed within the last 3 years. Eligibility for the Palase neighbors fee is current residence for at least 2 years within the zip codes 11207, 11221, and 11233, with proof of address upon acceptance of your application. LIMIT ONE SUBMISSION PER PERSON.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juried Awards: Best in Show, 2 Runner Ups&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show Grand Prize of $300 plus a 6 month term as a Friend supporter with PARADICE PALASE ($60 value)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Runner Ups each receive a 1 year term as a Friend supporter with PARADICE PALASE ($120 value each)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: You must have a gmail account to submit your application&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*exhibition dates may change or be extended dependent on location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit our website at www.paradicepalase.com/opencall to apply. The form link is at the bottom of the page. You must have a valid gmail account to apply (we use Google Forms)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please also review the TERMS &amp; CONDITIONS and the EXHIBITION CHECKLIST linked on our webpage for further details and artist expectations before completing your application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thanks and good luck! We look forward to reviewing each of your applications.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b5a423f3-de70-4b3e-a597-fcc4ec805925" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>af38319e-678d-4804-80df-7b519a70d43b</id><title>3/20 - Request for Temporary Public Art Proposals (RFP): Canal Convergence 2020</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116484+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Scottsdale Public Art&lt;br/&gt;📍 Scottsdale, AZ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/20/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://canalconvergence.com/call-for-art-2020/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scottsdale Public Art seeks proposals for outdoor, temporary public artworks to be featured in, around, and suspended above the Arizona Canal in Scottsdale, Arizona, during Canal Convergence | Water + Art + Light. Canal Convergence will be on view for 10 days, from November 6–15, 2020. Some projects may be selected to stay installed for an additional 1–2 months after the Canal Convergence event dates.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This call is specifically targeting interactive and/or light-based installations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Canal Convergence’s mission is to provide an authentic and immersive art experience in and around the Arizona Canal in Scottsdale. All local, regional, and international artists— including architects, designers, and multimedia specialists—are invited to submit proposals. We will accept budgets between $5,000 and $30,000 (USD), with a limited number of larger budgets being awarded to major works of a larger physical scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit &lt;a href="https://canalconvergence.com/call-for-art-2020/" target="_blank"&gt;https://canalconvergence.com&lt;/a&gt; and download the RFP PDF file for more information about Canal Convergence, artwork themes for 2020, site specifications, how to apply, etc. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit all proposals to Jennifer Gill via email at JenniferG@ScottsdaleArts.org with the subject line “Canal Convergence 2020 Art Proposal.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note that each artist or team may submit up to three ideas or artworks. Please submit a separate proposal with documentation for each separate idea or artwork being proposed.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/af38319e-678d-4804-80df-7b519a70d43b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f407ee5e-2152-470f-87ff-aa4bcc6685ae</id><title>6/1 - ART SCENE WEST - OPEN CALL TO ALL ARTIST IN THE WEST COAST</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116458+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ART SCENE WEST&lt;br/&gt;📍 los angeles, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/01/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://artscenewest.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New online art gallery that specializes in west coast artists is now considering for acceptance all submissions of work, from original paintings  to fine art photography. We are offering a chance for west coast artists to be represented by an avant-garde gallery that is launching in February 2020.&lt;br/&gt;Ready to make a splash in the art world and take a stand? Submit and let’s start this adventure.&lt;br/&gt;ART SCENE WEST TEAM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please email your portfolio to nadia@artscenewest.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f407ee5e-2152-470f-87ff-aa4bcc6685ae" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>fd364fad-5e44-432c-ad00-5bd657372731</id><title>2/11 - Call for Art: political disenfranchisement, voter repression, racism, sexism in our communities at l</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116429+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Puffin Cultural Forum&lt;br/&gt;📍 Teaneck, NJ, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/11/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversations 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;From February 14, 2020 to April 5, 2020, the Puffin Cultural Forum present Conversations 2020, a group exhibition that focuses on the social and political issues that is reverberating in our communities at large. We are looking for submissions of timely art that speak on issues of economic discrimination, inequities in the criminal justice system, environmental racism, health care racism, political disenfranchisement, sexism, and voter repression. The exhibition will be on view at the Puffin Cultural Forum and several events will be planned to support the exhibition including music concerts, film screenings, and speaker events. Please find below some preliminary parameters and instructions on how to submit works. Please feel free to share this request for submissions to other artists in your networks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission of artwork of all media will be accepted including 2 dimensional pieces, sculptures not exceeding 5 feet in any direction, video, etc. Most accepted works will be 2 dimensional pieces which can be displayed on our gallery walls not exceeding 5 feet in height. All submissions have to be emailed to alee@puffinfoundation.org. Please provide your name, email address, phone number, website and include title, medium, dimensions, value of artwork. Optional submission of artist’ statement or comment will be accepted.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Important Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Selected artwork will be exhibited February 14 to April 5, 2020 at the Puffin Gallery in Teaneck, NJ.&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be delivered or otherwise received before February 12.&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be picked up by April 10.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Gallery Information:&lt;br/&gt;There is a total of 120 feet of displayable wall space. Artwork height is limited at 5 feet.&lt;br/&gt;Photos of the Puffin Gallery: &lt;a href="https://photos.app.goo.gl/5XgGxdSyQYII8CQ73" target="_blank"&gt;https://photos.app.goo.gl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Please send your submissions to Director, Andrew Lee, alee@puffinfoundation.org, 201-500-7259.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send your submissions to Director, Andrew Lee, alee@puffinfoundation.org.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission of artwork of all media will be accepted including 2 dimensional pieces, sculptures not exceeding 5 feet in any direction, video, etc. Most accepted works will be 2 dimensional pieces which can be displayed on our gallery walls not exceeding 5 feet in height. All submissions have to be emailed to alee@puffinfoundation.org. Please provide your name, email address, phone number, website and include title, medium, dimensions, value of artwork. Optional submission of artist’ statement or comment will be accepted.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Important Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Selected artwork will be exhibited February 14 to April 5, 2020 at the Puffin Gallery in Teaneck, NJ.&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be delivered or otherwise received before February 12.&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be picked up by April 10.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fd364fad-5e44-432c-ad00-5bd657372731" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4ae0ca51-98b8-4573-8c1f-c9bb9f5b92d2</id><title>4/15 - Mobius Photo Spring Landscape Competition</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116401+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Mobius Photo LLC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/15/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $5.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.mobiusphoto.co/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking forward to seeing stunning images from all around the world. Works from decades ago are encouraged, as landscape are ever changing. Sometimes it's the quick snaps in our backyards that make the most impact.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About :: Mobius Photo is an online platform dedicated to the curation of emerging and established photographers through quarterly photography competitions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;How It Works :: Submissions are open for 15 week periods. Winners are announced 2 weeks after the closing date. Selected works live on the website for the following year.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Follow us on social at @mobiusphoto (instagram) &lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/MobiusPhotoCo/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.mobiusphoto.co/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply at &lt;a href="https://www.jotform.com/MobiusPhoto/spring-2020-landscape-submission" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4ae0ca51-98b8-4573-8c1f-c9bb9f5b92d2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2f718e41-db1a-4565-9f1a-087f00a63b74</id><title>3/28 - Open Call: Jamaica Flux Workspaces &amp;amp; Windows 2021</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116349+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jamaica Center for Arts and Learning&lt;br/&gt;📍 Jamaica, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/28/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.jcal.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview&lt;br/&gt;Jamaica Flux: Workspaces &amp; Windows 2021 organized by the Jamaica Center for Arts and Learning (JCAL) seeks proposals from artists to research the neighborhood of Jamaica, Queens, in 2020 for the presentation, and possible creation, of new, site-specific, public art projects that engage the local community in 2021. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists will receive $500 for their research that involves dialogue and collaboration with local businesses, sites, and/or social organizations around Jamaica Avenue. Research outputs (drawings, renderings, photographs, video, text, interviews, maquettes, mark-ups et. al) will be exhibited in the JCAL Miller Gallery, from May 14 through July 10th 2021. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Depending on available funding, the artists will receive additional support of up to $2,500 to materialize their visions of creating new, site-specific, public artworks, and present their project to the public in the physical site proposed, along with related programming in 2021. A published print catalog will be produced and distributed both on- and offline following the exhibition in 2021. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With dedicated support for under-recognized artists and disenfranchised arts communities, a total of 15 artist research projects that meaningfully explore the themes of Jamaica Flux will be selected by the Curatorial Team, with support from an Art Advisory and Community Committee. Selected artists will be required to attend three meetings with the Jamaica Flux team and a variety of community members for research guidance from June - December 2020 (meeting dates TBD). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Jamaica Flux&lt;br/&gt;With the intent to build equity and expand cultural inclusion throughout Southeast Queens, Jamaica Flux strives to commission and present art that involves the local community and creates changes in behavior and policy while also documenting the developments and contradictions that arise in the process. Informed by the local economy, history, cultural traditions, community stakeholders, and participating artists, Jamaica Flux 2021 is dedicated to advancing research and visual and performative actions that foster social change, critical public discourse on advocacy, policy change, economic growth, collective civic action, and community engagement. The project aims to bring artists, local residents, curators, scholars, community leaders, developers, and politicians together to catalyze the trans-formative power of the visual arts, building on the cultural legacy of Jamaica while addressing the challenges of a quickly growing local economy. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jamaica is a formerly dis-invested community that is on the cusp of dramatic change. The de Blasio administration’s Jamaica Planning Initiative aims to make the downtown area a showplace for its place-based, community-oriented housing and economic development policies. The Jamaica Rezoning Plan, approved in 2017, has further stimulated the private investment and the rise of several global chain hotels and businesses that are gearing up to open in the next few years. These developments have precipitated a critical time of rapid change in Jamaica as a neighborhood. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Success from past editions of Jamaica Flux includes raising dialogues within the local community on urban development, wellness, education, traditional or interdisciplinary art forms, fair trade issues, and small business development. Throughout the past four iterations, artists have undertaken diverse projects, from large-scale public installations, including an environmental oasis in a former litter depot; to interactive projects, including workshops on potato ecology, SAT tutoring, CGI/AR videos, walking audio tours, and mobile paper-making on the street; to paintings acquired by restaurants after the exhibition’s run. Participating artists and collectives from previous iterations of Jamaica Flux (2004, 2007, 2010, 2016) include Alicia Grullón, Lily &amp; Honglei, Christopher K. Ho, Ellie Irons and Dan Phiffer, Center for Urban Pedagogy, John Locke &amp; Joaquin Reyes, Olu Oguibe, Michael Rakowitz, Hank Willis Thomas, Juana Valdes to Saya Woolfalk, among many others. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Jamaica Center for Arts and Learning&lt;br/&gt;The Jamaica Center for Arts and Learning (JCAL) organizes the 5th edition of Jamaica Flux with the strategic vision of empowering Jamaica as a stronghold for the advancement of contemporary art. Founded in 1972 as part of the large-scale effort to revitalize the declining Jamaica business district, JCAL is a multidisciplinary urban arts center in the diverse community of Southeast Queens, NY, dedicated to offering quality visual, performing, and literary arts, and to providing accessible educational programs to encourage participation in the arts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Instructions / Contact Information&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposals must include:&lt;br/&gt;• 1-page condensed resume with current contact information&lt;br/&gt;• 1-page statement describing the artist’s work in general&lt;br/&gt;• Project proposal (no more than 2 pages)&lt;br/&gt;A detailed description of the research to be undertaken, answering the following questions &lt;br/&gt;What topic(s) of research do you plan to undertake?&lt;br/&gt;What is the relationship between the research, site, and Jamaica, Queens as a neighborhood? &lt;br/&gt;What impacts does your realized project hope to achieve? &lt;br/&gt;In what visual and physical forms will your research manifest? &lt;br/&gt;How will you use the funds allotted to you in the undertaking of this research?&lt;br/&gt;Proposed supplemental program(s) or event(s) &lt;br/&gt;• 6 images of previous work supporting your proposal; each image should be labeled.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All materials must be received by Saturday, March 28th, 2020, 11:59PM. For any questions, please contact jamicaflux@jcal.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2f718e41-db1a-4565-9f1a-087f00a63b74" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>4bc640d6-5327-4d02-a1ba-9c3c1df1b1b2</id><title>2/27 - What about Sports? Open call for 2-dimensional art dealing with the subject of Sports.</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116318+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Art Spaces @ Krasdale&lt;br/&gt;📍 White Plains, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/27/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DISCRIPTION OVERVIEW &lt;br/&gt;We are currently seeking 2-dimensional artwork from artists for an upcoming Exhibition on the theme of Sports. In particular ( but will consider other activities), we are looking for art that deals with NYC baseball teams (Mets, Yankees, etc) and woman’s sports from artists that live and work in the NYC metro area, Westchester County and the Hudson Valley. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE VENUE &lt;br/&gt;Works are hung in brightly lit foyers, executive offices and hallways enriching the day-to-day experience of all the employees. In 1984 Sig Balka, then general counsel at Krasdale Foods, founded Krasdale Galleries, now Art Spaces @ Krasdale. An avid collector himself, he had the idea of mounting exhibits so that employees, business visitors and the general public could be intellectually stimulated by changing exhibitions. He found that the employees felt a part of something, which added to their quality of life. This continues today. Art Spaces @ Krasdale is a non-for-profit exhibition space. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-The exhibition will be on view in the Krasdale Executive Headquarters in White Plains from mid-May until mid-August and then travel to Krasdale’s Hunts Point Distribution Offices through mid-November.&lt;br/&gt; -The exhibition will be composed of 2-dimensional work that is hung from picture railing using monofilament. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CURATOR&lt;br/&gt; Kirsten Kucer director and curator for Art Spaces @ Krasdale &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HONORARIUMS, FEES and ART SALES &lt;br/&gt;All selected artist will be given a honorarium of $100. There is no entry fee or sales commission. All sales will be made through direct contact between the client and the artist. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXTRAS &lt;br/&gt;A color catalogued is produced for each exhibition. A reception will be held at the White Plains office with access afterwards by appointment there and at the Hunts Point Distribution Center. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Check us out on our new Instagram page.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS &lt;br/&gt;IMAGES -&lt;br/&gt;Please submit up to 10 images. If the work is framed please note both sizes. All images should be 300dpi at 1200 pixels wide and sent as a jpg.&lt;br/&gt; -All entries must be made on line though artspacesatkrasdale@gmail.com &lt;br/&gt;Please put Sports in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/4bc640d6-5327-4d02-a1ba-9c3c1df1b1b2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>5a6f71fc-1dd2-4f47-be88-aa235d2fa291</id><title>3/17 - In The Abstract</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116271+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Site:Brooklyn&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/17/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $37.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.sitebrooklyn.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Abstract&lt;br/&gt;May 1, 2020– May 30, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Abstraction still presents the possibility of enchantment. It is the limb of 20th century modern art, stretched out into the present day. Not trying to represent visual reality but instead using the colors, shapes, and processes that create its effect, abstraction invokes questions of space, order, simplicity and the limits of art itself. Site:Brooklyn is looking for work across all media.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror:&lt;br/&gt;Gail Levin is an American art historian, biographer, distinguished professor of art history and curator. She is a specialist in the work of Edward Hopper, abstract expressionism and American modernist art. At the Whitney Museum of American Art, Levin served as the first curator of the Hopper Collection, she has curated of a number of landmark touring exhibitions including Edward Hopper: Prints and Illustrations and Edward Hopper: The Art and The Artist along with Synchronism and American Color Abstraction: 1910-1925. Levin and Robert Hobbs co-curator Abstract Expressionism: The Formative Years. In addition, she is the author of three biographies: "Edward Hopper: An Intimate Biography," "Becoming Judy Chicago: A Biography of the Artist" and "Lee Krasner A Biography."&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Gallery:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn Gallery located in Brooklyn, New York is dedicated to exhibiting the current practice of contemporary artists.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Dates:&lt;br/&gt;Call Announcement: February 6, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Final Submission Deadline: March 17, 2020 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;Notification Letter: March 26, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition: May 1, 2020– May 30, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Friday, May 1, 2020 from 6-9 PM&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;This is a juried exhibition for artists working in all media. This exhibition is open to all artists 18 years of age or older.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Submissions and Fees:&lt;br/&gt;Only original work may be submitted. The fee is $37.00 for up to three (3) images, $10 for each additional image. If adding additional images please do so prior to check out.&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be registered/received by March 17, 2020 11:59 PM MT&lt;br/&gt;All entry fees are non-refundable.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Directions For Online Submission: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/375FOn1" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Presentation:&lt;br/&gt;1. Maximum Size: 72” X 60” X 24” D&lt;br/&gt;2. All artwork must be suitably framed to a professional standard. Work must be wired or have a cleat attachment and be ready for hanging. All framed work must use Plexiglas, except hand-delivered work less than 24” x 30”. Wall mounted sculpture, canvas and wood panels do not require a frame. No clip frames, saw-tooth hangers or taped edges are permitted. Video work must include all equipment. No artwork can be substituted.&lt;br/&gt;Shipping:&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be responsible for delivery and return shipping of all their artwork. The artist assumes all responsibility for insuring the artwork against shipping damage or loss.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Liability:&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn is not responsible for any damage, breakage, replacement or cost associated with any damage or breakage that may have occurred during transport or unpacking the work. Every precaution will be taken in handling the work, but Site:Brooklyn assumes no liability for any loss or damage to any artist’s work while in our care, custody or control, before, during or after the exhibition. Each artist, if they wish, needs to provide their own insurance.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Sales/Commissions:&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must be priced for sale.&lt;br/&gt;Artwork cannot be withdrawn, nor sales shipped, before the end of the exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;Site:Brooklyn will retain a 50% commission on all exhibition sales. The price represented on the artist entry form will be the sale price. No changes will be allowed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Contact/Questions:&lt;br/&gt;Please direct all questions to sitebrooklyn@sitebrooklyn.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Entry Agreement:&lt;br/&gt;With the submission of artwork into the “In the Abstract” Exhibition, the artist agrees to all the terms and conditions set forth in this prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/375FOn1" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5a6f71fc-1dd2-4f47-be88-aa235d2fa291" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>41a5843d-fc56-4fda-99f6-ccffeb42c100</id><title>3/27 - Live Works Vol.8_Centrale Fies (Italy)</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116238+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Centrale Fies&lt;br/&gt;📍  , Italy&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Performing Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/27/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $26.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.liveworksaward.com/call2020"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIVE WORKS Vol.8&lt;br/&gt;6th– 27th July 2020&lt;br/&gt;OPEN CALL&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;a project by Centrale Fies&lt;br/&gt;deadline 27th March 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;curated by&lt;br/&gt;Barbara Boninsegna (artistic director and founder of Centrale Fies)&lt;br/&gt;Simone Frangi (researcher, writer and curator)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Mentoring 2020 Krystel Khoury (researcher, anthropologist and cultural manager)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The open call LIVE WORKS includes a creative residency period, for nine selected projects. LIVE WORKS sees&lt;br/&gt;performance as a work space, and as an instrument and cultural exercise.&lt;br/&gt;Starting from the notion of performance in the visual art practice, the project is unique in its particular&lt;br/&gt;attention to hybrid research, underlining the openness and fluidity of performance, its social and political&lt;br/&gt;implications and its level of public understandability. The announcement is open to a wide range of&lt;br/&gt;performative actions, also including sound and new media arts, text-based performances, lecture&lt;br/&gt;performances, multimedia storytelling, choreographic practices, relational and workshop-based projects, and&lt;br/&gt;other projects questioning the idea of performativity beyond the body.&lt;br/&gt;Artists and professionals from any geographic location and with no limits on age can enter the&lt;br/&gt;announcement, as individuals or in groups, with a single project. The open call only accepts unpublished or&lt;br/&gt;long-term projects that need to be developed and/or concluded, for which participation would represent an&lt;br/&gt;evolution of the project or it’s final chapter.&lt;br/&gt;The nine projects, selected by LIVE WORKS, will be invited to participate in a production residency at&lt;br/&gt;Centrale Fies from the 6th to the 27th July 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For each selected project will be awarded a budget of € 1.500,00: € 1.000,00 of this budget will be used for&lt;br/&gt;the production of the performance, € 500,00 will be assigned as a fee for the artistic work.&lt;br/&gt;Centrale Fies covers the travel costs to reach Centrale Fies (maximum of € 500,00 per project) and will&lt;br/&gt;provide accommodation and food services for the whole residency period.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The production of the performance projects during the residency will be supported by diverse types of&lt;br/&gt;curatorship, from theoretical to technical development, a Free School of Performance with Studio visit,&lt;br/&gt;critical session and reading group.&lt;br/&gt;During the residency phase, Centrale Fies will provide a production and curatorial staff to assist the artists as&lt;br/&gt;they develop the selected projects. The residency phase is an essential part of the development of the&lt;br/&gt;selected projects and it’s consider as mandatory.&lt;br/&gt;The performances produced will be presented during the 40th edition of the Drodesera Festival of&lt;br/&gt;Performing Arts (24th, 25th, 26th July 2020). During each evening a program of established guest artists will&lt;br/&gt;be presented alongside the projects of the 9 finalists.&lt;br/&gt;On this occasion, the nine winning projects will be seen and discussed by a board of international&lt;br/&gt;professionals, working for festivals, institutions, residencies and production programs that sustain and&lt;br/&gt;produce research in performance. The board will be actively involved in public and private meetings with the&lt;br/&gt;nine artists.&lt;br/&gt;For Live Works vol. 8 the guest board of professionals is composed by:&lt;br/&gt;Cédric Fauq (Curator, Nottingham Contemporary, Nottingham, England);&lt;br/&gt;Inga Lāce (Curator, Latvian Center Contemporary Art, Riga, Latvia);&lt;br/&gt;Mathilde Villeneuve (Artistic Leader, Kunstencentrum BUDA, Kortrijk, Belgium);&lt;br/&gt;Daniel Blanga Gubbay (Artistic Co-director, Kunstenfestivaldesarts, Bruxelles, Belgium);&lt;br/&gt;Vincent van Velsen (Co-curator, Sonsbeek 2020/2024, Arnhem, Netherlands) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Info: liveworks@centralefies.it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists who intend to participate must:&lt;br/&gt;1. Fill in the online participation form here : &lt;a href="https://liveworks.wufoo.com/forms/soocw201fzaxll/" target="_blank"&gt;https://liveworks.wufoo.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2. Attach their portfolio, including a personal statement and curriculum vitae. Required format: .pdf.&lt;br/&gt;Accepted languages: english, italian. The documentary material must be contained in a single&lt;br/&gt;compressed folder, no bigger than 10mb.&lt;br/&gt;3. Attach a description of the performance project to be developed during the residency period. The&lt;br/&gt;description should include an abstract (max three A4 pages, including photos, images) in .pdf format.&lt;br/&gt;Accepted languages: english, italian. The documentary material must be contained in a single&lt;br/&gt;compressed folder, no bigger than 10mb.&lt;br/&gt;4. Attach links to any audiovisual material. Accepted formats: .avi, .mov, mpeg, mp4, mp3. Accepted&lt;br/&gt;languages: all. The material must be contained in an external server (vimeo, YouTube, other) with the&lt;br/&gt;link and any necessary password provided.&lt;br/&gt;5. Other possible members of the group (co-authors or performers) have to be included within the on-line&lt;br/&gt;application form “Names and surnames of other members”, specifying the role of everyone within the&lt;br/&gt;submitted project.&lt;br/&gt;6. Pay a € 24,00 registration fee, which partially covers the administrative costs, via on-line form&lt;br/&gt;Application Live Works Vol.8, or bank transfer.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/41a5843d-fc56-4fda-99f6-ccffeb42c100" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>39d43bb3-1305-4c77-9d20-a2e1f479a07b</id><title>4/3 - REQUEST FOR PROPOSAL (RFP): SILICON VALLEY LANDMARK COMPETITION</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116201+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Urban Confluence Silicon Valley&lt;br/&gt;📍 San Jose, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/03/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.urbanconfluencesiliconvalley.org/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Urban Confluence Silicon Valley seeks proposals for an innovative design for a new landmark in the heart of Silicon Valley. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This new landmark will anchor and activate Arena Green at Guadalupe River Park and Gardens, San Jose’s most critical urban park, which rests at the confluence of the Guadalupe River and Los Gatos Creek. The park sits directly across the street from the site of Google’s future 6 million square foot Downtown West Mixed-Use Plan Project, a new BART Station and Diridon Station, which will soon be transformed into the largest transit hub in the western United States. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The competition seeks a transformative design complete with dramatic lighting, a net-zero energy approach, and an impressive physical presence that will become a powerful and enduring symbol of Silicon Valley.&lt;br/&gt;Proposals can be for a structure, an object, a sculpture, a work of architecture—with an activated landscape to be enjoyed both day and night. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We envision a work that will become an iconic destination that embodies Silicon Valley’s culture of innovation, builds civic pride, enhances community life, and welcomes diverse communities from around the world. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Three finalists (individuals or teams) selected from Phase 1 will each receive a $150,000 stipend to refine their proposals. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submissions: April 3, 2020 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information and submission details please visit:  &lt;br/&gt;http://www.urbanconfluencesiliconvalley.org/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.urbanconfluencesiliconvalley.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.urbanconfluencesiliconvalley.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/39d43bb3-1305-4c77-9d20-a2e1f479a07b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6410e514-e61b-4ab7-896b-251327df8ac8</id><title>Present your creative work on a new TV show (Manhattan)</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116085+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dreams Media&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://dreams.tv/apply"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Project 34" (codename) will be the most interactive show on the internet.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The format is simple: Guests present their talents, dreams or passions while viewers decide how much time each person gets. The day's winner goes home with $100. The show streams live on YouTube every weekday. Anyone can be a guest on the show. All disciplines welcome. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We're looking for guests to share their unique talents and perspectives on the show. For application details and submission form visit:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://dreams.tv/apply&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About us&lt;br/&gt;Dreams is a live TV network for the internet. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We're a team in New York building the next generation of live television: fun, interactive, people-centric shows that are easy to watch online.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our first flagship show, Tefi, launched in October 2019 and has been growing rapidly on YouTube since. We're always working on new shows and looking for great talent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make a short video (60 seconds max) that describes your broadcast idea and shows us why you should be on the show.&lt;br/&gt;Complete the following application form, including a YouTube/Instagram link to your video pitch.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;    Submit your application here:&lt;br/&gt;    &lt;a href="https://dreams.tv/apply" target="_blank"&gt;https://dreams.tv&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6410e514-e61b-4ab7-896b-251327df8ac8" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e938810f-7075-418e-86e2-f6732647e0cf</id><title>3/31 - Real Art Awards 2020 Open Call</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116058+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Real Art Ways&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hartford, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/31/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.realartways.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL FOR ENTRIES:&lt;br/&gt;Emerging artists are invited to submit their work for consideration for The Real Art Awards at Real Art Ways. Jurors will consider the quality of the artist’s work, the innovation evidenced by submitted work, the potential impact of the exhibition on the artist’s career and the economic and physical feasibility of the exhibition. Artists should submit work made within the last 3 years. Artists working in all media are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply Online: &lt;a href="https://www.realartways.org/arts/artist-submissions/real-art-awards-and-exhibitions-submissions/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.realartways.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In addition to a $2,500 prize, six artists will receive a solo exhibit at Real Art Ways, an exhibition publication with essay, curatorial assistance, and the opportunity for an artist talk.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: March 31, 11:59 PM EDT, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JURORS: &lt;br/&gt;Kemi Ilesanmi: Executive Director, The Laundromat Project&lt;br/&gt;Mary Mattingly: Artist and Educator&lt;br/&gt;Will K. Wilkins: Executive Director, Real Art Ways&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT REAL ART WAYS&lt;br/&gt;Real Art Ways is committed to presenting innovative contemporary art, building community, and supporting artists. Our visual arts programming ranges from solo exhibitions, to smaller group exhibitions, to long-planned, major multi-disciplinary projects with visual arts at the center of the work. Since 1975, Real Art Ways has fostered an alternative space for artists and creatives to thrive, encouraging new ideas, experiments, and risk.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY&lt;br/&gt;Emerging artists living and working in New England, New York or New Jersey who are no more than three years removed from a full-time educational program, or artists with less than five years of exhibition experience are eligible to apply to this call. Artists who do not fit either of these criteria but feel they can make a compelling case to be considered as emerging may also apply; the jury will determine their competitiveness based on review criteria. Artists should not be enrolled in any academic program during the time of exhibition. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists working in all media are encouraged to apply. Applicants should be aware of Real Art Ways’ mission and our commitment to innovative, non-traditional contemporary work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply Online: &lt;a href="https://www.realartways.org/arts/artist-submissions/real-art-awards-and-exhibitions-submissions/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.realartways.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Full rules: &lt;a href="https://www.realartways.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/2020-Real-Art-Awards-Rules.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.realartways.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Check out our FAQ: &lt;a href="https://www.realartways.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/2020-Real-Art-Awards-FAQ.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.realartways.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Other questions? Contact our Visual Arts Manager Neil Orians:&lt;br/&gt;norians@realartways.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e938810f-7075-418e-86e2-f6732647e0cf" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>20bb8a3f-4c1c-446a-ba33-c8ee8c6274e8</id><title>3/3 - The Immigrant Artist Biennial (TIAB) Summer 2020 Open Call</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.116031+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Immigrant Artist Biennial (TIAB)&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/03/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.theimmigrantartistbiennial.com/open-call"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Immigrant Artist Biennial (TIAB) 2020: Here, Together!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Open Call for Summer 2020 Programming, NYC, venue TBA. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We invite immigrant artists born outside of the U.S., living and working in the U.S., to submit proposals in response to the theme of Mother Tongue/Language. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All exhibiting artists will receive an artist fee, amount pending.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Co-curated by Katya Grokhovsky, Mary Annunziata, Allison Cannella, &lt;br/&gt;and Anna Mikaela Ekstrand.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Immigrant Artist Biennial (TIAB) is a multi-site artist-run project, presenting work by U.S based immigrant artists from around the world. To be presented in New York City every two years, TIAB sets out to form an international dialogue through exhibition of ambitious projects and events with an aim to facilitate a diverse and experimental discourse as well as build a globally connected and united community in the times of extreme anti-immigrant sentiment, unrest, discrimination and exclusion. TIAB #1: Here, Together! will launch in Spring 2020 and continue through August presenting 40 + artists over 6 + venues across NYC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://form.jotform.com/TheInfo/OpenCallTheImmigrantArtistBiennial" target="_blank"&gt;https://form.jotform.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: March 3rd, 2020 11:59 pm EST&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit your CV, bio, artist statement, and proposed work (description and a maximum of 8 images and/or 3 videos). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Theme: Mother Tongue/Language invites immigrant artists who explore the use of language in isolation, belonging, and becoming to submit work. Topics might include: how language is used to build or erase communities; the multilingual experience; digital languages, and/or how cultures and traditions are shared or lost across generations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/20bb8a3f-4c1c-446a-ba33-c8ee8c6274e8" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>abadefa8-58fd-461d-99a6-63cff6774585</id><title>3/2 - Wide Open 11: National Juried Show</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115998+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;BROOKLYN WATERFRONT ARTISTS COALTION&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/02/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $65.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://bwac.org/national-juried-art-show-nyc-may-9-june-21-2020/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce our eleventh annual national juried art show, Wide Open 11 opening May 9, 2020.  This year we are privileged and delighted to have returning to BWAC as a juror one of New York’s very knowledgeable curators, Paulina Pobocha, of MoMA.  With her guidance and selections, we look forward to another spectacular show.&lt;br/&gt;Ours is a truly unique and generous space – a beautiful stone Civil War‐era warehouse overlooking New York Harbor from the piers of Red Hook, in  Brooklyn NY. We welcome the opportunity to exhibit unusually large work, and look forward to exhibiting artwork from all around the country, work in all sizes, and subjects, and media. Virtually every medium is accepted including: Oil, Acrylic, Pastel, Watercolor, Photography, Drawing, Print, Mixed Media, Sculpture, Assemblage, Installation*, and Textile..&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Call to Artists for Submissions:&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility: This call for submission is open to all residents of the U.S. and its Territories 18 years of age or older. This is a juried exhibition for artists working in all traditional and non‐traditional 2D and 3D media, *including film/video only when part of an Installation. Works may be submitted in one or multiple media. All artwork must be original in concept, design and execution. Limited edition prints/photographs are accepted. Artwork not meeting the criteria, although juried, may be rejected. Note: Kit work or reproductions of original works in other media (such as giclee prints of oil paintings), unless used as part of a mixed media work, will not be considered.&lt;br/&gt;Submission Deadline: Early Bird: February 4, 2020; Final Application Deadline: March 2, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;Gallery Exhibition Dates: Saturday May 9 – Sunday June 21, 2020; weekends 1‐ 6P.M.&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Saturday May 9, 2020 from 1 ‐ 6 P.M.&lt;br/&gt;Theme:&lt;br/&gt;The broad theme of Wide Open 11 encompasses all the possibilities of knowledge and freedom and love ‐ wide open spaces…arms wide open…eyes wide open ‐ but as with all things, there is the inevitable opposite ‐ wide open to attack…corruption…failure. What kind of fantasy is this? What does it really indicate? This juried show looks to explore the idea of “wide open” in all the hidden niches of our collective psyche.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Applications will be process via www.smarterentry.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Register/Login into the Client account and read all instructions for this show.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/abadefa8-58fd-461d-99a6-63cff6774585" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7c597aae-939f-4f04-bc9e-3f8e1a6f689f</id><title>3/21 - Signs of the Times Ceres National Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115971+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ceres Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/21/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.ceresgallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;14th National Juried Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition May 27 - June 30, 2020  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The theme of this exhibition can be interpreted in any way the artist sees fit.  It can be expressed through abstraction, representation, political art, social commentary, identity art, etc.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Juror, Joanne Mattera is an artist who also writes and curates regularly. Her popular Joanne Mattera Art Blog offers a largely visual look at exhibitions and art fairs in New York City and elsewhere. Her most recent curatorial efforts include Depth Perception, a 19-artist exhibition that considered dimension in physical or implied space, for the Cape Cod Museum of Art, 2017;  and A Few Conversations About Color, a visual discourse among seven artists, for DM Contemporary in New York City, 2015.&lt;br/&gt;Ceres Gallery, founded in 1984, is a non-profit alternative center dedicated to the promotion of contemporary women artists. Located in Chelsea, the gallery has 2000+ square feet of gallery space at a premier location in a destination building. Ceres serves as a supportive base for a diversity of artistic endeavors. The heart of our work is the exhibition season consisting of solo exhibitions, curated group shows and special events.&lt;br/&gt;Ceres believes the arts provide an important social service and that there is an inherent power in art to enrich the quality and depth of people's lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please use EntryThingy:   &lt;br/&gt;to submit, process payment and contract.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is our preferred method of processing entries and has everything needed in one simple space.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7c597aae-939f-4f04-bc9e-3f8e1a6f689f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cce5dd93-c606-4792-b19f-c4911903bdb5</id><title>3/16 - Reflections National Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115945+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arc Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 San Francisco, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/16/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.arc-sf.com/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Reflections” can mean the throwing back of light, sound or images by a body or surface, an image you see when you look in a mirror, an image given back by a reflecting surface. It can also be interpreted as a careful thought about something or a thought occurring in consideration or meditation.  Artists are free to interpret “reflections” with either or both of these meanings.  Categories accepted:Sculpture, painting, drawing, photo, printmaking, ceramics, assemblage, collage, mixed media, fiber art, glass art, artist book. Juror: Shelley Barry, Slate Contemporary Gallery, Oakland, CA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prospectus and online application: &lt;a href="https://www.arc-sf.com/reflections.html" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.arc-sf.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cce5dd93-c606-4792-b19f-c4911903bdb5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>54147cee-d5da-489d-9d53-42892f904a2f</id><title>3/1 - FIGMENT Dream Bigger 2020: Call for Proposals</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115917+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;FIGMENT Project inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/01/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://newyork.figmentproject.org/dream_bigger_2020"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During FIGMENT NYC, hundreds of artists come together to transform Roosevelt Island into a large-scale interactive art event that is enjoyed by thousands of participants over the course of the weekend.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This year, we want to Dream Bigger. In addition to our annual call for art for the FIGMENT NYC event, we're looking for ten (10) high-impact participatory weekend-long projects for the FIGMENT NYC event, June 6-7, 2020. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For this special call, we are looking for projects in any discipline that can achieve significant impact by (1) involving a large number of participants, (2) being intensely interactive or participatory, (3) being visually stunning, (4) having an interesting or provocative concept, (5) displaying radical efforts towards sustainability throughout all phases of production, (6) embracing this year’s question “What if the future is possible?”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The anticipated dates of FIGMENT NYC 2020 are June 6-7, 2020. The public hours of the event will be 10a-10p on Saturday, and 10a-6p on Sunday.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Grant of $1000 will be offered the chosen projects as either a tax-free reimbursement covering expenses or as a taxable stipend. For projects that are more ambitious and require a larger budget, FIGMENT will partner with you to support the development and promotion of a Kickstarter campaign to raise additional funds for your project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit this link to learn how to apply: &lt;br/&gt;https://newyork.figmentproject.org/project_submission&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Public Contact: &lt;br/&gt;dreambigger@figmentproject.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/54147cee-d5da-489d-9d53-42892f904a2f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d985aac5-c6cc-4e90-bdbc-4f5b58d33564</id><title>4/1 - Call for Artists and Designers- Azarian McCullough Art Gallery - 2020 - 2021</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115889+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Azarian McCullough Art Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Sparkill, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.stac.edu/academics/school-arts-sciences/arts/azarian-mccullough-art-gallery"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Azarian McCullough Art Gallery invites art and design applications for our 2020 – 2021 exhibition calendar.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AMAG is located on the campus of St. Thomas Aquinas College in Sparkill N.Y.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists in the tri-state area  (NY.NJ.CT.) are eligible. There is no application fee. All media will be considered.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AMAG assumes the expenses of insurance, the opening and a postcard, handles publicity in the Rockland/Bergen areas and takes a 20%  “commission” on sales  (see below).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION DEADLINE: April 1, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELIGIBILITY AND TERMS&lt;br/&gt;- Because AMAG serves the educational community of St. Thomas Aquinas College, exhibiting artists agree to meet with our students (on one occasion) at a mutually convenient time to discuss their work.    &lt;br/&gt;- Works selected for exhibit must be assigned a dollar value and listed for insurance purposes. AMAG should have this list two weeks prior to delivery.  Works delivered in good condition are insured against loss or damage while in the gallery, from the date of delivery through the last date of retrieval.   (These dates will be specified in a letter of agreement between the artist &amp; AMAG.).    &lt;br/&gt;- AMAG inspects all delivered works for damage. AMAG and St. Thomas Aquinas College are not responsible for loss or damage of:  works in transit; works not listed for insurance purposes; works exhibited outside of the gallery; works left in the gallery beyond the last date of retrieval.  &lt;br/&gt;- Artists must hand deliver and retrieve works.   &lt;br/&gt;- Delivered works should be ready for hanging and/or installation.     &lt;br/&gt;- Artists are responsible for transportation costs to and from the gallery.  &lt;br/&gt;-  Artists who accept an invitation to exhibit at AMAG, grant AMAG and St. Thomas Aquinas College the right to use images of their work, as well as submitted biographical information, for educational and publicity purposes.&lt;br/&gt;- Artists who sell works while displayed at AMAG, agree to donate 20% of these sales to St. Thomas Aquinas College.    &lt;br/&gt;- Artists who accept an invitation to exhibit at AMAG agree upon the specified dates for: delivery, set up, display, reception and retrieval.&lt;br/&gt;- Artists who accept an invitation to exhibit at AMAG will be asked to donate a small work, sketch or example of process to the AMAG Archive to be used in future academic capacities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION PROCEDURE  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE SUBMIT&lt;br/&gt;A single, compressed (Reduced Size) PDF with the following: &lt;br/&gt;1.   20 images with titles, dimensions and dates underneath &lt;br/&gt;(It is preferred if the submitted work is representative of the work you would like to exhibit)    &lt;br/&gt;2.   Contact information &lt;br/&gt;3.   Artist's Statement OR description of proposed exhibition (1-2 pages)  &lt;br/&gt;4.   CV or Resume indicating exhibition history and education &lt;br/&gt;5.  One page description of how your work could enhance the curriculum of departments outside of art (eg. political science, biology, English, history)&lt;br/&gt;NOTE: Time-based artists can include a link in their submission email to videos online in addition to the above information  &lt;br/&gt;PLEASE SEND MATERIALS TO amag@stac.edu with &lt;br/&gt;2020 – 2021 Submissions in the subject line&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Visit AMAG on the web:  stac.edu/amag&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d985aac5-c6cc-4e90-bdbc-4f5b58d33564" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1e972bed-2e6c-4fc3-b8a4-b54ffcddc504</id><title>2/24 - La Bodega Gallery looking for portrait art</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115861+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;La Bodega Art Space and Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/24/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.labodegastudios.com/opencall"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi Wonderful artists of the world!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Who has ever dare to represent another human being? Or maybe yourself? How about your Pet?&lt;br/&gt;It's a bit of a challenge. No matter if you've done this once or this is what you breath every day, here is an opportunity to share your efforts with the world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contemporary portraiture takes many forms and encompasses countless conceptual viewpoints, mediums and techniques that explore a myriad of subject matter. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At La Bodega Art Space and Gallery we are currently accepting submissions for the contemporary portraiture exhibition entitled (DE)PICT. This open call is open to both emerging and established artists who create works of portraiture in any style or medium.  For this open call we are inviting to demonstrate their creative approach to portraiture. Portraits can be figurative, abstract or conceptual.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition dates: March 6th – April 5th,  2020&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline:  February 24th, 2020   11:59:59 pm&lt;br/&gt;Location: La Bodega Gallery, 695 5th Ave Brooklyn, NY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please follow the instructions to apply by visiting our website.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.labodegastudios.com/opencall&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1e972bed-2e6c-4fc3-b8a4-b54ffcddc504" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>82d377a6-2e4e-463c-aed4-eb7046069338</id><title>2/15 - Out of Character - OPEN CALL</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115831+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open&lt;br/&gt;📍 LIC, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/15/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open invites artists who have created a character that is near and dear to share these personas in a utopian group show, "Out of Character," opening Thursday, April 16th 5 PM - 8 PM at The Gallery LIC.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Do you have an alter-ego that has been living in your artwork? Do you have a character with their own and energy? This can be a character that is NEW or OLD, SMALL or BIG, FLUID or STATIC. We want to explore how character art reflects our personal journeys and also gives expression to a whole new world. Characters reflect facets of ourselves and grow, develop and die just as we do. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Let's join and meet one another's! We encourage you to submit multiple works that reflect the same recurring characters. Of course, this may be one or multiple characters. Show us the trajectory of your character(s) through your works. We want to weave a story that shows how YOU have brought this character to LIFE! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We invite artists of all disciplines and mediums to participate in this group show at LIC Arts Open's Gallery ONE at The Factory LIC, 30-30 47th Ave, LIC, 11101, a premier 2000 sq. ft. art space. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We accept all disciplines including painting, performance, sculpture, photography, video, installation and multi-media. Video equipment is not provided. If your project requires technology please state so on your application and the equipment you will provide.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Dates&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline February 14th x Notification February 22nd&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art drop-off February April11th and 12th at The Factory LIC between 2 PM - 5 PM.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Opening reception April 16th, 5 PM - 8 PM.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art pick up March 14th and 15th between 12 PM - 5 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fees&lt;br/&gt;Please note there is an application fee that offsets the installation costs and helps to pay for the refreshments. If you have previously participated please select option 2 otherwise if new to LIC Arts Open please select option 1.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork&lt;br/&gt;Work must be ready to hang. We do not allow shipping; all work must be hand-delivered on the designated times and dates.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Gallery commission is 25%. Please price accordingly.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Information&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Standard Artwork Drop off&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork must be ready to hang with appropriate fixings. Please know that some walls are the cinderblock/cement and others are drywall. If you are bringing a sculptural or video work, please provide the necessary technology.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have proposed performance or other live work (an installation, etc.) we will contact you directly with further information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Please take/remove your wrappings at drop off unless you are fine with it being disposed of; we do not have storage for wrappings, boxes, bubble wrap, etc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Storage&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;While we are open to NY artists from all boroughs all work must be hand-delivered in person (i.e. either yourself or someone dropping off in your place). If you live in another city but can drop off and pick up the work at the specified dates and times then please feel free to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no storage option; by completing and submitting this application you agree to pick up on the dates listed above (3/14 &amp; 3/15 btwn 2 pm - 5 pm). The inability to do so will release the ownership and work to the disposal of the Factory as they see fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please cut and paste this link and use the form to submit: &lt;br/&gt;https://form.jotform.com/200126806356955&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/82d377a6-2e4e-463c-aed4-eb7046069338" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a74aebc4-d9f3-4cbf-886b-480852e716e3</id><title>3/31 - Made in New York 2020</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115800+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Schweinfurth Art Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Auburn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/31/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.schweinfurthartcenter.org/opportunities_othercalls.cfm"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EXHIBIT DATES: June 5th- August 16th, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Made in NY is an annual exhibit at the Schweinfurth Art Center located in Auburn, New York that features work by New York artists. The exhibit is an opportunity for artists residing in New York State to showcase their work in a competitive, juried exhibition. Prizes will be awarded, including $1000 for Best of Show. The exhibit is open to all media, such as photography, sculpture, ceramics, painting, drawing, fiber, installation, and video.&lt;br/&gt;Applicants may submit up to 2 works completed in the last three years. All entries must be made online through cafe.org.&lt;br/&gt;The Schweinfurth is a non-profit multi-arts center situated in the heart of the Finger Lakes that features exhibitions, art classes for youth and adults, quilting and fiber arts workshops, and multi-arts programs including music, folk arts, poetry and much more, along with a unique gift shop. Learn more by visiting us at www.myartcenter.org, and on Facebook at www.facebook.com/myartcenter.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jurors:&lt;br/&gt;DeWitt Godfrey is a large-scale sculptor working in Hamilton, NY.  His work employs carefully conceived structural processes, combining cutting edge digital technologies with custom craftsmanship, all grounded in empirical knowledge and experimentation.  Natural geometries and systems - plant spores, seashells, honeycombs – inspire his sculptures; and through his unique process of packing and stacking of conic and cylindrical steel forms, simple rules give rise to extraordinary complexity.  Godfrey completed his undergraduate work at Yale University, was a member of the inaugural group of CORE Fellows at the Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, and received his MFA from Edinburgh College of Art, Edinburgh, Scotland.  Godfrey has received numerous grants and fellowships, including the National Endowment for the Arts Artist’s Fellowship, the New York Foundation for the Arts Artists Fellowship, the Japan Foundation Artist’s Fellowship, and the Louis Comfort Tiffany Foundation Artist Fellowship.  He also served as a Senior Advisor for the Terre Foundation of American Art’s program in Giverny, France.  Godfrey’s work can be found in several private and public collections including the Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, the Brooklyn Museum, the deCordova Museum and Sculpture Park, and Art OMI.  His commissioned work includes Capital, in Seattle, WA; Concordia for Lexarts, Lexington, KY; Quake, Cambridge Arts Council, Cambridge, MA; Enspire Traverse City, MI, and installations at Frederik Meijer Garden and Sculpture Park, Grand Rapids, MI; The DeCordova Museum and Sculpture Park, Lincoln, MA; and the Kennedy Art Museum, Ohio University, Athens, OH.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jaroslava Prihodova is a visual artist, designer, and curator interested in interdisciplinary topics and collaborations. Her artistic practice generally revolves around issues associated with the object. "I spent most of my informative years developing language that sufficiently translates my ideas into a material. Being a maker, I tend to explore ideas and their application across disciplines. As a result, I am continually searching for a balance between two core doctrines: design, science, and fine art. In many instances, this schism creates a climate for particular limitations with interesting challenges." Prihodova received her BFA from School of Art and Design, Studio of Natural Materials, Jan Evangelista Purkyne University, Usti nad Labem, Czech Republic, and MFA from School of Visual and Performing Arts, Jewelry and Metalsmithing, Syracuse University, NY. She now works as the director of the Dowd Gallery at SUNY Cortland, NY. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee&lt;br/&gt;The entry fee is $35.00 and includes membership at the Art Center for February-December 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For More Information&lt;br/&gt;If you have any questions, please contact Davana Robedee at mail@schweinfurthartcenter.org. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Professional artists 18 years old &amp; up residing in New York State may submit digital images of no more than two pieces completed within the last three years (2017 and after) and not previously exhibited at the Art Center.&lt;br/&gt;Two and three dimensional work will be accepted including, but not limited to, photography, sculpture, ceramics, painting, drawing, fiber, installation, and video. (Note: All equipment must be provided by the artist for videos and multi-media installations).&lt;br/&gt;All entries must be of original design and personal execution.&lt;br/&gt;All work must be received installation-ready with appropriate hanging device, hardware and/or installation instructions included. Each work must be clearly labeled with artist’s name and title of the work. Unframed works on paper will not be accepted. Works cannot be suspended from the ceiling.&lt;br/&gt;Only completed work may be entered. Proposals/works in progress are not accepted.&lt;br/&gt;Accepted work may not be withdrawn before the close of the exhibition on August 16th, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;If artwork is for sale, the Art Center will retain a 25% commission on all sales made during the exhibition. An insurance value and a sale price including the commission, must be included on the entry form.&lt;br/&gt;The jurors/staff of the Schweinfurth Art Center reserve the right to refuse any entry because of special conditions of installation or if the quality of the work was not accurately represented in the submitted image.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a74aebc4-d9f3-4cbf-886b-480852e716e3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e50c7053-5a10-40b9-8c51-a5d6e5084961</id><title>2/15 - 440 Gallery Seeking Artists</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115772+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;440 Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/15/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://440gallery.formstack.com/forms/membership_application"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 440 Gallery was formed in January of 2005 as an artist-run institution, and we are looking to add two new members beginning in April and May 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The fiscal and general responsibilities are enumerated below. We are looking for artists who are also team players.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Dues of $200 a month&lt;br/&gt;•	About 10-15 hours per month of work, including 3 hours of gallery sitting and 7-11 hours of tasks assigned to a committee&lt;br/&gt;•	The Gallery will secure liability insurance. Artists must insure their own artwork&lt;br/&gt;•	30% of all sales will go back into the gallery&lt;br/&gt;•	Artists will share their mailing lists with the collective&lt;br/&gt;•	Attend monthly meetings on Monday evenings at 7pm&lt;br/&gt;•	Help at events&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist’s Benefits:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;•	Main gallery space: To have one solo show, one month long (including five weekends)  every 2 years. (This allows a week turnover between shows) with experienced installers)&lt;br/&gt;•	The Project Space: A members’ gallery to show work between solo shows&lt;br/&gt;•	Flat files: A place to have matted pieces available for sale year round&lt;br/&gt;•	A marketing team of members who post, blog and send regular promotional material and maintain the website&lt;br/&gt;•	All artist members will have access to the Gallery mailing list and resources&lt;br/&gt;•	24-hour access to the gallery to bring clients for private viewings&lt;br/&gt;•	A gallery Director actively working on sales&lt;br/&gt;•	A hands-on immersion in the professional experience of exhibiting as a working artist&lt;br/&gt;•	Access to shared knowledge and resources from new trends in framing and installation to the latest strategies in social media promotion&lt;br/&gt;•	Many of our members also benefit from actual, live, social interaction and support within the shared experience of work/life balance in a creative environment&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for application is February 15th.  Selected artists will be contacted for portfolio reviews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information about the gallery, visit our website at www.440gallery.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For questions, please email Amy Williams: info@440gallery.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e50c7053-5a10-40b9-8c51-a5d6e5084961" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>699e346a-f04f-4c5c-92a6-7d6f8433ccdd</id><title>3/20 - Detroit Art Week - Young Curators, New Ideas VI</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115743+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Detroit Art Week&lt;br/&gt;📍 Detroit, MI, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/20/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.detroitartweek.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Detroit Art Week is now accepting submissions for the 6th iteration of Young Curators, New Ideas. Detroit Art Week is an annual celebration of contemporary art in Detroit. In 2008, Detroit Art Week Co-Founder Amani Olu, established Young Curators, New Ideas to promote and support emerging curatorial practices. Young Curators, New Ideas VI will take place from Wednesday, July 15 to Sunday, July 19, 2020 at Trumbull &amp; Porter Detroit Hotel. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Featuring 12 independent curators, Young Curators, New Ideas VI will shine light on the cultural, artistic, social and political transformations initiated by women, LGBTQ and gender variant people through their creative, and at times independent, curatorial practices. With a sense of relevance and urgency, these multifaceted and dynamic micro-exhibitions consider contemporary issues that exist at the intersection of curatorial practice and artistic production. Within a 320 square-foot hotel room, each curator will present one artist whose work is a thoughtful and provocative exploration on the most pressing issues of our time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GUIDELINES:&lt;br/&gt;- Young Curators, New Ideas is open to exhibition organizers working in all disciplines.&lt;br/&gt;- There is no age restriction.&lt;br/&gt;- We will only accept proposals for one-person exhibitions only. We will not consider proposals for group exhibitions.&lt;br/&gt;- We will give extra consideration to proposals that fit the exhibition's theme of inclusion and diversity and engage viewers in a thoughtful and provocative discussion on the most pressing issues of our time. Young Curators, New Ideas VI will not only privilege historically oppressed and institutionally underrepresented voices in curatorship and the global art market, but also set the stage to center contemporary artists' perspectives on: gender; sexuality; the body; global migration; the political economy; climate change; war and violence; ethical dilemmas in the development of science and technology; and social stratification and racial hierarchies. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS:&lt;br/&gt;Please visit www.detroitartweek.org/young-curators-new-ideas-vi-open-call for our complete requirements, as well as, additional information and FAQs. There is a non-refundable application fee of $35.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information on Detroit Art Week, please visit: www.detroitartweek.org. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To learn more about the 2019 Young Curators, New Ideas exhibition please visit: &lt;a href="https://detroitartweek.org/young-curators-new-ideas-v-announcement" target="_blank"&gt;https://detroitartweek.org&lt;/a&gt; , as well as, view images from the exhibition at: &lt;a href="https://imgsrvr.net/open/4foWXTSmW6cbG9eq." target="_blank"&gt;https://imgsrvr.net&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Should you have any questions, please email olivia@detroitartweek.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/699e346a-f04f-4c5c-92a6-7d6f8433ccdd" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>dcf81d9e-c1b6-46f3-8634-718ae751a05f</id><title>3/22 - 12th Annual Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115716+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Prince Street Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/22/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.princestreetgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prince Street gallery / Call For Entries&lt;br/&gt;12th Annual Juried Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;Dates July 7 - 25, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Juror: SUSAN LICHTMAN&lt;br/&gt;Deadline:March 22, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility: 2-Dimensional art, artists living in the USA&lt;br/&gt;For Details, visit; www.princestreetgallery.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;visit www.princestreetgallery.com for additional information.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/dcf81d9e-c1b6-46f3-8634-718ae751a05f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>36c0855e-cd1d-45b4-9e05-1004ca96d35c</id><title>2/28 - Paid Public Art Opportunities: Highly Visible New York City Locations</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115686+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;New York City Department of Transportation&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/28/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www1.nyc.gov/html/dot/html/pedestrians/dotart-overview.shtml"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New York City Department of Transportation’s Temporary Art Program (DOT Art) has two current open calls for art installations throughout the City: Asphalt Art Activations and Barrier Beautification.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. ASPHALT ART ACTIVATIONS – Request for Qualifications&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DOT Art is seeking to identify qualified artists to be included in a registry for potential asphalt art commissions to be implemented between spring and fall 2020. As part of DOT’s efforts to make our streets more pedestrian friendly, the agency continues to reclaim underutilized street space for pedestrian use whether it be a curb extension to create larger waiting areas at corners with a more direct crosswalk; a slip lane closure to encourage pedestrian circulation along the curb line adjacent to a heavily trafficked sidewalk; or an entire street transformation from that of a thoroughfare for cars into an active public space for pedestrians to stop and linger. To highlight these infrastructure changes, DOT Art is partnering with internal teams to commission temporary art treatments that will be painted onto repurposed asphalt street spaces transforming them from ordinary asphalt spaces into canvases for art. DOT Art will provide selected artists with up to twenty thousand dollars ($20,000) towards direct project costs associated with designing, installing, maintaining and removing the Artwork. Artists should submit an application with samples of past work by Friday, February 21, 2020 to be considered for projects this spring.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2. BARRIER BEAUTIFICATION – Request for Proposals&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DOT Art invites artists and designers to propose mural designs as part of the Barrier Beautification initiative. In 2020, as part of DOT’s Green Wave Plan to improve safety for cyclists citywide, DOT will increase implementation of protected bicycle lanes by 20 miles. With a total of 30 miles projected for execution in 2020, DOT Art seeks to highlight the new safety initiative with the installation of painted designs onto jersey barriers enclosing protected bike lanes. Up to five protected bike lanes will be selected as priority locations for Barrier Beautification in spring 2020. A $3,000 design fee will be awarded to selected artists to finalize design, prepare stencils and oversee painting onto the barriers by volunteers one day in the spring. DOT will also cover costs for all paint and supplies. Artists should submit an application, design proposal and samples of past work by Friday, February 14, 2020 for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application Instructions/Public Contact Information:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Download the Asphalt Art Activations Application here: &lt;br/&gt;https://www1.nyc.gov/html/dot/downloads/pdf/asphalt-art-rfq-2020.pdf&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Download the Barrier Beautification Application here:&lt;br/&gt;https://www1.nyc.gov/html/dot/downloads/pdf/barrier-beautification-rfp-2020.pdf&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Questions should be emailed to arts@dot.nyc.gov.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Download the Asphalt Art Activations Application here: &lt;br/&gt;https://www1.nyc.gov/html/dot/downloads/pdf/asphalt-art-rfq-2020.pdf&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Download the Barrier Beautification Application here:&lt;br/&gt;https://www1.nyc.gov/html/dot/downloads/pdf/barrier-beautification-rfp-2020.pdf&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Questions should be emailed to arts@dot.nyc.gov.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/36c0855e-cd1d-45b4-9e05-1004ca96d35c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8ea9c352-224d-493b-94be-3911ab7b0b5f</id><title>2/5 - FUTURES</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115658+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Studio Place Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Barre, VT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/05/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.studioplacearts.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Science fiction artists often predict the future and its technology with surprising,and sometimes alarming accuracy.  Space travel, electric vehicles, cloning and AI - these and many more made appearances in the art of science fiction long before they were realities.  This show invites artists to share works of science fiction, in traditional and non-traditional media.  Whether your vision warns us of apocalyptic consequences of our actions, or offers innovative solutions for the problems of the modern world; whether your vision is based in science and technology, or borrows heavily from fiction, we want to see it!  Ultimately, science fiction poses, and sometimes answers the question of who we are and where we may be going.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To submit a proposal to the show, send:&lt;br/&gt;digital image(s) [limit to no more than 8];&lt;br/&gt;complete description of images (size of work, medium, date, price);&lt;br/&gt;contact information of artist;&lt;br/&gt;brief artist statement.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8ea9c352-224d-493b-94be-3911ab7b0b5f" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>11ebcb93-945d-49e3-ae98-5ba0c18ccbd3</id><title>2/11 - $550.00 Innovate Grants – Call for Artists + Photographers</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115628+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Innovate Grant&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/11/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://innovateartistgrants.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Innovate Grant is now accepting submissions for the Winter Cycle. Innovate Grant awards (2) $550.00 grants each quarter, to one Visual Artist and one Photographer. In addition to receiving a grant award, winners will be featured and recognized on our website and join a growing community of vibrant and talented artists. For more information and to apply visit &lt;a href="https://innovateartistgrants.org" target="_blank"&gt;https://innovateartistgrants.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Innovate Grant supports photographers and artists through quarterly grants. We've simplified the grant process, so that artists and photographers can focus on making their innovative work. The work should speak for itself and our application reflects that.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Innovate Grant Winners  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Christine Atkinson&lt;br/&gt;Los Angeles, CA Fall Grant Recipient – Art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Brendon Kahn&lt;br/&gt;Dallas, TX Fall Grant Recipient – Photography&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Joe Hedges&lt;br/&gt;Pullman, WA Summer Grant Recipient – Art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Leafy Yeh&lt;br/&gt;Los Angeles, CA Summer Grant Recipient – Photography&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Margaret Jacobs&lt;br/&gt;Enfield, NH Spring Grant Recipient – Art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ceaphas Stubbs&lt;br/&gt;Newark, NJ Spring Grant Recipient – Photography&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Taylor O. Thomas&lt;br/&gt;Tampa, FL Winter Grant Recipient – Art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shane Lavalette&lt;br/&gt;Syracuse, NY Winter Grant Recipient – Photography&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Category: Multiple disciplines and genres accepted&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: February 11, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Region: US &amp; International&lt;br/&gt;Awards: $550.00 Grants&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply Online Today&lt;br/&gt;https://innovateartistgrants.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Innovate Grant is an international grant program. Visual Artists and Photographers 18 years and older, from all around the world, are eligible to apply. All media and genres are accepted. All applicants retain the right to the work they submit. Apply today at &lt;a href="https://innovateartistgrants.org" target="_blank"&gt;https://innovateartistgrants.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/11ebcb93-945d-49e3-ae98-5ba0c18ccbd3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c30e5809-4419-4c34-a4b0-1f5012d1f505</id><title>2/9 - DRAWN: 7th Annual International Exhibition of Contemporary Drawing</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115596+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/09/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/drawn"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cincinnati based non-profit arts organization and gallery, Manifest, invites visual artists to submit works of contemporary drawing in any media relevant to the practice (including non-traditional approaches), any style, and any genre (fine art, illustration, design, conceptual, realism, etc.).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Manifest was founded in-part to stand for the importance of drawing as a process, skill, and discipline, and as a continuing viable product of the creative fine art and design fields. Since its inception our organization has continued to incorporate drawing-based programming, including education (Drawing Center), publications (INDA), and gallery exhibits into the broader spectrum of its projects. The artists who formed Manifest in 2004 knew that despite their diverging career paths (architecture, art history, painting, industrial design, photography) they were brought together because of their connection to drawing and their mutually intense but multi-faceted pursuit of this fundamental discipline.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In honor of the original spirit of the founding ideals of Manifest, the gallery launched DRAWN as a new annual exhibition project marking the organization's 10th season. DRAWN seeks to survey and present the broad scope of drawing being made today.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$40 for up to FOUR entries submitted. $5 per each additional entry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To view the full prospectus and entry form visit &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/drawn." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email info@manifestgallery.org with questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c30e5809-4419-4c34-a4b0-1f5012d1f505" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c363cb9e-2373-4b24-a87a-7c79183964ab</id><title>1/31 - Call For ArtTable Fellowship Proposals</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115543+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtTable&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/31/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/ATFellowship2020"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ArtTable is currently soliciting proposals from arts organizations and institutions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For 20 years, the ArtTable Fellowship program has addressed the marked lack of diversity in arts employment. The objective is to provide quality real work experiences and mentorship for women identifying graduate/pre/post-doc students and emerging professionals from backgrounds generally underrepresented in the field to aid their transition from academic to professional careers.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Through one-on-one mentoring relationships with ArtTable members, every year, a selected number of fellows have the opportunity to work with an established leader in the field and gain exposure to a range of professional activities at first class cultural institutions throughout a five to eight week period during the summer. Each fellow will be connected with an ArtTable 'mentor' for the duration of their fellowship and be awarded a $4,000 stipend for the five to eight-week commitment during the summer.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The program was established in 2000 as a conscious effort to enrich and strengthen the visual arts field by supporting an inclusive and diverse professional landscape. The ArtTable Fellowship is one of the longest-standing programs supporting diversity in the visual arts. The mentored fellowships introduce emerging women-identifying professionals to the range of professional career tracks in the visual arts, including but not limited to: curatorial, education, public programming, archival research and collections management. ArtTable has already supported eighty-five fellows around the country.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ArtTable is soliciting proposals from arts organizations and institutions that meet the following criteria:&lt;br/&gt;•	Enable the fellow to work collaboratively as well as independently on a focused and cohesive project that significantly contributes to a public exhibition or program initiatives&lt;br/&gt;•	Offer opportunities to expand their research, writing, communication and project management skills&lt;br/&gt;•	Provide integration into the institution's staff and interface with other departments for maximum experience and exposure to day-to-day activities&lt;br/&gt;•	Encourage working closely with and receiving consistent direct supervision from a designated mentor&lt;br/&gt;•	Have a take-away component, be it research or skills-based with recognition given for contributions made to a major current or forthcoming project or program&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This year, ArtTable will accept proposals from host institutions through January 31, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The ArtTable Fellowship program is made possible thanks to the invaluable support of individuals and foundations. To learn more about contributing to this program please email director@arttable.org&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;ArtTable is the foremost professional organization dedicated to advancing the leadership of women in the visual arts. Through our national membership network and community initiatives, we expand opportunities for women from diverse backgrounds and at all stages of their careers, fostering a stronger future for all women in the arts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Learn more about our impact programs:&lt;br/&gt;https://arttable.org/impact/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selection Process and Program Timeline:&lt;br/&gt;The process for selecting both hosts and fellows across the US is highly personalized and competitive. ArtTable staff, along with an ad hoc selection Fellowship Committee composed of current ArtTable members who represent professional, cultural, and geographic diversity review applications.&lt;br/&gt;Prospective fellows are selected through a similar competitive application. ArtTable will begin to accept fellow’s applications on February 12 through March 6, 2020. A final decision will be communicated to applicants on April 6.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, please contact Lucia Roldan, Education and Community Engagement Coordinator at lroldan@arttable.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c363cb9e-2373-4b24-a87a-7c79183964ab" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2f436c2f-4b25-473b-aa48-1cb0defd0e04</id><title>3/10 - 2020 Farm/Art DTour Call for Artists</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115509+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wormfarm Institute&lt;br/&gt;📍 Reedsburg, WI, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/10/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://wormfarminstitute.org/call-for-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OVERVIEW&lt;br/&gt;The Farm/Art DTour is a 50-mile, self-guided drive through the beautiful working lands of Sauk County, Wisconsin, punctuated by Art Works (large-scale temporary art installations), pasture performances, roadside poetry, local food, and more. The DTour is part of Fermentation Fest - A Live Culture Convergence including classes, workshops, and art events celebrating live culture in all its forms. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Wormfarm Institute will commission 6-8 original Art Works to be installed along the DTour route. The work will be on public view from September 25-October 4, 2020. We seek artists (individuals or teams) who are interested in creating site-responsive works that engage with the agricultural landscape, the farmers, landowners, and surrounding rural communities. This is an opportunity to contribute to a unique and exciting project with an established reputation for its innovative approach to creative placemaking.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We seek to curate a diverse group of artists for projects that respond to the land on the edge of Wisconsin’s Driftless Region. Successful past projects have ranged from fixed objects, to interactive environments, to work activated by natural processes. Some have invited hands-on participation, utilized existing agricultural infrastructure, or were installed in/on buildings in the small towns along the route. The viewers (DTourists) are usually traveling by car and guided by a map, so proposals should be large-scale and visually compelling. Artists are responsible for both installation and de-installation (volunteer assistance possible) and will have about two weeks to install and one week to de-install. Unless other arrangements are made, artists retain ownership of the work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This project has been supported by The National Endowment for the Arts, Wisconsin Arts Board, ArtPlace America, The Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, and The Educational Foundation of America. The Wormfarm Institute, the event’s presenter, is an award-winning non-profit organization with the mission to integrate culture and agriculture along the rural/urban continuum. This will be the 8th year of the DTour (now a biennial) and the first year along a new route.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BUDGET&lt;br/&gt;Wormfarm will fund projects at two levels: $5,000 and $2,500. Six to eight proposals will be selected from a combination of funding levels. Please indicate on your application which funding level you are applying for. &lt;br/&gt;An itemized budget is not required for Phase One.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;VISION: “Art Amplifies what landscape quietly asserts” - Max Garland, past Wisconsin Poet Laureate&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This project, which began as a celebration of food, farming and rural life, has revealed itself to be a powerful tool for bringing people together across perceived divides. Rooted in an arts and culture focus, we emphasize the cross-sector collaboration necessary to build a vibrant region that values both its rural and urban parts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In ecology there is a concept called "edge environments” – areas between one sort of landscape and another, where ecosystems overlap. These edges tend to have more diversity (and therefore more hardiness) than either of the adjoining environments alone. These mixed-use zones, both literal and conceptual, characterize the DTour experience and allow us to see new possibilities for our land, our work, and our communities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The DTour is an invitation for people, both rural and urban dwellers, to follow a path and take a closer look at a rural community and landscape where farming plays a central though changing role. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION PROCESS&lt;br/&gt;Artists will be chosen to participate through a two-part selection process. Initial proposals will be reviewed by a jury consisting of the organizers, past DTour artists, and regional and national arts professionals. Up to 15 finalists will be selected and notified by March 30. Finalists will be expected to attend a two-day Orientation in Sauk County, WI in May.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Orientation aims to deepen the participants’ understanding of the event, the landscape, the current state of agriculture as well as provide an opportunity for artists to meet with event organizers, landowners, past DTour artists, and one another. The weekend will include a tour of the DTour route, shared meals, and ample opportunity to share ideas and ask questions. Meals and housing will be provided. It is our hope that this experience has value independent of being selected for this year. Participants will receive a stipend to help cover travel expenses and subsequently develop a full proposal. Afterwards, finalists will have two weeks to develop a full proposal.    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION CRITERIA&lt;br/&gt;- Artistic excellence&lt;br/&gt;- Visual Impact&lt;br/&gt;- Demonstrated ability to realize&lt;br/&gt;- Community Engagement&lt;br/&gt;- Feasibility in the context of the larger event&lt;br/&gt;- Curatorial vision&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSION REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;Please respond with: &lt;br/&gt;- One page Letter of Interest including contact information &lt;br/&gt;- Preliminary Project Concept indicating funding level, not to exceed one page &lt;br/&gt;- Concept drawings or visual references &lt;br/&gt;- 8-10 images of applicant’s recent work demonstrating capacity to realize large-scale outdoor project &lt;br/&gt;- Resume or C.V. not to exceed two pages.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Format:&lt;br/&gt;- Letter of Interest, Project Concept, Drawings, Resume/C.V. should be saved as a single PDF or Word doc.&lt;br/&gt;- Images must be JPEG format, “high” or “fine” quality, not to exceed 2 MB per image. &lt;br/&gt;- Image file names should include artist’s last name and be numbered: “Smith-01.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Things to keep in mind when developing your proposal:&lt;br/&gt;- Wisconsin weather can be unpredictable, plan for rain, cold &amp; high winds.&lt;br/&gt;- The landscape can dwarf even the most ambitious projects.&lt;br/&gt;- DTour audience interaction ranges from drive-by to direct engagement with installations. Keep both scenarios in mind as you develop your idea.&lt;br/&gt;- The DTour runs primarily along farm fields, but also includes woods, wetlands, and small towns. Most sites however, will be located in hay fields or pasture.&lt;br/&gt;- The DTour is expected to attract 20,000-30,000 people from near and far. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;TIMELINE  &lt;br/&gt;March 10:  Email Applications due by 5 p.m. CST   &lt;br/&gt;March 30:  Finalists selected, notification sent to applicants&lt;br/&gt;May 2-3:  Finalist Orientation in Sauk County, WI &lt;br/&gt;May 20:  Final Proposals due&lt;br/&gt;June 1:  Artists chosen, notified&lt;br/&gt;June: Contracts with selected artists, final site selection &lt;br/&gt;September 11- 23: Installation of Art Work&lt;br/&gt;Sept 25 – Oct 4: Farm/Art DTour + Fermentation Fest&lt;br/&gt;October 5 – 19: De-installation of work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Email application to info@wormfarminstitute.org by March 10, 5 p.m. CST. Please include "DTour Proposal" in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2f436c2f-4b25-473b-aa48-1cb0defd0e04" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>58e16591-27f6-46c1-8a58-e9904ce2c4a9</id><title>2/20 - INTERNATIONAL CALL FOR ART, ArtMaze Magazine Spring Edition: Issue 17</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115478+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtMaze Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍  , United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/20/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artmazemag.com/call-for-art/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art Maze Magazine is an independent artist-run and ad-free international print and online publication dedicated to showcasing and promoting experimental and progressive contemporary art, which reflects modern society and its environment, provokes conversation and action; fosters innovation and diversity of mediums which make today’s art scene so intriguing and versatile.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: Artists are welcome to submit works in any medium: painting, drawing, sculpture, ceramics, printmaking, photography, textile, installation, mixed media, digital, film (only jpg + link to video) etc. All visual art mediums are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists or any art organisations on behalf of artists from all countries are welcome to submit their works for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each submitted artist, whether selected for a publication or not, will receive a digital copy of the magazine's issue which they applied for.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: February 20th, 2019 (12:00 AM, midnight: end of the day 20th February - Eastern Standard Time)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUEST CURATOR: Matthew F Fisher, artist and independent curator&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO APPLY: www.artmazemag.com/call-for-art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DISTRIBUTION: Physical and digital copies of ArtMaze Mag are distributed worldwide via bookshops, galleries and online. More info: &lt;a href="http://artmazemag.com/shop/" target="_blank"&gt;http://artmazemag.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Matthew F Fisheris a painter living and working in Brooklyn, NY. He has had solo shows with SHRINE, New York, NY (2020), Taymour Grahne, London, UK (2019, 2017), Ochi Projects, Los Angeles, CA (2019), and Johansson Projects, Oakland, CA (2018). He has also had an active side hustle curating group shows such as Crunch, The Breeder, Athens, GK (2017), Nothing Less, SARDINE, Brooklyn, NY (2014), New York, New Work: The Object Direct, Mississippi State University (2008), and The Longest Day, co-curated with Jon Lutz, Brooklyn, NY (2008). He maintains an Instagram account where he actively promotes artists whose work differs greatly from his own; but, like himself, these are artists who use the act of painting or sculpting in combination with the inaccuracies of the handmade as the best way to translate their ideas into reality.&lt;br/&gt;www.matthewffisher.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selected artists will be asked for high resolution images and will be published in the next print and digital issue of ArtMaze Magazine. Each (selected) artist will receive a 1 or 2-page spread in print and digital (PDF) magazine including bio, statement, website, and 1-5 featured artworks. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All submitted artists will receive a complimentary PDF copy of the magazine and all published artists will be promoted on our website/social media. Physical copies of Art Maze Magazine are printed to the highest quality in London, UK.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/58e16591-27f6-46c1-8a58-e9904ce2c4a9" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>403582a0-c2a6-42fd-a8f0-9db9c2a48577</id><title>3/2 - Open Call: Art Underneath the Elevated 2020</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115447+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Rockaway Waterfront Alliance&lt;br/&gt;📍 Queens, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/02/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://riserockaway.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Rockaway Initiative for Sustainability and Equity (RISE) is soliciting proposals for the 2020 Art Underneath the Elevated II initiative, which will commission two to three artists to envision, produce, and exhibit temporary public art installations underneath or adjacent to the elevated A-train in Far Rockaway, Queens.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This exciting initiative will use art and creative placemaking as a catalyst to temporarily transform and animate this fragmented and underutilized roadway into a vibrant and active public space. Through this initiative, RISE hopes to inspire the community to re-imagine the potential of Rockaway Freeway to reconnect the Peninsula and serve as an adaptable civic space.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This call for proposals invites an individual or a group of artists to submit a project proposal for temporary public artworks. Two to three projects will be selected. Potential project mediums include lighting installations, digital projections, street furniture, signage, murals, or sculptures. The RISE Center (58-03 Rockaway Beach Blvd) will serve as the hub of activity, and it’s gallery for public programs and community engagement that build on the chosen projects. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected artists will receive a $3,000 to 6,000 production grant to support all costs associated with their project and a one month community engagement residency that includes access to the resources and facilities at the RISE Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The application deadline is March 2nd, 2020 at 11:59 PM EST. Selected artists will be notified in April. Please visit our website (riserockaway.org) for more detailed program information and application instructions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/403582a0-c2a6-42fd-a8f0-9db9c2a48577" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0927c629-fbe4-4a18-9b87-7188173ef3c8</id><title>3/15 - The Creative Time Emerging Artist Open Call</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115418+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;CREATIVE TIME&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/15/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://creativetime.org/open-call-2020-2021/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Creative Time Emerging Artist Open Call is back! Following the resounding success of the inaugural iteration -- which culminated in Risa Puno’s The Privilege of Escape in summer 2019 -- New York’s leading public art nonprofit is once again inviting emerging artists to submit proposals for a socially engaged public artwork.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The call is open to New York City-based, practicing artists at a pivotal juncture in their career, who have not yet received substantial support from a major cultural institution. Creative Time is most interested in ideas that take unconventional exhibition formats, speak to a pressing social issue, and engender public dialogue or debate. The project should be timely, and hold the potential to spark critical public exchange.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposals will be accepted between January 21 and March 15, and the selected project will be presented in New York City in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;Applications are accepted electronically via Submittable. All complete applications received by March 15 at 11:59PM will be reviewed. Application materials sent by mail, in person, or by phone will not be considered.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;The open call is intended for emerging artists, regardless of age, at a critical career juncture in which the opportunity to experiment and receive resources from a major arts organization would be impactful. Please see the specific parameters of eligibility below:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists must have experience conceiving and executing works or projects, but have not yet received substantial support from a major arts institution&lt;br/&gt;Artist must be over 21, and based in the New York City area &lt;br/&gt;Applicants cannot be currently enrolled in a degree program &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We encourage anyone who considers themselves an emerging artist to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, including application guidelines and FAQs, visit our website or contact opencall@creativetime.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0927c629-fbe4-4a18-9b87-7188173ef3c8" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cd72afce-4a05-4926-9edb-591641fe6310</id><title>2/10 - Open Call for Art: &amp;quot;reflecting on social transformation&amp;quot; curated by Lisa di Donato</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115385+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LiC-A @ The Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/10/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.licartists.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call for Art: Title TBD "reflecting on social transformation" curated by Lisa Di Donato&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An exhibition in response to the centennial anniversary of Women’s Suffrage in the United States that queries &lt;br/&gt;-Who are We- in relation to our complicated histories and present realities as individuals and communities, as women and as citizens. In keeping with the theme of Woman’s History Month, the focus is mainly feminist-centric, but, the call also seeks to include works that highlight adjacent movements and concerns to those of women and feminism, which notably have a history of engaging in self-examination. Artists and creatives, individual or collective, of all genders, nationalities, and mediums- visual arts, video, sound art, text, and poetry are encouraged to apply.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;During this very uncertain time of increasing divisiveness in the country and the world, the remembrance of the Suffragette Movement could serve as a cautionary tale on the struggle and preservation of human rights. The Nineteenth Amendment all too frequently is viewed only &lt;br/&gt;in its decisive moment of victory, a fait accompli, glossing over its problematic and arduous progression towards ratification and the current day disenfranchisement and oppression that continue to threaten many here and abroad.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Rather than striking with defensive declarations of -We Are- that flatten conversation and knowledge, this exhibition looks to the heart of our cultural and political clashes where the question of -Who are We- resides. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists are in a unique position to ask this question through their work; politics in art is not limited merely to statement-making. Art offers us the opportunity to explore how we understand and apprehend our worlds, the manifold methods of communication that may reveal otherwise untold perceptions, and exposure of a creative process the vulnerability of which is an invitation to the shared meanings that are the underpinnings of every society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To apply please copy and paste the below link into your browser or visit us at www.licartists.org for more information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_social_transformation&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the curator:&lt;br/&gt;Lisa di Donato received her BFA from the Rhode Island School of Design. Her artwork has been shown in the US and Europe, and she also has independently curated numerous exhibitions. She received recognition in the 2019 Julia Margaret Cameron Women in Photography Award in the category of Abstraction and is currently in the accompanying exhibition in Barcelona, Spain. In May 2019 she was artist in residence at Fusion Gallery AIR Inaudita in Torino, Italy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cd72afce-4a05-4926-9edb-591641fe6310" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>d7f39fca-87ea-4bbd-9093-f8fee936d6ff</id><title>2/15 - Submit to “The Sick” for publication</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115353+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Seventh Child&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/15/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://seventh-child.com/submit"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New art &amp; literary press, Seventh Child, is seeking submissions for its first open call, to result in a print publication dissecting THE SICK. All interpretations of the theme are welcome, including those which are arguably challenging, subversive, unorthodox, or uncomfortably subjective. Art of every stripe is encouraged, with little or no restriction: poetry, photography, illustration, creative nonfiction, three-dimensional work represented two-dimensionally in order to be fit for print, etc. Final selection from submissions will be based on considerations of craft, relevance, and potential for stimulating connections with other pieces set for inclusion. Everyone featured in the final publication will receive a free copy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send 1-5 work samples as email attachments (hi-res jpegs or pdfs) to info@seventh-child.com and include your name as you wish it to be printed, as well as website, social media handles, or other online presence, if applicable. There is no fee to submit.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d7f39fca-87ea-4bbd-9093-f8fee936d6ff" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c7786f71-63c0-4fc3-b3f7-d4627a084be5</id><title>2/7 - OPEN CALL - Night &amp;amp; Day - Group Show - Local Project NYC</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115323+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Local Project&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/07/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://localproject.org/night-day-group-show-open-call/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for works of art that symbolize the day and the night.&lt;br/&gt;As we head into a new decade, we want to show the artist’s vision, state of mind,  and the effects of light and darkness pertaining to the direction we are headed.&lt;br/&gt;As Dorothy M. Richardson said : ”Night is torment. This is why people go to sleep. To avoid clear sight and torment” &lt;br/&gt;Do you see the light ahead ?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are really excited to be partnering with Departure Studios in LIC, to make this a 2 part exhibition simultaneously happening in each space, creating a flow of light and darkness between both locations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Dates :&lt;br/&gt;Open call Deadline: FRIDAY FEB 7&lt;br/&gt;Notification: MONDAY FEB 10&lt;br/&gt;Delivery of selected works: FEB 14-15 Time TBC via email&lt;br/&gt;Opening Thursday FEB 20  6-9pm in conjunction with the LIC Gallery Nights&lt;br/&gt;Show runs through March 14, 2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-Artwork must be original and come from you – the artist. (no digital reproductions).&lt;br/&gt;-Artist must live in NYC or NJ.&lt;br/&gt;-There is no entry fee to submit your work but accepted artists pay a hanging fee of $30, by cash, check or Venmo.&lt;br/&gt;-Hanging fees go directly toward the expenses of the exhibition and the reception.&lt;br/&gt;-Work must be ready to hang ie; frames or wired, no clips or pins&lt;br/&gt;–no size limit and prices bellow $1,000 preferable ( we hold the right to make exceptions)&lt;br/&gt;-Please SUBMIT up to 2 jpeg images of the works you like to show, include title, year, dimension, material, and price to opencall@localproject.org including NIGHT &amp; DAY in the subject.&lt;br/&gt;-Jpegs must not exceed 2mb.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Local Project takes a 30% fee if your work is sold. Sales will be finalized at the end of each exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;-This exhibition will be Juried by LP curators John Baber and Carolina Peñafiel.&lt;br/&gt;-Once notified, you will be guided to drop off dates, payment must be done at drop off.&lt;br/&gt;-Artists are responsible for the drop-off and pick-up of any and all artwork.&lt;br/&gt;-Any artwork left without notice for more than a week after the end of the show at LP, Local Project will not be held responsible.&lt;br/&gt;-Please note Local Project and Departure Studios does NOT provide insurance for the artwork.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c7786f71-63c0-4fc3-b3f7-d4627a084be5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0e31352c-596c-4ab8-b66d-d10028c17238</id><title>2/29 - EMERGING CURATORS - OPEN CALL - LOCAL PROJECT NYC</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115290+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Local Project&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/29/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://localproject.org/emerging-curators-2020/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEADLINE: February 29, 5pm, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;Notifications by March 5, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Emerging Curators is an open call invitation to independent curators who may not have had opportunities to present a project to an audience, or first time curators to submit a Project/Exhibition proposal to be part of Local Project’s 2020 exhibition calendar. This program will provide the curator with a $500 honorarium and a budget of $500 to split between the artists of each show, exhibition space, guidance in marketing and art handling and a printed catalog.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposals will be reviewed by our LP curatorial team, we will then select 6 proposals for the year 2020 to happen in the LP gallery and at site specific locations or other galleries in LIC area between March and June 2020.&lt;br/&gt;The Emerging Curators will represent the vision of a new generation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Application is FREE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;Proposals must include :&lt;br/&gt;-Title of the project, number of artist involved (min 2 – max 10) name of the curator/s.&lt;br/&gt;-Proposals must be submitted as a PDF.&lt;br/&gt;-Proposals can be 1-2 weeks exhibitions, 2-3 days popups, or 1 day events.&lt;br/&gt;-For a 2 week exhibitions Programming during the exhibition on view is required (performance, screening, artist talk/walk, workshop),&lt;br/&gt;-Describe your idea in a simple way – up to 1000 words.&lt;br/&gt;-Include up to 5 sample images of the work to be selected.&lt;br/&gt;-Curator and Artists must be residents of New York City.&lt;br/&gt;-All mediums and ideas are accepted.&lt;br/&gt;-Curators can’t  include their own work in the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;– Once selected curator must supply all the content for the catalogue, including high res images, artist bio and a paragraph about the exhibition etc via PDF&lt;br/&gt;-Only one proposal per curator, curatorial collaborations accepted.&lt;br/&gt;-Selected Curators must be present all the times during installation, opening, programs and closing ceremony, and embrace the DIY mentality of LP, by participating, collaborating and sitting at the gallery.&lt;br/&gt;-Submit a PDF to opencall@localproject.org with EMERGING CURATORS on the subject line.&lt;br/&gt;-Do NOT send/attach CV/PRESS or any other information not listed here&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions email opencall@localproject.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0e31352c-596c-4ab8-b66d-d10028c17238" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>428d0e3b-c921-422e-a241-dd920e420284</id><title>1/30 - January 31st Open Call People&amp;#39;s Choice Salon Show! WIN $200 AND A SOLO SHOW!</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115252+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/30/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our January 31st People's Choice Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Friday, January 31st , 2020 from 8pm- 12am.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, January 30th, 2020 at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For this show, we let the people decide, which means everyone who attends votes for the winners! We pass out ballots at the door and guests who attends choose the winners! It is always one of our most well attended nights, boasting record art sales and a large community of fellow artists and art lovers!&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of local bands!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, Jan. 30th at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces already this past year. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com  Instagram: @ GreenpointGallery&lt;br/&gt;Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/greenpointgallery/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To submit, send us JPEG's of your artwork or a link to your website at greenpointgallery@gmail.com!&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/428d0e3b-c921-422e-a241-dd920e420284" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6c10d1ca-ba27-4aee-9e52-c0604514255f</id><title>2/7 - AD ART SHOW 2020- Call for Artists at the Oculus at the World Trade Center-</title><updated>2020-02-18T19:30:24.115191+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;MvVO ART creator of AD ART SHOW&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/07/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $75.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.mvvoart.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a successful debut at Sotheby's in 2018, and at the Oculus in 2019, AD ART SHOW is BACK at the Oculus in a BIG WAY. Opening during Frieze Art week (May 2020), AD ART SHOW will be showcasing artists from all over the world on the monumental SCREENS at the Oculus at Westfield World Trade Center , one of the most famous architectural landmarks in New York City. The show is on for the whole month of May! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is easy to apply. All you have to do is to submit 4 images of your Art.  Our renown Art selection committee will review it and if you are selected then you will be part of the show. (no commercial work please- only your fine Art). All the Art will also be featured for sale on MvVOART's Artsy gallery, the leading Art market place for collectors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is a selling exhibition (fees apply). Includes VIP invitation to the May 4 opening reception attended by Art professionals, collectors, press and Ad industry. Eligible to win a creative immersion day at NBC Universal and your Art will be reviewed by well know NY Art professionals and important collectors. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Go to www.mvvoart.com for details and application and to check if you qualify.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thank you. &lt;br/&gt;MvVO ART team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Access application via www.mvvoart.com. Also follow Mvvoart on Instagram for constant updates. It is easy to apply. Just submit 4 images of your Art! and answer a few questions. The artists are selected based on their submission not their experience in the Art world. Please see FAQ on Mvvoart and application for all info.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6c10d1ca-ba27-4aee-9e52-c0604514255f" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>