<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml</id><title>open-calls-7</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-7.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>e54ca407-c82d-4864-b2e6-7f9d36212bfb</id><title>1/15 - 31st National Drawing &amp;amp; Print Competitive Exhibition</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.096323+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Gormley Gallery - Notre Dame of Maryland University&lt;br/&gt;📍 Baltimore, MD, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Printmaking&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/15/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $36.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://ndm.edu/gormleygallery"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gormley Gallery at Notre Dame of Maryland University invites artists to submit drawings and prints for our annual juried exhibition. This year’s juror is Doreen Bolger, Former Director of the Baltimore Museum of Art. A minimum of $1,500 is available in purchase prize awards.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility and Media: Drawing and prints (not photography) in any medium up to 60" high (framed) are eligible, with no limitations as to color, surface, or materials. All drawings and prints must be original works of art. Each artist may submit up to 3 works online only. No mailed or emailed entries will be accepted. Accepted artworks must arrive at the gallery ready to hang.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee: A nonrefundable entry fee of $36.00 entitles the artist to submit up to three entries.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selection process: Initial jury will be of online submissions received by January 15, 2020. Notification will be by email on January 31, 2020. Accepted drawings and prints received by March 2 will be juried for purchase prize awards at the value set by the artist. Works selected for purchase prize awards will become the property of Notre Dame of Maryland University.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition dates: March 23 through April 24, 2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To apply:&lt;br/&gt;https://artndm.slideroom.com/#/login/program/52095&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More information: &lt;br/&gt;ndm.edu/gormleygallery&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contact: &lt;br/&gt;gormleygallery@ndm.edu&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e54ca407-c82d-4864-b2e6-7f9d36212bfb" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>5ead4d3b-23c6-4d8c-a8bf-f788a3902f03</id><title>2/7 - FIBER 2020</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.096297+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Silvermine Arts Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Canaan, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Crafts&lt;br/&gt;📅 02/07/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://silvermineart.org/exhibition/fiber-2020/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIBER 2020 – seeks to exhibit the best of contemporary fiber art. Submissions are invited that reflect the breadth of functional or non-functional works that use fiber and/or fiber art techniques in traditional or innovative ways. Works made from natural or high tech materials that reference fiber and that blur the lines between art, architecture and craft are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;CURATOR – Beth C. McLaughlin is Chief Curator of Exhibitions and Collections at Fuller Craft Museum in Brockton, Massachusetts. Ms. McLaughlin has held leadership and curatorial roles in the arts and museum fields for over 25 years at institutions across the U.S., including Fuller Craft Museum, Oakland Museum of California, and DeCordova Sculpture Park and Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eligibility – Open to all artists, 18 years of age and older, residing in the United States. Original artwork in any media will be considered. Eligible artwork must have been completed after January 1, 2018, and fall within the restrictions. Check website for prospectus.&lt;br/&gt;Awards – Best in Show awards an artist a solo exhibition at Silvermine Arts Center with a $1,000 stipend for show related expenses. The Juror has additional awards to give at their discretion.&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee – $45 for up to 5 entries. To be considered for the Best in Show Award, artists are required to enter a minimum of three works.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/5ead4d3b-23c6-4d8c-a8bf-f788a3902f03" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7f4116c6-e4b5-4325-a73b-d6efd0beaa8e</id><title>12/30 - SOLO EXHIBITION 2020 at The Untitled Space gallery in Tribeca, NY</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.096269+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Untitled Space&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://untitled-space.com/artist-opportunities/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Untitled Space gallery invites artists to apply for a Solo Exhibition to take place at the gallery in Tribeca, New York in 2020.&lt;br/&gt;The Untitled Space is looking for an artist with an exceptional body of work that has not been previously exhibited for this unique opportunity. The exhibit will be curated by gallery director Indira Cesarine who will work directly with the artist to select final artwork for exhibition as well as promote it via print and online media. Artists who submit may also be considered for future opportunities with The Untitled Space gallery such as international art fairs, group shows, and online exclusives.&lt;br/&gt;Artists should have an established exhibition track record, and the focus of the proposal should be on new, unexhibited work. The recipient of the solo exhibition will additionally be represented by The Untitled Space gallery for a minimum of 6 months in support of the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT THE UNTITLED SPACE&lt;br/&gt;The Untitled Space is an art gallery located in Tribeca, New York in a landmark building on Lispenard Street. Founded in 2015 by Indira Cesarine, the gallery features exhibits of emerging and established contemporary artists exploring conceptual framework and boundary pushing ideology through mediums of painting, sculpture, printmaking, photography, video and performance art. The gallery is committing to exploring new ideas vis-à-vis traditional and new mediums and highlights a program of women in art as well as special events aligned with our creative vision.&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT CURATOR INDIRA CESARINE&lt;br/&gt;Indira Cesarine’s curatorial for The Untitled Space includes includes solo shows for artists Sarah Maple, Rebecca Leveille, Alison Jackson, Fahren Feingold, Miss Meatface, and Jeanette Hayes as well as group shows "BODY BEAUTIFUL", “IRL: Investigating Reality”, "EDEN" and "(HOTEL) XX" at SPRING/BREAK Art Show; ”SECRET GARDEN”, “SHE INSPIRES,” and internationally-celebrated group shows “UPRISE/ANGRY WOMEN” and “ONE YEAR OF RESISTANCE” responding to the political climate in America, as well as numerous other critically-acclaimed exhibitions. &lt;br/&gt;Recent press on Indira Cesarine &amp; The Untitled Space includes Vogue (US), Vogue Italia, CNN, Forbes, Newsweek, W Magazine, Harper’s Bazaar, Teen Vogue, New York Magazine, i-D Magazine, Dazed and Confused, and The New York Times among many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online - visit our website for more information: &lt;br/&gt;http://untitled-space.com/artist-opportunities/&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7f4116c6-e4b5-4325-a73b-d6efd0beaa8e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>fea0876c-980c-4d5f-bbc1-81b1e4b8ddce</id><title>12/20 - Japan Day Art Contest 2020</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.096242+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Japan Day Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/20/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.japandaynyc.org/artcontest2020"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan Day is inviting all visual artists to submit their work to Japan Day Art Contest to select our Japan Day Official Artist 2020. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are accepting submissions that incorporate all of the three themes of New York, Japan, and Central Park. The chosen artwork will become the official image of Japan Day @ Central Park 2020, and will be used for collateral materials including poster, program, flyer, and T-shirts. Several artists will receive honorable mentions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Japan Day Official Artists will receive a round trip ticket for two (2) to Japan, provided by ANA and Digital camera, provided by Nikon Inc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All winners will be announced in late March/early April 2020. The awards will be presented on the day of event in May 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RULES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Art must incorporate all of the following three themes: “New York,” ”Japan,” and “Central Park.”&lt;br/&gt;- Size must be 24" tall x 18" wide.&lt;br/&gt;- Only two-dimensional media is accepted.&lt;br/&gt;- Only one submission per artist will be accepted.&lt;br/&gt;- All entries must be the original work of the entering artist.  &lt;br/&gt;- Artwork which has been submitted to previous contests and/or previously shown or published is not eligible. &lt;br/&gt;- Artwork does not need to include the Japan Day logo or any text related to the event.&lt;br/&gt;- Artwork that violates copyrights, intellectual property rights, and/or any related rights of a third party, is not eligible. (For example, the use of existing anime characters would be a violation of copyrights.)&lt;br/&gt;- Art must not contain explicit sexuality, violence, or any discriminatory elements.&lt;br/&gt;- The final layout and design of the poster, flyer and other publicity materials will be created and approved by Japan Day Inc.  Artist’s approval is not required for publication.&lt;br/&gt;- By submitting their artwork, artists grant Japan Day Inc. the right to use their work for the purpose of marketing, exhibition and other Japan Day-related uses. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please visit the website (http://www.japandaynyc.org/artcontest2020) for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fea0876c-980c-4d5f-bbc1-81b1e4b8ddce" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>136b594c-46f3-417b-9bab-e6bd96744b58</id><title>1/3 - Dog Days of Winter - Member Artist Showcase</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.096213+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;AKC Museum of the Dog&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/03/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $60.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://museumofthedog.org/events-and-education/calendar/dog-days-of-winter"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This February, the AKC Museum of the Dog will be hosting a Members Only pop-up exhibition showcasing the artistic talent within our community called Dog Days of Winter. Anyone currently enrolled in a membership program is encouraged to submit their art for consideration—this includes all membership levels and types. If you’re a non-member and wish to submit your work, never fear! Memberships start at $60 and you can join at any time during the entry period—which runs from October 31st to January 3rd—in order to submit your work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition will be juried. Individual Members are allowed one submission. Family/Dual and all higher levels of Membership are allowed up to four submissions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To submit your work to be considered for Dog Days of Weekend members showcase, you must be a member of the Museum. To become a member, visit our website or contact Molly Marcotte at molly.marcotte@museumofthedog.org. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guidelines for Juried Artwork Submission:&lt;br/&gt;-Anyone currently enrolled in a membership program will be encouraged to submit their work - this will include ALL membership levels and types.&lt;br/&gt;-Individual Members are allowed one submission.&lt;br/&gt;-Family/Dual Members and all higher levels of Membership are allowed up to 4 submissions.&lt;br/&gt;-Member Libraries who wish to participate will field submissions for their patrons and submit the top 4.&lt;br/&gt;-Any non-members who wish to submit must become a member in order to submit their art.&lt;br/&gt;-20 submissions will be chosen and featured on our third floor gallery.&lt;br/&gt;-All other submissions that are not selected will be featured on our Community Wall.&lt;br/&gt;-All mediums welcome with a size limitation of 25" x 30".&lt;br/&gt;-All artists will be responsible for getting their own pieces to the Museum no later than January 17, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;-Museum will not be responsible for framing any artworks that will be displayed, nor is the Museum responsible for any damage that may occur to a piece.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/136b594c-46f3-417b-9bab-e6bd96744b58" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3d5ad007-6f0a-402e-80f5-61b0a0bb0060</id><title>12/31 - 8th International Photography Annual [$2000 in Cash Awards]</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.096167+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/inpha8"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cincinnati based non-profit arts organization and gallery, Manifest, invites visual artists to submit works that incorporate the lens or photographic process in some significant way, including manipulated and mixed processes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;INPHA is not a gallery exhibition. It does not require shipping works to Manifest. It is an award-winning non-profit hardcover publication with cash awards.&lt;br/&gt;INPHA is open to a very broad range of lens-based and photographic submissions. This is not just for 'photographers' and 'photography' but also for anyone working creatively in a visual art (or design) field with work that incorporates the lens or photographic process in some significant way, including manipulated and mixed processes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;First, Second, and Third Place awards for VISUAL works will be decided by the jury committee. Each award winner will have a brief artist's statement included in the publication. There will be three cash prizes of $1200, $500, and $300 for first, second, and third place winners.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$40 for up to FOUR entries submitted. $5 per each additional entry.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;**The next open call for INPHA 9 will be in 2022**&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To view the full prospectus and entry form visit &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/inpha8." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email info@manifestgallery.org with questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3d5ad007-6f0a-402e-80f5-61b0a0bb0060" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9264811c-a00a-45db-8da4-89b249d7ebbf</id><title>1/14 - Solo Shows 2020-2021 at Locust Grove Estate</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.096139+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Barrett Art Center (Dutchess County Art Association)&lt;br/&gt;📍 Poughkeepsie, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/14/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.barrettartcenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Locust Grove Estate, is partnering with Barrett Art Center to announce four Solo Show opportunities in 2020-2021.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each 10-12 week show presents artists with the opportunity to present a solo show of 20-30 artworks in the Transverse Gallery in the Visitor Center at Locust Grove, a National Historic Landmark museum, education center, and nature preserve which attracts over 90,000 visitors annually.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;http://www.lgny.org/&lt;br/&gt;http://www.barrettartcenter.org/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Locust Grove was the nineteenth-century country estate of Samuel Morse, who, in addition to inventing the telegraph and Morse Code, was an artist and the founder of the National Academy of Design. In the twentieth century, the estate was owned by Poughkeepsie’s prominent Young family, noted collectors of Hudson River School paintings and the founders of the museum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Barrett Art Center works with curators from around the globe to bring exemplary contemporary art from international artists to its exhibitions in the Hudson Valley. Our reputation for high-quality exhibitions and programs attracts thousands of art enthusiasts to our 1840s Greek Revival townhouse-turned gallery annually. Arts professionals from Barrett Art Center are part of the curatorial team juroring the shows.&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Information&lt;br/&gt; Solo shows are available for 2-D artwork. Please note the galleries are frequented by visitors of all ages, including school groups. Artists’ discretion is requested. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We encourage artists to develop new works of art for this exhibition opportunity. If selected for a solo show, the images submitted for review do not necessarily have to be among the works exhibited. In an effort to give artists time to prepare, solo shows are being offered now for July 2020 through June 2021. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted artwork must be properly mounted, framed and ready to hang from a track-type hanging system. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork may be either for sale or for exhibition only. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Terms for sale of artwork: artist receives 75%; commission is 25% &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Recommended number of works for display is 20-30 pieces, depending on size. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Locust Grove reserves the right to not exhibit any artwork that does not meet our display criteria. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;BAC Members, please email info@barrettartcenter.org or call us at 845-471-2550 for coupon code to receive discount.  To become a member, visit, www.barrettartcenter.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applications can be made directly to: &lt;br/&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=7280&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9264811c-a00a-45db-8da4-89b249d7ebbf" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a9d132f2-6601-4d84-bbfa-be227080b1ac</id><title>1/5 - Straight Through the Wall 2020 -- CALL FOR ARTISTS</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.096111+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Straight Through the Wall&lt;br/&gt;📍 BROOKLYN, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/05/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://sttw.nyc/open-call/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeking artists working in Video, Experimental Film, Performance &amp; Animation for STRAIGHT THROUGH THE WALL’s 2020 program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NEXT DEADLINE: DECEMBER 5TH&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are STRAIGHT THROUGH THE WALL, a guerrilla Arts collective that projects video art onto walls throughout NYC. We scour the city for blank building facades, willing canvases waiting above busy avenues or hovering over quiet gardens and empty lots. With every screening, we incorporate art into the cityscape, merging it with New York’s varied architecture, bringing it out of the rigid structures of galleries &amp; exhibitions, and delivering it directly to the masses.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our first two seasons included screenings in the Lower East Side, Bed Stuy, Crown Heights, Chelsea, Dumbo, Two Bridges, Downtown Brooklyn, Brownsville &amp; the East Village. Each screening is 30 minute program that plays on loop &amp; the events are free to all. Emerging &amp; established artists are invited to submit their video proposals following the guidelines below.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EARLY DEADLINE - NOVEMBER 5 - FREE&lt;br/&gt;STANDARD DEADLINE - DECEMBER 5 - $10&lt;br/&gt;LATE DEADLINE - JANUARY 5 - $20&lt;br/&gt;If applying after November 5th, paypal your submission fee to sttw.nyc@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected artists will create videos that play with the idea of portraits. All videos should explore the human experience or human figure. What is it to be human in this time of history, what defines us and unites us? Alternative takes on portraiture are welcome &amp; encouraged. Straight Through the Wall seeks to better understand people both collectively &amp; individually by assembling a diverse video program consisting of different voices &amp; viewpoints.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All proposals must be for portrait videos (vertical dimensions - 1080 x 1920). All videos should be 3 - 5 minutes long. Once selected, you'll be asked to complete your video by April 5, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Email your submission to: sttw.nyc@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE INCLUDE:&lt;br/&gt;-Contact Info&lt;br/&gt;-Description of proposed work (max 500 words)&lt;br/&gt;-Artist statement or bio (max 200 words)&lt;br/&gt;-1 - 3 Video Samples (Links to Youtube or Vimeo)&lt;br/&gt;**Don't forget to Paypal submission fee to sttw.nyc@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a9d132f2-6601-4d84-bbfa-be227080b1ac" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>0fc3a2db-6750-4c8f-a963-8fa34e914f29</id><title>12/29 - Upstream Gallery Juried Photography Show 2020</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.096082+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Upstream Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Hastings on Hudson, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/29/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.upstreamgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upstream Gallery Juried Photography Show 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; “Chaos &amp; Calm: Envisioning Order” &lt;br/&gt;There is no argument that the world around us is changing in a multitude of disturbing ways. Photographers are invited to submit work from their own practice that speaks to randomness and unpredictability or the creation of order from chaos for our annual juried exhibit of photographically based work.  Exhibition will be held at Upstream Gallery, Hastings on Hudson, NY, Jan. 30th to Feb. 23rd, 2020. Reception: Sunday, Feb. 2nd 2-5 pm. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Work: Artists from around the world are invited to submit photographs in any technique. All work must be photographically based.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Specifications: All work must be suitably framed.  The maximum framed size may not exceed 30 x 40 inches. Accepted pieces must be wired for hanging. The gallery reserves the right to reject poorly presented pieces. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Entries, Sunday Dec. 29th, 2019.  All entries must be made via Submittable: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee: Minimum entry of 3 pieces $45; each additional entry $5 up to a maximum of 6 pieces ($60).  The jury may select one, several, all, or none of your submissions. All pieces must be for sale. The gallery will retain a 30% commission on all sales. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IMPORTANT DATES &lt;br/&gt;Friday, January 24th: All shipped work must be received no later than 5 pm.&lt;br/&gt;Monday, January 27th 10 a.m. to 2 pm: Delivery of artwork to gallery by local artists &lt;br/&gt;Thursday, Jan. 30th: Opening of exhibition &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sunday, February 2nd, Opening reception – 2 to 5 pm&lt;br/&gt;Sunday, Feb 23rd, Last day of exhibition &lt;br/&gt;Monday, Feb. 24th Local Artists pick up work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All entries must be made through Submittable:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://upstreamgallery.submittable.com/submit&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0fc3a2db-6750-4c8f-a963-8fa34e914f29" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a67ef9a9-2624-4e96-9c29-2548da07ccec</id><title>1/19 - CALL FOR ARTWORK - Suffrage and Struggle: Feminist Art and the 19th Amendment Centennial</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.096049+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hamilton Gallery, Salve Regina University, Newport, Rhode Island&lt;br/&gt;📍 Newport, RI, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/19/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://art.salvereginauniversity.com/juried-show/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suffrage and Struggle: Feminist Art and the 19th Amendment Centennial&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: March 5 – April 7, 2020 Deadline: January 19, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Fee: (USD) $30.00&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;“Suffrage and Struggle: Feminist Art and the 19th Amendment Centennial” commemorates the centennial of women’s suffrage in the United States by marking the milestone of the 19th Amendment. This exhibition aims to celebrate women’s empowerment and the changes that have occurred over the last century, while at the same time acknowledging that more work remains to be done to achieve equality in our society. Regional in scope, this exhibition seeks to recognize the outstanding creative accomplishments of visual artists working in the New England and New York area whose work explores the complex place of women in society. We welcome submissions from all people that broadly interpret this theme around any issues of gender and sexuality.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror&lt;br/&gt;Jan Howard is the Chief Curator and Houghton P. Metcalf Jr. Curator of Prints, Drawings and Photographs at the RISD Museum. Prior to coming to RISD in 2000, she spent fourteen years as a curator in the Department of Prints, Drawings and Photographs at The Baltimore Museum of Art. Her exhibitions and publications have primarily focused on modern and contemporary art, including Drawing Ambience: Alvin Boyarsky and the Architectural Association 2014; America in View: Landscape Photography 1865 to Now, 2012; Made in the UK: Contemporary Art from the Richard Brown Baker Collection, 2011; Pat Steir: Drawing Out of Line, 2010; Interior Drama: Aaron Siskind’s Photographs of the 1940s, 2003; Laurie Simmons: The Music of Regret, 1997; Roni Horn: Inner Geography, 1994.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Dorrance H. Hamilton Gallery&lt;br/&gt;The Hamilton Gallery is a vibrant exhibition space on the campus of Salve Regina University in Newport, Rhode Island. This newly renovated Gallery hosts seven to ten exhibitions per academic year and serves as a center for art and visual culture.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility&lt;br/&gt;The Hamilton Gallery is currently accepting submissions in all media. This is an open call to artists living in Rhode Island, Massachusetts, Maine, Vermont, Connecticut, New Hampshire and New York. Artists must 18 years of age or older and all artwork must fit through a standard 36” x 80” door.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Entry Fee&lt;br/&gt;The application fee for this exhibition is $30.00. Credit card payments must be made through the following weblink: www.salve.edu/ArtAppFee&lt;br/&gt;Checks must be made to the order of “Salve Regina University”. Do not email, fax or leave personal or financial information on voice mail. All inquiries and online submissions can be sent&lt;br/&gt;to ernest.jolicoeur@salve.edu. Please type “Suffrage and Struggle Exhibition” in the subject line. Entry fees will support the opening reception, printed materials and a stipend for the juror.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submissions&lt;br/&gt;The following items must be sent in a single email to ernest.jolicoeur@salve.edu or mailed in a single package to the mailing address listed below. All materials must be clearly labeled with the artist’s name. Materials received without payment of the application fee will not be given consideration. (Example: Jane_Smith_IMAGES or Jane_Smith_CV)&lt;br/&gt;   &lt;br/&gt;Resume&lt;br/&gt;A typewritten CV of no more than two pages that includes your contact information&lt;br/&gt;List of Works: A typewritten illustrated list (thumbnails only) of no more than three pieces including title, dimensions, date, medium and insurance value that includes your contact information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement: A brief typewritten statement about your submission(s) of no more than 200 words that includes your contact information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Images&lt;br/&gt;A single .pdf file or a dedicated weblink including no more than three high quality images (2MB or less) or three video shorts (5 minutes or less). Do not send link to websites or bodies of work. The juror will only review three works from each artist.&lt;br/&gt;    &lt;br/&gt;Mailing Address&lt;br/&gt;Hamilton Gallery: Suffrage and Struggle Dorrance H. Hamilton Gallery&lt;br/&gt;Antone Academic Center&lt;br/&gt;Salve Regina University&lt;br/&gt;100 Ochre Point Avenue Newport, RI 02840&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;All fees must be received and all materials must be postmarked or submitted by January 19, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;Conditions of Acceptance&lt;br/&gt;Artwork must arrive at the Hamilton Gallery ready for exhibition with all appropriate hardware and equipment. All accepted work must remain on display for the full duration of the exhibition, from March 5 through April 7, 2020. Please consider any potentially conflicting commitments before making your selections for submission.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Terms&lt;br/&gt;The Hamilton Gallery reserves the right to not exhibit work that is not ready for installation or differs from the images submitted. Images of all work accepted into this exhibition must be available for publicity purposes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Notification of Acceptance&lt;br/&gt;Notifications will be sent by email during the week of January 27-31, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shipping&lt;br/&gt;All shipping and transportation are the responsibility of the artist. Shipped works must arrive in a reusable container that includes all necessary PREPAID postage. Artists may also hand deliver work to and from the gallery on February 25 or 26, 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Insurance&lt;br/&gt;The Hamilton Gallery provides insurance for all artwork while on its premises for exhibition purposes. The Gallery does not cover insurance while work is in transit.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a67ef9a9-2624-4e96-9c29-2548da07ccec" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>019ca8c9-3a20-4c50-8a1f-c147d3b6c30b</id><title>12/14 - Chelsea Gallery OPEN CALL</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.096019+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Field Projects&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com/open-call/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Field Projects is pleased to announce our Winter Open Call! Emerging and mid-career artists are invited to submit their work for consideration.. All submissions will be considered by our Guest Curators: Christin Graham &amp; Sam Trioli (LAUNCH F18 Gallery, NY). Simultaneously, Field Projects Panel (4-5 curators) will be considering the submissions for future solo exhibitions, group exhibitions, 2 person exhibitions, art fairs, pop-up shows, off-site exhibitions and our studio visit program, where we invite outside curators to accompany us to your studio. (85% of the artists we have shown in the last 8 years have been discovered through the Open Call.) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With your submission you will get several opportunities:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. Winter Exhibition by our Guest Curator: Christin Graham &amp; Sam Trioli (LAUNCH F18 Gallery, NY)&lt;br/&gt;2. Online Exhibition &lt;br/&gt;3. Future Solo and Group Exhibitions at Field Projects.&lt;br/&gt;4. Future Art Fairs with Field Projects.&lt;br/&gt;5. Outside Exhibitions by our FP panel members.&lt;br/&gt;6. Studio Visit pool for NYC Artists.&lt;br/&gt;7. Field Magazine&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Field Projects is an NYC-based project space located in the heart of Chelsea's gallery district. As an artist run space, we are committed to opening the field of exhibition opportunities to other working artists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow our website link above or cut and paste : &lt;a href="http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com/open-call/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit :&lt;br/&gt;up to 5 images of your work&lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement&lt;br/&gt;CV&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline : December 14th, 11:59 PM !!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Winter Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;The theme of the show will come from the work submitted. &lt;br/&gt;Selected artists will be notified by Dec 23rd, 2020&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must arrive at Field Projects by Thursday, January 2nd, 2020. &lt;br/&gt;Winter Exhibition opens Thursday January 9th, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Winter Exhibition closes Saturday February 8th, 2020&lt;br/&gt;All artwork in the exhibition will be for sale, with artists receiving 50% of final sale. &lt;br/&gt;We look forward to seeing your work!!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Field Projects&lt;br/&gt;526 W 26th Street, &lt;br/&gt;#807&lt;br/&gt;New York, NY 10001&lt;br/&gt;info@fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;www.fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/019ca8c9-3a20-4c50-8a1f-c147d3b6c30b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>cb33efad-e6e9-467e-927d-f92d79ae09e6</id><title>12/15 - ACCEPTING CURATORIAL APPLICATIONS | SPRING/BREAK Art Show NYC + Los Angeles 2020</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.095984+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SPRING/BREAK Art Show&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $150.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.springbreakartshow.com/2020-application/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SPRING/BREAK Art Show is accepting submissions by curators until December 15, 2019*, midnight (your time), for the upcoming 2020 New York City and Los Angeles exhibitions. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*This is our late application deadline. Regular applications were accepted until November 22, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2020 THEME | IN EXCESS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“The more the merrier.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;                          - Traditional&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The term ‘tipping point’ is used frequently in current affairs in regards to a variety of topics. Environmental extinction predominantly first and foremost, but also resumed economic stability, political divisiveness, information overloads, cancel culture mania, all are together thought to be at every manner of places along an axis of toppling the heck over, with varying ideas circulated as to which side of their scales are too overstuffed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art and entertainment feel indistinguishable from one another, piled together as “content”, which is consistently billed as in overwhelming supply from creators both amateur and professional; News peppers everyday moments through our devices’ push notifications and peer updates; tech-aided romantic possibilities appear infinite, as do all the other seductions of a globalized world—people to meet, people to follow, things to buy and eat and do. (Should one be able to afford it…For better or worse, then, the ‘too much’-ness of everything is certainly on the mind. In line with these grumblings of overmuch, SPRING/BREAK Art Show 2020 seeks similar inquiries into the paradoxes and nuances of ‘more’. For both upcoming New York and Los Angeles shows, IN EXCESS is actively searching for exhibitions dealing with virtues and/or limitations of maximalism, materialism, digression, hysterical realism, capitalism, encyclopedii, redundancy, consumerism, the over-foot-noted and the overlabored. Submissions may or may not include touchstones on multimedia, multiracial, or multiverse theories and perspectives; environmentalism, globalization, and future shock; the baroque, the Simulacrum, the epic, human play, the hall of mirrors, or any manner of other meditations on the Anthropocene and its anxieties; and, maybe—where we can find them—joys.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The pleasure of ‘more is more’ may be explored through the joyously overindulged overabundance of ideas, forms, perspectives. Aesthetically, ‘the bigger, brighter, busier, the better’ was once the zeitgeist with the intent to create, not a nauseous geegaw of consumer pleasures, but an impression that rattled complacency—generating, instead, awe, surprise, wonder; a sense of the infinitude of our World. Where is our awe now in all this excess? Where is the new Rocaille? Is it any good? Is it a spectre of Greed or Good? How much is not enough, and when is too little too soon?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;References in the current and former art landscape include, but are not limited to, Peter Saul’s rambunctious hypercolor paintings of interwoven political brutality, Joyce Kozloff’s reframing of “women’s work” in her P &amp; D movement pieces and their extension over into, and reframing by, artist Liz Collins, William Powhida’s art world cartography of complicit capitalism. Marco Brambilla crafts sprawling video pop cultural hells and heavens, packed with re-appropriated movie characters all fighting each other for a place in the pantheon, Mickalene Thomas constructs dizzying pastiche domiciles where tactile textiles, personal experience, and the figure from memory converge, authors like Thomas Pynchon and Zadie Smith jam-pack characters into stories teeming with a dance of detritus both intimate and historical; Stan Brakhage deploys the barrage for the sake of recalibrating our vision, Anselm Kiefer, with his fussy gigantic meditations, employs scale to save our soul. Robert Breer’s lightning speed animations stagger in their short running time pummel, Azikiwe Mohammed toils to find overstocked thrift store tapestries of Black utopias, and for Alison Zuckerman, art history, digital self-documentation, and Photoshop fiddling all find themselves locked, arm-in-arm, in triplicate.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Wilde suggested moderation in art and life was a fatal thing. But how does it support or subvert our consumptive excesses? Like Gittes once said to Mulwray, “how much better can you eat? What can you buy that you can’t already afford?”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;People, go for baroque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATION GUIDELINES + CURATORIAL REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There are separate applications for the New York City and Los Angeles shows. Please note that curators may apply to both the New York City and Los Angeles shows and will need to submit separate applications for each show to be considered for either and/or both. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications will be accepted by independent curators, galleries and non-profit organizations during the late application period between November 23 - December 15, 2019. The online application form will be available during those dates until December 15, 2019 at 11:59pm your time. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;No proposals nor applications will be accepted via email.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Please note that "Late Applications" are reviewed in the same manner as "Regular Applications". We do not prioritize applications based on when they were submitted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION FEE&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is a non-refundable late application fee of $150.00 per application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our mission is to create an unique environment for showcasing independent curators by providing free exhibition space to each selected curator, and therefore, require an application fee to cover our administrative fees for processing the applications.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;WHO MAY APPLY&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1) INDEPENDENT CURATORS: Independent Curators may submit an application for the 2020 SPRING/BREAK Art Show, including a curatorial proposal related to the theme of IN EXCESS, sample images of art work, a curatorial statement and additional information necessary to complete the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that an artist may apply as an Independent Curator only if they are applying with a group show or a solo show of another artist's work. An artist may not apply with their own art work in a solo show, but must have a curator who applies on behalf of him/her/they.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is NO FEE for the exhibition space if you are selected as an independent curator.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2) GALLERIES + PROJECT SPACES + NON PROFIT ORGANIZATIONS: Applicants affiliated with a gallery or project space/non-profit organization may submit a curatorial proposal comprised of artists from the gallery's roster and this curatorial proposal will fall into our SPECIAL PROJECT section. If you have an affiliation with a gallery, project space or non-profit organization, please define your affiliation/title and include the full roster of artists in the application below for our reference.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Special Project section was initiated in 2015 as a way to invite established, new and recently closed galleries to participate in the show. We encourage participants in the Special Project section to explore the theme in full and to go beyond what they typically would do in a traditional art fair environment. In 2019, there were 26 Special Projects as part of the program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each Special Project contributes a fee to participate, which helps to cover the production costs of the event.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information on applying at an Independent Curator, Gallery or a Non-Profit Organization, please visit our website for more details:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;http://www.springbreakartshow.com/2020-application/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTED CURATORIAL APPLICATIONS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission of an application does not guarantee participation. We will review applications in December and notify selected curators by the beginning of January, if not before. If we have any questions about your proposal, we will contact the primary curator listed on the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each curatorial proposal will be given one (1) room/space for exhibiting artworks. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected curators will receive a consignment agreement to review and complete. All artworks included in the show must be included in and subject to the terms of the consignment agreement. Artworks that are not listed on the consignment agreement will not be permitted on the show premises. If you have any questions about the consignment terms, please contact us for details.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/cb33efad-e6e9-467e-927d-f92d79ae09e6" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>43b3dd19-4fa4-4e8f-aba8-89405d5a2c1b</id><title>12/3 - Request for Proposals - Rosalie Garder Jones Monument</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.095951+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Parks Recreation &amp;amp; Historic Preservation&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cold Spring Harbor State Park, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/03/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.nyscr.ny.gov/iframes/openAdDetail.cfm?id=77B04B69-54CD-48B7-A966-053D540DDB16"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPRHP is interested in commissioning a figurative or abstract work of art, not necessarily a sculptural portrait, of Rosalie Gardiner Jones that captures her unrelenting dedication to women’s rights. Bidders are encouraged to develop their own understanding of the context of her life and her achievements. The key objectives are to create a lasting tribute to Rosalie Gardiner Jones that is integrated with the Cold Spring Harbor State Park site and utilizes materials that are durable and require minimal maintenance and care.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you choose to visit the site, OPRHP will be holding an optional site visit on 10/8/2019, please reference the RFP for further details.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To obtain a copy of the Request for Proposal package, please contact contracts@parks.ny.gov&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Due Date: 12/03/2019 3:00 PM&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contract Term: 2-year contract upon OSC approval&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: Cold Spring Harbor State Park&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Direct Requests for RFP details and any questions can be submitted to contracts@parks.ny.gov. The deadline for proposal is December 3.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/43b3dd19-4fa4-4e8f-aba8-89405d5a2c1b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>09dea911-e0d1-46f4-be5f-e802462427d0</id><title>Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transportation Authority (Metro) launches Call to Artists</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.095875+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transportation Authority&lt;br/&gt;📍 Los Angeles, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.metro.net/artistpool"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL TO ARTISTS – 2020 Artist Pool&lt;br/&gt;(Request for Qualifications)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Metro Art invites visual artists to respond to our 2020 Call to Artists. Metro Art commissions artists to create artworks that improve the transit customer experience and contribute to the artistic vibrancy of the communities we serve. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: Online submittal must be completed via SlideRoom by 11:59 p.m. (PST) on December 9, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Interested artists are encouraged to learn more about the 2020 Artist Pool through our website. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist Opportunities&lt;br/&gt;•	The Artist Pool will be one of the primary methods for inviting artists to apply for future Metro art opportunities.&lt;br/&gt;•	Opportunities include artwork integration within the built environment and short-term exhibitions in media such as lightboxes, posters and construction phase banners.&lt;br/&gt;•	Inclusion in the Artist Pool does not guarantee a commission. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility&lt;br/&gt;•	Professional artists working in two- and three-dimensional media at all career stages that are interested in creating art for the public realm.  Prior public art experience is not a requirement.&lt;br/&gt;•	Artists who are legally authorized to work in the United States (per U.S. Department of Labor).&lt;br/&gt;•	Metro employees and contractors are not eligible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Metro Art&lt;br/&gt;For more information about the Metro Art program, projects in the works, tours, events, publications and artist opportunities:&lt;br/&gt;•	metro.net/art&lt;br/&gt;•	Instagram.com/metro.art.la&lt;br/&gt;•	facebook.com/metroartla&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Information and support materials must be submitted through Slideroom.com at &lt;a href="https://metroart.slideroom.com/#/login" target="_blank"&gt;https://metroart.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The submittal package must include up to 10 digital files of their artwork, a professional resume and an artist statement.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applicants can receive technical support for submissions by emailing support@slideroom.com or by accessing the online help desk: &lt;a href="https://support.slideroom.com/" target="_blank"&gt;https://support.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Allow adequate time to familiarize yourself with the SlideRoom submittal process and to receive any needed technical support.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Information submitted by mail, email, fax, hand-delivery or after the deadline will not be considered.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Incomplete submittals will not be evaluated.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists who do not meet the eligibility requirements will not be evaluated.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/09dea911-e0d1-46f4-be5f-e802462427d0" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>128dbbac-d566-4222-bd1a-c0e9ba9bc521</id><title>12/21 - Open Call for Contemporary Ceramics Exhibition curated by Matt Nolen</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.095845+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Long Island City Artists @ The 12,000 sq ft Plaxall Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Islanc City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/21/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_claytopian_ny"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Deadline: Saturday, December 21st, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition on View: February 20th, 2020 to March 15th, 2020&lt;br/&gt;“Claytopian New York” curated by Matt Nolen invites sculptors to apply who use the universal language of ceramics to express the idealized universe of their artistic vision and diversity. Visions that include references to the spectrum of history, traditions, world culture, gender, social and political issues and notions of beauty- life in the Metropolis.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Invited Artists include: Ron Baron, Sin-ying Ho, Julia Kunin, Sana Musasama, Steven Montgomery, Melissa Stern, Derek Weisberg, Adams Puryear, Eun-Ha Paek, Elise Siegel, among others.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: The Plaxall Gallery, 5-25 46th Avenue, Long Island City, NY&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Saturday, February 22nd, 7-10:00 PM&lt;br/&gt;Curators Talk: Saturday, February 22nd, 6-7:00 PM &lt;br/&gt;Medium: Ceramics&lt;br/&gt;Curated by: Matt Nolan&lt;br/&gt;Application Fee: $25.00 LiC-A members, $40.00 non-members&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: Saturday, December 21st, 2019&lt;br/&gt;www.licartists.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the curator:&lt;br/&gt;Matt Nolen is a studio artist living and working in New York City and Narrowsburg, NY.  Nolen’s work has been written about and reviewed in the New York Times, American Ceramics, Ceramics Art and Perception, Masters of Craft, Confrontational Clay, Postmodern Ceramics, Painted Clay and more...He has recently served as President of the Board of Trustees for Watershed Center for the Ceramic Arts in Newcastle, Maine, is currently serving as Trustee of the Robert M. MacNamara Foundation and is Adjunct Professor of Art at New York University, Hunter College, and Ceramics Area Coordinator at Pratt Institute.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.nolenstudios.com/about&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please go to the online submission form to enter:&lt;br/&gt;https://licartists.formstack.com/forms/submission_form_claytopian_ny&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/128dbbac-d566-4222-bd1a-c0e9ba9bc521" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e9228982-504b-4658-8750-3580d4d8a957</id><title>1/13 - Earth Works:  Art in Ecological Context National Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.095816+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Barrett Art Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Poughkeepsie, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/13/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.barrettartcenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juror: Karl Kusserow, John Wilmerding Curator of American Art, Princeton University Art Museum&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: January 13, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: March 28 – May 2, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$500 Juror’s Prize, $250 Second Prize, $125 Honorable Mention&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Barrett Art Center invites artists to submit work that explores mankind’s impact on the environment and our relationship with the earth.  Artists are likewise invited to submit works that stimulate conversation about our evolving ideas about the landscape, the landscape tradition, and climate change in contemporary culture. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Drawing, painting (all mediums), pastel, printmaking, photography, sculpture, fiber, mixed-media, new media, and installation works are eligible. We invite proposals of both contemporary and traditional pieces that create a visually-compelling complement, or counterpoint, to Barrett Art Center’s 1840s Greek Revival townhouse interior. &lt;br/&gt;About the Juror:&lt;br/&gt;Karl Kusserow is John Wilmerding Curator of American Art at the Princeton University Art Museum. He recently co-organized Nature’s Nation: American Art and Environment (2018), a traveling exhibition reexamining 18th-21st-century American art in relation to issues of ecology and environmental history. Its catalogue received a 2019 Award for Excellence from the Association of Art Museum Curators and was named the Art Exhibitions category winner by the Association of American Publishers in its 2019 PROSE Awards. Kusserow is currently preparing a related volume, Picture Ecology: Art and Ecocriticism in Planetary Perspective, for publication, in addition to Object Lessons: American Art from Princeton, accompanying a forthcoming traveling exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;His exhibition, Nature’s Nation: American Art and Environment was featured at the Princeton University Museum of Art; the Peabody Essex Museum in Salem, MA; and the Crystal Bridges Museum of American Art, in Bentonville, Ark.  See, “Can Art Help Save the Planet?”, New York Times, March 12, 2019:  &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/12/arts/art-climate-change.html" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.nytimes.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists can submit artwork through Call for Entry: &lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=7209" target="_blank"&gt;https://artist.callforentry.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e9228982-504b-4658-8750-3580d4d8a957" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>6aa3c50d-4730-4473-996d-ef2d778aa02e</id><title>1/8 - She: an expression of womanhood</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.095786+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Annmarie Sculpture Garden &amp;amp; Arts Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Solomons, MD, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/08/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $25.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She: an Expression of Womanhood focuses on the theme of women in art, as creators, innovators, consumers, and subject matter. In an era of multiplying female voices, world-wide political movements, and fluid gender roles and identities, this exhibit invites artists to dive into the vast and often contentious conversation about the meaning of she. Works that delve into human rights and agency, gender roles and relationships, and cultural events like the #metoo movement, are also welcome. The goal is to create a rich exploration of womanhood that celebrates and embraces different voices, experiences, and interpretations. All media welcome; small to large scale works; indoor and outdoor works; cash awards will be presented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PROSPECTUS/APPLICATION: &lt;a href="https://annmariegarden.wufoo.com/forms/she-an-expression-of-womanhood/" target="_blank"&gt;https://annmariegarden.wufoo.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CALL FOR ENTRIES - a national juried exhibition. All media welcome; small to large-scale works; indoor and outdoor works accepted; cash awards.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;She: an Expression of Womanhood&lt;br/&gt;February 14 - September 27, 2020, Kay Daugherty Gallery&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNMARIE SCULPTURE GARDEN &amp; ARTS CENTER&lt;br/&gt;In Association with the Smithsonian Institution&lt;br/&gt;Solomons, Maryland, 20688 USA&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE to apply: January 8, 2020&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CONTACT: art@annmariegarden.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/6aa3c50d-4730-4473-996d-ef2d778aa02e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>10639141-4e71-466a-b5de-7bce50f1e3ca</id><title>12/11 - Viewpoint: Landscape and Architectrue</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.095757+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Black Box Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Portland, OR, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/11/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A juried group photo show on landscape and architecture at Black Box Gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="https://blackboxgallery.com" target="_blank"&gt;https://blackboxgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See prospectus on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/10639141-4e71-466a-b5de-7bce50f1e3ca" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>05390190-baeb-44ff-b523-5da25aeeeec3</id><title>12/13 - Publication Opportunity for All Artist</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.095724+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Plus Magazine, LLC&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/13/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.plusmagazines.net"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Publication Opportunity for All Artist&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are seeking passionate artists/creatives to join us for our issue 2 of Plus Magazine!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Plus Magazine seeks to offer encouragement, to provide opportunities for growth and to highlight gifts the world may have overlooked. Here, art is more than a canvas or clay. Here, we honor ingenuity and drive. We showcase rising talent in all disciplines and fields and aspire to find their common threads. Here, we feature experienced voices to inspire those who are working to find their way; who are trying to make an impact in this complex world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details:&lt;br/&gt;Artists working in all media are encouraged to apply for this open call. We are looking for artists who are willing to create new works starting from January through March 31. Selected artists will be awarded an opportunity to showcase their new works in our second issue of Plus Magazine, which will be expanded not only in the U.S. market but also in Europe and Asia. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are always excited to see new works and rising artists who are passionate about the creative field and we want to learn more about your stories and works through Plus Magazine!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE SUBMIT&lt;br/&gt;Submission materials:&lt;br/&gt;• Up to 8 images of work/link to the portfolio&lt;br/&gt;• CV &lt;br/&gt;• Short statement &amp; bio&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;Submission- December 13, 2019 (midnight, GMT) &lt;br/&gt;Notification -December 16, 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please contact us with questions at  info@plus-mag.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/05390190-baeb-44ff-b523-5da25aeeeec3" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>9f2b0cb7-7e5d-46bc-939e-7e78ecb1afbe</id><title>12/1 - ECOCA&amp;#39;S Open Call 2020</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.095684+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ely Center of Contemporary Art&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Haven, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 12/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://elycenter.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ely Center of Contemporary Art is pleased to announce Open Call 2020. &lt;br/&gt;Submissions will be considered for:&lt;br/&gt;	•	Exhibition guest curated by Two Coats of Paint's, Sharon Butler, Jan. 12–Feb. 16, 2020 &lt;br/&gt;	•	Solo exhibitions curated by ECOCA&lt;br/&gt;	•	Grace’s Trust, an on-line exhibition platform&lt;br/&gt;	•	Thematic exhibitions&lt;br/&gt;	•	Project space for video, installation, and experimental works&lt;br/&gt;	•	Perspectives Gallery @ Whitney Center, Hamden, curated by Debbie Hesse&lt;br/&gt;	•	Other off-site programs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://elycenter.org/open-call-2020" target="_blank"&gt;https://elycenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/9f2b0cb7-7e5d-46bc-939e-7e78ecb1afbe" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>512326af-3b1b-4563-97e6-5c887d01f665</id><title>Events+Workshops // a platform for launching open-ended and experimental events+workshops</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.095592+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Painted Cloud&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅   deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.thepaintedcloud.com/open-call"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Events+Workshops are ideas that are not fully realized and do not have a planned outcome. Presenters, who are experienced and experts in their fields, explore a material or a facet of a topic that they themselves have not yet fully explored. As a presenter, think of yourself as an experienced captain steering a boat in uncharted waters.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are not limited to visual arts. Past events+workshops consisted of performance, screenings, readings, and more. We are open to your ideas.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are promoted to the public as pay-as-you-wish (suggested $10-$20). All money collected for events+workshops is split 50/50 between the presenter and The Painted Cloud after material costs(up to $35) are reimbursed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are 2-4 hours long in duration and occur one Saturday per month.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are one-offs.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are open to the public.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are developed for adult participants, but teens can be included depending on the proposal.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Events+Workshops are promoted through our email newsletter and social media. The presenter's 'fee' requires presenters to promote through their newsletters and social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Call link here. Read the information on the link and submit your proposal at the bottom of the page.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/512326af-3b1b-4563-97e6-5c887d01f665" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c74598ce-a7f6-4888-a030-4b9794daa124</id><title>11/25 - Dear Diary - open call for art</title><updated>2019-12-10T03:28:32.095509+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LIC ARTS OPEN&lt;br/&gt;📍 Long Island City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 11/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://licartsopen.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIC Arts Open invites artists who document, report and journal to participate in Dear Diary.    Diaries are fascinating objects that usually contain secrets, private thoughts and we invite artists of all disciplines and mediums to participate in our show which will be on show at LIC Arts Open's Gallery ONE at The Factory LIC, 30-30 47th Ave, LIC, 11101.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We accept all disciplines including painting, sculpture, photography, video, installation and multi-media however video equipment is not provided and if your project requires technology please state so on the application.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are encouraging as many artists as possible to show in our 2000 sq foot gallery in one of LIC's signature buildings, The Factory.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline Nov 25th, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Notification Nov 27th, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Drop off Artwork Nov 30 &amp; Dec 1 (Times TBC)&lt;br/&gt;Reception December 5th 5pm - 8pm&lt;br/&gt;Show Closes on Jan 3rd&lt;br/&gt;Pick up Jan 4th &amp; 5th (Times TBC)&lt;br/&gt;*Please note there is an application fee that offsets the installation costs and helps to pay for the refreshments. If you have previously participated please select option 2 otherwise if new to LIC Arts Open please select option 1.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork should be dropped off on November 30th &amp; Dec 1st between the hours of 2 -5 pm only. We cannot accept work at other times.&lt;br/&gt;Work must be ready to hang and we do not allow shipping; all work must be hand-delivered on the designated times and dates.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Gallery commission is 25% please price accordingly&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Important Information&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Standard Artwork Drop off&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork must be ready to hang with appropriate fixings etc. Please know that some walls are the cinderblock/cement and others are drywall. If you are bringing a sculptural or video work, please provide the necessary technology. If you can provide pedestals that are helpful but not required.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have proposed performance or other live work (an installation, etc.) we will contact you directly with further information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Please take/remove your wrappings at drop off unless you are fine with it being disposed of; we do not have storage for wrappings, boxes, bubble wrap, etc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Storage:  We have no storage for wrappings or art.  Please only bring the pieces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are really interested in showing the work of artists from outside of LIC, Queens &amp; NYC but all work must be hand-delivered in person (i.e. either yourself or someone dropping off in your place). Nevertheless, if you live in another city but can drop off and pick up the work at the specified dates and times then please feel free to apply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please use this form to apply, please cut and paste into your browser&lt;br/&gt;https://form.jotform.com/trimistopheles/dear-diary-open-call&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c74598ce-a7f6-4888-a030-4b9794daa124" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>