<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-04T04:16:25-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>bcbc21b1-aa22-4333-bd69-01209feb601b</id><title>6/1 - SOLO, GROUP &amp;amp; CONCEPT SUBMISSIONS (SEASON 16: 2019/2020)</title><updated>2019-05-04T04:16:25.222210+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Manifest Creative Research Gallery and Drawing Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Cincinnati, OH, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSION PROCESS FOR SEASON 16 IS NOW OPEN!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Manifest is happy to receive proposals of various types and accepts these on an ongoing basis starting usually in late winter, reviewing them starting in early June in consideration for the upcoming exhibit season. No notifications are made until the final season schedule is decided (usually by the end of July), but updates are sent to all artists at the start of our committee's review process. Anyone can submit a proposal, and selections are open to all traditional and non-traditional genre and media.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On average, one-third of Manifest's exhibits are dedicated to solo exhibits. Solo exhibitors have included local, regional, and national artists from as far away as New York City, San Francisco, Canada, and Hong Kong. Our exhibits are routinely reviewed in local and sometimes national news and art publications (including Sculpture Magazine, Drawing Magazine, and Art Papers among others). And while our focus is on providing a museum-like experience of visual art, patrons and collectors, including museums, watch Manifest and our publications for future acquisitions and exhibitors. We believe this makes the spots in our schedule reserved for solo or proposed exhibits highly valuable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNUAL CASH AWARD: The annual Manifest Grand Jury Prize will result in the awarding of one significant cash prize ($2500) to a single work selected as the 'best of the entire season'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;View the full prospectus and apply online at &lt;a href="http://www.manifestgallery.org/proposals." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manifestgallery.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For questions email info@manifestgallery.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/bcbc21b1-aa22-4333-bd69-01209feb601b" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8cc63b69-4be4-428e-98ae-54bc541bebfc</id><title>7/13 - Chelsea Gallery OPEN CALL</title><updated>2019-05-04T04:16:25.222153+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Field Projects&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/13/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com/open-call/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Field Projects is pleased to announce our Summer 2019 Open Call! Emerging and mid-career artists are invited to submit their work for consideration.. All submissions will be considered by our Guest Curators: Tess Schwab, Diretor Jenkins Johnson Projects. Simultaneously, Field Projects Panel (4-5 curators) will be considering the submissions for future solo exhibitions, group exhibitions, 2 person exhibitions, art fairs, pop-up shows, off-site exhibitions and our studio visit program, where we invite outside curators to accompany us to your studio. (85% of the artists we have shown in the last 8 years have been discovered through the Open Call.) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With your submission you will get several opportunities:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. Summer Exhibition by our Guest Curator: Tess Schwab, Director Jenkins Johnson Projects&lt;br/&gt;2. Online Exhibition &lt;br/&gt;3. Future Solo and Group Exhibitions at Field Projects.&lt;br/&gt;4. Future Art Fairs with Field Projects.&lt;br/&gt;5. Outside Exhibitions by our FP panel members.&lt;br/&gt;6. Studio Visit pool for NYC Artists.&lt;br/&gt;7. Field Magazine&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Field Projects is an NYC-based project space located in the heart of Chelsea's gallery district. As an artist run space, we are committed to opening the field of exhibition opportunities to other working artists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow our website link above or cut and paste : &lt;a href="http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com/open-call/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submit :&lt;br/&gt;up to 5 images of your work&lt;br/&gt;Artist Statement&lt;br/&gt;CV&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline : July 13th, 11:59 PM !!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Summer Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;The theme of the show will come from the work submitted. &lt;br/&gt;Selected artists will be notified by July 22nd, 2019&lt;br/&gt;All artwork must arrive at Field Projects by Thursday, August 1st, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;Summer Exhibition opens August 8th, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Summer Exhibition closes August 31th, 2019&lt;br/&gt;All artwork in the exhibition will be for sale, with artists receiving 50% of final sale. &lt;br/&gt;We look forward to seeing your work!!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Field Projects&lt;br/&gt;526 W 26th Street, &lt;br/&gt;#807&lt;br/&gt;New York, NY 10001&lt;br/&gt;info@fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;www.fieldprojectsgallery.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8cc63b69-4be4-428e-98ae-54bc541bebfc" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>