<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-31T01:17:01-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>958d04d4-ae52-4e24-b25e-741c7ad51f12</id><title>7/15 - Call for proposals/open reading period</title><updated>2019-05-31T01:17:01.763188+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Catalpa&lt;br/&gt;📍 Los Angeles, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://catalpa3000.net/proposals"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This reading period/call for proposals is open to all genres, mediums, and disciplines. If we think the work/project/proposal is a good fit we will contact you to discuss next steps. Our “publications” can take the shape of books, video, audio, objects, exhibitions, performances, etc. We welcome work in progress, interdisciplinary, and collaborative projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application instructions are available here: &lt;a href="https://catalpa3000.net/proposals" target="_blank"&gt;https://catalpa3000.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/958d04d4-ae52-4e24-b25e-741c7ad51f12" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>011793b9-11eb-4b40-8c37-bf5182cd9a27</id><title>6/30 - Open Call: ARTWorks Inc</title><updated>2019-05-31T01:17:01.763153+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jamaica Arts Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 Jamaica, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.jcal.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamaica Center for Arts &amp; Learning, Inc. (JCAL) invites Queens County artists to apply to participate in our newly initiated professional development program, Artists Residency &amp; Training Seminar Series (ARTWorks, Inc.) Program.  It teaches visual artists to regard their work as a small business, identify their entrepreneurial and professional goals and create a long-term plan for accomplishing them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTWorks, Inc. is a two tier program:  Resident Fellows Tier: 2 Resident Fellows receive monetary support of $10,000 each, a full time studio at Jamaica Art Center, access to the ARTWorks, Inc. Seminar Series which will culminate in a curated solo exhibit with inclusion in the ARTWorks, Inc catalogue; Seminar Fellows Tier: Twelve Seminar Fellows are invited to access the 10 month Seminar Series, some scheduled studio time, an exhibit stipend and be included in a group show in JAC’s Miller gallery and inclusion in the ARTWork, Inc catalogue and receive a $500 stipend. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;​&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTWorks, Inc. is a fellowship that serves New York City’s (favorable to Queens’ artists) emerging and underrepresented artists. It offers training in cultural entrepreneurial skills through hands on practicum, educational seminars and mentorships with established working artists and cultural leaders. The program culminates in a group exhibit that has an ARTWorks, Inc. catalogue for the works created and/or curated during the ARTWorks, Inc. fellowship period. The goal is for the fellows to walk away with knowledge for a successful self fulfilled arts career in a range of communities from self defined and emergent to an existing, well defined and competitive global marketplace. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The ARTWork, Inc. artists have access to JCAL’s administrative offices and equipment, including a fax machine, copy machine and computers.  In addition to the studio provided, the artist may also use JCAL’s workshop studio facilities, including a ceramics studio equipped with kilns and a computer design studio.  Theses studios are generally available for use during operating hours Monday through Friday and whenever they are not occupied by JCAL workshops that regularly take place on Saturdays.    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ARTWorks, Inc. Seminar Series - From October 2019 to August 2020, the seminar schedule includes monthly Off-site Saturdays and/or 3rd Wednesday lectures. Each of the artists will be exposed to mentoring artists and institutional leaders through studio &amp; institutional visits, with peer-to-peer, group and one-on-one guidance and feedback. In addition, JCAL’s Director of Programs &amp; Artist Services will be available as a resource to discuss issues and provide advice to these artists. At the end of the series, in honor of the group’s accomplishments, there will be both solo exhibits of the designated two Resident Fellows and the group exhibition for up to 10 ARTWorks, Inc. artists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;apply through submitable platform, &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2Xf6xt1" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;please visit www.jcal.org for instruction&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/011793b9-11eb-4b40-8c37-bf5182cd9a27" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7011c4f3-8411-472c-a36a-18298a48252e</id><title>6/30 - Open Call: Artist Co-Op 2019</title><updated>2019-05-31T01:17:01.763112+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jamaica Center for Arts and Learning&lt;br/&gt;📍 Jamaica, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.jcal.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Platform for Queens Based Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Once a membership based program, JCAL's Artist Co-Op has been reborn as the center's annual exhibition featuring emerging and mid-career artists from the borough of Queens and NYC. The goal of the exhibition seeks to reflect the diversity of artistic expression in Queens. Submissions will be reviewed by a distinguished panel of peer artists, curators, and JCAL administrators. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;​Since its founding, JCAL has supported the creation and presentation of local, emerging, or established artists. JCAL serves visual and performing artists by providing free/low cost work and exhibition space. It has exhibited renowned artists such as Romare Bearden, Isamu Noguchi, and Elizabeth Catlett, and provided residencies to Lorenzo Pace, Lorna Simpson, and Wangechi Mutu, during the early stages of their careers.&lt;br/&gt;Accepted Media: painting, drawing, sculpture, mixed media, installation, and video/multi-media &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Video/multi-media: If works are accepted, the artist must provide all equipment for display. JCAL is not liable for damage or theft. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Performance &amp; Social Practice: Artists working in Performance and Social Practice are welcome, but physical artworks as a result of the process or documentation of the process can only be submitted and displayed, please include a description of the process in your Artists Statement.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork Size Limit: Flexible in size constraints, but keep in mind the nature of a group exhibition. Gallery Height total 18', Height to track lighting 7'. Gallery Dimensions: 48 'x 22 'x 18'/10'/8' x 22'    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: June 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Announcement of Artists Accepted: August 2019&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: To Be Decided 2020&lt;br/&gt;Location: JCAL's Miller Gallery  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Requirements for the Application: &lt;br/&gt;-Artist Statement (300 words or less)&lt;br/&gt;-CV&lt;br/&gt;-Image  List: Title, Medium, Size, Date (Titles of Images must correspond with  the list, all JPEG's must be labeled ie."01_ArtistLastName"  "02_ArtistLastName" etc.)&lt;br/&gt;-3 JPEGS &lt;br/&gt;-Additional Notes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;apply through submittable platform at &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2JORCmr" target="_blank"&gt;https://bit.ly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;visit www.jcal.org for application instruction&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7011c4f3-8411-472c-a36a-18298a48252e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2124ccb2-0d3a-4abc-9590-73bfd381b01b</id><title>6/26 - 2019 LONDON, UK ARTIST RESIDENCY OPEN CALL (ART-LED GRIEF RESEARCH)</title><updated>2019-05-31T01:17:01.763047+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;CENTRE. SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS: Applied Grief &amp;amp; Bereavement Research&lt;br/&gt;📍  , United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/26/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING:&lt;br/&gt;OPEN CALL&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ANNUM: &lt;br/&gt;2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PARTICIPATING CITIES:&lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For Berlin, Germany deadlines please see our website for more information.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;***NEXT DEADLINE - SHORT-TERM RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING***:&lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom Autumn 2019 Residency Cohort 1 (1 Month Program): 03 JUN 2019 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ADDITIONAL DEADLINES - SHORT-TERM RESIDENCY PROGRAMMING:&lt;br/&gt;London, United Kingdom Autumn 2019 Residency Cohort 2 (1 Month Program): 26 JUN 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS is now accepting applications for residency programming commencing in 2019. Artists, researchers, and other arts professionals are encouraged to apply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ORGANIZATION:&lt;br/&gt;Established in 2009, the CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS is a Canadian organization dedicated to the development of applied grief and bereavement research. Documented through the use of practice-led methods within art and comprised of work from an interdisciplinary network of creative and technical practitioners; the CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS  is committed to the advancement of the arts and sciences; providing programming in support of education; public and professional engagement; and the development of field research in partnership with local, national, and international academic bodies, institutions, foundations, and non-profits.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SELECTION CRITERIA &amp; ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:&lt;br/&gt;The artist-in-residence candidates are selected annually through an open call application process or in some cases, by invitation. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The residency program encourages experimentation and the development of multi/interdisciplinary studio work grounded in research within the field of grief and bereavement. The work can encompass and explore varying physical and emotional processes (or loss) that people undergo. Previous residents and collaborators have undertaken both theoretical-historical and practice-led projects working with, but not limited to the following subject matter: the aging process and the elderly; cancer, disease, and terminal illness; sex work and sexual assault; abortion and miscarriage; suicide and survivorship; mental illness, mental health, and trauma; spousal and familial loss; and associated grief and bereavement-centered themes etc.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The residency aims to provide working artistic professionals with a platform for research and production; one that may lead to expanded possibilities, collaboration, a broader network, and possibly new works. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information and to apply please review the Residency Guide and complete an Application Form by visiting:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To be notified of upcoming opportunities including new and existing programming, open calls, and initiatives, please subscribe to our newsletter here:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/contact/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;——&lt;br/&gt;CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS (Est. 2009) &lt;br/&gt;Applied Grief and Bereavement Research&lt;br/&gt;Interdisciplinary/Multidisciplinary Studio &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Follow us here:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/&lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/substructuredloss/&lt;br/&gt;https://vimeo.com/substructuredloss&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and to apply please review the Residency Guide and complete an Application Form by visiting:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/residencies/&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The completed application form and all applicable supplementary attachments must be submitted by email.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;——&lt;br/&gt;CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF SUBSTRUCTURED LOSS (Est. 2009) &lt;br/&gt;Applied Grief and Bereavement Research&lt;br/&gt;Interdisciplinary/Multidisciplinary Studio &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Follow us here:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.substructuredloss.org/&lt;br/&gt;https://www.facebook.com/substructuredloss/&lt;br/&gt;https://vimeo.com/substructuredloss&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2124ccb2-0d3a-4abc-9590-73bfd381b01b" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>