<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-30T03:18:23-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>8255fc99-e32c-40a8-8249-41df6bc760f4</id><title>8/10 - Bare Men: The Group Show</title><updated>2019-07-30T03:18:23.278828+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Abigail Ekue Photography&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 08/10/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.abigailekuephotography.com/bare-men-group-show"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bare Men: The Group Show is a group photography exhibition of the male nude curated and presented by Abigail Ekue Photography. This exhibit will showcase art which celebrates all expressions of the male nude - the sensuality, strength, vulnerability and sexuality.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All genres of photography featuring the male nude will be considered -- fine art, conceptual, fashion or glamour, erotic, outdoor/nature or urban, self-portraits, dance et al. Works do not have to feature a single body/model. Work must depict men/models age 21 and over.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Photographers at any stage of their career can submit. POC and LGBTQ photographers and those that represent those populations in their work are encouraged to submit their work. The show is also open to amateurs as long as your work is presented professionally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All submissions to send via this page: &lt;a href="https://www.abigailekuephotography.com/bare-men-group-show" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.abigailekuephotography.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8255fc99-e32c-40a8-8249-41df6bc760f4" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>3cf69f43-967b-418d-af5a-fa7103da78b6</id><title>7/31 - Sponsored Studio Space in World Trade Center</title><updated>2019-07-30T03:18:23.278773+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Silver Art Projects&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York City, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://silverart.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Silver Art Projects will establish itself on the entire 50th floor of 3 World Trade Center, hosting 30 artists every September for up to 8 months that are selected through an annual open call application process. Silver Art Projects hopes to foster a continual dialogue around contemporary art in the lower Manhattan community.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Artists will be selected by a rotating jury of fellow artists, curators, and neighborhood leaders based on a brief statement and examples of their work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is unstructured studio time and not product-oriented. Artists are encouraged to host studio visits and are welcome to make their own studio hours. Most importantly, Silver Art Projects asks artists to immersive themselves with the cohort and local community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All applications must be submitted using our online application system. We are unable to accept and will not review email or paper submissions. For all inquiries regarding Silver Art Projects, please email info@silverart.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/3cf69f43-967b-418d-af5a-fa7103da78b6" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>