<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-06T17:14:58-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>66ad27f9-149d-490e-803d-861a612b0e67</id><title>4/1 - OPEN CALL FOR VISUAL ARTISTS</title><updated>2019-03-06T17:14:58.789661+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;NOGO Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.NOGOArts.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOGO Arts announces an open call to visual and installation artists. &lt;br/&gt;WERQ: We’ve Been Doing This Our Whole Lives &lt;br/&gt;June 7, 2019 – June 30, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Cluster Gallery at Playground Brooklyn &lt;br/&gt;NOGO Arts seeks submissions from visual artists for a group show that fit into the larger theme of queer work and labor. WERQ is intended to celebrate bodies that labor, that do the work society can take for granted or simply chooses to ignore in order to queer office spaces. While we welcome submissions from all points of view, NOGO Arts encourages artists from under represented communities to submit work.  &lt;br/&gt;With WERQ, NOGO Arts seeks to queer a common workspace while recognizing the momentous 50th anniversary of the Stonewall Riots. While Stonewall is a historical marker, it was not the first time queer people rose up to do the work of social justice, hence: We’ve Been Doing This Our Whole Lives. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOGO Arts has its offices at the Playground Brooklyn, an independent coworking space in Gowanus. The Playground also is the home of Brooklyn Art Cluster’s new gallery space. Selected artists will have their work shown in the gallery which also serves as a common space for the Playground. Themes/topics could include (but are not limited to):&lt;br/&gt;•	Equal pay&lt;br/&gt;•	Equity and Inclusivity &lt;br/&gt;•	Inclusivity&lt;br/&gt;•	LGBTQ protection in the work place&lt;br/&gt;•	Queer Labor&lt;br/&gt;•	In/Visibility of work &lt;br/&gt;•	Play as work&lt;br/&gt;•	Work as subject&lt;br/&gt;•	Labor of art making&lt;br/&gt;•	Capitalism&lt;br/&gt;We are interested in curating an exhibit that crosses media and disciplines. &lt;br/&gt;The exhibit will include live performance twice during its run: at the opening night Friday June 7th and again on Wednesday June 19th.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOGO Arts is a nonprofit organization dedicated to promoting and presenting work in the LGBTQ Arts and Humanities. NOGO Arts does not charge a submission fee. Artists will be expected to meet technical requirements as stated by the gallery, ensure delivery and pickup of artwork by agreed upon date, and attend the opening party or performance event (if they live locally). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;NOGO Arts, Inc. is a 501(c)(3) charitable organization under the IRS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested artists should go to www.NOGOArts.org/werqsubmission to submit work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contact Todd Coulter at todd@nogoarts.org with any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/66ad27f9-149d-490e-803d-861a612b0e67" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f11f8c9e-dbb4-4fc5-8593-2600b564b145</id><title>4/17 - 4 WEEKS LEFT TO APPLY: Superfine! Art Fair | New York 2019</title><updated>2019-03-06T17:14:58.789630+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Superfine! Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.superfine.world/exhibit-nyc"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rapidly growing art fair that has spread its "make art yours" mantra to Washington DC, Miami, and Los Angeles returns for the third year to its easy-to-get-to, high traffic Meatpacking location in Manhattan. Superfine! NYC '19 applications close on Wednesday, April 17th, however applications are reviewed and accepted on a rolling basis. 80% of artist booths and 50% of gallery booths are already reserved by other cutting-edge leaders of the new contemporary movement, and all booths will likely be sold out before the application deadline. Here's what's still available:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GALLERIES:&lt;br/&gt;• 14 booths in our Gallery Pavilion ranging from 16 - 28 linear feet of wall ($4,000 - $7,000)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SOLO ARTISTS:&lt;br/&gt;• 7 Elevate Booths: 12-foot artist booths; the fair's most popular size ($3,000)&lt;br/&gt;• 3 Immerse Booths: 16-foot artist booths for artists wishing to have a larger footprint in the fair ($4,000)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! receives frequent and consistent media coverage in outlets like Washington Post, New York Post, and Artnet, and the fair holds the key to the growing, "maturing", and engaging young collector masses. About 20% of visitors make a significant purchase of at least $500, and 90% of past exhibitors report selling to almost exclusively new clients outside of their existing collector network.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! NYC will be hosted from May 1-5 on 14th Street in the Meatpacking District (at the foot of the bustling High Line Park). Superfine! is an art fair engineered for galleries who recognize a needed shift in the art market and for artists treating their talents as a serious art business.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GET A BETTER SENSE OF THE FAIR:&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! on Artnet: &lt;a href="https://news.artnet.com/partner-content/superfine-la" target="_blank"&gt;https://news.artnet.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! NY '18 Recap Video: &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/_vyyZ8LQjOk" target="_blank"&gt;https://youtu.be&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibitor Testimonials: &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/testimonials/" target="_blank"&gt;https://superfine.world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Review our floor plan and decide which available space you would like (link below).&lt;br/&gt;2. Fill out and submit your application (~10-15 min., link below).&lt;br/&gt;3. Email five high-quality artwork images to exhibit@superfine.world (these are only examples for initial promotion, you may show different/more works for the fair itself).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FLOOR PLAN + EXHIBITOR INFO:&lt;br/&gt;https://superfine.world/exhibit-nyc&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DIRECT LINK TO APPLICATION:&lt;br/&gt;https://na3.docusign.net/Member/PowerFormSigning.aspx?PowerFormId=7ef148e8-58c5-4885-896a-a3b157674304&amp;env=na3&amp;v=2&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f11f8c9e-dbb4-4fc5-8593-2600b564b145" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>32222504-b5fe-41a4-aef5-1cb98cfc7d0c</id><title>3/18 - Sanctuary, National Juried Exhibition</title><updated>2019-03-06T17:14:58.789601+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arc Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 San Francisco, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/18/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href=" "&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The word 'Sanctuary' has recently been associated with individual and municipality resistance to the Federal enforcement of immigration laws. 'Sanctuary' itself has a wide range of definitions: a place offering shelter, a sacred or consecrated place, a container of holy things, a refuge for humans or wildlife, and a place offering immunity from law. We are seeking works that broadly define 'Sanctuary.' Works that convey political activism, faith and religion, wildlife protections, and a place of refuge, peace and safety are welcome, as well as abstract works that express the meaning of 'Sanctuary.'  Juror: Bryan Yedinak, Themes + Projects, San Francisco, CA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online application: &lt;a href="https://www.arc-sf.com/sanctuary.html" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.arc-sf.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Email ArcgallerySF@gmail.com with any questions. If you would like to talk to us by phone, please include your phone number in your email.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/32222504-b5fe-41a4-aef5-1cb98cfc7d0c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>980d6525-2470-41c7-a01b-f0928c4bd9fc</id><title>3/14 - Grennpoint Gallery March 15th People&amp;#39;s Choice Salon Show- WIN $200 AND A SOLO SHOW!</title><updated>2019-03-06T17:14:58.789567+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greenpoint Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://thegreenpointgallery.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WIN 200$ and a SOLO SHOW!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Greenpoint Gallery is now accepting submissions for our March 15th People's Choice Salon Show!&lt;br/&gt;Friday, March 15th, 2019 at 8pm.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: Thursday, March 14th, 2019 at 11pm&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For this show, we let the people decide, which means everyone who attends votes for the winners! We pass out ballots at the door and guests who attends choose the winners! It is always one of our most well attended nights, boasting record art sales and a large community of fellow artists and art lovers!&lt;br/&gt;Best in Show wins $200 and a solo show! Runner-up winners receive a slot in a group show with other runner-up winners! Submit today-&lt;br/&gt;We have two gallery floors and a stellar lineup of local bands!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt;Though it is free to submit, there is a $5 registration fee per piece for works accepted into the show. Registration fees go directly toward furnishing the cash prize and expenses of the reception.&lt;br/&gt;The show is for one night only. Artists must deliver the work to the Gallery IN PERSON and the work must arrive READY TO HANG. Artists must also come back to pick up any unsold work after the show.&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE FOR REGISTRATION AND DROP OFF IS THURSDAY, March 14th  at 11pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We sell works at EVERY SHOW! We have sold hundreds of pieces in the $150-$500 range. And, as always, we NEVER take a percentage of any works sold in our dedication to support our artistic community.&lt;br/&gt;Curator Shawn James personally reviews each submission and everyone who enters will receive a personal email notifying them if they are accepted or not. Drop off and pick up times will be included in acceptance emails.&lt;br/&gt;Good luck to you all!&lt;br/&gt;Please help us spread the word to all artists you know! Come and GET YOUR ART ON !&lt;br/&gt;Website: www.thegreenpointgallery.com&lt;br/&gt;Facebook: www.facebook.com/events/1041774649345225/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All MEDIUMS ARE ACCEPTED!!&lt;br/&gt;Size Limit: 24" x 36" and under&lt;br/&gt;As always....It's FREE to submit work.&lt;br/&gt;Submit jpegs or a link to your website to: greenpointgallery@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/980d6525-2470-41c7-a01b-f0928c4bd9fc" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>74399a3d-740b-4182-a50d-4dae996c7252</id><title>3/17 - Call for Applications:  Saas-Fee Summer Institute of Art 2019 | New York City</title><updated>2019-03-06T17:14:58.789526+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Saas-Fee Summer Institute of Art&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://sfsia.art/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hosted by Performance Space New York&lt;br/&gt;June 1 - June 15&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;States of Consciousness in Cognitive Capitalism&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Building upon our past four year engagement with topics concerning estrangement, individuation, collectivity and art and politics in cognitive capitalism, Saas-Fee Summer Institute of Art 2019 will focus upon states of consciousness. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As we have witnessed firsthand in the 2016 U.S. election, the political potential stored in the complex networked analytics of information and their neural analogues are now being fully engaged as apparatuses of control. Economies of attention and dis-attention, click bait, cloud analytics, memes, social media and fake news have now taken center stage in the process of subjectivation and the interiorization of domination. Could the spreading wave of Populism worldwide be the result of forms of embodied and extended cognition linked to contemporary neoliberal apparatuses? The central thesis of this year’s program posits that these are the initial constituents and first signs of an impending crisis that define a later stage of cognitive capitalism. New technologies on the horizon, such as brain computer interfaces, cortical implants and optogenetics, provide an imminent threat and could create the core technologies that instigate, track, measure, and record the brains’ capacities to generate electrical signals (or brain waves) during wake and sleep which then might be linked to the Internet and virtual platforms. Companies funded by DARPA, like Neuralink and Kernel, are at the forefront of these efforts to produce “total subsumption”. On the other hand, perhaps these new technologies will make brain power obsolete as humans are replaced by AI and robots and are no longer necessary for military regimes or physical and mental labor. As such, the nightmare of science fiction and right-leaning accelerationism might become reality. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SFSIA 2019 asks what effect these transformations might have on human consciousness and its various social and cultural expressions and permutations as defined in the fields of neuroaesthetics, psychology, politics, philosophy of mind, queer and gender studies, popular and visual culture, cultural and decolonial studies, art history, visual and sound art, film studies, as well as, sociology and economics. How might we together understand these changes in the context of artistic research programs that (already) use the lenses of post-humanism, transhumanism, and speculative materialism? Through discussions, workshops, deep readings and performative lectures, we aim to co-create new pathways of understanding and dissensus. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FACULTY&lt;br/&gt;Claire Bishop, Patricia Clough, Suzanne Dikker, Coco Fusco, Agnieszka Kurant, Sanford Kwinter, Joseph E. LeDoux, Carlo McCormick, Paul D. Miller aka DJ Spooky, Yann Moulier-Boutang, Warren Neidich (founder/director), Reza Negarestani, Alva Noë, Luciana Parisi, Christiane Paul, Daniel Pinchbeck, Florencia Portocarrero, Barry Schwabsky (co-director), Martha Schwendener, Sensorium (John Fitzgerald and Matthew Niederhauser), and Laura Wexler.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPLICATIONS&lt;br/&gt;Applications for SFSIA 2019 | New York City are open to students, practitioners and scholars from the fields of art (including video, photography, installation and multimedia), design, architecture, critical writing, science and technology studies, critical theory, cultural studies, film and media studies, and beyond. Please see our application for more information. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ABOUT SFSIA&lt;br/&gt;Saas-Fee Summer Institute of Art (SFSIA) is a nomadic, intensive summer academy with shifting programs in contemporary critical theory. SFSIA stresses an interdisciplinary approach to understanding the relationship between art and politics. SFSIA originated in Saas-Fee, Switzerland in 2015 and migrated to Berlin, Germany in 2016 where it is currently hosted by Spike. In 2019, this additional program will be hosted by Performance Space New York. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Saas-Fee Summer Institute of Art was founded and is directed by Warren Neidich and is co-directed by Barry Schwabsky. Sarrita Hunn is the artistic coordinator. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please see our website or contact info@sfsia.art for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/74399a3d-740b-4182-a50d-4dae996c7252" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>bb275487-af1a-4e29-9643-a267d5e169f0</id><title>4/1 - Open Call for a Solo Exhibition at Marlboro College&amp;#39;s Drury Gallery with $1k Stipend</title><updated>2019-03-06T17:14:58.789469+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Marlboro College&lt;br/&gt;📍 Marlboro , VT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.marlboro.edu/news/drury/open-call"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marlboro College is pleased to announce an Open Call for a solo exhibition in its Drury Gallery to open in the fall of 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This opportunity includes a reception, a $1,000 honorarium for the selected artist/proposal, and an event that actively engages both Marlboro College and the local community such as an interactive artist’s talk, workshop, or collaborative work of art. Both the exhibition and related program will be promoted on Marlboro College’s social media outlets. Marlboro College gallery directors and student associates will schedule a studio visit (virtual or in-person)  leading up to the opening of the exhibition. Artists are required to participate in the exhibitions' installation, although this participation need not include on-site supervision or physical labor.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Visual artists of all disciplines, at any stage of their career, from all geographical locations are encouraged to apply. Women, non-binary people, people of color, and non-able-bodied people are especially encouraged to apply. Proposals that include community engagement and meaningful interaction with the Marlboro Community will be prioritized. Artists will be selected based on the quality of their work, clarity of their proposal, and commitment to their artistic practice by a committee of students and faculty from Marlboro College. An alternate list of candidates/runners-up will be considered for future programming at the gallery and/or visiting artist engagements at the college.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Images: Please include at least 10 and up to 20 images of work that will be included in your exhibition or that exemplify the type of work you would present. Digital renderings or project schematics must be limited to three of these images. Parameters for digital files are indicated on the form.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist's Statement: 500 words max&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Narrative Bio: 200 words max&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CV&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proposal: 500 words max&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please describe your exhibition. What will be included in the gallery?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What are some of your inspirations and influences for this particular work?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please describe how your exhibition and/or related program will actively engage the students of Marlboro College and the local Marlboro community.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/bb275487-af1a-4e29-9643-a267d5e169f0" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>