<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-17T16:15:59-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>ab5e1e44-cd52-4b73-b080-0830fac4481a</id><title>5/17 - Combined Talents 2019 Annual Juried Competition</title><updated>2019-04-17T16:15:59.885064+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Florida State University Museum of Fine Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Tallahassee, FL, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://mofa.fsu.edu/participate/tallahassee-international/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Combined Talents" is an annual juried competition sponsored by the Florida State University Museum of Fine Arts (MoFA). The competition is open to artists within the United States, eighteen years of age or older, with all subject matter and media eligible for consideration. The entry fee is $20 for two works. Deadline to enter is May 17, 2019. Hallie Ringle, the Hugh Kaul Curator of Contemporary Art at the Birmingham Museum of Art (BMA) will be the juror for the competition. First prize is $1,000 and second prize is $500. The exhibition is scheduled for August 16 to September 29, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a complete prospectus, with link to the online entry form, please visit our website:&lt;br/&gt;http://mofa.fsu.edu/participate/tallahassee-international/&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ab5e1e44-cd52-4b73-b080-0830fac4481a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e69ce864-ad90-41dc-b360-b8483b259170</id><title>5/19 - FJORD Gallery 6th Annual Open Call</title><updated>2019-04-17T16:15:59.885009+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;FJORD Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.fjordspace.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FJORD Gallery is pleased to announce our 2019 Open Call!&lt;br/&gt;Artists are invited to submit their work for consideration in this group exhibition, to run July 6 – August 1, 2019. Applicants will be notified of acceptance by approximately two weeks after the submission deadline&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork must be delivered to gallery by June 29th and be install-ready.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists working in all mediums are encouraged to apply. The exhibition will be curated by Fjord members; there is no specified theme. Artists outside of Philadelphia are encouraged to apply, but will be responsible for shipping or delivering their work to and from the gallery. Please visit our website to see our previous juried exhibitions. This is an opportunity for us to learn about your work and to hopefully establish future relationships. We look forward to reviewing your work!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline to apply: May 19, 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition to run: July 6 – August 1&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Thursday, July 11 6-9pm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;-​Please submit a single multi-page PDF of your work, image list, CV and statement to fjord.submissions@gmail.com.&lt;br/&gt;-Name your PDF using the following format: LastName_FirstName_2019OpenCall.pdf&lt;br/&gt;-Files should be no larger than 10mb&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Submissions should include:&lt;br/&gt;-Up to 5 images or 3 videos (additional detail shots of 3d work or video stills may also be included)&lt;br/&gt;-If submitting video, please include Vimeo links&lt;br/&gt;-Image list; please include title, year, dimensions, and media&lt;br/&gt;-One page CV&lt;br/&gt;-Artist Statement (250 word max.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission fee is $20, payable through Paypal. Please submit payment to fjord.curator@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e69ce864-ad90-41dc-b360-b8483b259170" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>