<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-14T13:15:49-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>ca3b77fa-9bac-401a-b840-ca088cc29b0c</id><title>3/14 - INTERNATIONAL CALL FOR ART, ArtMaze Magazine Spring Edition: Issue 12</title><updated>2019-02-14T13:15:49.041455+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ArtMaze Magazine&lt;br/&gt;📍  , United Kingdom&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artmazemagazine.submittable.com/submit/133107/international-call-for-art-artmaze-mag-spring-edition-12"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art Maze Magazine is an independent artist-run and ad-free international print and online publication dedicated to showcasing and promoting experimental and progressive contemporary art, which reflects modern society and its environment, provokes conversation and action; fosters innovation and diversity of mediums which make today’s art scene so intriguing and versatile.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ELIGIBILITY: Artists are welcome to submit works in any medium: painting, drawing, sculpture, ceramics, printmaking, photography, textile, installation, mixed media, digital, film (only jpg + link to video) etc. All visual art mediums are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists or any art organisations on behalf of artists from all countries are welcome to submit their works for consideration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each submitted artist, wether selected for a publication or not, will receive a digital copy of the magazine's issue which he/she applied for.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: March 14th, 2019 (12:00 AM, midnight: end of the day 14th March - Eastern Standard Time)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;GUEST CURATOR: Tristian Koenig, Melbourne-based Gallerist&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW TO APPLY: www.artmazemag.com/call-for-art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DISTRIBUTION: Physical and digital copies of ArtMaze Mag are distributed worldwide via bookshops, galleries and online. More info: &lt;a href="http://artmazemag.com/shop/" target="_blank"&gt;http://artmazemag.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selected artists will be asked for high resolution images and will be published in the next print and digital issue of ArtMaze Magazine. Each (selected) artist will receive a 1 or 2-page spread in print and digital (PDF) magazine including bio, statement, website, and 1-5 featured artworks. All submitted artists will receive a complimentary PDF copy of the magazine and all published artists will be promoted on our website/social media. &lt;br/&gt;Physical copies of Art Maze Magazine are printed to the highest quality in London, UK.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ca3b77fa-9bac-401a-b840-ca088cc29b0c" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e39fed63-d69d-4ad1-8fc1-d167295ee629</id><title>6/15 - Rust Belt Biennial - open for photographic submissions</title><updated>2019-02-14T13:15:49.041408+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Rust Belt Biennial&lt;br/&gt;📍 Wilkes-Barre, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/15/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $35.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.rustbeltbiennial.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to introduce the first RUST BELT BIENNIAL, a celebration of photography with work realized throughout the Rust Belt Region in all its manifestations. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This land, its people, the pride and the struggles, the patina of the past and above all, the histories and memories ingrained in the soil across the region. It is time to make new memories and new histories, while revisiting and reevaluating old ones; It is time to start a new dialogue about the state of photography and it’s social, cultural and political effects in our society; it is time to give back to the photographic community but also the region; it is time for you to join us! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For our an inaugural Biennial we are grateful to have Andrew L. Moore as competition juror.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are honored to collaborate with the Sordoni Gallery at Wilkes University, in Wilkes-Barre, Penn., where the Biennial will be held from August 27th to October 5h of 2019. Additional information regarding the dates of the main exhibition with lectures and presentations will be published in the Spring.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our juried competition is hosted in an agreement between LensCulture and Rust Belt Biennial.  Using the SUBMIT HERE button &lt;br/&gt;(https://www.lensculture.com/competitions/Rust-Belt-Biennial/events) &lt;br/&gt;on our website will redirect you to LensCulture so that you can sign up for an account and submit your entry through the online entry portal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use this link to skip our website and go directly to the submission form on LensCulture:&lt;br/&gt;https://www.lensculture.com/competitions/Rust-Belt-Biennial/events&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What are we looking for?&lt;br/&gt;We are looking for photographic bodies of works that explore the social and cultural realities that represent or make a commentary of this very important region within the American landscape. &lt;br/&gt;Additionally, we are looking for both in progress or fully realized photographic work in printed form.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Who is eligible?&lt;br/&gt;All are welcome to submit work that was created within the Rust Belt Region (New York, Missouri, Pennsylvania, Ohio, Indiana, Michigan, West Virginia, Illinois, Iowa, Wisconsin)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist information:&lt;br/&gt;Legal Name&lt;br/&gt;Artist Name if different&lt;br/&gt;Address&lt;br/&gt;Email Address&lt;br/&gt;Telephone&lt;br/&gt;Statement (up to 500 words)&lt;br/&gt;Bio (up to 300 words)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Image information and file requirements:&lt;br/&gt;Title format for each image: Title, caption(optional), location&lt;br/&gt;Date&lt;br/&gt;Medium (Print Type)&lt;br/&gt;File naming: First and last name, image title&lt;br/&gt;Example: John_Smith-Image_Title.jpg&lt;br/&gt;File format: JPG&lt;br/&gt;File dimensions: 2500 pixels on the longest side&lt;br/&gt;Color space: sRGB&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission fee:&lt;br/&gt;$35 for up to 25 images&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e39fed63-d69d-4ad1-8fc1-d167295ee629" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>b5894a3b-52c1-4735-b2ab-9ae7eaf56fdc</id><title>5/1 - Flow</title><updated>2019-02-14T13:15:49.041369+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Philadelphia Sculptors&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Sculpture&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.philaflow.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philadelphia Sculptors seeks artists to create temporary outdoor floating sculptural installations for our Fall, 2019 exhibition "Flow," a collaboration with the Independence Seaport Museum. The exhibition will be sited in the boat basin adjacent to the Museum, located at Penn’s Landing on the Delaware River in Philadelphia and will run from October 11 – November 30, 2019. The intent of the exhibition is to unite art with the river, and with the Museum’s mission and programming.  Five juried artists, along with five invited artists previously selected, will interpret the river and how it affects, and is affected by, human and natural history; human and natural migrations; climate change and the environment; economic development; and political currents. The geographic focus of the show is on the Americas and we are seeking artists from Mexico, South and Central America, and Canada, along with artists from the US and its territories. The jurors will be Nato Thompson, and Teresa Jaynes. The exhibition is also co-sponsored by the Dina Wind Art Foundation. Accepted artists will receive a $2,000 honorarium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and how to apply, go to www.philaflow.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/b5894a3b-52c1-4735-b2ab-9ae7eaf56fdc" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>baf7223d-18ff-4d2c-8ae1-bf0e8a9290f7</id><title>3/22 - Open Call for Solo Exhibitions and Curatorial Projects</title><updated>2019-02-14T13:15:49.041311+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;CUE Art Foundation&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/22/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://cueartfoundation.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CUE’s Open Calls provide artists and emerging curators the opportunity and necessary resources to realize an exhibition at CUE’s storefront gallery in East Chelsea, New York.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each year, a panel of established artists and curators select two solo exhibitions and one curatorial project to be realized at CUE. Finalists are paired with a member of the selection panel, who works with them as a mentor throughout the process of planning and mounting the exhibition. CUE provides institutional guidance, generous honoraria, a shipping budget, and an accompanying exhibition catalogue with a critical essay by a participant in CUE's Art Critic Mentoring Program. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications are accepted once annually in the spring. The deadline for the current Open Call is March 22, 2019.    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SOLO EXHIBITION INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;CUE's Solo Exhibition Open Call is for artists who:&lt;br/&gt;-Have not had a solo show in a commercial NYC gallery within the last five years&lt;br/&gt;-Do not have current, consistent commercial gallery representation in the United States&lt;br/&gt;-Are not currently enrolled in a degree program&lt;br/&gt;-Have a demonstrated, consistent studio practice outside an academic setting for three or more years&lt;br/&gt;-Must currently live and work in the United States&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;-The exhibition program is open to artists working in all disciplines.&lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to artists who present ideas or topics that are not well-represented in the commercial sector.&lt;br/&gt;-CUE strongly encourages applications that contribute to our ongoing commitment to diversity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What Finalists receive:&lt;br/&gt;-Five-week solo exhibition at CUE Art Foundation in 2020&lt;br/&gt;-Curatorial support/mentoring from an established artist or curator on the selection panel&lt;br/&gt;-Opportunities to develop related public programming &lt;br/&gt;-32-page full color catalogue with essay produced through the Art Critic Mentoring Program and a statement by the curator&lt;br/&gt;-$5,000 unrestricted honorarium&lt;br/&gt;-An art shipping and art handling budget&lt;br/&gt;-Opening reception&lt;br/&gt;-Press materials and PR support &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CURATORIAL PROJECT INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;-Proposals must be conceptually rigorous and focus on artists, projects, and themes that are innovative, challenging, and engaging.&lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to proposals that demonstrate a creative approach to curatorial research methods and the exhibition plan, as well as those that present ideas or topics that are not well-represented in the commercial sector.&lt;br/&gt;-The proposal must include four or more artists, half of whom must qualify as under-recognized (no gallery representation and no solo exhibitions in a major venue within the past five years).&lt;br/&gt;-Curators may not include their own work in the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;-The curator and all proposed artists must live and work in the United States.    &lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to those in the beginning stages of their curatorial careers.&lt;br/&gt;-CUE strongly encourages applications that contribute to our ongoing commitment to diversity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What the opportunity includes:&lt;br/&gt;-Five-week exhibition at CUE Art Foundation in 2020&lt;br/&gt;-Curatorial support/mentoring from an established artist or curator on the selection panel&lt;br/&gt;-Opportunities to develop related public programming &lt;br/&gt;-Full color catalogue with essay produced through the Art Critic Mentoring Program&lt;br/&gt;-$2,500 unrestricted honorarium&lt;br/&gt;-$2,500 to divide amongst the participating artists and program speakers&lt;br/&gt;-$2,000 production budget&lt;br/&gt;-An art shipping and art handling budget&lt;br/&gt;-Opening reception&lt;br/&gt;-Press materials and PR support&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at &lt;a href="http://cueartfoundation.org/open-call" target="_blank"&gt;http://cueartfoundation.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, please visit our website or email Lilly Hern-Fondation, Programs Associate: lilly@cueartfoundation.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/baf7223d-18ff-4d2c-8ae1-bf0e8a9290f7" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>