<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-07T21:48:19-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>d4d10671-61f6-47ae-a3bd-bcc3ef01487e</id><title>4/1 - The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show - Open Call to Artists for Submissions</title><updated>2019-02-07T21:48:19.608792+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Episcopal Church of the Heavenly Rest&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://heavenlyrest.wufoo.com/forms/z1hr8tsj0w3znbe/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Episcopal Church of the Heavenly Rest’s (CHR) new arts initiative’s mission is for CHR to shine as a community where artistic creativity of many forms is valued as a spiritual practice and a force for reconciliation. We aim to nurture artists, deepen our shared experience of their work, and invite the greater community of all faiths to explore our common humanity through the medium of art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CHR is hosting The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Theme: We All Belong&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Call for Submissions: We all draw inspiration from our communities. What does belonging mean to you?  We call on New York City artists to respond to the question and the community around them across media and styles. A committee will select works for the exhibition based on how well the artist responds to the theme within the criteria set forth in the registration form. Selected works will be exhibited at The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show.&lt;br/&gt;      &lt;br/&gt;Requirements: Open to New York City Artists (from one of the five boroughs) over the age of 21, work submitted must be appropriate for viewing of all ages. Submitted work must be complete and exhibition ready. To be considered, work must meet standards of quality determined by committee. Every work submitted must be accompanied by an artist contract provided by CHR at time of drop off. Artists must meet professional standards of composition and presentation of their work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Additional Information: The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show and opening reception will take place Thursday, May 9, 2019, 6 -8pm. Art will be exhibited in CHR’s Darlington Hall and Gallery Undercroft Exhibition Spaces from May 9 through September 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Instructions: submissions must be made online via the provided Registration Link or on the CHR website, &lt;a href="http://heavenlyrest.org/upcoming-events/" target="_blank"&gt;http://heavenlyrest.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d4d10671-61f6-47ae-a3bd-bcc3ef01487e" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>