<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-04-17T09:15:59-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>ab5e1e44-cd52-4b73-b080-0830fac4481a</id><title>5/17 - Combined Talents 2019 Annual Juried Competition</title><updated>2019-04-17T09:15:59.457738+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Florida State University Museum of Fine Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 Tallahassee, FL, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/17/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://mofa.fsu.edu/participate/tallahassee-international/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Combined Talents" is an annual juried competition sponsored by the Florida State University Museum of Fine Arts (MoFA). The competition is open to artists within the United States, eighteen years of age or older, with all subject matter and media eligible for consideration. The entry fee is $20 for two works. Deadline to enter is May 17, 2019. Hallie Ringle, the Hugh Kaul Curator of Contemporary Art at the Birmingham Museum of Art (BMA) will be the juror for the competition. First prize is $1,000 and second prize is $500. The exhibition is scheduled for August 16 to September 29, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a complete prospectus, with link to the online entry form, please visit our website:&lt;br/&gt;http://mofa.fsu.edu/participate/tallahassee-international/&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/ab5e1e44-cd52-4b73-b080-0830fac4481a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e69ce864-ad90-41dc-b360-b8483b259170</id><title>5/19 - FJORD Gallery 6th Annual Open Call</title><updated>2019-04-17T09:15:59.457707+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;FJORD Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Philadelphia, PA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.fjordspace.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FJORD Gallery is pleased to announce our 2019 Open Call!&lt;br/&gt;Artists are invited to submit their work for consideration in this group exhibition, to run July 6 – August 1, 2019. Applicants will be notified of acceptance by approximately two weeks after the submission deadline&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artwork must be delivered to gallery by June 29th and be install-ready.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists working in all mediums are encouraged to apply. The exhibition will be curated by Fjord members; there is no specified theme. Artists outside of Philadelphia are encouraged to apply, but will be responsible for shipping or delivering their work to and from the gallery. Please visit our website to see our previous juried exhibitions. This is an opportunity for us to learn about your work and to hopefully establish future relationships. We look forward to reviewing your work!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline to apply: May 19, 11:59pm&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition to run: July 6 – August 1&lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Thursday, July 11 6-9pm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submission Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;-​Please submit a single multi-page PDF of your work, image list, CV and statement to fjord.submissions@gmail.com.&lt;br/&gt;-Name your PDF using the following format: LastName_FirstName_2019OpenCall.pdf&lt;br/&gt;-Files should be no larger than 10mb&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Submissions should include:&lt;br/&gt;-Up to 5 images or 3 videos (additional detail shots of 3d work or video stills may also be included)&lt;br/&gt;-If submitting video, please include Vimeo links&lt;br/&gt;-Image list; please include title, year, dimensions, and media&lt;br/&gt;-One page CV&lt;br/&gt;-Artist Statement (250 word max.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission fee is $20, payable through Paypal. Please submit payment to fjord.curator@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e69ce864-ad90-41dc-b360-b8483b259170" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>e827f435-f4ea-46f1-9aea-007d447f0995</id><title>5/25 - Open Call for Artists - &amp;quot;Patterns of Influence&amp;quot;</title><updated>2019-04-17T09:15:59.457671+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Painting Center&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/25/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.thepaintingcenter.org/juried-exhibitions/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How does your artistic practice inform your teaching practice? How does observing and nurturing your student’s artistic growth and development impact your own art? Artist/Educators are invited to submit to a juried exhibition highlighting their work at The Painting Center, an artist run, non-profit art gallery in the heart of Chelsea, NYC. Patterns of Influence will be highly publicized with a catalogue featuring the artists' images and personal statements addressing the interrelationship of their artistic and teaching practices. The Painting Center is interested in work in all media (under 36” in any direction) by artist/educators for this juried exhibition. This exhibition is curated by Andrea Kantrowitz, Sue Collier and Barbara Laube.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition is open to all media. &lt;br/&gt;Exhibition Dates: July 16 – August 10, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: May 25, 2019 &lt;br/&gt;Notification Date: June 1, 2019 &lt;br/&gt;Opening Reception: Thursday, July 18, 6 - 8 pm&lt;br/&gt;Artists and Educators Public Forum: Saturday, July 27, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Application Fee: $40 for 1 to 5 images.&lt;br/&gt;Size Limitation: Artwork that exceeds 36" in any dimension will not be considered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To Apply Visit:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://thepaintingcenter.slideroom.com/#/login/program/47763&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/e827f435-f4ea-46f1-9aea-007d447f0995" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>2870d9f9-5a1e-4bbc-9f6a-76f84a598452</id><title>5/14 - Open Call For Portraiture: Rendering Likeness Volume 2 at two Brooklyn Gallery locations</title><updated>2019-04-17T09:15:59.457613+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;La Bodega Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.labodega-gallery.com/opportunities-1#/renderinglikeness"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEN CALL: Rendering Likeness: Volume 2&lt;br/&gt;Contemporary portraiture takes many forms and encompasses countless conceptual viewpoints, mediums and techniques that explore a myriad of subject matter. Last year in one of our most popular shows La Bodega Gallery exhibited a hugely diverse group of portraits and this year we are doing it again…in two locations! This year we are collaborating with a second space, the artist run gallery "Established Gallery" in Brooklyn to bring you even more!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are currently accepting submissions for the contemporary portraiture exhibitions entitled “Rendering Likeness, Volume 2”. This open call is open to both emerging and established artists who create works of portraiture in any style or medium. For this open call we are inviting to demonstrate their creative approach to portraiture. Portraits can be figurative, abstract or conceptual. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There will be TWO curated shows at TWO separate spaces in Brooklyn (La Bodega Gallery and Established Gallery), if your submission is accepted you will be placed in either space depending on which exhibition better suits the work.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION DEADLINE: &lt;br/&gt;5/14 11:59:59 pm &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Exhibition dates: &lt;br/&gt;May 31st – June 24th, 2019&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Locations: &lt;br/&gt;La Bodega Gallery, 695 5th Ave Brooklyn, NY &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Established Gallery, 75 6th Ave, Brooklyn, NY&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Contact: gallerylabodega@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Eligibility&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition is open to any artist, anywhere. ALL SUBMISSIONS MUST BE RECEIVED BY 5/14 11:59:59 pm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to apply:&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;1. Submissions must be via email at submission.gallerylabodega@gmail.com. We require you to upload 1 - 3 images, your CV, and artist statement. Submission does not guarantee acceptance into the exhibition, all entrants will be notified on May 19th, 2018&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;2. Cost of submission is $15 for up to 3 entries and $5 per every entry thereafter (maximum 5). It is a non-refundable fee and no changes of images can be made after you submit. Your submissions do not guarantee inclusion into a show.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;3. Your JPEGs data files must be labeled: First name Last &lt;br/&gt; name_Title of the piece_Medium_Height x Width in inches.jpg making sure that underscores go between your name and the name of the piece: (Jane Doe_Self-Portrait_Oil_32x40in.JPG). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Things to include:&lt;br/&gt;-Art work images (Correctly Labeled)&lt;br/&gt;-Image list with a short description of each image (please also include dimensions &amp; medium)&lt;br/&gt;-Artist Statement&lt;br/&gt;-CV&lt;br/&gt;-Submission Fee ($15 via paypal submission.gallerylabodega@gmail.com or via Venmo @LaBodega-Gallery)&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Rules:&lt;br/&gt;Types of art accepted&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 4. All two-dimensional work including photography, paintings, drawings, digital, mixed media, fabric art, chalk, ink, pastels, wax, graphite and printmaking. Essentially, if we can hang it on a wall, we will consider your art for acceptance. We will also accept free standing sculptures and small sculptures that can fit on a pedestal. Video work is accepted, La Bodega Gallery/Established Gallery will provide the monitor and the media player. The maximum size for each piece submitted needs to be less than 48 inches on the longest side.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Shipping + presentation&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 5. If your submission is accepted, you will be notified with information for drop off or shipping your artwork(s) to the gallery. Please take care to ship your artwork carefully with padding and in ther event that it does not sell we will return it to you in the same box with the same padding. Artist is responsible for shipping to/from the gallery. The return postage can be a label or a bill of lading from either UPS, Fedex or UPS must be included with your artwork.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 6. All artwork must be received at least 4 days before the art reception.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 7. All works must be prepared and ready to hang. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Gallery commission&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 8. La Bodega Gallery/Established Gallery retains the right to represent an artist in a sale of the artwork that was accepted and exhibited for the duration of the exhibition. All artworks will be offered for sale. The gallery takes a 50% commission on all sales.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 9. Accepted entries are represented by La Bodega Gallery/Established Gallery for the duration of the exhibition, and artworks will be promoted on our website and other social media.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Gallery installation rules&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 10. La Bodega Gallery/Established Gallery reserves the right to refuse to hang an artwork or exhibit it if it is radically different from the image that was submitted.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Copyright&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 11. Artist maintains copyright.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/2870d9f9-5a1e-4bbc-9f6a-76f84a598452" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>