<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-07-19T19:18:09-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>d528fa18-8447-44cd-84d3-d77574e728fe</id><title>1/6 - Build Your LA Collector List | Apply to Superfine! Art Fair in LA</title><updated>2019-07-19T19:18:09.094431+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Superfine! Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 Los Angeles, CA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 01/06/2020 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artists: there's a better way.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Level up your career. Learn how to build sales and a collector list from our marketing experts. Curate to sell with our friendly guidelines, and meet your next collector in our hip DTLA location just blocks from the LA Art Show, the country's highest-attended art fair. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: The Reef, 1933 S. Broadway, Los Angeles, CA 90007&lt;br/&gt;Fair dates: February 6 - 9, 2020&lt;br/&gt;Application Deadline: January 6, 2020. Booths are selling quickly, so we recommend applying early! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Learn more about exhibiting at Superfine! LA: &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/before-you-apply" target="_blank"&gt;https://superfine.world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A whole year of exhibitions in one weekend.&lt;br/&gt;- 6-10,000 motivated, art-hungry visitors during the four days of the fair.&lt;br/&gt;- 25% of our visitors make a significant ($100-$2,500+) art purchase.&lt;br/&gt;- More than 50% of our exhibiting artists receive major media coverage.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Make art. Sell art. We do the rest.&lt;br/&gt;- Meet your next collectors in a friendly, welcoming space: the ideal environment to discover, collect, and sell art.&lt;br/&gt;- Innovative cost-saving and cost-spreading financing options that work with every artist's budget to make exhibiting and selling a reality.&lt;br/&gt;- Serious opportunities for features in Superfine!'s earned (press + PR), owned (website, blog, and social), and paid (advertising) media.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: Superfine! takes no commission on any artwork sold either in person at the fair or via our online E-Fair.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You’re the art-making expert. We’re the art-marketing experts.&lt;br/&gt;- The smartest and most sophisticated marketing engine in the industry: we get the eyes you want in front of your work. Our audience is 26-45, affluent ($120k+/year), and buying art now.&lt;br/&gt;- We're top drawer: a professional, courteous, and knowledgeable team of experts guiding you every step of the way. Exhibit and sell your work, and gain champions of your career.&lt;br/&gt;- Lead-up webinars and curatorial guidelines geared towards success. Take what you learn with you and make it work for you year-round.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Get to Know Us&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Founded by art collectors Alex Mitow and James Miille, Superfine! started out in 2015 as an alternative to boring, stuffy art shows and complicated art world politics. From the start, we caught flack from the art establishment when we broke down barriers and opened the gates to everyone from serious long-time art collectors to people who just love art and never thought they’d collect. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As it turned out, nobody cared about the art world and their politics. Our open and transparent approach worked: imaginations have been sparked and countless new collections have been jump-started at Superfine! fairs as we continue to spread our message of a more inclusive art market across the country. Since 2015, we’ve had one goal: produce badass, expertly curated art shows where über-talented, diverse global artists meet their new fans in iconic locations across the US and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://superfine.world/before-you-apply" target="_blank"&gt;https://superfine.world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://superfine.world/exhibit-la&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d528fa18-8447-44cd-84d3-d77574e728fe" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>fb9b66a8-8cde-4cc0-afdf-ca8314270899</id><title>9/4 - Artist Collectives: Make Your Mark on the Art Market This Fall at Superfine! Art Fair in DC</title><updated>2019-07-19T19:18:09.094391+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Superfine! Art Fair&lt;br/&gt;📍 Washington, DC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 09/04/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $40.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://superfine.world/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the second year in a row, Superfine! is returning to the bustling Union Market in Washington DC and we're inviting the cutting-edge of emerging talent to apply for a booth. We're all but sold out of solo artist booths, but we do have a handful of larger booths available which are ideal for an artist collective or gallery. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Location: Union Market, 1309 5th St. NE, Washington, DC 20002 &lt;br/&gt;Fair dates: October 30 - November 3, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Application deadline: September 4, 2019. We are more than 80% full and DC's fair is in very high demand, so apply soon to confirm your placement. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Here's what you can expect from Superfine! DC:&lt;br/&gt;- 8-12,000 unique visitors during the five days of the fair.&lt;br/&gt;- 25% of our visitors make a significant ($100-$2,500+) art purchase.&lt;br/&gt;- An easy, efficient exhibition guided by our expert curators.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Benefits of Showing as a Collective&lt;br/&gt;- Larger booth = greater impact + higher visibility.&lt;br/&gt;- Split booth fees and share expenses among multiple artists.&lt;br/&gt;- Build your platform to exhibit in future fairs around the world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: A single collective member must be appointed for all financial and curatorial communications with the Superfine! team.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Superfine! Art Fair: A Year of Exhibitions in One Week&lt;br/&gt;- Connect with collectors in a friendly, welcoming space designed as the ideal environment to discover, buy, and sell art.&lt;br/&gt;- Innovative cost-saving and cost-spreading financing options that work with every artist's budget to make exhibiting and selling a reality.&lt;br/&gt;- Opportunities for features in Superfine!'s earned (press + PR), owned (website, blog, and social), and paid (advertising) media.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Note: Superfine! takes no commission on any artwork sold, either in person at the fair or via our online E-Fair.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Make art. Sell art. We do the rest.&lt;br/&gt;- The smartest and most sophisticated marketing engine in the industry.&lt;br/&gt;- A professional, courteous, and knowledgeable team of experts guiding you every step of the way.&lt;br/&gt;- Lead-up webinars and curatorial guidelines geared towards success.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Pricing &amp; Booth Availability (as of 7/19/19)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artist Booths (2 left) &lt;br/&gt;Artist Collective / Gallery Booths (8 left)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://superfine.world/before-you-apply" target="_blank"&gt;https://superfine.world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fb9b66a8-8cde-4cc0-afdf-ca8314270899" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>f25efff1-19ad-4ca1-8bb2-ebf05ebc7f93</id><title>7/31 - Juried Exhibition &amp;quot;SHOW YOUR WORLD&amp;quot;</title><updated>2019-07-19T19:18:09.094331+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;RE:ARTISTE International Art Organization&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $39.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.reartiste.com/show-your-world-2019-juried-exhibition"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All entries are accepted. Twenty Winners will display original work at the “Show Your World” exhibition in New York City in November 2019 at Gallery MC. The digital installation is part of our art show: artwork of all participants is projected at the gallery during the entire show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is more than just a plain exhibition. To promote our artists we host various art &amp; social events to attract a broader audience and your potential buyers. For artists, we organize networking meetups, workshops, consultations. This festival-like art show attracts thousands of visitors - YOUR ART WILL BE SEEN. Show your art and make new connections. Meet new art enthusiasts and sell your art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our Fifth Annual Art Competition and Juried Exhibition “SHOW YOUR WORLD” is open to artists of various media around the globe. Artists of all career levels are welcome. Painters, photographers, mixed media artists from more than 40 countries took part in the previous four editions of “Show Your World”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Be exhibited in New York City - New York is considered a center of contemporary art life. The world famous art neighborhoods - Chelsea and Soho, Lower East Side and Bushwick, Dumbo and Williamsburg - are located in New York City. The city hosts more than 1500 galleries and hundreds of art shows each year. New York is the place where you can view internationally renowned artworks along with witnessing how modern art emerges. Get the chance to show your world and art to thousands of visitors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;"The artist's job is to be a witness to his time in history." - Robert Rauschenberg&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Art is a non-verbal language understood by people speaking different mother tongues. It conveys both historical and social facts, lifestyle, inspiration, and feelings. We’ve been creating a dialogue among artists from various cities and countries.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EVALUATION: The Jury Panel represented by gallery board members, curators, exhibiting artists, art business professionals is evaluating our 5th International Juried Exhibition “Show Your World”. Find out more about the Jurors here.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;INSPIRATION: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Being traditional or rebellious, figurative or conceptual artist, SHOW YOUR WORLD, views, ideas:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Show YOUR World – happy or sad, active or laid back, open or intimate&lt;br/&gt;Show what only artists can depict – feelings, emotions, or relationships&lt;br/&gt;Show wildlife, nature, or urban landscapes&lt;br/&gt;Show what’s close to your heart or what destroys your comfort&lt;br/&gt;Show your inspiration – whether it’s a person, a place, a book, or another work of art&lt;br/&gt;Show your childhood or your future&lt;br/&gt;Show the world you love, hate, or dream about&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SUBMISSIONS: Entries must be in JPEG format, no larger than 1400 x 1800 pixels, and under 2MB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following disciplines are accepted:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Painting&lt;br/&gt;Drawing/Illustration&lt;br/&gt;Photography&lt;br/&gt;Mixed Media and 3-D Art including Ceramics and Textile&lt;br/&gt;Digital Art&lt;br/&gt;Installation&lt;br/&gt;Performance&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE include your show statement – it will help the jurors and curators understand your work better.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;DEADLINE: JULY 31, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EXHIBITION: As soon as your entry is submitted you receive a popup web page confirming your submission. The finalists will be announced on the RE:ARTISTE website by October 1, 2019 and will be personally notified via email. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;COPYRIGHT: The submitting artists own the copyright to their competition entries as their author(s). By submitting an entry to the art competition the artist gives RE:ARTISTE permission for the entry to be used on the RE:ARTISTE website and its social media channels. The artist gives RE:ARTISTE the right to use his/her name and city of residence for the sole purpose of identifying the artist as the author of the entry. The entry fee is not refundable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Entries must be in JPEG format, no larger than 1400 x 1800 pixels, and under 2MB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The following disciplines are accepted:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Painting&lt;br/&gt;- Drawing/Illustration&lt;br/&gt;- Photography&lt;br/&gt;- Mixed Media and 3-D Art including Ceramics and Textile&lt;br/&gt;- Digital Art&lt;br/&gt;- Installation&lt;br/&gt;PLEASE include your show statement – it will help the jurors and curators understand your work better.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more info please email at info@reartiste.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/f25efff1-19ad-4ca1-8bb2-ebf05ebc7f93" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>