<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-07T20:48:19-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>d4d10671-61f6-47ae-a3bd-bcc3ef01487e</id><title>4/1 - The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show - Open Call to Artists for Submissions</title><updated>2019-02-07T20:48:19.697914+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Episcopal Church of the Heavenly Rest&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://heavenlyrest.wufoo.com/forms/z1hr8tsj0w3znbe/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Episcopal Church of the Heavenly Rest’s (CHR) new arts initiative’s mission is for CHR to shine as a community where artistic creativity of many forms is valued as a spiritual practice and a force for reconciliation. We aim to nurture artists, deepen our shared experience of their work, and invite the greater community of all faiths to explore our common humanity through the medium of art.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CHR is hosting The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Theme: We All Belong&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Call for Submissions: We all draw inspiration from our communities. What does belonging mean to you?  We call on New York City artists to respond to the question and the community around them across media and styles. A committee will select works for the exhibition based on how well the artist responds to the theme within the criteria set forth in the registration form. Selected works will be exhibited at The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show.&lt;br/&gt;      &lt;br/&gt;Requirements: Open to New York City Artists (from one of the five boroughs) over the age of 21, work submitted must be appropriate for viewing of all ages. Submitted work must be complete and exhibition ready. To be considered, work must meet standards of quality determined by committee. Every work submitted must be accompanied by an artist contract provided by CHR at time of drop off. Artists must meet professional standards of composition and presentation of their work. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Additional Information: The Second Annual Heavenly Lights Art Show and opening reception will take place Thursday, May 9, 2019, 6 -8pm. Art will be exhibited in CHR’s Darlington Hall and Gallery Undercroft Exhibition Spaces from May 9 through September 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application Instructions: submissions must be made online via the provided Registration Link or on the CHR website, &lt;a href="http://heavenlyrest.org/upcoming-events/" target="_blank"&gt;http://heavenlyrest.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/d4d10671-61f6-47ae-a3bd-bcc3ef01487e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>a41e6157-26d2-4ab9-91be-b2b1cef238ea</id><title>3/1 - Arcadia Earth 2019 - Calling All Sustainable Artists</title><updated>2019-02-07T20:48:19.697857+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arcadia Earth&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Disciplines&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.arcadia.earth"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ABOUT ARCADIA:&lt;br/&gt;Arcadia is a platform to raise awareness on sustainability through immersive art experiences, a solution driven marketplace and educational talks. Our mission is to gather like minded partners, brands, and organizations to create content and innovative sustainable solutions to connect with the new generation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THE OPPORTUNITY:&lt;br/&gt;We are looking for artists interested in creating immersive environment Installations to promote sustainability. The artwork will be displayed during a collective event. The event will be promoted with strong marketing strategy where all installations and their creators will be highlighted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THE INCENTIVES:&lt;br/&gt;- 3 grant levels: $2500, $5000, $7500. Apply to see what you qualify for.&lt;br/&gt;- Promotion and Marketing&lt;br/&gt;- Marketing Exposure - Social Media exposure &lt;br/&gt;- Arcadia web presence &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;HOW:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists will need to create immersive sustainable experiences by: &lt;br/&gt;1. Areas to Activate : activate an area of 15’ x 10’ more or less &lt;br/&gt;2. Materials used: upcycled / recycled / sustainable &lt;br/&gt;3. Messaging: sustainability and global warming&lt;br/&gt;4. Immersive/ Experiential: Teleport guests into an experiential and engaging environment using mixed media&lt;br/&gt;5. innovative: Use of new technologies such as Projection Mapping, VR, and AR&lt;br/&gt;6. Interactive: art experiences where guests can participate in creating or being part of the artwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBMISSIONS&lt;br/&gt;Depending on the category artists will need to submit the following to Arcadia to review at ap@arcadia.earth :&lt;br/&gt;1.     IMMERSIVE / EXPERIENTIAL:&lt;br/&gt;	a. Example of the immersive installation (renderings, layout, photos etc.)&lt;br/&gt;	b. Materials being used&lt;br/&gt;	c.  A paragraph explaining the concept and message behind the piece&lt;br/&gt;2.     INNOVATIVE:&lt;br/&gt;	a. A link or video explaining the technology being used&lt;br/&gt;	b.  Materials being used (if applicable)&lt;br/&gt;	c.  A paragraph explaining the concept and message behind the piece&lt;br/&gt;3.     INTERACTIVE:&lt;br/&gt;	a.  A paragraph explaining the concept and message behind the piece&lt;br/&gt;	b.  A rendering/ reference of installation&lt;br/&gt;	c.  Materials being used&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a41e6157-26d2-4ab9-91be-b2b1cef238ea" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>