<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-02T14:16:22-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>a93512ba-7b1f-422f-a853-2d6978b336e5</id><title>5/14 - Open Call For Portraiture: Rendering Likeness Volume 2 at two Brooklyn Gallery locations</title><updated>2019-05-02T14:16:22.779550+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;La Bodega Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/14/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $15.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.labodega-gallery.com/opportunities-1#/renderinglikeness"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEN CALL: Rendering Likeness: Volume 2&lt;br/&gt;Contemporary portraiture takes many forms and encompasses countless conceptual viewpoints, mediums and techniques that explore a myriad of subject matter. Last year in one of our most popular shows La Bodega Gallery exhibited a hugely diverse group of portraits and this year we are doing it again…in two locations! This year we are collaborating with a second space, the artist run gallery "Established Gallery" in Brooklyn to bring you even more!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are currently accepting submissions for the contemporary portraiture exhibitions entitled “Rendering Likeness, Volume 2”. This open call is open to both emerging and established artists who create works of portraiture in any style or medium. For this open call we are inviting artists  to demonstrate their creative approach to portraiture. Portraits can be figurative, abstract or conceptual. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There will be TWO curated shows at TWO separate spaces in Brooklyn (La Bodega Gallery and Established Gallery), if your submission is accepted you will be placed in either space depending on which exhibition better suits the work.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION DEADLINE: &lt;br/&gt;5/14 11:59:59 pm &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Exhibition dates: &lt;br/&gt;May 31st – June 24th, 2019&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Locations: &lt;br/&gt;La Bodega Gallery, 695 5th Ave Brooklyn, NY &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Established Gallery, 75 6th Ave, Brooklyn, NY&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Contact: gallerylabodega@gmail.com&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Eligibility&lt;br/&gt;This exhibition is open to any artist, anywhere. ALL SUBMISSIONS MUST BE RECEIVED BY 5/14 11:59:59 pm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to apply:&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;1. Submissions must be via email at submission.gallerylabodega@gmail.com. We require you to upload 1 - 3 images, your CV, and artist statement. Submission does not guarantee acceptance into the exhibition, all entrants will be notified on May 19th, 2018&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;2. Cost of submission is $15 for up to 3 entries and $5 per every entry thereafter (maximum 5). It is a non-refundable fee and no changes of images can be made after you submit. Your submissions do not guarantee inclusion into a show.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;3. Your JPEGs data files must be labeled: First name Last &lt;br/&gt; name_Title of the piece_Medium_Height x Width in inches.jpg making sure that underscores go between your name and the name of the piece: (Jane Doe_Self-Portrait_Oil_32x40in.JPG). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Things to include:&lt;br/&gt;-Art work images (Correctly Labeled)&lt;br/&gt;-Image list with a short description of each image (please also include dimensions &amp; medium)&lt;br/&gt;-Artist Statement&lt;br/&gt;-CV&lt;br/&gt;-Submission Fee ($15 via paypal submission.gallerylabodega@gmail.com or via Venmo @LaBodega-Gallery)&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Rules:&lt;br/&gt;Types of art accepted&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 4. All two-dimensional work including photography, paintings, drawings, digital, mixed media, fabric art, chalk, ink, pastels, wax, graphite and printmaking. Essentially, if we can hang it on a wall, we will consider your art for acceptance. We will also accept free standing sculptures and small sculptures that can fit on a pedestal. Video work is accepted, La Bodega Gallery/Established Gallery will provide the monitor and the media player. The maximum size for each piece submitted needs to be less than 48 inches on the longest side.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Shipping + presentation&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 5. If your submission is accepted, you will be notified with information for drop off or shipping your artwork(s) to the gallery. Please take care to ship your artwork carefully with padding and in ther event that it does not sell we will return it to you in the same box with the same padding. Artist is responsible for shipping to/from the gallery. The return postage can be a label or a bill of lading from either UPS, Fedex or UPS must be included with your artwork.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 6. All artwork must be received at least 4 days before the art reception.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 7. All works must be prepared and ready to hang. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Gallery commission&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 8. La Bodega Gallery/Established Gallery retains the right to represent an artist in a sale of the artwork that was accepted and exhibited for the duration of the exhibition. All artworks will be offered for sale. The gallery takes a 50% commission on all sales.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 9. Accepted entries are represented by La Bodega Gallery/Established Gallery for the duration of the exhibition, and artworks will be promoted on our website and other social media.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Gallery installation rules&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 10. La Bodega Gallery/Established Gallery reserves the right to refuse to hang an artwork or exhibit it if it is radically different from the image that was submitted.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Copyright&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 11. Artist maintains copyright.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/a93512ba-7b1f-422f-a853-2d6978b336e5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>1d9755a8-0a16-4933-b8ef-e1b1701f212c</id><title>5/30 - Open Call for Emerging Artists - Fall 2019 Exhibition</title><updated>2019-05-02T14:16:22.779490+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Smack Mellon&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/30/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.smackmellon.org/opportunities/artists"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In November–December 2019, Smack Mellon will present "Idol Worship," an exhibition celebrating the ongoing cultural, social and political significance of role model adoration as an essential survival strategy. Smack Mellon is currently accepting applications from Emerging Artists to be considered for this exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Self-identifying women, in particular, are often overlooked as figures to be emulated, exempt from the label of “genius” so readily bestowed upon men. Partially inspired by John Waters’s Role Models, a pseudo-autobiography through his influences or “filth elders,” the exhibition will emphasize work that presents women and women-identifying role models as sources of possibility, creativity, courage, self-fashioning and sometimes, transgression. While teens’ fanatical impulse to paper their bedroom walls with imagery of their favorite stars is seen as merely an adolescent phase, Idol Worship asserts how the identification with role models is especially significant for those alienated from dominant social institutions, whether the biological family, history, or mainstream culture.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Idol Worship will be organized by guest curator Emily Colucci, whose proposal was selected through the Curatorial Proposal open call. To help elevate the profile of and bring greater exposure to emerging artists, this exhibition will include a combination of emerging artists chosen from an open call, as well as selected established artists. This open call is only for emerging artists, and at least half of the artists in the exhibition will be selected from this pool of applicants. An emerging artist is considered to be an artist without commercial representation who has a dedicated art practice but few opportunities to show at gallery or non-profit spaces. Submissions will be reviewed by the guest curator and Smack Mellon staff.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists whose practice includes paying tribute to, obsessing over, embodying, or otherwise complex engagements with women and women-identifying role models, heroes, idols, or filth elders, whether famous public figures, underground cult superstars, lesser known private muses, problematic faves, or unlikely sources of inspiration, are encouraged to apply. Transdisciplinary artists and cultural producers exploring the potential of role model worship as a source of sustainment are also of interest.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The exhibition will run from November 16 through December 29, 2019 (opening date to be confirmed).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Emily Colucci is a writer, curator and co-founder of Filthy Dreams, an award-winning blog analyzing art, culture and politics through a queer lens and a touch of camp. In 2016, she was awarded the Creative Capital | Andy Warhol Foundation Arts Writers Grant for Filthy Dreams. In addition, Colucci has contributed to exhibition catalogues, most recently for Devan Shimoyama’s Cry, Baby at the Andy Warhol Museum, artist books, and online and print magazines, such as Conde Nast’s them., VICE, Salon, LA Review of Books and more. She has previously curated Night Fever at Pittsburgh’s Future Tenant, and co-curated Party Out Of Bounds: Nightlife As Activism Since 1980 at New York’s La MaMa Galleria with Visual AIDS, as well as its satellite installation Courtship Disorder by John Walter in London’s White Cubicle Toilet Gallery at the late George &amp; Dragon Pub.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submit your application using Smack Mellon’s online application portal on Submittable: &lt;a href="https://smackmellon.submittable.com/submit." target="_blank"&gt;https://smackmellon.submittable.com&lt;/a&gt; We welcome submissions of existing works and proposals for new projects. All media will be considered, including but not limited to 2D, 3D, sound, performance, installations, time-based, research-based, speculative projects, and public programs. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission deadline is May 30 at 11:59pm. Artists are encouraged to submit early. All submissions will be reviewed in the order they are received. Selected artists will be notified in early July. If selected, artwork must be received at Smack Mellon between 10am and 6pm on November 11. We recommend hand-delivering the work. Artwork can be shipped to the gallery, but Smack Mellon is unable to cover shipping or return costs. Under most circumstances artists will be expected to install their own work. Artists must pick up their work on either January 2 or 3, 2020 between 10am and 6pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Any questions? Please contact info@smackmellon.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/1d9755a8-0a16-4933-b8ef-e1b1701f212c" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>