<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-03-19T20:15:19-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>0b586dfc-9703-4251-bc21-d62761ee4030</id><title>4/19 - Dear Earth,</title><updated>2019-03-19T20:15:19.166784+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Woman Made Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Chicago, IL, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/19/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.womanmade.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chicago's Woman Made Gallery, Openlands, and Brushwood Center at Ryerson Woods partner to illuminate women’s voices of action and hope for the planet. Together, we invite artists to submit artwork that highly reflects personal concerns and connections to the natural environment where they live.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dear Earth was inspired by Sibylle Szaggars Redford whose performance, The Way of The Rain, was created as a “love letter to Mother Earth.” Szaggars Redford and her husband, Robert Redford, were Brushwood Center’s 2018 environmental leadership award recipients.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All applicants should submit a brief artist statement. The first sentence of the statement should begin, “Dear Earth…[add your message of action, hope, or inspiration]”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Works in all media are welcome.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About the Juror:  &lt;br/&gt;Catherine Game is the Executive Director of Brushwood Center at Ryerson Woods. &lt;br/&gt;Catherine ensures that the legacy of Brushwood Center thrives through strong partnerships and inspiring programs that connect art, nature, and wellness. Prior to joining Brushwood Center, Catherine served as Director of Communications and Engagement for Chicago Wilderness where she oversaw the organization’s communications, member engagement, and efforts to cultivate a diverse conservation constituency. Catherine has held previous positions in communications, program evaluation, and education with conservation groups. She holds a Master’s degree in Natural Resources and Environment from the University of Michigan, Bachelor’s degree in Biology and Art from Albion College, and is the recipient of the Doris Duke Conservation Fellowship and a Morris K. Udall Scholar. Catherine is an artist, using homemade, natural paints to bring visibility to urban nature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Works in all media are welcome. The application fee for our juried exhibitions is $30 for up to three images of work, plus one detail image if necessary. &lt;br/&gt;Any questions, please call us :  (312) 738-0400&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To submit your work:  &lt;br/&gt;https://womanmadegallery.submittable.com/submit/135676/dear-earth&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/0b586dfc-9703-4251-bc21-d62761ee4030" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>553ce6a1-968b-496b-b0ac-1d186c0b8cc5</id><title>5/6 - OPEN CALL FOR ARTISTS IN THE AD INDUSTRY — CHANCE TO SHOW WORK ON 60+ SCREENS IN TIMES SQ</title><updated>2019-03-19T20:15:19.166751+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Times Square Arts&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Film/Video/Media&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/06/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="TSq.org/arts"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re an artist working in the advertising industry, Times Square Arts, Advertising Week, and the Out of Home Advertising Association of America (OAAA) invite you to submit original moving image artwork to Midnight Moment, the world’s largest, longest-running digital art exhibition. The selected 3-minute work will be shown on electronic billboards throughout Times Square every night in September 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The submission deadline is May 6, 2019.&lt;br/&gt;For more information, visit TSq.org/AdArt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit TSq.org/AdArt for information on submission guidelines and technical specifications. Applications for the Midnight Moment program are accepted through the online Slideroom portal linked to at the bottom of the page.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/553ce6a1-968b-496b-b0ac-1d186c0b8cc5" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>46957a44-c27e-4d78-954c-29ee09a85125</id><title>4/1 - Call for Entries: 118th Annual Juried Art Exhibition</title><updated>2019-03-19T20:15:19.166698+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;New Haven Paint and Clay Club&lt;br/&gt;📍 New Haven, CT, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 04/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $20.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.newhavenpaintandclayclub.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 118th Annual Exhibition of the New Haven Paint and Clay Club will be juried by Dr. Elizabeth Hodermarsky, the Sutphin Family Associate Curator of Prints and Drawings at Yale University Art Gallery. She will award prizes in excess of $4000 with additional funds available for purchases to the NHP&amp;CC Permanent Collection. The exhibition will be on view at the Susan B. Hilles Gallery at the Creative Arts Workshop from May 11- June 1.&lt;br/&gt;Selected work must be hand delivered to the Creative Arts Workshop, 80 Audubon St. New Haven, CT.&lt;br/&gt;Eligible media include drawing, painting, mixed media (no larger than 40" in width) and sculpture (no heavier than 75 lbs). Giclees, photography, digital work and video are not eligible for entry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit www.newhavenpaintandclayclub.org to access the prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/46957a44-c27e-4d78-954c-29ee09a85125" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>