<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-13T22:48:28-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>baf7223d-18ff-4d2c-8ae1-bf0e8a9290f7</id><title>3/22 - Open Call for Solo Exhibitions and Curatorial Projects</title><updated>2019-02-13T22:48:28.083403+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;CUE Art Foundation&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/22/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://cueartfoundation.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CUE’s Open Calls provide artists and emerging curators the opportunity and necessary resources to realize an exhibition at CUE’s storefront gallery in East Chelsea, New York.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Each year, a panel of established artists and curators select two solo exhibitions and one curatorial project to be realized at CUE. Finalists are paired with a member of the selection panel, who works with them as a mentor throughout the process of planning and mounting the exhibition. CUE provides institutional guidance, generous honoraria, a shipping budget, and an accompanying exhibition catalogue with a critical essay by a participant in CUE's Art Critic Mentoring Program. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Applications are accepted once annually in the spring. The deadline for the current Open Call is March 22, 2019.    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SOLO EXHIBITION INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligibility:&lt;br/&gt;CUE's Solo Exhibition Open Call is for artists who:&lt;br/&gt;-Have not had a solo show in a commercial NYC gallery within the last five years&lt;br/&gt;-Do not have current, consistent commercial gallery representation in the United States&lt;br/&gt;-Are not currently enrolled in a degree program&lt;br/&gt;-Have a demonstrated, consistent studio practice outside an academic setting for three or more years&lt;br/&gt;-Must currently live and work in the United States&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;-The exhibition program is open to artists working in all disciplines.&lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to artists who present ideas or topics that are not well-represented in the commercial sector.&lt;br/&gt;-CUE strongly encourages applications that contribute to our ongoing commitment to diversity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What Finalists receive:&lt;br/&gt;-Five-week solo exhibition at CUE Art Foundation in 2020&lt;br/&gt;-Curatorial support/mentoring from an established artist or curator on the selection panel&lt;br/&gt;-Opportunities to develop related public programming &lt;br/&gt;-32-page full color catalogue with essay produced through the Art Critic Mentoring Program and a statement by the curator&lt;br/&gt;-$5,000 unrestricted honorarium&lt;br/&gt;-An art shipping and art handling budget&lt;br/&gt;-Opening reception&lt;br/&gt;-Press materials and PR support &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;CURATORIAL PROJECT INFORMATION&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br/&gt;-Proposals must be conceptually rigorous and focus on artists, projects, and themes that are innovative, challenging, and engaging.&lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to proposals that demonstrate a creative approach to curatorial research methods and the exhibition plan, as well as those that present ideas or topics that are not well-represented in the commercial sector.&lt;br/&gt;-The proposal must include four or more artists, half of whom must qualify as under-recognized (no gallery representation and no solo exhibitions in a major venue within the past five years).&lt;br/&gt;-Curators may not include their own work in the exhibition.&lt;br/&gt;-The curator and all proposed artists must live and work in the United States.    &lt;br/&gt;-Extra consideration will be given to those in the beginning stages of their curatorial careers.&lt;br/&gt;-CUE strongly encourages applications that contribute to our ongoing commitment to diversity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What the opportunity includes:&lt;br/&gt;-Five-week exhibition at CUE Art Foundation in 2020&lt;br/&gt;-Curatorial support/mentoring from an established artist or curator on the selection panel&lt;br/&gt;-Opportunities to develop related public programming &lt;br/&gt;-Full color catalogue with essay produced through the Art Critic Mentoring Program&lt;br/&gt;-$2,500 unrestricted honorarium&lt;br/&gt;-$2,500 to divide amongst the participating artists and program speakers&lt;br/&gt;-$2,000 production budget&lt;br/&gt;-An art shipping and art handling budget&lt;br/&gt;-Opening reception&lt;br/&gt;-Press materials and PR support&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at &lt;a href="http://cueartfoundation.org/open-call" target="_blank"&gt;http://cueartfoundation.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, please visit our website or email Lilly Hern-Fondation, Programs Associate: lilly@cueartfoundation.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/baf7223d-18ff-4d2c-8ae1-bf0e8a9290f7" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>