<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-02-23T01:14:40-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>7721ebeb-a03c-4719-b1ce-12f54ad0c9f9</id><title>3/8 - New American Paintings 2019 Midwest Competition!</title><updated>2019-02-23T01:14:40.285410+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;New American Paintings&lt;br/&gt;📍 Boston, MA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Painting&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/08/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $50.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.newamericanpaintings.com"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MIDWEST COMPETITION&lt;br/&gt;Deadline: March 8th, 2019 (Midnight EST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are pleased to be accepting applications to New American Paintings' 2019 review of painters working in the midwestern United States. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists from the following states are eligible to apply:&lt;br/&gt;IL, IN, IA, MI, MN, MO, OH, WI.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;JUROR:  Emily Liebert,  Associate Curator of Contemporary Art &lt;br/&gt;The Cleveland Museum of Art&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Since 1993, New American Paintings' sole mission has been to connect under-known artists with an audience that has a deep interest in contemporary painting. The publication is received by thousands of collectors, art world professionals and art aficionados, internationally. Many past featured artists have gone on to achieve substantial critical and commercial success.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We define the activity of painting broadly. All styles and media are welcome as long as they involve, or are conceptually related to the activity of painting. Works must be original and cannot be editioned.&lt;br/&gt;Please note that if you have been in a past issue of New American Paintings, or have applied to a competition in the past 5 years, then you already have an Account on the web site. DO NOT REGISTER A NEW ACCOUNT. Please follow the instruction on the site to gain access to your account.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TO APPLY YOU WILL NEED:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;* 1) Four jpegs of your work (no larger than 1200 pixels at their greatest dimension)&lt;br/&gt;* 2) A credit card for the entry fee of $50 (You may also take advantage of a special artist's offer: $99, which includes your application fee and a one year subscription to the magazine).&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7721ebeb-a03c-4719-b1ce-12f54ad0c9f9" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>730d8e02-1be8-464f-a325-7d554de49f75</id><title>3/31 - Whitney Museum of American Art-Call for Docents</title><updated>2019-02-23T01:14:40.285360+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Whitney Museum of American Art&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 03/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://whitney.org/About/Docents"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHITNEY MUSEUM &lt;br/&gt;DOCENT TRAINING PROGRAM &lt;br/&gt;OPEN CALL &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have ever thought about leading free public tours at the Whitney Museum, here is your opportunity!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are now accepting applications for our new docent training program which will begin in Fall 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Whitney docents volunteer their time, leading tours two or three times a month, and should be willing to make a minimum commitment to the docent program of three years after training. You must be available to tour on Mondays, Fridays, or weekends to apply and all docents are also expected to tour throughout the year including summers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For further information or to apply, go to &lt;a href="https://whitney.org/about/job-postings," target="_blank"&gt;https://whitney.org&lt;/a&gt; or for questions, e-mail DocentProgram@whitney.org.  Application deadline is March 31, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/730d8e02-1be8-464f-a325-7d554de49f75" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>