<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-10T17:16:34-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>fa1f10ba-78ed-41be-9578-3dbdbffb0dfb</id><title>6/7 - City of Charlotte - Charlotte Water Zone Four Field Opperations Facility</title><updated>2019-05-10T17:16:34.449775+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Arts &amp;amp; Science Council&lt;br/&gt;📍 Charlotte, NC, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/07/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 unknown fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Arts &amp; Science Council is accepting qualifications from artists for a public art opportunity at the upcoming Charlotte Water Zone Four Field Operation facility. The selected artist will work with the ASC, Charlotte Water staff, C Design, and local communities to create artwork that is complementary to the architectural design of the facility and reflect the service of Charlotte Water and the history and character of West Charlotte. The selected artist or artist team will be expected to engage with both Charlotte Water staff and area residents to develop the concept for their work. The selected artist will have the opportunity to create engaging, freestanding artwork/s that are complementary to the sites. Two site locations have been identified as possible opportunities for artwork placement: the front entrance along Tyvola Road and the plaza space directly adjacent to the facility. The selected artist/s may choose to site artwork at either or both sites. The artwork should be visually impactful, so scale, materials, and project budget will need to be closely considered. The Tyvola Road entrance site will be highly visible to vehicular traffic. Artwork sited at this location should serve as a landmark representing Charlotte Water and the communities of West Charlotte. For security purposes, access to the Zone Four Field Operations facility is limited. Charlotte Water staff will primarily enjoy artwork sited at the facility plaza with local residents encountering the artwork during visits to the facility’s community space.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the complete RFQ, please visit: &lt;a href="https://www.artsandscience.org/resources-for/artists/calls-to-artists/." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.artsandscience.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/fa1f10ba-78ed-41be-9578-3dbdbffb0dfb" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>c48d377d-ed90-4a31-af9e-df5e2e61ba59</id><title>5/24 - 1708 Gallery Call for Proposals</title><updated>2019-05-10T17:16:34.449717+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;1708 Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Richmond, VA, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/24/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $10.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.1708gallery.org/index.php"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1708 Gallery welcomes all artists to submit exhibition proposals for the year 2020-2021. 1708 Gallery strongly encourages proposals for new or developing projects and bodies of work. In addition to proposals for exhibitions in 1708’s gallery space, public works and other non-gallery based projects will be considered. If you are currently a student, you must have graduated by the exhibition year.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Exhibition periods are approximately six weeks. 1708 provides a $1000 honorarium, plus shipping, travel, installation and other exhibition support.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1708 Gallery is committed to providing opportunity and space for experimentation, freedom and artistic growth, while promoting understanding and appreciation of contemporary art. We also support artists’ professional development through creation and facilitation of public or educational programming; interaction with curators, other arts professionals and collectors; and engagement with diverse audiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information and to submit a proposal, please visit www.1708gallery.org.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The deadline for submissions is 11:59 PM EST on Friday, May 24, 2019. Final notifications will be sent by late spring 2020.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please contact 1708 Gallery Coordinator Erin Willett with any questions at ewillett@1708gallery.org or 804.643.1708&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/c48d377d-ed90-4a31-af9e-df5e2e61ba59" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>