<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml</id><title>open-calls-6</title><updated>2019-05-07T16:16:30-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/art-opp/master/open-calls-6.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Art Show Open Call Opportunities</subtitle><entry><id>addb5bca-09e1-4875-bc24-54baf321325a</id><title>7/7 - OPEN CALL: Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists</title><updated>2019-05-07T16:16:30.671673+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Friend of The Artist&lt;br/&gt;📍  , N/A&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 07/07/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.friendoftheartist.com/apply/vol10?utm_source=NYFA"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Publication Opportunity for Emerging Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;FOA is a quarterly book dedicated to elevating the work of emerging artists around the world. Our publication releases in a hardcover art book every quarter and includes the work of artists who work in a variety of mediums, informative articles, and interviews. Accepted artists will have a four-page spread of their work, information, and artist statement. Volume 10 will be juried by Diana Cerezino, Michael Dewberry, and Tim Ralston.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Details:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accepted Artists Receive&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3 works published in Volume 10, complimentary digital copy of the publication, social media post of work, discounts on books for family and friends, and free digital access to future publications&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Submission Fee&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$30 for 5 Images&lt;br/&gt;or&lt;br/&gt;$50 for 5 Images + Book&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;July 7, 2019 (midnight, CST)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eligible Artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artists of all academic disciples are welcome to apply. This includes painting, sculpture, photography, installation, and performance art. Works must be submitted in a printable format.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guest Jurors&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Diana Cerezino&lt;br/&gt;Michael Dewberry&lt;br/&gt;Tim Ralston&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Diana Cerezino &amp; Tim Ralston&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Diana Cerezino and Tim Ralston are founding directors of PADA, an artist-led, non-profit arts organisation based in Barreiro on Lisbon’s South Bay. Set within a derelict industrial Park, PADA is a studio provider, international residency and gallery promoting interaction between national and international artists. Both practicing artists, Tim and Diana set up PADA with the aim of creating a unique resource for artists, to provide excellent studios and fabrication facilities alongside the opportunity to exhibit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Having both graduated with BA Hons they have worked in the London art scene for the last 15 years and gained a wealth of experience that they bring to this new project in Lisbon. In this time they have worked for artists such as Damien Hirst, Raqib Shaw and Julian Opie, galleries Alison Jacques and Hauser and Wirth as well as institutions including The Tate, ICA and BFI. The knowledge from assisting and working with these established and well known artists, galleries and institutions informs PADA as a residency that encourages and supports artists development. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As PADA they have curated exhibitions in London and Lisbon, the latest exhibition at AMAC in Lisbon, included 40 artists over 4 galleries. 'Out of Office' curated by Alice Bonnot opens on the 11th May at PADA gallery and Recreational Grounds V opens on 17th May in the project space Tim still co curates in London.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Michael H. Dewberry&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A native of Dallas, TX, Michael H. Dewberry is an emerging curator who has coordinated and collaborated on international traveling exhibitions in Mexico, Dallas, and New York City. He has held positions at the Crow Museum of Asian Art, Brooklyn Museum, Wadsworth Atheneum, Academia Nazionale di San Luca, Museo Internacional del Barroco, and the Bard Graduate Center Gallery. His mission is to curate exhibitions and programming that bridges cultures and creates communities united around art and action. Prior to attending graduate school to focus on decorative arts he studied product design at the Scuola Politecnico di Design in Milan, Italy. Michael earned his master’s degree in Decorative Arts, Design History, and Material Culture from the Bard Graduate Center in New York City and a holds a Bachelor of Arts with honors in Art History from Trinity College in Hartford, Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply online at friendoftheartist.com/apply/vol10?utm_source=NYFA&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Questions? Email contact@friendoftheartist.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/addb5bca-09e1-4875-bc24-54baf321325a" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>7135e2a1-f3dd-4a65-b70d-e958df0ec83e</id><title>6/1 - 22nd International Open</title><updated>2019-05-07T16:16:30.671644+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Woman Made Gallery&lt;br/&gt;📍 Chicago, IL, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/01/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $30.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.womanmade.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exhibition Dates: August 9 - Aug 31, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Description: Invitation to all female identified artists worldwide to submit artwork for this open exhibition. All themes, styles, and media will be considered. Artwork that explores or challenges conceptual and material boundaries is encouraged. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Prizes Awarded:  Best of Show $500 / 2nd Place $250 / 3rd Place $100.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All applicants should submit an artist’s statement about their body of work (up to 250 words.) Accepted artworks must not exceed 72" horizontally and must not have been previously shown at WMG. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Juror: Dolores Mercado&lt;br/&gt;Dolores Mercado is the Associate Curator at the National Museum of Mexican Art (NMMA) in Chicago, Illinois, and former Associate Director of Education and Senior Arts Educator. &lt;br/&gt;She studied at the National School of Painting, Sculpture and Printing La Esmeralda in Mexico City, The Academy of San Carlos from the UNAM in Mexico City, The School of Video of the University of Guadalajara, and at the School of Visual Arts of the University of Guadalajara.&lt;br/&gt;Mercado was the Curator of Women Artists of Modern Mexico: Frida’s Contemporaries; La vida sobre papel: Judithe Hernández; Contemplations: Dan Ramirez, Works from the Permanent Collection; Deportable Aliens: New Work by Rodrigo Lara Zendejas; La Muerte Niña: Day of the Dead; Carmen Parra: Suave Patria; Rito y Recuerdo: Day of the Dead; Quilt Me A Story: Nuestros relatos (Immigration Stories); Maquila Blues: Oscar Moya; Fragmentos: Pilar Acevedo; and Abyss: Rocío Caballero among many others. Mercado has also Co-curated Memoria Presente: An Artistic Journey; !No se olvida! Remembering the Tlatelolco Massacre and Rastros y Crónicas: Women of Juarez, and others.  She has hosted Camino Tierra Adentro radio program at WRTE 90.5 FM (1999 to 2004, MFACM), and Alquimia radio program at WRTE 90.5 FM. (2004-2006) NMMA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use this link to submit your art:&lt;br/&gt;https://womanmadegallery.submittable.com/submit/136404/22nd-international-open&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Direct questions to:  general@womanmade.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/7135e2a1-f3dd-4a65-b70d-e958df0ec83e" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>8343bb21-941e-42ca-b903-16400e017374</id><title>5/31 - Artfare Submissions Program</title><updated>2019-05-07T16:16:30.671612+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Artfare, Inc.&lt;br/&gt;📍 New York, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 05/31/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://www.artfare.com/for-artists/"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are now accepting submissions through May 31, 2019. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Artfare allows artists to present their work to a broad audience and connect with patrons both digitally and in person through studio visits, exhibitions and events. Using our iPhone app, artists can also discover and communicate with other artists and curators, and work together to independently organize exhibitions and events.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our tools and services will allow you to:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. Easily share links to your available works and facilitate sales from your studio, both on and offline&lt;br/&gt;2. Build a following of potential patrons and curators in a professional context&lt;br/&gt;3. Receive tax documents at year end and let Artfare collect, file, and pay sales tax on your behalf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use the link below to submit:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;https://artfare.slideroom.com/#/login/program/48475&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/8343bb21-941e-42ca-b903-16400e017374" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>291d099f-de8b-4e51-a88c-65b593a2a6d2</id><title>6/5 - Call for Artists - 12th Annual Portal: Governors Island (formerly Governors Island Art Fair)</title><updated>2019-05-07T16:16:30.671571+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;4heads&lt;br/&gt;📍 Brooklyn, NY, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 All Visual Arts&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/05/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="http://www.4heads.org"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York’s Largest Independent Exhibition&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: June 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;"The Art Fair for the 99%" -New York Times&lt;br/&gt;Seeking independent artists worldwide working in all disciplines; Painting, Photography, Sculpture, Installation, Video, and Sound Art. Submit your work for the 2019 Portal: Governors Island (formerly Governors Island Art Fair) opening this September. Portal: GI - New York’s largest independent exhibition - will once again feature scores of artists of exceptional talent, and each will be awarded an exhibition room or large outdoor space in the historic and beautifully dilapidated buildings of Colonels Row. The lines between artwork and its environment are blurred across the lawns and landmark houses of bucolic Governors Island. Founded by 4heads, a group of New York artists, Portal: GI champions an art fair model that puts the artists first. &lt;br/&gt;Once selected by 4heads jury, your exhibition space is free. The entire massive event is free to the general public. And as an emerging or established artist, you are free to present your work, your way, at this acclaimed independent art fair in New York City. Because 4heads works hard to keep artists’ costs to a bare minimum, gallery scouts, journalists and collectors know that this is where to find the freshest talent, and they come back every year to see what’s been discovered. Many past Portal/GIAF artists have launched their art careers here. We hope you can too. - 4heads&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Heads up! - 4heads is specifically seeking outdoor artists working in all disciplines&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Apply at: &lt;a href="https://4heads.slideroom.com/" target="_blank"&gt;https://4heads.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More Info at: &lt;a href="http://www.4heads.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.4heads.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: June 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Application Fee: $45  -  No Additional Charges&lt;br/&gt;Fair Dates: Every Weekend in September 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Email: info@4heads.org&lt;br/&gt;Apply at: &lt;a href="https://4heads.slideroom.com/" target="_blank"&gt;https://4heads.slideroom.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More Info at: &lt;a href="http://www.4heads.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.4heads.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deadline for Submission: June 5, 2019&lt;br/&gt;Application Fee: $45  -  No Additional Charges&lt;br/&gt;Fair Dates: Every Weekend in September 2019&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/291d099f-de8b-4e51-a88c-65b593a2a6d2" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>709447bd-2beb-40f2-89af-fc4578068579</id><title>6/22 - Meed3: When Photography Ruled the Streets</title><updated>2019-05-07T16:16:30.671503+00:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Gallery19&lt;br/&gt;📍 Chicago , IL, United States&lt;br/&gt;🎨 Photography&lt;br/&gt;📅 06/22/2019 deadline&lt;br/&gt;💰 $45.00 fee&lt;br/&gt;➡ &lt;a href="https://artist.callforentry.org/festivals_unique_info.php?ID=6515"&gt;Apply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;====== DESCRIPTION ======&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gallery19 announces a call for entries for our Third annual juried competition, Meed3: When Photography Ruled the Streets. Photographers at all experience levels are invited to submit work.  Artists selected as finalists will have their work exhibited (and available for purchase*) at Gallery19 for the month of July 2019. ** As competition judge, Ahmed Ozsever, artist and educator, will review all entries, select finalists, and announce the winner at an opening reception at Gallery19, on July 12th, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===== INSTRUCTIONS =====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;THEME: When Photography Ruled the Streets&lt;br/&gt;Gallery19 and juror Ahmed Ozever delve into the ever-changing world of street photography. There is no clear definition of street photography, but for this competition we will define street photography as the preservation of special moments of our time, in which artists make accessible to future generations.  These images are a documentation of who we are and where we have been.  Street photography fully immerses the viewer into a different time and experience.  Our hope is that artists of all levels will submit work that will tell stories like street photographers Vivian Maier and William Eggleston.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;THE PAYOFF:&lt;br/&gt;The winner of Gallery19 Meed3 will receive a solo show at Gallery19 for the month of August 2020.  The winner will also have a one-year contract with Gallery19, which includes exposure on the gallery’s website, ongoing multi-media, promotion, including social media, participation in gallery programming (openings, events, artist talks, etc.), and direct sales efforts.  In addition, Ahmed Ozsever will mentor the winner for a full year August 2019 through August 2020, by reviewing and evaluating work product, and assisting in development of a gallery-ready exhibition, all culminating in a solo exhibition at Gallery19.&lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://www.nyfa.org/Opportunities/Show/709447bd-2beb-40f2-89af-fc4578068579" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>